<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Error_game_js5 Connect</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174</link>
    <description>Greetings and sorry for posting another thread.

So I&#39;ve had my server up and running for a few weeks now with (basically) no connection problems whatsoever for other players. I&#39;ve never had this issue in the past week of running my server. My ports are correct in both my source folder and client folder, my ip is correct, and my revision is correct. For some reason today, after enabling a VPN (cyberghost, to be exact), and disabling it, my server won&#39;t start. I didn&#39;t even change, compile, or modify any of the client or server files. Just out of the blue, my server stopped working. When I run my server, it does what it normally does (says it&#39;s online on port 43594) but when I run my jarred client (which I always use to run the game), it gets stuck on &quot;Checking for updates - 0%&quot; and when I run it using the jarmaker batch file, after about 5 minutes of it trying to load (and getting nowhere), it gives me that god awful &quot;error_game_js5 connect&quot; error.

I uninstalled cyberghost completely from my laptop and it&#39;s clearly disabled. Why won&#39;t it connect? What did cyberghost (if that is the cause) do to my laptop to stop my server from working? 

Things I&#39;ve tried:

Doubled checked ports, ip, revision in both source &amp; client folders.
Checked No-IP to make sure it was working as intended.
Restarted my wireless network adapter. 
Checked the server status checker. Server is &quot;offline&quot; even though it says it&#39;s online in the cmd window.

Any suggestions would be very helpful, thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 18:25:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Error_game_js5 Connect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rickymac6 Rickymac6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rickymac6">@Rickymac6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I redownloaded Cyberghost and enabled it, then disabled it and now it works fine. But I definitely won’t be using that again. Terrible VPN.</p>
<p>Thank you for the help though. Glad I could get this fixed. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 18:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540174-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174.rss">Error_game_js5 Connect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error_game_js5 Connect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It might have not properly reset your networking settings.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 18:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540174-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174.rss">Error_game_js5 Connect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error_game_js5 Connect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rickymac6 Rickymac6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rickymac6">@Rickymac6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Greetings and sorry for posting another thread.</p>
<p>So I’ve had my server up and running for a few weeks now with (basically) no connection problems whatsoever for other players. I’ve never had this issue in the past week of running my server. My ports are correct in both my source folder and client folder, my ip is correct, and my revision is correct. For some reason today, after enabling a VPN (cyberghost, to be exact), and disabling it, my server won’t start. I didn’t even change, compile, or modify any of the client or server files. Just out of the blue, my server stopped working. When I run my server, it does what it normally does (says it’s online on port 43594) but when I run my jarred client (which I always use to run the game), it gets stuck on “Checking for updates - 0%” and when I run it using the jarmaker batch file, after about 5 minutes of it trying to load (and getting nowhere), it gives me that god awful “error_game_js5 connect” error.</p>
<p>I uninstalled cyberghost completely from my laptop and it’s clearly disabled. Why won’t it connect? What did cyberghost (if that is the cause) do to my laptop to stop my server from working?</p>
<p>Things I’ve tried:</p>
<p>Doubled checked ports, ip, revision in both source &amp; client folders.<br>
Checked No-IP to make sure it was working as intended.<br>
Restarted my wireless network adapter.<br>
Checked the server status checker. Server is “offline” even though it says it’s online in the cmd window.</p>
<p>Any suggestions would be very helpful, thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 09:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540174-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-game-js5-connect/540174.rss">Error_game_js5 Connect</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
