<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problem with Run.bat</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-run-bat/454933</link>
    <description>Hey guys! I have recently downloaded the RuneEclipse source and client to test it out. It has a lot of potential so I am going to continue working on it. However I do have a problem. When I change all of the dialogue and server names and owner names and etc to my own and compile I get this error. Could you guys please tell me how to fix this. I am currently on holiday and using my sisters laptop, I don&#39;t remember this happening on my home PC but it happens on my sisters laptop.

[img]http://i.imgur.com/zGRHs.png[/img]

EDIT: I have just been outside and shut down the laptop, I have just tried to open the server without compiling and it has worked, This is ok I guess. Do you guys know how to fix it? I don&#39;t want to have to restart the laptop every time I change something :/</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 12:12:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-run-bat/454933.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problem with Run.bat</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KingLuke KingLuke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kingluke">@KingLuke</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys! I have recently downloaded the RuneEclipse source and client to test it out. It has a lot of potential so I am going to continue working on it. However I do have a problem. When I change all of the dialogue and server names and owner names and etc to my own and compile I get this error. Could you guys please tell me how to fix this. I am currently on holiday and using my sisters laptop, I don’t remember this happening on my home PC but it happens on my sisters laptop.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/zGRHs.png" alt width="640" height="302"></p>
<p>EDIT: I have just been outside and shut down the laptop, I have just tried to open the server without compiling and it has worked, This is ok I guess. Do you guys know how to fix it? I don’t want to have to restart the laptop every time I change something <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-run-bat/454933/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-run-bat/454933/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 12:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454933-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-run-bat/454933.rss">Problem with Run.bat</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
