<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[718] Loading different worlds</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-loading-different-worlds/546842</link>
    <description>Currently, I have lobby and worldlist on my server, and they appear on the client. However, the client does not actually connect to the different worlds&#39; specific addresses, which it should. So for example, if I have world 1 set to localhost and world 2 to test.mysite.com, I shouldn&#39;t be able to connect when trying to load world 2, however it doesn&#39;t change the address and is always loading world 1. 
I&#39;ve went through the client packets and the closest thing I found was an incoming packet with id 8 but attempting to send it via the server didn&#39;t do anything. If anyone knows how to make the client connect to the selected world&#39;s address when logging in from the lobby, please lead me in the right direction.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 03:23:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-loading-different-worlds/546842.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[718] Loading different worlds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@grundyboy34 grundyboy34]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/grundyboy34">@grundyboy34</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Currently, I have lobby and worldlist on my server, and they appear on the client. However, the client does not actually connect to the different worlds’ specific addresses, which it should. So for example, if I have world 1 set to localhost and world 2 to <a href="http://test.mysite.com" rel="nofollow noopener">test.mysite.com</a>, I shouldn’t be able to connect when trying to load world 2, however it doesn’t change the address and is always loading world 1.<br>
I’ve went through the client packets and the closest thing I found was an incoming packet with id 8 but attempting to send it via the server didn’t do anything. If anyone knows how to make the client connect to the selected world’s address when logging in from the lobby, please lead me in the right direction.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-loading-different-worlds/546842/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-loading-different-worlds/546842/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 03:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-546842-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/718-loading-different-worlds/546842.rss">[718] Loading different worlds</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
