<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to fix errors!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381</link>
    <description>Ok so I&#39;ve seen posts where people try to compile things and they get like 100 errors or something. Well, a very easy way to fix this is to actually quit being lazy and read the errors! First it will say the file name that the error occurred in. Then it will say the line that the error was in. Then a brief description of the error. An example:

client.java:7100: cannot find symbol
symbol     : variable signlink
location: class client
            signlink.errorname = s;


So what you need to do is first open up the file the error was in. Then go to the line the error was in. This is tricky and can be EXTREMELY time consuming, unless you have this application called Xcode. Xcode can be downloaded when installing developer. You can buy it here..
http://developer.apple.com/programs/
But I&#39;m sure 99% of you DON&#39;T want to pay $99 for it. So google it or something looking for free download link. I don&#39;t really know any free ones, but you can give it a shot. Anyway, whenever you get Xcode, you&#39;re going to want to open up client.java or whatever file it was. BUT OPEN IT WITH XCODE!!!!!!!!! DO NOT RIGHT CLICK AND SELECT EDIT!!!!! OPEN! WITH! XCODE! Once you have it you should have your file. What&#39;s cool about Xcode is that it is programmed for the Java language, unlike notepad. Now here&#39;s a quick summary of the lettering colors that you will see when using Xcode.

Green = will not appear as script, basically used as a note. Does not effect file at all.
Pink = Basically just java language like &quot;if, else, end, break, case&quot; etc. Pretty much starting words for lines.
Blue = Numbers.
Black = Actions. Telling whats going to happen, comes after pink words.
Red = Text that will appear, like sendmessage and stuff.


Okay that should help you identify problems much much easier than looking through a bunch of black text. But that&#39;s not the biggest advantage of this. Probably the biggest advantage of Xcode (at least for debugging) is the thing that tells you what line number you&#39;re on. All you have to do is click on any line in the file and up in the top left hand corner it will say the name of the file and what line your blinking cursor thing is on. This is helpful cause it&#39;s WAY easier to find the line your error was on than if you were to go on notepad and count the lines one by one, especially when there&#39;s thousands and thousands of lines.


So once you&#39;ve found the line that your error was on, you should be able to see what was wrong. If you can&#39;t figure it out, post a reply here and a picture of the file with the line that&#39;s screwed up, and be sure to tell me which one it is. I realize it can still take a long time to find and fix 100 errors, but at least you can do it quicker, as well as having a more understandable application to edit your java files with. 

Ok so I hope this helped. Here&#39;s a quick explanatory picture.

[IMG]http://i822.photobucket.com/albums/zz142/PhoToeBuckAwt69/Picture10-1.png[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 04:11:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to fix errors!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kihomura Kihomura]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kihomura">@kihomura</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This isn’t exactly a proper tutorial.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 04:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352381-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381.rss">How to fix errors!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to fix errors!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Masta_69 Masta 69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/masta_69">@Masta_69</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This program tells you when you make a mistake too. Just trying to show a good editing program.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 02:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352381-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381.rss">How to fix errors!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to fix errors!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>An IDE will tell you when you about errors the second you make a mistake, all this program does is syntax highlighting. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
The smart thing to do when dealing with errors is to use an IDE. Also, there’s a topic in this board on common compiler errors.</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/default-apple-touch-icon.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="144" height="144">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 02:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352381-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381.rss">How to fix errors!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to fix errors!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Masta_69 Masta 69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/masta_69">@Masta_69</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so I’ve seen posts where people try to compile things and they get like 100 errors or something. Well, a very easy way to fix this is to actually quit being lazy and read the errors! First it will say the file name that the error occurred in. Then it will say the line that the error was in. Then a brief description of the error. An example:</p>
<p>client.java:7100: cannot find symbol<br>
symbol     : variable signlink<br>
location: class client<br>
signlink.errorname = s;</p>
<p>So what you need to do is first open up the file the error was in. Then go to the line the error was in. This is tricky and can be EXTREMELY time consuming, unless you have this application called Xcode. Xcode can be downloaded when installing developer. You can buy it here…<br>
<a href="http://developer.apple.com/programs/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://developer.apple.com/programs/</a><br>
But I’m sure 99% of you DON’T want to pay $99 for it. So google it or something looking for free download link. I don’t really know any free ones, but you can give it a shot. Anyway, whenever you get Xcode, you’re going to want to open up client.java or whatever file it was. BUT OPEN IT WITH XCODE!!! DO NOT RIGHT CLICK AND SELECT EDIT!!! OPEN! WITH! XCODE! Once you have it you should have your file. What’s cool about Xcode is that it is programmed for the Java language, unlike notepad. Now here’s a quick summary of the lettering colors that you will see when using Xcode.</p>
<p>Green = will not appear as script, basically used as a note. Does not effect file at all.<br>
Pink = Basically just java language like “if, else, end, break, case” etc. Pretty much starting words for lines.<br>
Blue = Numbers.<br>
Black = Actions. Telling whats going to happen, comes after pink words.<br>
Red = Text that will appear, like sendmessage and stuff.</p>
<p>Okay that should help you identify problems much much easier than looking through a bunch of black text. But that’s not the biggest advantage of this. Probably the biggest advantage of Xcode (at least for debugging) is the thing that tells you what line number you’re on. All you have to do is click on any line in the file and up in the top left hand corner it will say the name of the file and what line your blinking cursor thing is on. This is helpful cause it’s WAY easier to find the line your error was on than if you were to go on notepad and count the lines one by one, especially when there’s thousands and thousands of lines.</p>
<p>So once you’ve found the line that your error was on, you should be able to see what was wrong. If you can’t figure it out, post a reply here and a picture of the file with the line that’s screwed up, and be sure to tell me which one it is. I realize it can still take a long time to find and fix 100 errors, but at least you can do it quicker, as well as having a more understandable application to edit your java files with.</p>
<p>Ok so I hope this helped. Here’s a quick explanatory picture.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i822.photobucket.com/albums/zz142/PhoToeBuckAwt69/Picture10-1.png" title="Picture10-1.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i822.photobucket.com/albums/zz142/PhoToeBuckAwt69/Picture10-1.png" alt width="690" height="462"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">Picture10-1.png</span><span class="informations">752×504</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 01:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352381-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-fix-errors/352381.rss">How to fix errors!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
