<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>D claws</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/d-claws/548383</link>
    <description>So between this, and my teleportation issues... This is the last thing stopping me from a complete BETA release. The dragon claws special had to be removed by my head dev and I because they were glitching in a way where it would hit pretty much unlimited times per 50% special, we removed the code and just left it so if you clicking claws special, it wouldn&#39;t attack at all and would send you a messsage saying they were removed. All in all, We are un able to re-add the special and I have no idea why, when we rework the combatassistant class to add back the claws, it says theres an issue because c.clawsDelay is unrecognized via Client class, even though we ripped the client portion from our old server and the combatassistant portion as well, the 2 servers are compatible because we&#39;ve collided the 2 before in our original release back in 2013, we can&#39;t figure the issue? Little help ?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 00:09:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/d-claws/548383.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>D claws</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lol_space1 lol space]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lol_space1">@lol_space1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So between this, and my teleportation issues… This is the last thing stopping me from a complete BETA release. The dragon claws special had to be removed by my head dev and I because they were glitching in a way where it would hit pretty much unlimited times per 50% special, we removed the code and just left it so if you clicking claws special, it wouldn’t attack at all and would send you a messsage saying they were removed. All in all, We are un able to re-add the special and I have no idea why, when we rework the combatassistant class to add back the claws, it says theres an issue because c.clawsDelay is unrecognized via Client class, even though we ripped the client portion from our old server and the combatassistant portion as well, the 2 servers are compatible because we’ve collided the 2 before in our original release back in 2013, we can’t figure the issue? Little help ?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/d-claws/548383/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/d-claws/548383/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 00:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548383-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/d-claws/548383.rss">D claws</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
