<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My MoparScape client won&#39;t work</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-moparscape-client-wont-work/72444</link>
    <description>I&#39;m at school, and I decided to try to download the MoparScape client on the computer that I have been moved to. I actually copied the files from my old computer into my folder on the network, and pasted them into the computer that I am on now. I had this problem earlier on a different computer, and I thought that it was just the computer because it was a peice of junk. But anyways, my problem is that when I go and run MoparScape, it loads but then it exits, just like it did when V2 came out and we all had to update... I&#39;ve tried everything that I could think of, and I&#39;m debating on whether or not to dl an open source and just run that, but that would mean that I would have to go download rar aswell,  :|

So, anyways. What do you think is the problem?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2007 01:12:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-moparscape-client-wont-work/72444.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My MoparScape client won&#39;t work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Click_Here Click Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/click_here">@Click_Here</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Usually the problem is java jdk 6, have you tried that? because out of all the people ive saw post this, the answer is usually they havnt downloaded jdk6 multi language, download that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-moparscape-client-wont-work/72444/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-moparscape-client-wont-work/72444/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2007 01:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72444-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-moparscape-client-wont-work/72444.rss">My MoparScape client won&#39;t work</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My MoparScape client won&#39;t work</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fozzy fozzy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fozzy">@fozzy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m at school, and I decided to try to download the MoparScape client on the computer that I have been moved to. I actually copied the files from my old computer into my folder on the network, and pasted them into the computer that I am on now. I had this problem earlier on a different computer, and I thought that it was just the computer because it was a peice of junk. But anyways, my problem is that when I go and run MoparScape, it loads but then it exits, just like it did when V2 came out and we all had to update… I’ve tried everything that I could think of, and I’m debating on whether or not to dl an open source and just run that, but that would mean that I would have to go download rar aswell,  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>So, anyways. What do you think is the problem?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-moparscape-client-wont-work/72444/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-moparscape-client-wont-work/72444/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2007 01:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72444-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-moparscape-client-wont-work/72444.rss">My MoparScape client won&#39;t work</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
