<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mass clicking spec</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-clicking-spec/297719</link>
    <description>To stop this i want to make it like:
when you spec with a Gmaul and you have no spec Left, it says &quot;you do not have enough special energy left!&quot;

and also, in most servers, when your fighting, you can just maul spec without clicking the person! how can i change this it could be saying &quot;your not fighting anything..&quot; and doesnt allow you to spec unless you click the enemy.

Soz, and also again -.- They is a Glicth, you may not think it is, but it is for instance your like 5 steps away from your emeny and you can just spec from there, when actually your supposed to be right next to the person to spec, maybe like this?
[code]
if (c.playerEquipment[c.playerWeapon] == 4153 &amp;&amp; withinDistance(#,#) {
c.sM(&quot;You need to get close to the enemy before using the special!&quot;);
return;[/code]
Anyways can someone help me out????

PS: for any noobs out there who arent going to help, please dont post, i dont want to be spoonfed all i want to know how can i do it, not for you to show me how to do, Also Don&#39;t be a nerd, saying whatever.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 14:03:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-clicking-spec/297719.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mass clicking spec</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@12mil 12mil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/12mil">@12mil</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>To stop this i want to make it like:<br>
when you spec with a Gmaul and you have no spec Left, it says “you do not have enough special energy left!”</p>
<p>and also, in most servers, when your fighting, you can just maul spec without clicking the person! how can i change this it could be saying “your not fighting anything…” and doesnt allow you to spec unless you click the enemy.</p>
<p>Soz, and also again -.- They is a Glicth, you may not think it is, but it is for instance your like 5 steps away from your emeny and you can just spec from there, when actually your supposed to be right next to the person to spec, maybe like this?</p>
<p><code>
if (c.playerEquipment[c.playerWeapon] == 4153 &amp;&amp; withinDistance(#,#) {
c.sM("You need to get close to the enemy before using the special!");
return;</code><br>
Anyways can someone help me out???</p>
<p>PS: for any noobs out there who arent going to help, please dont post, i dont want to be spoonfed all i want to know how can i do it, not for you to show me how to do, Also Don’t be a nerd, saying whatever.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-clicking-spec/297719/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-clicking-spec/297719/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 14:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-297719-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-clicking-spec/297719.rss">Mass clicking spec</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
