<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646</link>
    <description>I&#39;m thinking about looking for two coders to help finish up with my server and if I have enough money I might get a vps and host it, but how would I trust someone so that they don&#39;t release my work?  Do I have to trust them that they won&#39;t do such a thing?  Any ideas on how you guys determine a good trustworthy coder when you guys get coders for your server.
Thanks for your help</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 07:26:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Teem_Rocket Teem_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teem_rocket">@Teem_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <pre><code> The thing is, no matter what you have the person agree to sign, whether it be a legally binding contract with all of the paper work, or partaking in a blood oath (ha). You can never truly trust anyone you know online. Also, if crackers are after your info, they will find something if you are a careless interwebber. It probably won't be vital information, but it can lead to other things and add up to I.D. crimes in some cases. There is also some real life activity required or this simply isn't as effective as it could be. 

 People usually get "hacked", or cracked due to their own errors or stupidity. It's often times a combination of the two. What is the best and most secure way to be sure that your work is safe and sound with It's current Developers? Having two Source/Client Developers who know both of the subjects very well and like them equally is a solid plan. If something goes missing or anything is tampered with in some manner, you will KNOW that it was not you. You'll most likely be able to figure out if your security has been exploited or compromised at some point by a 3rd party wolf. It's not hard and default operating system programs + honey pot will most likely alert the user in some way. 

 One of the principle keys in these situations, is to remember, that you NEVER EVER give out your Dedicated Host/Virtual Private Server/Virtual Private Network/Host/Private Network/etcetera; information. This is vital to remember. Do not ever give out personal or critical information that could possibly be an asset to anyone working against you or your operations.  If you give out this information to a potential 'developer' you just met who is a budding 16 year old social engineer and just played you like a piano -- within 7 business days, you will receive a certificate via the U.S. Postal service which confirms your eligibility for metal disability assistance 
</code></pre>
<p>IF YOU DO THIS YOU’RE |=|_|(|&lt;1||9 1237@12|)3|). ^^</p>
<pre><code> It's also important that your other Developer should have the same common interests and goals as you. If you both are working towards the same goals, then you will be able to work together successfully WITH the proper communication, which is vital to any partnership; ever. Multiple Developers with entirely different styles, intentions, visions, plans, and programming techniques does NOT in the end create a very solid product. What's that? You want some examples? Look at pretty much every R.S.P.S. ever. There you go. champ.
</code></pre>
<p>P.S. Check High Scores for SQLi vulnerabilities. This is NOT a good security loophole to have and is well known. Most security issues you encounter will be able to be solved with a little effort and due diligence to search for solutions. If you are stuck with a problem, the odds are in your favor that another person has been confronted with the same problem under matching or similar circumstances. You should always keep this in mind as it would be advantageous for your projects. Another tip I can offer to always remember, is to not get frustrated and hear others out. Do NOT have too big of an ego, don’t be very penisy, etcetera. Everyone on these forums should always remember the rule:  No matter how much one knows there is always someone who knows much more.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">I don’t endorse any of this. Just chatting about this as a casual subject</span></p>
<p>TL;DR</p>
<blockquote>You can't ever truly trust anyone you meet online and don't know in real life. Even if you know them in real life, you should still be wary. You can never underestimate another person's greed or how many morals they will ignore and step over to achieve what they work towards. You should always be a cautious intererweb user and there are hundreds of websites upon hundreds of websites who specialize in giving advice on this very subject. You should check them out.</blockquote>   
<p><em><strong><span class="bbcode-b">Non-Lecture Version</span></strong></em>_</p>
<p>You can’t ever trust another person 100%. Get to know them, call them out and give them tests and situational errors to resolve in Java. Ask them what to do in certain situations and get familiar with their persona and them in general, or at least the persona that they attempt to give off. You’re much better off if you can bring a lot to the Development table so-to-speak and partner up with a well-known programmer who has a lot of experience in both Client and Server-sided Design and Development.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 07:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Tutorial, post:19, topic:527646”]I really don’t see your concern, especially since this is not a game you have created completely by yourself, which would be a completely different thing. If you are worried about your code being stolen or reproduced, simply do not give other developers access to that code. I just really think you should consider making it an open source project, and your biggest concern then will be criticism.[/quote]Or hackerz. Nothing like a bit of security through obscurity.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 06:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tutorial Tutorial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tutorial">@Tutorial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I really don’t see your concern, especially since this is not a game you have created completely by yourself, which would be a completely different thing. If you are worried about your code being stolen or reproduced, simply do not give other developers access to that code. I just really think you should consider making it an open source project, and your biggest concern then will be criticism.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 02:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MrFun MrFun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrfun">@MrFun</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Vain_, post:17, topic:527646”]<a class="mention" href="/u/mrfun">@mrfun</a>; you changed “formats” and <span class="bbcode-i">rewrote</span> code. That doesn’t add to 40% of accreditation.</p>
<p>Formats can be easily understood by looking at the code supplied. So it’s not like “OMG you have to find it on YouTube” but yeah.[/quote]<br>
Okay so adding stuff without help counts as 0% since its already been done?  yea my % might have came out my ass(it did) but that would be my max since I have done alot of stuff and put the codes so I could understand it, but this is totally off topic of this topics meaning lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 01:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a class="mention" href="/u/mrfun">@mrfun</a>; you changed “formats” and <span class="bbcode-i">rewrote</span> code. That doesn’t add to 40% of accreditation.</p>
<p>Formats can be easily understood by looking at the code supplied. So it’s not like “OMG you have to find it on YouTube” but yeah.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 21:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="15" data-topic="527646">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Clawz fury:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Learn how to program yourself. I do projects completely alone unless I’m working with trusted friends.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>…and if my conscious tells me otherwise…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 21:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Learn how to program yourself. I do projects completely alone unless I’m working with trusted friends.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 19:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java-RSPS-Noob Java-RSPS-Noob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java-rsps-noob">@Java-RSPS-Noob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>I'm surprise devs want money right away when even if the server might not be successful at all, yet thanks for all your opinions on this matter I think your ideas can help out alot of new owners.</blockquote>
<p>That isn’t how the world works. A developer expects payment up front for his work no matter of difficulty or success of the project. it’s like hiring a person on a contractual basis. They are paid no matter what for the basis of what is written in the contract. They are also legally entitled to whatever it states in the contract.</p>
<p>The same would fall under also electronic messages sent by person to person. If you promise somebody on a web design forum 200$ to build and support a site for so many months/years than they are entitled to pay them the fair sum that is agreed upon.</p>
<p>I.E. If I was to purchase a month membership into a game they are required to either compensate me for the lost days of membership if the server/game closes or to keep it up until that finalization date unless it states in their terms other wise.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 19:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MrFun MrFun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrfun">@MrFun</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for all the feedback but how I was wanting to host the server is…well just host it and all donations will go to the hosting of the private server and if I do become big and get more donations…the donations will go to a better looking website, but to all what you guys said this idea will probably get trashed.  I’m surprise devs want money right away when even if the server might not be successful at all, yet thanks for all your opinions on this matter I think your ideas can help out alot of new owners.</p>
<p>[quote=“Vain_, post:7, topic:527646”]Just gonna state the obvious. It’s probably 99% not your work to begin with, so you shouldn’t worry about someone taking it from you. If you’re looking for developers and you’re afraid they’ll take your work, don’t get developers. L</p>
<p>Generally speaking, kids apply for ‘coder’ to get in a position to take x amount of donations. If you attempt to stop them from receiving donations or whatever, they’ll probably quit and ruin your server as much as possible. (Rsps is full of immature fu<span class="bbcode-b"></span>ckwits.</p>
<p>So yeah. Either take the risk and move on, or stay as the sole developer.[/quote]<br>
Okay 99% is pretty harsh I say at max 40% is what I’ve done on the server since I reformatted the client and source and rewrote some code to a basic format and easy to use.  Also they might want my client and source since the base I used, the format, isn’t on any forums and can only be found on youtube, but you will have to be searching for along time to find my base since its pretty old video.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 18:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“MrFun, post:3, topic:527646”][quote author=xx matty xx link=topic=646400.msg4346996#msg4346996 date=1376030933]<br>
You get them to sign an NDA.<br>
[/quote]<br>
That’s what people do X.X on private servers[/quote]Well no, everyone trusts each other and everyone dicks each other over because nobody is going to work for nothing. I’m assuming you’re thinking of paying these developers (either as a % of donations or for their time) - in which case you should be agreeing on some sort of contract. Then if they release code they wrote for you it really is theft and you can at least threaten them, even if you don’t intend on fudgeing them with the long dick of the law. But if they’re contributing for free then your project should really be open source and the line between what’s their and what’s yours is blurred.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 17:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Driman_Rune Driman Rune]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/driman_rune">@Driman_Rune</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ORRR</p>
<p>Just give them junks of files, and they have to tell you what they did.</p>
<p>OR</p>
<p>let them take it, if they say it’s theirs, and it isn’t then don’t get to mad, because after all it’s yours right?..</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@HcoJustin HcoJustin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hcojustin">@HcoJustin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Don’t let them have access to the VPS, and don’t let them get access to the core of the server. Let them write plugins and only plugins.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 15:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java-RSPS-Noob Java-RSPS-Noob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java-rsps-noob">@Java-RSPS-Noob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Driman Rune, post:8, topic:527646”]Easy.</p>
<p>Like my mother says to me. “Trust doesn’t appear in the sky, it is earned.”[/quote]I see I see…you trust me right? &lt;3 Give me your bank card.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 15:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Driman_Rune Driman Rune]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/driman_rune">@Driman_Rune</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Easy.</p>
<p>Like my mother says to me. “Trust doesn’t appear in the sky, it is earned.”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 15:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just gonna state the obvious. It’s probably 99% not your work to begin with, so you shouldn’t worry about someone taking it from you. If you’re looking for developers and you’re afraid they’ll take your work, don’t get developers. L</p>
<p>Generally speaking, kids apply for ‘coder’ to get in a position to take x amount of donations. If you attempt to stop them from receiving donations or whatever, they’ll probably quit and ruin your server as much as possible. (Rsps is full of immature fu<span class="bbcode-b"></span>ckwits.</p>
<p>So yeah. Either take the risk and move on, or stay as the sole developer.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 13:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java-RSPS-Noob Java-RSPS-Noob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java-rsps-noob">@Java-RSPS-Noob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Another option: have them create their own classes with a general relative source and then you convert it your own self as needed. I’m under the assumption that these would be hired developers so yeah.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 13:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Null_Amount N_A]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/null_amount">@Null_Amount</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Solution: make your server open source.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 07:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thats happened every other time one way or another it feels like, which is why i prefer to work alone as much as possible</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 07:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MrFun MrFun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrfun">@MrFun</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="527646">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 xx matty xx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You get them to sign an NDA.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s what people do X.X on private servers</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You get them to sign an NDA.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 06:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How can I trust someone?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MrFun MrFun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrfun">@MrFun</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m thinking about looking for two coders to help finish up with my server and if I have enough money I might get a vps and host it, but how would I trust someone so that they don’t release my work?  Do I have to trust them that they won’t do such a thing?  Any ideas on how you guys determine a good trustworthy coder when you guys get coders for your server.<br>
Thanks for your help</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 06:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527646-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-can-i-trust-someone/527646.rss">How can I trust someone?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
