<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912</link>
    <description>I would like to continue this topic, and I would like to to be open for everyone to read because I want others to chirp in and allow their point of views if they want as well. If i wanted this to be private I would make it a pm.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from: hat trix on July 07, 2012, 09:37:56 PM
Quote from: xx matty xx on July 07, 2012, 05:51:38 PM
Quote from: asshole_rule on July 07, 2012, 12:48:28 PM
Quote from: zaz278 on July 07, 2012, 12:42:04 AM
Fairly simple, relm and jrub said they &#39;found something cool&#39; so I stalked them on worldmap after they left I went to the coords I saw them at and dug straight down.


Quote from: Travas on July 06, 2012, 10:39:09 PM
Don&#39;t try saying you got the coords from somebody and dug straight down; everyone uses that excuse.


Come on zaz y u no read? loljk

Pre-empting his response doesn&#39;t make it invalid. I&#39;ve dug 1x1 holes straight into spawners - not because I xray, but because I got the coords underground and dug down from the surface. Lots of reasons why people might have holes dug directly into interesting shit.



This is basically what I did. I died at a spawner. knowing the coords, i simply dug straight down to it to get my items. Then, herobrine reports me to tom and leaves a sign on my property saying &quot;I have proof you xray&quot;.


also herobrine, ever heard of minimap with wp&#39;s? you should look into that, snitch.

The thing is, there isn&#39;t any caves around the spawner I found that you &#39;got the coords and dug into&#39;.  Yes, I know what a world map is, but the thing I don&#39;t understand is, how is reporting rule breakers &#39;snitching&#39;.  If anything, I should be thanked for caring about people breaking rules on the server.  And IIRC, on the old map, you had stacks and stacks of diamond blocks, you just don&#39;t come across those easily.  I have nothing against you nor jrub.  You were somewhat of a friend at one point, and so was jrub.  Honestly, I&#39;d report my best friend if he was breaking the rules.&lt;/blockquote&gt;


Travis, I have round only 2 mob spawners. Two of witch I have placed blocks over top of them to allow myself to find them when I need to. One of them I have is a spider spawner, the other is a zombie spanwer. both of these spawners are found from caves, as my proof I will post pictures of where the cave entrance is/was WITH proof of where it was if it still isn&#39;t there.

The reason I&#39;m calling you out is because you just go around reporting random (dedicated) server players who are on more then you and have time to find items that you have yet to find. At first, I might have had suspicion of other players xraying because some people had over 20 diamond after an hour of play on the server. The thing is, I dont go straight for diamond (could actually care less about it) and I have no use for mob spawners. I cbf to build farms because I would rather spend my time building up my town, not afking string or xp. 


And last but not least, the &quot;stacks upon stacks&quot; of diamond I came across in world2 on the old server. Yes, I remember. So does everyone else that was on. Coonhunter was looting a town that hadn&#39;t reset res (the town very close to my huge town) and he came across almost 10 stacks of rails, and about 6 stacks of diamond blocks. He freaks out about the loot on chat, then died. I ran in and took his items. Later, after giving tom hell about them, I burned more then half the items because I had given the rest to other players before tom even got to me. Coonhunter, fuscate, manbearpig, and chull can most likely vouch for me on this.

pics:
Marking the area so I dont have to look for it incase I lose minimap
[url=http://aar.im/u/20120-6h][img]http://aar.im/i/20120-6h.png[/img][/url]
Straight to the spawner, cave from behind
[url=http://aar.im/u/20120-8e][img]http://aar.im/i/20120-8e.png[/img][/url]
Closer look at cave from behind
[url=http://aar.im/u/20120-a0][img]http://aar.im/i/20120-a0.png[/img][/url]
2nd spawner, has spawner and Mine shaft in the back
[url=http://aar.im/u/20120-9d][img]http://aar.im/i/20120-9d.png[/img][/url]
A view from the mineshaft (spawner is between cobble and fence)
[url=http://aar.im/u/20120-ig][img]http://aar.im/i/20120-ig.png[/img][/url]
broke the cobble for a better look, there is the glass and entrance to my spawner (behind glass)
[url=http://aar.im/u/20120-9f][img]http://aar.im/i/20120-9f.png[/img][/url]


If I have forgotten a spawner, please point it out to me. I cant remember because I barely go down in the caves anymore. I got what i need, witch was cobble coal and iron
oh, and here is your &quot;xrayed&quot; diamonds

[url=http://aar.im/u/20120-h1][img]http://aar.im/i/20120-h1.png[/img][/url]


now please, everyone add your 2 cents. ;)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 14:55:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hat_trix hat trix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hat_trix">@hat_trix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Anywho, Thanks for the apology and I apologize for calling you out lol. I’m pretty easy to get along with, just ask tom <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I personally don’t mind people going on my property, but with someone else placing items on my property It allows others to think that could be okay and do the same. I rarely have enough time to play as it is, so I don’t really have enough time to look after my builds and make sure they are looking as expected. again, sorry for freaking out last night on ya. 11 hour shift had me stressed and irritable. Thanks for the on-topic input tristram.</p>
<p>cowfish, did you even post anything?<br>
lock this shit if you think is necessary</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 14:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@omgilikepie omgilikepie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omgilikepie">@omgilikepie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>inb4 someone de-rails the topic…oh wait lmao</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 12:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@badger41 badger41]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/badger41">@badger41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>quote train woo-woo!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 09:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“triston001, post:15, topic:448912”][quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4043018#msg4043018 date=1341817461]</p>
<p>[quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4043014#msg4043014 date=1341817020]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4043013#msg4043013 date=1341816823]</p>
<p>[quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4043009#msg4043009 date=1341816568]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042998#msg4042998 date=1341815821]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.<br>
[/quote]It was a joke because I knew it would piss you off, which it did.  I never even spoke to Tom, so stop bringing that up.  Yes, it is funny, that’s why It’s a joke  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   Oh you got you’re reply now.  Happy?  Every single one of your statements have been proven false, so you could stop bringing that up also.  I did indeed read what you said, apart from all the bullshit I read, I did see you say that.  Oh, you got a sign on you’re property, poor grass block <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it must suck having a sign that can be easily removed on top of you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  I’d be more than happy to go remove my sign if that’s why you’re so pissy, if not, then be glad you got a free sign.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   No one should be upset if people snoop, unless you are hiding something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dude, when you was speaking to bryan in this, u said how he IS a cheater instead of saying possibly. no one likes being called a cheater, expecially if its a joke. and how are you gonna go from saying “why are people saying im a snitch for reporting about possible xrays” to “oh its just a joke”. i find bullshit in that. i dont like people snooping because it arouses suspicion of what are they doing, and distracts me from whatever im doing. one of the reasons why i didnt like it when meep would just pop into my house and stay next to me. my paranoia nature makes me wanna watch him, expecially since he does things like pushing me off. Just go on world map and not actually wander around. unless thats what u are doing then ignore that one comment.<br>
[/quote]I was talking about the whole jrub thing, he said I was a snitch for that, so your point is invalid.  You can’t stop people from snooping, if you don’t like it, play singleplayer.  Most of the time my internet is too slow to play, let alone watch the world map whilst playing.  Either I play, or use the world map, or neither.  I’m kinda low on options on what I can do ingame.  I can’t do anything PvP related, I can’t do a lot of things because my connection, so usually I just lay low and wander about.</p>
<p>Besides, we already settled this, there is no need to bring it up and start another fight.  If you’d like to speak more, bring it to PM, or if you like, join IRC.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well human error for misplacing who from both incidents. i would play singleplayer, but i would rather build with friends and chat with them. and i think i have small amount of available memory so i also can only do one or the other. all i was getting at is snooping can bother some people, so instead of snooping and wandering, find a ring of buddies and/or build some cool buildings. plus i wanted to say how that is kinda of a crappy joke to pull. :I that is all.<br>
[/quote]Plus I wanted to say the joke wasn’t towards you and you are in no way, shape, or form associated with this whole joke and or discussion, so thank you for your time.</p>
<p>But really, of course it isn’t going to be good for you :3</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>i know im not associated with it, but it’s something called empathy, and me acting upon it to better community, like u said when your reported your suspicions of jrub x-raying. :I<br>
and im confused what the last sentence is. are you talking about the joke, the being blamed, or the snooping?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"><br>
[/quote]Honestly, I might have been doing something else when I was typing that because I have no idea what it means either.  :o</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lolol. im good and through with this as long as you can see where im coming from, not so much that u must believe me or whatever.[/quote]Yeah I think it’s about time this is locked :3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 07:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@triston001 triston001]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/triston001">@triston001</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Travas, post:14, topic:448912”][quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4043014#msg4043014 date=1341817020]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4043013#msg4043013 date=1341816823]</p>
<p>[quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4043009#msg4043009 date=1341816568]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042998#msg4042998 date=1341815821]</p>
<p>[quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4042994#msg4042994 date=1341815420]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.<br>
[/quote]It was a joke because I knew it would piss you off, which it did.  I never even spoke to Tom, so stop bringing that up.  Yes, it is funny, that’s why It’s a joke  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   Oh you got you’re reply now.  Happy?  Every single one of your statements have been proven false, so you could stop bringing that up also.  I did indeed read what you said, apart from all the bullshit I read, I did see you say that.  Oh, you got a sign on you’re property, poor grass block <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it must suck having a sign that can be easily removed on top of you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  I’d be more than happy to go remove my sign if that’s why you’re so pissy, if not, then be glad you got a free sign.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   No one should be upset if people snoop, unless you are hiding something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dude, when you was speaking to bryan in this, u said how he IS a cheater instead of saying possibly. no one likes being called a cheater, expecially if its a joke. and how are you gonna go from saying “why are people saying im a snitch for reporting about possible xrays” to “oh its just a joke”. i find bullshit in that. i dont like people snooping because it arouses suspicion of what are they doing, and distracts me from whatever im doing. one of the reasons why i didnt like it when meep would just pop into my house and stay next to me. my paranoia nature makes me wanna watch him, expecially since he does things like pushing me off. Just go on world map and not actually wander around. unless thats what u are doing then ignore that one comment.<br>
[/quote]I was talking about the whole jrub thing, he said I was a snitch for that, so your point is invalid.  You can’t stop people from snooping, if you don’t like it, play singleplayer.  Most of the time my internet is too slow to play, let alone watch the world map whilst playing.  Either I play, or use the world map, or neither.  I’m kinda low on options on what I can do ingame.  I can’t do anything PvP related, I can’t do a lot of things because my connection, so usually I just lay low and wander about.</p>
<p>Besides, we already settled this, there is no need to bring it up and start another fight.  If you’d like to speak more, bring it to PM, or if you like, join IRC.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well human error for misplacing who from both incidents. i would play singleplayer, but i would rather build with friends and chat with them. and i think i have small amount of available memory so i also can only do one or the other. all i was getting at is snooping can bother some people, so instead of snooping and wandering, find a ring of buddies and/or build some cool buildings. plus i wanted to say how that is kinda of a crappy joke to pull. :I that is all.<br>
[/quote]Plus I wanted to say the joke wasn’t towards you and you are in no way, shape, or form associated with this whole joke and or discussion, so thank you for your time.</p>
<p>But really, of course it isn’t going to be good for you :3</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>i know im not associated with it, but it’s something called empathy, and me acting upon it to better community, like u said when your reported your suspicions of jrub x-raying. :I<br>
and im confused what the last sentence is. are you talking about the joke, the being blamed, or the snooping?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"><br>
[/quote]Honestly, I might have been doing something else when I was typing that because I have no idea what it means either.  :o[/quote]<br>
lolol. im good and through with this as long as you can see where im coming from, not so much that u must believe me or whatever.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 07:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“triston001, post:13, topic:448912”][quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4043013#msg4043013 date=1341816823]</p>
<p>[quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4043009#msg4043009 date=1341816568]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042998#msg4042998 date=1341815821]</p>
<p>[quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4042994#msg4042994 date=1341815420]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.<br>
[/quote]It was a joke because I knew it would piss you off, which it did.  I never even spoke to Tom, so stop bringing that up.  Yes, it is funny, that’s why It’s a joke  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   Oh you got you’re reply now.  Happy?  Every single one of your statements have been proven false, so you could stop bringing that up also.  I did indeed read what you said, apart from all the bullshit I read, I did see you say that.  Oh, you got a sign on you’re property, poor grass block <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it must suck having a sign that can be easily removed on top of you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  I’d be more than happy to go remove my sign if that’s why you’re so pissy, if not, then be glad you got a free sign.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   No one should be upset if people snoop, unless you are hiding something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dude, when you was speaking to bryan in this, u said how he IS a cheater instead of saying possibly. no one likes being called a cheater, expecially if its a joke. and how are you gonna go from saying “why are people saying im a snitch for reporting about possible xrays” to “oh its just a joke”. i find bullshit in that. i dont like people snooping because it arouses suspicion of what are they doing, and distracts me from whatever im doing. one of the reasons why i didnt like it when meep would just pop into my house and stay next to me. my paranoia nature makes me wanna watch him, expecially since he does things like pushing me off. Just go on world map and not actually wander around. unless thats what u are doing then ignore that one comment.<br>
[/quote]I was talking about the whole jrub thing, he said I was a snitch for that, so your point is invalid.  You can’t stop people from snooping, if you don’t like it, play singleplayer.  Most of the time my internet is too slow to play, let alone watch the world map whilst playing.  Either I play, or use the world map, or neither.  I’m kinda low on options on what I can do ingame.  I can’t do anything PvP related, I can’t do a lot of things because my connection, so usually I just lay low and wander about.</p>
<p>Besides, we already settled this, there is no need to bring it up and start another fight.  If you’d like to speak more, bring it to PM, or if you like, join IRC.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well human error for misplacing who from both incidents. i would play singleplayer, but i would rather build with friends and chat with them. and i think i have small amount of available memory so i also can only do one or the other. all i was getting at is snooping can bother some people, so instead of snooping and wandering, find a ring of buddies and/or build some cool buildings. plus i wanted to say how that is kinda of a crappy joke to pull. :I that is all.<br>
[/quote]Plus I wanted to say the joke wasn’t towards you and you are in no way, shape, or form associated with this whole joke and or discussion, so thank you for your time.</p>
<p>But really, of course it isn’t going to be good for you :3</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>i know im not associated with it, but it’s something called empathy, and me acting upon it to better community, like u said when your reported your suspicions of jrub x-raying. :I<br>
and im confused what the last sentence is. are you talking about the joke, the being blamed, or the snooping?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:">[/quote]Honestly, I might have been doing something else when I was typing that because I have no idea what it means either.  :o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 07:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@triston001 triston001]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/triston001">@triston001</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Travas, post:12, topic:448912”][quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4043009#msg4043009 date=1341816568]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042998#msg4042998 date=1341815821]</p>
<p>[quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4042994#msg4042994 date=1341815420]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042974#msg4042974 date=1341812805]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.<br>
[/quote]It was a joke because I knew it would piss you off, which it did.  I never even spoke to Tom, so stop bringing that up.  Yes, it is funny, that’s why It’s a joke  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   Oh you got you’re reply now.  Happy?  Every single one of your statements have been proven false, so you could stop bringing that up also.  I did indeed read what you said, apart from all the bullshit I read, I did see you say that.  Oh, you got a sign on you’re property, poor grass block <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it must suck having a sign that can be easily removed on top of you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  I’d be more than happy to go remove my sign if that’s why you’re so pissy, if not, then be glad you got a free sign.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   No one should be upset if people snoop, unless you are hiding something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dude, when you was speaking to bryan in this, u said how he IS a cheater instead of saying possibly. no one likes being called a cheater, expecially if its a joke. and how are you gonna go from saying “why are people saying im a snitch for reporting about possible xrays” to “oh its just a joke”. i find bullshit in that. i dont like people snooping because it arouses suspicion of what are they doing, and distracts me from whatever im doing. one of the reasons why i didnt like it when meep would just pop into my house and stay next to me. my paranoia nature makes me wanna watch him, expecially since he does things like pushing me off. Just go on world map and not actually wander around. unless thats what u are doing then ignore that one comment.<br>
[/quote]I was talking about the whole jrub thing, he said I was a snitch for that, so your point is invalid.  You can’t stop people from snooping, if you don’t like it, play singleplayer.  Most of the time my internet is too slow to play, let alone watch the world map whilst playing.  Either I play, or use the world map, or neither.  I’m kinda low on options on what I can do ingame.  I can’t do anything PvP related, I can’t do a lot of things because my connection, so usually I just lay low and wander about.</p>
<p>Besides, we already settled this, there is no need to bring it up and start another fight.  If you’d like to speak more, bring it to PM, or if you like, join IRC.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well human error for misplacing who from both incidents. i would play singleplayer, but i would rather build with friends and chat with them. and i think i have small amount of available memory so i also can only do one or the other. all i was getting at is snooping can bother some people, so instead of snooping and wandering, find a ring of buddies and/or build some cool buildings. plus i wanted to say how that is kinda of a crappy joke to pull. :I that is all.<br>
[/quote]Plus I wanted to say the joke wasn’t towards you and you are in no way, shape, or form associated with this whole joke and or discussion, so thank you for your time.</p>
<p>But really, of course it isn’t going to be good for you :3[/quote]<br>
i know im not associated with it, but it’s something called empathy, and me acting upon it to better community, like u said when your reported your suspicions of jrub x-raying. :I<br>
and im confused what the last sentence is. are you talking about the joke, the being blamed, or the snooping?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 06:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“triston001, post:11, topic:448912”][quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042998#msg4042998 date=1341815821]</p>
<p>[quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4042994#msg4042994 date=1341815420]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042974#msg4042974 date=1341812805]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.<br>
[/quote]It was a joke because I knew it would piss you off, which it did.  I never even spoke to Tom, so stop bringing that up.  Yes, it is funny, that’s why It’s a joke  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   Oh you got you’re reply now.  Happy?  Every single one of your statements have been proven false, so you could stop bringing that up also.  I did indeed read what you said, apart from all the bullshit I read, I did see you say that.  Oh, you got a sign on you’re property, poor grass block <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it must suck having a sign that can be easily removed on top of you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  I’d be more than happy to go remove my sign if that’s why you’re so pissy, if not, then be glad you got a free sign.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   No one should be upset if people snoop, unless you are hiding something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dude, when you was speaking to bryan in this, u said how he IS a cheater instead of saying possibly. no one likes being called a cheater, expecially if its a joke. and how are you gonna go from saying “why are people saying im a snitch for reporting about possible xrays” to “oh its just a joke”. i find bullshit in that. i dont like people snooping because it arouses suspicion of what are they doing, and distracts me from whatever im doing. one of the reasons why i didnt like it when meep would just pop into my house and stay next to me. my paranoia nature makes me wanna watch him, expecially since he does things like pushing me off. Just go on world map and not actually wander around. unless thats what u are doing then ignore that one comment.<br>
[/quote]I was talking about the whole jrub thing, he said I was a snitch for that, so your point is invalid.  You can’t stop people from snooping, if you don’t like it, play singleplayer.  Most of the time my internet is too slow to play, let alone watch the world map whilst playing.  Either I play, or use the world map, or neither.  I’m kinda low on options on what I can do ingame.  I can’t do anything PvP related, I can’t do a lot of things because my connection, so usually I just lay low and wander about.</p>
<p>Besides, we already settled this, there is no need to bring it up and start another fight.  If you’d like to speak more, bring it to PM, or if you like, join IRC.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well human error for misplacing who from both incidents. i would play singleplayer, but i would rather build with friends and chat with them. and i think i have small amount of available memory so i also can only do one or the other. all i was getting at is snooping can bother some people, so instead of snooping and wandering, find a ring of buddies and/or build some cool buildings. plus i wanted to say how that is kinda of a crappy joke to pull. :I that is all.[/quote]Plus I wanted to say the joke wasn’t towards you and you are in no way, shape, or form associated with this whole joke and or discussion, so thank you for your time.</p>
<p>But really, of course it isn’t going to be good for you :3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 06:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@triston001 triston001]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/triston001">@triston001</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Travas, post:10, topic:448912”][quote author=triston001 link=topic=551806.msg4042994#msg4042994 date=1341815420]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042974#msg4042974 date=1341812805]</p>
<p>[quote author=hat trix link=topic=551806.msg4042966#msg4042966 date=1341812304]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.<br>
[/quote]It was a joke because I knew it would piss you off, which it did.  I never even spoke to Tom, so stop bringing that up.  Yes, it is funny, that’s why It’s a joke  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   Oh you got you’re reply now.  Happy?  Every single one of your statements have been proven false, so you could stop bringing that up also.  I did indeed read what you said, apart from all the bullshit I read, I did see you say that.  Oh, you got a sign on you’re property, poor grass block <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it must suck having a sign that can be easily removed on top of you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  I’d be more than happy to go remove my sign if that’s why you’re so pissy, if not, then be glad you got a free sign.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   No one should be upset if people snoop, unless you are hiding something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dude, when you was speaking to bryan in this, u said how he IS a cheater instead of saying possibly. no one likes being called a cheater, expecially if its a joke. and how are you gonna go from saying “why are people saying im a snitch for reporting about possible xrays” to “oh its just a joke”. i find bullshit in that. i dont like people snooping because it arouses suspicion of what are they doing, and distracts me from whatever im doing. one of the reasons why i didnt like it when meep would just pop into my house and stay next to me. my paranoia nature makes me wanna watch him, expecially since he does things like pushing me off. Just go on world map and not actually wander around. unless thats what u are doing then ignore that one comment.<br>
[/quote]I was talking about the whole jrub thing, he said I was a snitch for that, so your point is invalid.  You can’t stop people from snooping, if you don’t like it, play singleplayer.  Most of the time my internet is too slow to play, let alone watch the world map whilst playing.  Either I play, or use the world map, or neither.  I’m kinda low on options on what I can do ingame.  I can’t do anything PvP related, I can’t do a lot of things because my connection, so usually I just lay low and wander about.</p>
<p>Besides, we already settled this, there is no need to bring it up and start another fight.  If you’d like to speak more, bring it to PM, or if you like, join IRC.[/quote]<br>
well human error for misplacing who from both incidents. i would play singleplayer, but i would rather build with friends and chat with them. and i think i have small amount of available memory so i also can only do one or the other. all i was getting at is snooping can bother some people, so instead of snooping and wandering, find a ring of buddies and/or build some cool buildings. plus i wanted to say how that is kinda of a crappy joke to pull. :I that is all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 06:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“triston001, post:9, topic:448912”][quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042974#msg4042974 date=1341812805]</p>
<p>[quote author=hat trix link=topic=551806.msg4042966#msg4042966 date=1341812304]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.<br>
[/quote]It was a joke because I knew it would piss you off, which it did.  I never even spoke to Tom, so stop bringing that up.  Yes, it is funny, that’s why It’s a joke  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   Oh you got you’re reply now.  Happy?  Every single one of your statements have been proven false, so you could stop bringing that up also.  I did indeed read what you said, apart from all the bullshit I read, I did see you say that.  Oh, you got a sign on you’re property, poor grass block <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it must suck having a sign that can be easily removed on top of you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  I’d be more than happy to go remove my sign if that’s why you’re so pissy, if not, then be glad you got a free sign.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   No one should be upset if people snoop, unless you are hiding something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>dude, when you was speaking to bryan in this, u said how he IS a cheater instead of saying possibly. no one likes being called a cheater, expecially if its a joke. and how are you gonna go from saying “why are people saying im a snitch for reporting about possible xrays” to “oh its just a joke”. i find bullshit in that. i dont like people snooping because it arouses suspicion of what are they doing, and distracts me from whatever im doing. one of the reasons why i didnt like it when meep would just pop into my house and stay next to me. my paranoia nature makes me wanna watch him, expecially since he does things like pushing me off. Just go on world map and not actually wander around. unless thats what u are doing then ignore that one comment.[/quote]I was talking about the whole jrub thing, he said I was a snitch for that, so your point is invalid.  You can’t stop people from snooping, if you don’t like it, play singleplayer.  Most of the time my internet is too slow to play, let alone watch the world map whilst playing.  Either I play, or use the world map, or neither.  I’m kinda low on options on what I can do ingame.  I can’t do anything PvP related, I can’t do a lot of things because my connection, so usually I just lay low and wander about.</p>
<p>Besides, we already settled this, there is no need to bring it up and start another fight.  If you’d like to speak more, bring it to PM, or if you like, join IRC.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 06:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@triston001 triston001]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/triston001">@triston001</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Travas, post:6, topic:448912”][quote author=hat trix link=topic=551806.msg4042966#msg4042966 date=1341812304]</p>
<p>[quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042947#msg4042947 date=1341810542]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.<br>
[/quote]It was a joke because I knew it would piss you off, which it did.  I never even spoke to Tom, so stop bringing that up.  Yes, it is funny, that’s why It’s a joke  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   Oh you got you’re reply now.  Happy?  Every single one of your statements have been proven false, so you could stop bringing that up also.  I did indeed read what you said, apart from all the bullshit I read, I did see you say that.  Oh, you got a sign on you’re property, poor grass block <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it must suck having a sign that can be easily removed on top of you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  I’d be more than happy to go remove my sign if that’s why you’re so pissy, if not, then be glad you got a free sign.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   No one should be upset if people snoop, unless you are hiding something?[/quote]<br>
dude, when you was speaking to bryan in this, u said how he IS a cheater instead of saying possibly. no one likes being called a cheater, expecially if its a joke. and how are you gonna go from saying “why are people saying im a snitch for reporting about possible xrays” to “oh its just a joke”. i find bullshit in that. i dont like people snooping because it arouses suspicion of what are they doing, and distracts me from whatever im doing. one of the reasons why i didnt like it when meep would just pop into my house and stay next to me. my paranoia nature makes me wanna watch him, expecially since he does things like pushing me off. Just go on world map and not actually wander around. unless thats what u are doing then ignore that one comment.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 06:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“hat trix, post:7, topic:448912”]I could give a shit if you snoop, it avoids conflict. I do give a shit that you placed a sign on my property. and yes, you did make me mad. good job <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>not every one of my statements have been proven false. Most of mine were facts because the assumption of you speaking to tom.[/quote]Well you got a free sign out of it, so congratulations <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Well, I’m sorry this ever happened. (An apology really means something, since I hardly ever say sorry)  Anyway, I’d like it if we just stopped all this bullshit.  We have been fighting for months now (not really fighting, but we did not respect each other) and I would like that to stop.  I don’t even know how it all started, but I probably said something I shouldn’t have when I was in one of my moods.  But yeah, maybe we can be friends, if not, then hopefully we stop spamming the forums with our fights and stop fighting altogether <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 06:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hat_trix hat trix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hat_trix">@hat_trix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I could give a shit if you snoop, it avoids conflict. I do give a shit that you placed a sign on my property. and yes, you did make me mad. good job <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>not every one of my statements have been proven false. Most of mine were facts because the assumption of you speaking to tom.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“hat trix, post:5, topic:448912”][quote author=Travas link=topic=551806.msg4042947#msg4042947 date=1341810542]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.[/quote]It was a joke because I knew it would piss you off, which it did.  I never even spoke to Tom, so stop bringing that up.  Yes, it is funny, that’s why It’s a joke  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   Oh you got you’re reply now.  Happy?  Every single one of your statements have been proven false, so you could stop bringing that up also.  I did indeed read what you said, apart from all the bullshit I read, I did see you say that.  Oh, you got a sign on you’re property, poor grass block <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> it must suck having a sign that can be easily removed on top of you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:">  I’d be more than happy to go remove my sign if that’s why you’re so pissy, if not, then be glad you got a free sign.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">   No one should be upset if people snoop, unless you are hiding something?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 05:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hat_trix hat trix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hat_trix">@hat_trix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Travas, post:4, topic:448912”][quote author=hat trix link=topic=551806.msg4042943#msg4042943 date=1341809973]<br>
Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.<br>
[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.[/quote]</p>
<p>How was the sign a “joke”? and I said you either spoke to tom or said it out loud. because tom obviously heard it from someone, and its funny as hell YOU were the one that placed the sign on my property. If it were a pm, other players (who i pointed out before) wouldn’t be able to back me up In the situation you pointed out in the other topic about the diamonds.<br>
and by other statements being proven false, i was talking about the other statements regarding my “xrayed” diamonds. and why would i “pm you again”? I wanted a reply from you, and you didn’t answer. I took it public, and finally got my reply. And Im sure others know Im not a cheater. manbearpig plays moparcraft at my house, along with chullx3 and sniffle6. none of us cheat, and they can vouch for that.<br>
If you read what I said, I never said you couldn’t go on someone elses property. I simply said it would stop conflict when you do stupid things like placing signs on others property. and yeah, the way you snoop around looking to get people in trouble, im sure there will be more too.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 05:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“hat trix, post:3, topic:448912”]Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.[/quote]Really, got any proof of me speaking to Tom?  Because I hardly ever talk to Tom, unless we are in a debate on the forum, where anyone can see.  That sign there was somewhat of a joke, obviously I do not have proof.  Anyone with common sense knows that, if I had proof, don’t you think I would of posted it?</p>
<p>There isn’t a need for this.  This should have been contained straight to PM, if I didn’t answer, why wouldn’t you PM me again?  I must have viewed it and forgotten all about it.  There are no rules on the server stating I cannot go on your property or seeing what you are up to; or anyone for that matter.  I’m pretty sure no one knows you are a cheater, so making more arguments and threads about it isn’t helping you in the slightest.</p>
<p>How have the proven false?  Name one example?  If I recall correctly, I reported a person I suspected of Xraying, if you’re so offended by the report, then please don’t view the topic, or create more topics discussing it.  Once again, there is no rule stating I am not allowed to roam the world looking at people’s creations, so stop saying that.  How do I look like the worse person?  Tired of my reports?  This is the first report I have made, and I’m sure there will be more.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 05:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hat_trix hat trix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hat_trix">@hat_trix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Because, You either reported me to tom as well, or spoke of me xraying. You then proceeded to place a sign on my land stating that “you have proof of me xraing” witch, I think should be against the rules for you to place anything on anyone’s property in the first place without their permission. another reason I didn’t pm you is because you Ignored my pm when I confronted you about it (obvious you had no proof of me xraing) and lastly, the topic was locked and I wasn’t finished <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>There Is a need for this. You basically said you don’t play, you just log on and go around to see what others are doing. But its obvious you are looking for trouble/trying to get someone else in trouble. A simple way to avoid conflict is to stay away from those you already have conflict with. but, since there was already a conflict going on between you and I, I figured why the hell not? I don’t want to be made out as a cheater, and as everyone knows “your proof of me xraying” still doesn’t exist because you have yet to show any evidence.</p>
<p>Your other statements have been proven false as well. basically, my whole point to this topic is to stay out of everyone elses business. You end up making yourself look worse then the person your report. sooner or later, mods will get tired of your false reports and will (hopefully) just lock your topics/ignore the topics when they see them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is there really a need for this?</p>
<p>I reported one person, which you call ‘snitching’.  IIRC, snitching is if you know someone is breaking the rules, they tell you not to tell, but you do anyway.  I don’t see how it is snitching if I am reporting someone for possibly Xraying.  I don’t see how I’m ‘going around and reporting dedicated players’ when I only reported one person, who is a troll to begin with.  As I said before, I’m sorry for reporting someone that is using Xray.  God forbid people on this server actually follow rules.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 04:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Travas (herobrine)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hat_trix hat trix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hat_trix">@hat_trix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would like to continue this topic, and I would like to to be open for everyone to read because I want others to chirp in and allow their point of views if they want as well. If i wanted this to be private I would make it a pm.</p>
<blockquote>Quote from: hat trix on July 07, 2012, 09:37:56 PM
Quote from: xx matty xx on July 07, 2012, 05:51:38 PM
Quote from: asshole_rule on July 07, 2012, 12:48:28 PM
Quote from: zaz278 on July 07, 2012, 12:42:04 AM
Fairly simple, relm and jrub said they 'found something cool' so I stalked them on worldmap after they left I went to the coords I saw them at and dug straight down.
<p>Quote from: Travas on July 06, 2012, 10:39:09 PM<br>
Don’t try saying you got the coords from somebody and dug straight down; everyone uses that excuse.</p>
<p>Come on zaz y u no read? loljk</p>
<p>Pre-empting his response doesn’t make it invalid. I’ve dug 1x1 holes straight into spawners - not because I xray, but because I got the coords underground and dug down from the surface. Lots of reasons why people might have holes dug directly into interesting shit.</p>
<p>This is basically what I did. I died at a spawner. knowing the coords, i simply dug straight down to it to get my items. Then, herobrine reports me to tom and leaves a sign on my property saying “I have proof you xray”.</p>
<p>also herobrine, ever heard of minimap with wp’s? you should look into that, snitch.</p>
<p>The thing is, there isn’t any caves around the spawner I found that you ‘got the coords and dug into’.  Yes, I know what a world map is, but the thing I don’t understand is, how is reporting rule breakers ‘snitching’.  If anything, I should be thanked for caring about people breaking rules on the server.  And IIRC, on the old map, you had stacks and stacks of diamond blocks, you just don’t come across those easily.  I have nothing against you nor jrub.  You were somewhat of a friend at one point, and so was jrub.  Honestly, I’d report my best friend if he was breaking the rules.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Travis, I have round only 2 mob spawners. Two of witch I have placed blocks over top of them to allow myself to find them when I need to. One of them I have is a spider spawner, the other is a zombie spanwer. both of these spawners are found from caves, as my proof I will post pictures of where the cave entrance is/was WITH proof of where it was if it still isn’t there.</p>
<p>The reason I’m calling you out is because you just go around reporting random (dedicated) server players who are on more then you and have time to find items that you have yet to find. At first, I might have had suspicion of other players xraying because some people had over 20 diamond after an hour of play on the server. The thing is, I dont go straight for diamond (could actually care less about it) and I have no use for mob spawners. I cbf to build farms because I would rather spend my time building up my town, not afking string or xp.</p>
<p>And last but not least, the “stacks upon stacks” of diamond I came across in world2 on the old server. Yes, I remember. So does everyone else that was on. Coonhunter was looting a town that hadn’t reset res (the town very close to my huge town) and he came across almost 10 stacks of rails, and about 6 stacks of diamond blocks. He freaks out about the loot on chat, then died. I ran in and took his items. Later, after giving tom hell about them, I burned more then half the items because I had given the rest to other players before tom even got to me. Coonhunter, fuscate, manbearpig, and chull can most likely vouch for me on this.</p>
<p>pics:<br>
Marking the area so I dont have to look for it incase I lose minimap<br>
<a href="http://aar.im/u/20120-6h" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://aar.im/i/20120-6h.png" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
Straight to the spawner, cave from behind<br>
<a href="http://aar.im/u/20120-8e" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://aar.im/i/20120-8e.png" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
Closer look at cave from behind<br>
<a href="http://aar.im/u/20120-a0" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://aar.im/i/20120-a0.png" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
2nd spawner, has spawner and Mine shaft in the back<br>
<a href="http://aar.im/u/20120-9d" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://aar.im/i/20120-9d.png" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
A view from the mineshaft (spawner is between cobble and fence)<br>
<a href="http://aar.im/u/20120-ig" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://aar.im/i/20120-ig.png" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
broke the cobble for a better look, there is the glass and entrance to my spawner (behind glass)<br>
<a href="http://aar.im/u/20120-9f" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://aar.im/i/20120-9f.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>If I have forgotten a spawner, please point it out to me. I cant remember because I barely go down in the caves anymore. I got what i need, witch was cobble coal and iron<br>
oh, and here is your “xrayed” diamonds</p>
<p><a href="http://aar.im/u/20120-h1" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://aar.im/i/20120-h1.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>now please, everyone add your 2 cents. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 04:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448912-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/travas-herobrine/448912.rss">Travas (herobrine)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
