<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>OBjects within the server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/objects-within-the-server/357476</link>
    <description>I couldn&#39;t think of an appropriate title for this, but let me explain my situation.

You know on the minimap if there is a wall it will just be like a white line on the minimap representing it, I want to add my own.

I&#39;m making my own home area with a map editor, I got the bank area built in nice and neat, the hight settings are perfect, etc. I don&#39;t want to load objects for my walls, I want it to load.. how can i put it.. within the server. In other words..
I want this:
[img]http://img831.imageshack.us/img831/2169/96717898.png[/img]
To look like this:
[img]http://img685.imageshack.us/img685/6126/50650505.png[/img]
but not only that, have an actual like.. wall there that isn&#39;t an object so when u right click on it, it will act like it&#39;s just a part of the map.

I realized that these objects aren&#39;t added in via the map editor.. How can I add them?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:08:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/objects-within-the-server/357476.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>OBjects within the server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runeite51 runeite51]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runeite51">@runeite51</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I couldn’t think of an appropriate title for this, but let me explain my situation.</p>
<p>You know on the minimap if there is a wall it will just be like a white line on the minimap representing it, I want to add my own.</p>
<p>I’m making my own home area with a map editor, I got the bank area built in nice and neat, the hight settings are perfect, etc. I don’t want to load objects for my walls, I want it to load… how can i put it… within the server. In other words…<br>
I want this:<br>
<img src="http://img831.imageshack.us/img831/2169/96717898.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
To look like this:<br>
<img src="http://img685.imageshack.us/img685/6126/50650505.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
but not only that, have an actual like… wall there that isn’t an object so when u right click on it, it will act like it’s just a part of the map.</p>
<p>I realized that these objects aren’t added in via the map editor… How can I add them?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/objects-within-the-server/357476/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/objects-within-the-server/357476/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-357476-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/objects-within-the-server/357476.rss">OBjects within the server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
