<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mopar Monthly Template #5</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659</link>
    <description>---
layout: post
title: &quot;The Mopar Monthly&quot;
date: 2013-08-30 00:00
comments: true
categories: [MoparScape, RSPS, RS, Mopar, Monthly]
author: Flame_
---
The Mopar Monthly
===============
##Edition 5
---

This month on the Mopar Monthly:
Welcome to the fifth edition of the Mopar Monthly! For those of you who don&#39;t know what this is, the Mopar Monthly is a monthly magazine where users can see the best of the best in the forums for each month, user interviews, rants, and more! Forum members are free to submit controversial news articles, thought-provoking rants, and anything else by contacting any members of the Mopar Monthly team. For those of you that read the previous edition and provided feedback, a big thanks to you all for keeping this possible!

####Included in this edition will be:

* The Overall Most Helpful Member(s) of the Month
* Notable Developments
* Hot Suggestion Topics
* A Submission From Sk8rdude461

Before we begin, it&#39;s only right to announce, for those who haven&#39;t seen it already, that MoparScape now has begun development for its official community server. The project, being developed mainly by Sinisoul and Davidi2, has made good progress since its birth. If you&#39;d like to visit the project thread, [click me](https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,651901.0.html), and if you&#39;d like to join the IRC channel, [click me](http://www.moparisthebest.com/irc.php?img=0&amp;host=irc.moparisthebest.com&amp;channel=mopardev), or join #mopardev on irc.moparisthebest.xxx
The server is a community project, and that means that anyone can contribute and develop content for the game. The scripting language is Ruby utilizing jRuby. If you have any interest in developing for the server, you should learn the basics of Ruby. This means outside of the server core, no content will be written in Java. You can probably learn Ruby well-enough in a few days if you study existing examples and have some previous programming experience at all. The server&#39;s github can be found [here](https://github.com/Hadyn/rune-emu).

#####Section 1: The Overall Most Helpful Member(s) of the Month:

This category is for users who are willing to help people in need of help. This award doesn&#39;t mean that these users know everything - they may also need help from time to time - but they&#39;re always willing to give up some of their time to help someone who needs it. Users have been listed depending on which section they have the most influence in.

######Server Help:
- [Sk8rdude461](https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=341531)
- [Null Amount](https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=567674)

If you have any other nominations for future editions of the Mopar Monthly, please [send a private message to Flame_](//www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=pm;sa=send;u=600800) or [send a private message to Ambokile](//www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=pm;sa=send;u=576712). Please don&#39;t publicly dispute any listings for this month, instead contact a member of the team if you feel one of them is incorrect.

#####Section 2: Notable Developments

######2006Redone:
* Type: Indie game development
* Genre: pirates, oceanic warfare
* Development Started: August 12, 2013
* Developer: frell
* Link: [click me](https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,646683.0.html)

######Ask-Engines:
* Type: Website
* Genre: Question-Answer
* Development Started: September 14, 2013
* Developer: pkerjosh13
* Link: [click me](https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,649090.0.html)

######2009Remade:
* Type: RSPS
* Genre: RSPS Development
* Development Started: August 24, 2013
* Developer: south-park
* Link: [click me](https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,647540.0.html)

#####Section 3: Hot Suggestion Topics

This category is dedicated to giving attention to suggestions that have caught the community&#39;s eye and are a hot topic for debate on whether or not it should be added. Any noted suggestion is by no means an indicator that it shall be added to the website/forums.

- [Bring over the music board from MITB or create a new one](https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,649213.0.html)
- [Re: Giving awards moderation abilities](https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,648817.0.html)
- [An rsps repository](https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,646959.0.html)

#####Section 4: A Submission From Sk8rdude461
_RSPS: My Viewpoint:_

&gt; So, I&#39;ve been in the RSPS scene for a good while now, since I was about 12 or 13. In that time, I&#39;ve picked up a vast amount of knowledge, ranging from how to make a simple HTML document, to writing full Java apps to do miscellaneous things. The sad thing is, I never moved on from that simple 317 server. You know, the ones that used to be wildly popular, and everyone in the world plus their parents owned. Yeah, I can&#39;t exactly say why I haven&#39;t moved on, perhaps it&#39;s because I&#39;m just not comfortable enough to do so. And I&#39;m not comfortable enough because I don&#39;t know enough about Java, and you know what, it&#39;s good I haven&#39;t. Why? Because the servers that are being released now (700+&#39;s) don&#39;t have documentation like a 317. The 317 server isn&#39;t even fully documented and yet we&#39;re moving on to higher revisions. If we can&#39;t even perfect something JaGeX made YEARS ago, why are we working on something they just barely put out? I can tell you why. The people that are just getting into the RSPS scene aren&#39;t in it for the reasons I, or many of you others joined. The top 2 reasons they&#39;re in it are because A) they want to make a quick buck and B) they want to relive the old days. They aren&#39;t getting into it for reasons like I did, and most of you. I saw the game, and I saw it lacked potential. It was missing user creativity. RSPS&#39; allowed me to essentially make RuneScape in my own image. In life, you never want to do something for the wrong reason. Like school, for instance. Most of us will sit there day by day, bored out of our minds, just waiting for it to end. But if school revolved around you, and what you wanted to do, you&#39;d want be there everyday, on time, and ready to learn. That&#39;s what I&#39;m doing with my RSPS. I&#39;m making it to my liking. Not the general public&#39;s, not some companies, not some other person, and definitely not the individuals on MoparScape. If someone doesn&#39;t like my server, they can gladly leave. The server is for my enjoyment, not yours. Anyways, on the topic of 317s. I believe everyone that goes into RSPS should start on an easy revision/base, and take some form of a course of Java and HTML. If they like what they worked on with those courses, then they&#39;ll like RSPS; because RSPS isn&#39;t about the visuals, it&#39;s about the code behind it. The gears to make the clock move, the engine to move the car. As I end my statement, I just want to restate one simple point: Do not get into RSPS or writing code for the wrong reasons! Make sure it&#39;s something you want to do before you pursue it.

#####Section 6: An Interview With a Forum User

Due to me being extremely busy from school and soccer committments, the Interview will be coming in a following sub-edition.

##

That concludes this month&#39;s edition of the Mopar Monthly! The Mopar Monthly team would like to thank everyone who has taken the time to contribute to the fifth edition, which is still coming strong, and we are always welcome to more contributions. You can view the Mopar Monthly thread on the forums by clicking [here](http://goo.gl/Nh65g). Interested in becoming an editor/writer? Contact [Flame_](http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=600800) or [Ambokile](http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=576712)!

#####This edition of the [Mopar Monthly](http://goo.gl/Nh65g) was published by [Flame_](http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=600800).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 22:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mopar Monthly Template #5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks, I’ve added your fixed version.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-s">Just a heads up, Si Force is sending in a game review tomorrow as our “Submission <span class="hashtag">#2</span>,” so that should fill in the two spots that I’d hoped to use this month.</span></p>
<p>EDIT: Submitted, this is the final draft on <span class="hashtag">#5</span>.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 22:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532659-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659.rss">Mopar Monthly Template #5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mopar Monthly Template #5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>So, I've been in the RSPS scene for a good while now, since I was about 12 or 13. In that time, I've picked up a vast amount of knowledge, ranging from how to make a simple HTML document, to writing full Java apps to do miscellaneous things. The sad thing is, I never moved on from that simple 317 server. You know, the ones that used to be wildly popular, and everyone in the world plus their parents owned. Yeah, I can't exactly say why I haven't moved on, perhaps it's because I'm just not comfortable enough to do so. And I'm not comfortable enough because I don't know enough about Java, and you know what, it's good I haven't. Why? Because the servers that are being released now (700+'s) don't have documentation like a 317. The 317 server isn't even fully documented and yet we're moving on to higher revisions. If we can't even perfect something JaGeX made YEARS ago, why are we working on something they just barely put out? I can tell you why. The people that are just getting into the RSPS scene aren't in it for the reasons I, or many of you others joined. The top 2 reasons they're in it are because A) they want to make a quick buck and B) they want to relive the old days. They aren't getting into it for reasons like I did, and most of you. I saw the game, and I saw it lacked potential. It was missing user creativity. RSPS' allowed me to essentially make RuneScape in my own image. In life, you never want to do something for the wrong reason. Like school, for instance. Most of us will sit there day by day, bored out of our minds, just waiting for it to end. But if school revolved around you, and what you wanted to do, you'd want be there everyday, on time, and ready to learn. That's what I'm doing with my RSPS. I'm making it to my liking. Not the general public's, not some companies, not some other person, and definitely not the individuals on MoparScape. If someone doesn't like my server, they can gladly leave. The server is for my enjoyment, not yours. Anyways, on the topic of 317s. I believe everyone that goes into RSPS should start on an easy revision/base, and take some form of a course of Java and HTML. If they like what they worked on with those courses, then they'll like RSPS; because RSPS isn't about the visuals, it's about the code behind it. The gears to make the clock move, the engine to move the car. As I end my statement, I just want to restate one simple point: Do not get into RSPS or writing code for the wrong reasons! Make sure it's something you want to do before you pursue it.</blockquote>
<p>I got a lot of complains about the interview having bad spelling/grammar etc. The above has been (mostly) corrected.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 16:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532659-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659.rss">Mopar Monthly Template #5</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mopar Monthly Template #5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <hr>
<h2>layout: post<br>
title: “The Mopar Monthly”<br>
date: 2013-08-30 00:00<br>
comments: true<br>
categories: [MoparScape, RSPS, RS, Mopar, Monthly]<br>
author: Flame_</h2>
<h1>The Mopar Monthly</h1>
<h2>#<span class="hashtag">#Edition</span> 5</h2>
<p>This month on the Mopar Monthly:<br>
Welcome to the fifth edition of the Mopar Monthly! For those of you who don’t know what this is, the Mopar Monthly is a monthly magazine where users can see the best of the best in the forums for each month, user interviews, rants, and more! Forum members are free to submit controversial news articles, thought-provoking rants, and anything else by contacting any members of the Mopar Monthly team. For those of you that read the previous edition and provided feedback, a big thanks to you all for keeping this possible!</p>
<p>###<span class="hashtag">#Included</span> in this edition will be:</p>
<ul>
<li>The Overall Most Helpful Member(s) of the Month</li>
<li>Notable Developments</li>
<li>Hot Suggestion Topics</li>
<li>A Submission From Sk8rdude461</li>
</ul>
<p>Before we begin, it’s only right to announce, for those who haven’t seen it already, that MoparScape now has begun development for its official community server. The project, being developed mainly by Sinisoul and Davidi2, has made good progress since its birth. If you’d like to visit the project thread, <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,651901.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">click me</a>, and if you’d like to join the IRC channel, <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/irc.php?img=0&amp;host=irc.moparisthebest.com&amp;channel=mopardev" rel="nofollow noopener">click me</a>, or join <span class="hashtag">#mopardev</span> on irc.moparisthebest.xxx<br>
The server is a community project, and that means that anyone can contribute and develop content for the game. The scripting language is Ruby utilizing jRuby. If you have any interest in developing for the server, you should learn the basics of Ruby. This means outside of the server core, no content will be written in Java. You can probably learn Ruby well-enough in a few days if you study existing examples and have some previous programming experience at all. The server’s github can be found <a href="https://github.com/Hadyn/rune-emu" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 1: The Overall Most Helpful Member(s) of the Month:</p>
<p>This category is for users who are willing to help people in need of help. This award doesn’t mean that these users know everything - they may also need help from time to time - but they’re always willing to give up some of their time to help someone who needs it. Users have been listed depending on which section they have the most influence in.</p>
<p>#####<span class="hashtag">#Server</span> Help:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=341531" rel="nofollow noopener">Sk8rdude461</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=567674" rel="nofollow noopener">Null Amount</a></li>
</ul>
<p>If you have any other nominations for future editions of the Mopar Monthly, please <a href="//www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=pm;sa=send;u=600800" rel="nofollow noopener">send a private message to Flame_</a> or <a href="//www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=pm;sa=send;u=576712" rel="nofollow noopener">send a private message to Ambokile</a>. Please don’t publicly dispute any listings for this month, instead contact a member of the team if you feel one of them is incorrect.</p>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 2: Notable Developments</p>
<p>#####<span class="hashtag">#2006Redone:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>Type: Indie game development</li>
<li>Genre: pirates, oceanic warfare</li>
<li>Development Started: August 12, 2013</li>
<li>Developer: frell</li>
<li>Link: <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,646683.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">click me</a>
</li>
</ul>
<p>#####<span class="hashtag">#Ask-Engines:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>Type: Website</li>
<li>Genre: Question-Answer</li>
<li>Development Started: September 14, 2013</li>
<li>Developer: pkerjosh13</li>
<li>Link: <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,649090.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">click me</a>
</li>
</ul>
<p>#####<span class="hashtag">#2009Remade:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>Type: RSPS</li>
<li>Genre: RSPS Development</li>
<li>Development Started: August 24, 2013</li>
<li>Developer: south-park</li>
<li>Link: <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,647540.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">click me</a>
</li>
</ul>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 3: Hot Suggestion Topics</p>
<p>This category is dedicated to giving attention to suggestions that have caught the community’s eye and are a hot topic for debate on whether or not it should be added. Any noted suggestion is by no means an indicator that it shall be added to the website/forums.</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,649213.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">Bring over the music board from MITB or create a new one</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,648817.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">Re: Giving awards moderation abilities</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,646959.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">An rsps repository</a></li>
</ul>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 4: A Submission From Sk8rdude461<br>
<em>RSPS: My Viewpoint:</em></p>
<blockquote>
<p>So, I’ve been in the RSPS scene for a good while now, since I was about 12 or 13. In that time, I’ve picked up a vast amount of knowledge, ranging from how to make a simple HTML document, to writing full Java apps to do miscellaneous things. The sad thing is, I never moved on from that simple 317 server. You know, the ones that used to be wildly popular, and everyone in the world plus their parents owned. Yeah, I can’t exactly say why I haven’t moved on, perhaps it’s because I’m just not comfortable enough to do so. And I’m not comfortable enough because I don’t know enough about Java, and you know what, it’s good I haven’t. Why? Because the servers that are being released now (700+‘s) don’t have documentation like a 317. The 317 server isn’t even fully documented and yet we’re moving on to higher revisions. If we can’t even perfect something JaGeX made YEARS ago, why are we working on something they just barely put out? I can tell you why. The people that are just getting into the RSPS scene aren’t in it for the reasons I, or many of you others joined. The top 2 reasons they’re in it are because A) they want to make a quick buck and B) they want to relive the old days. They aren’t getting into it for reasons like I did, and most of you. I saw the game, and I saw it lacked potential. It was missing user creativity. RSPS’ allowed me to essentially make RuneScape in my own image. In life, you never want to do something for the wrong reason. Like school, for instance. Most of us will sit there day by day, bored out of our minds, just waiting for it to end. But if school revolved around you, and what you wanted to do, you’d want be there everyday, on time, and ready to learn. That’s what I’m doing with my RSPS. I’m making it to my liking. Not the general public’s, not some companies, not some other person, and definitely not the individuals on MoparScape. If someone doesn’t like my server, they can gladly leave. The server is for my enjoyment, not yours. Anyways, on the topic of 317s. I believe everyone that goes into RSPS should start on an easy revision/base, and take some form of a course of Java and HTML. If they like what they worked on with those courses, then they’ll like RSPS; because RSPS isn’t about the visuals, it’s about the code behind it. The gears to make the clock move, the engine to move the car. As I end my statement, I just want to restate one simple point: Do not get into RSPS or writing code for the wrong reasons! Make sure it’s something you want to do before you pursue it.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#Section</span> 6: An Interview With a Forum User</p>
<p>Due to me being extremely busy from school and soccer committments, the Interview will be coming in a following sub-edition.</p>
<h2></h2>
<p>That concludes this month’s edition of the Mopar Monthly! The Mopar Monthly team would like to thank everyone who has taken the time to contribute to the fifth edition, which is still coming strong, and we are always welcome to more contributions. You can view the Mopar Monthly thread on the forums by clicking <a href="http://goo.gl/Nh65g" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>. Interested in becoming an editor/writer? Contact <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=600800" rel="nofollow noopener">Flame_</a> or <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=576712" rel="nofollow noopener">Ambokile</a>!</p>
<p>####<span class="hashtag">#This</span> edition of the <a href="http://goo.gl/Nh65g" rel="nofollow noopener">Mopar Monthly</a> was published by <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile;u=600800" rel="nofollow noopener">Flame_</a>.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 01:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532659-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-monthly-template-5/532659.rss">Mopar Monthly Template #5</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
