<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please help!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help/223652</link>
    <description>In the sticky post in server tuts &quot;how to create a server&quot; i did everything, but when i got to the part at end where it said &quot;if your server isn&#39;t still up, try opening up your ports 43594 in firewall/router&quot; well i went to my firewall overview and than to firewall, but i couldn&#39;t find 43594 port in the list that was populated. I need help, i did everything but my server still doesn&#39;t work because i think its because of the ports.

Other information: I have a firewall broadband router, and i use a access point for my computer only (the one that im trying to make the server with). Do i have to do something with the router? Because than ill have to change options, details in my other computer with the router connected, and i don&#39;t know anything about that.

Please help,
Thanks[br][br][size=1]Posted on: August 03, 2008, 02:43:02 pm[/size][hr]I need help, comon[br][br][size=1]Posted on: August 03, 2008, 03:02:19 pm[/size][hr]plzz</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 20:14:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help/223652.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please help!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fluster fluster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fluster">@fluster</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In the sticky post in server tuts “how to create a server” i did everything, but when i got to the part at end where it said “if your server isn’t still up, try opening up your ports 43594 in firewall/router” well i went to my firewall overview and than to firewall, but i couldn’t find 43594 port in the list that was populated. I need help, i did everything but my server still doesn’t work because i think its because of the ports.</p>
<p>Other information: I have a firewall broadband router, and i use a access point for my computer only (the one that im trying to make the server with). Do i have to do something with the router? Because than ill have to change options, details in my other computer with the router connected, and i don’t know anything about that.</p>
<p>Please help,<br>
Thanks[br][br][size=1]Posted on: August 03, 2008, 02:43:02 pm[/size][hr]I need help, comon[br][br][size=1]Posted on: August 03, 2008, 03:02:19 pm[/size][hr]plzz</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help/223652/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help/223652/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 20:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-223652-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help/223652.rss">Please help!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
