<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Question on staker</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845</link>
    <description>Hey I&#39;m thinking of buying / making a staker but i literally have no idea where to start could someone send me a guide or tell me the diffrent types of stakers and some helpful guidelines \=)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 11:53:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pure strength stakers should <em>never</em> have def/prayer. These increase levels ALOT.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 11:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@leader leader]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leader">@leader</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here is a guide. Hope it helps.</p>
<p>Table of Contents -</p>
<ol>
<li>Staker Types</li>
<li>Equipment</li>
<li>Hiding</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<p>Part 1.</p>
<p>Staker Types.</p>
<p>When it comes to Melee Staking, there are 3 types that are the main population of the Melee Stakers, in this chapter I will explain all 3 so you can get an idea on which one you would like to make, choose wisely because all 3 can be great stakers, or horrible, depending on your enemy, your levels, your equipment, and hiding your true staking set.</p>
<p>Pure Strength Staker -</p>
<p>These are the high hitters of the stakers, ignoring defense and going all out in strength, with a decent attack level. Problem is that they tend to get owned by Defense Stakers because these pures have low defense, while defense Stakers are based on pure defense, meaning they won’t hit often, but when they do it will be a high hit, so you still have a small chance winning, because 50% of staking is luck, while the other 50% depends on your stats and equipment. These types of stakers own Balanced Stakers because their tuff attack and strength rip through their medium defense, and aren’t too phased by their attack and strength. This type of staker is what can be used in the wilderness for a lot of kills. Prayer is recommended up to 34 so you can use Ultimate Strength and Increased Reflexes for the best performance with your high strength, or 1 pray to avoid defense stakers from protecting against your melee, by staking with no prayer at all times.</p>
<p>Here are 3 examples of a Pure Strength Staker -</p>
<p>60 attack, 80 strength, 10 defense, 43 prayer, 1 magic, 1 range.</p>
<p>75 attack, 90 strength, 1 defense, 34 prayer, 1 magic, 1 range.</p>
<p>70 attack, 85 strength, 20 defense, 43 prayer, 1 magic, 1 range.</p>
<p>Pure Defense Staker -</p>
<p>The Pure Defense Stakers usually owns the Pure Strength Stakers, unless they are shit out of luck :rolleyes: . This is because it is difficult for the Strength Staker to hit the high defense, and the Strength Stakers get hit often because of the low defense they have. This is the most successful staker to date if you ask me, because they seem to perform very well with the right equipment. The only weakness Pure Defense Stakers have is fighting Balanced Stakers, because balanced Stakers usually have higher attack and strength, and still a nice amount of defense, making the Defense Stakers stats useless. Lower the level, the more stakes you’re going to win as a Defense Staker, because Balanced and Strength Stakers start to rule when it comes to 75+ combat. Not at all times, but most of the time. You can still win above 75 combat because luck is a big roll in staking no matter what your levels are. Pray is usually a must with these stakers so they can protect from melee, boosting their specialty of defense. Smite is also helpful to these stakers.</p>
<p>Here is 3 examples of a Defense Staker -</p>
<p>60 attack, 40 strength, 75 defense, 52 pray, 1 magic, 1 range.</p>
<p>75 attack, 50 strength, 90 defense, 43 pray, 1 magic, 1 range.</p>
<p>70 attack, 45 strength, 80 defense, 52 pray, 1 magic, 1 range.</p>
<p>Balanced Staker -</p>
<p>The Balanced Stakers have very close attack, strength, and defense, most of the time all 3 of those skills are the same exact level. This is nice because you have decent accuracy, deal decent damage, and avoid hits with your decent defense. They have a very big weakness to Pure Strength Stakers because a Balanced Staker has close stats to an NPC (usually balanced stats on an NPC), so their defense isn’t too hard to hit, and their attack and strength isn’t tuff enough to take out the Strength Staker quickly enough before getting hit with very high damage amounts. On the other hand, balanced stakers have a good chance of beating Defense Stakers because they usually have higher attack and strength, and still a nice defense level, making them hit higher damage and still avoiding the Defense Stakers swings because of the not too bad defense.</p>
<p>Here are 3 examples of a Balanced Staker -</p>
<p>70 attack, 80 strength, 70 defense, 43 pray, 1 magic, 1 range.</p>
<p>65 attack, 60 strength, 50 defense, 43 pray, 1 magic, 1 range.</p>
<p>70 attack, 70 strength, 70 defense, 52 pray, 1 magic, 1 range.</p>
<p>I hope this kind of gave you a good idea of what type of staker you would prefer, all 3 can be great if used correctly, meaning the right equipment and stats.</p>
<hr>
<p>Part 2.</p>
<p>Equipment.</p>
<p>Equipment is basically 25% of your whole strategy of winning a stake, including Hiding which will be explained later. There is perfect staking equipment for each of the Staker Types, depending on their levels. I’ll explain what to use on each type of staker, so you know what gear to buy for your staker.</p>
<p>Pure Strength Staker -</p>
<p>The Pure Strength Staker is very good in monk robes if he has 1-10 defense, and 31+ pray because it boosts up the prayer bonus, making it more effective. If your Strength Staker has 20 defense, Initiate is very good amour to use, and/or parts of monk robes, if your attack is 70, use a DDS for specials and a whip when your special bar runs out. If you can’t afford a whip use a Dragon Scimitar because it is just as fast and still decent Strength bonus. Always use a Strength Ammy for best results in the stake. Amour isn’t a big deal to Strength Stakers because they are based on strength, meaning what they wear on their body doesn’t help much.</p>
<p>Pure Defense Staker -</p>
<p>The Pure Defense Staker is made to wear top notch amour such as barrows sets, and dragon amour parts. This is because it gives you as much extra defense as possible to make you even harder to hit on top of your rock hard defense level. If you are 60 defense, get as much dragon parts as you can, if you can’t afford some rune parts will do, Rune Boots, obby cape, and obby shield is a must after 60 defense. Once you hit 70 defense, Torags or Dharoks amour is HIGHLY recommended. Always use a Glory Ammy because it has a nice bonus to both Strength and Defense, helping you a lot believe it or not. Use the best weapon you can, Defense Stakers usually have decent attack but a low strength level, meaning they can usually wield a whip or a d scimmy, use DDS spec or Dragon Scimitar to cut their prayer of protecting from you, making them more of an easy target. Amour is the most important part of a Defense Staker so don’t mind investing a lot of money for Amour because you will be thankful in the long run from winning so many stakes.</p>
<p>Balanced Staker - The Balanced Staker performs best in Barrows sets. Preferably Veracs because it is almost untouchable AND cuts right through prayer! If you can’t afford Veracs, try going for Dharoks, and if you can’t afford that your better off with making a different type of staker because your staker will not perform as good as possible. Always use a Glory Ammy to even out your stat bonuses, just like how your levels are close to even. There’s not much more to say about them, just always fight in accurate and wish for the best!</p>
<hr>
<p>Part 3.</p>
<p>Hiding.</p>
<p>Hiding is tricking people by wearing cheap amour and weapons until the duel starts, then putting on your real set. Most people consider this cheating but who gives a fuck, this is a cheating website <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> . This helps you because you get a lot more duel offers because the people don’t know you’re as good as you really are. Try switching worlds often if you are a Hider because if you run into a person you beat, he will bug you a lot.</p>
<hr>
<p>Thank You and Enjoy.</p>
<p>All credit goes to Grill Em.<br>
Credit for correcting spelling goes to Leader. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 10:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go for 70 attack, as much str as possible, mage + range up to you(I suggest 94 mage though) and keep def + prayer on 1 unless your doing desert treasure for ancients(thus 94 mage).</p>
<p>Use whip + dds else mage + range, then dds(use crystal bow or somthing then dds spec). Then again, I’m not a staker so I don’t know how good this will be.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 09:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ry024_sk8ter ry024_sk8ter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ry024_sk8ter">@ry024_sk8ter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>would something like this be worth it or would get killed cuz of defence?<br>
<a href="http://img243.imageshack.us/my.php?image=statusrv6.png" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://img243.imageshack.us/my.php?image=statusrv6.png</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 09:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ry024_sk8ter, post:5, topic:21845”]like a pure staker no skills just combat sumthing that would own and win like 9outa10?<br>
and are we allowed to buy acc’s on here?[/quote]</p>
<p>No selling/buying with the exception of scar scripts.</p>
<p>Anyways, 60/70 attack, 99 str, any mage/range is good if you can use it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 08:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ry024_sk8ter ry024_sk8ter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ry024_sk8ter">@ry024_sk8ter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>like a pure staker no skills just combat sumthing that would own and win like 9outa10?<br>
and are we allowed to buy acc’s on here?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 08:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Depends on stats. I mean I have a 96 main but it sucks at staking.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 08:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ry024_sk8ter ry024_sk8ter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ry024_sk8ter">@ry024_sk8ter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im talking like a lv 80+ staker that would own?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 08:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go for 60 att 60-99 str(higher the better) and use a dds, should be fine for your first few mills.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 07:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question on staker</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ry024_sk8ter ry024_sk8ter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ry024_sk8ter">@ry024_sk8ter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey I’m thinking of buying / making a staker but i literally have no idea where to start could someone send me a guide or tell me the diffrent types of stakers and some helpful guidelines =)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 07:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-21845-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-staker/21845.rss">Question on staker</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
