<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946</link>
    <description>I havent made it.. i got it from desimasalaforum.com 
ENJOY :D
Opening Ports or Adding Allowed Programs with SP2&#39;s Firewall

1.Click on Start / Run
2.Enter in firewall.cpl
3.Click on the Exceptions tab

Adding a Port for Internet Access:
1.Click on the Add Port button
2.Name it whatever you want
3.Enter in the ports you want to open

Adding a Program for Internet Access
1.Click on Add Program... button
2.A list of all installed programs will be displayed
3.Highlight the one you want to include for Internet access
4.Click on the OK button

Autoexec.nt or Config.nt Errors

If you are getting errors similar to:
The system file is not suitable for running MS-DOS and Microsoft Windows applications. Choose &#39;Close&#39; to terminate the application.
Try copying the file from \windows\repair directory to the one that is in the \windows\system32 directory.


Common Control Panel Applets

The follow are some common Control Panel Applets that are located in the \windows\system32 directory.
If you find yourself using any of these frequently, then you can simply make shortcuts to them on your desktop.

appwiz.cpl &gt;&gt;Add/Remove Programs
desk.cpl &gt;&gt; Display Properties
firewall.cpl &gt;&gt; Firewall Settings
inetcpl.cpl &gt;&gt; Internet Options
mmsys.cpl &gt;&gt; Sound and Audio
ncpa.cpl &gt;&gt; Network Connections
nusrmgr.cpl &gt;&gt; User Accounts
powercfg.cpl &gt;&gt; Power Options
sysdm.cpl &gt;&gt;System Properties
wscui.cpl &gt;&gt; Security Center
wuaucpl.cpl &gt;&gt; Automatic Updates Configuration


Windows Explorer Opens Search Companion Rather than the Folder
If the Windows Explorer opens up the Search Companion rather than opening up the actual folder, the default setting for opening a folder is changed.

To correct this:
Start Regedit
Go to HKEY_CLASSES_ROOT \ Directory \ shell
Edit the default value to be explorer or none


Guest Only Network Access

If you try and connect to an XP computer and are shown a logins screen with only the computername/Guest,
You may need to change one of the Local Security Policies:
Got to Control Panel - Administrative Tools
Go to Local Policies - Security Options
Check teh Network access: Sharing and security model for local accounts
Set it to Classic - local users authenticate as themselves


Hiding a XP Computer from Network Neighborhood

If you want to share files from a XP computer,
yet want to remove it from showing up in the Network Neighborhood,
Run net config server /hidden:yes


Easy Way to Share Multiple Folders

If you need to share multiple folders, running the program SHRPUBW.EXE will bring up a simple dialog box to let you:
Browse to the folder you want to share
Enter in a Share name
Ender in a Share description
Set permissions. Several choices are available
Restart the process from within the same program


Not Viewing Zip Files as Folders

If you want to turn of WindowsXP showing Zip files as folders,
just run:
regsvr32 /u zipfldr.dll


Setting Capslock, Numlock, Scroll Lock

If you want to set the startup state for any or all of these keys,
you just need to edit the registry.
Start Regedit
Go to HKEY_CURRENT_USER \ Control Panel \ Keyboard
Open InitialKeyboardIndicators
Change the value to one of the following numbers
0 - All Keys off
1 - Caps Lock on
2 - Num Lock on
4 - Scroll Lock on
For multiple keys, add their values:
3 - Caps Lock and Num Lock on
5 - Caps Lock and Scroll Lock on
6 - Num Lock and Scroll Lock on
7 - Caps Lock, Num Lock, and Scroll Lock on
Log off and back on again


Restoring Desktop Icon to the Quicklaunch Bar

If you mistakenly deleted the icon for the Desktop on the Quicklaunch toolbar
Go to C:\Documents and Settings\user_name\Application Data\Microsoft\Internet Explorer\Quick Launch
(where user_name is replaced by your login name)
Create a Text file called ShowDesktop.SCF with the following contents:
[Shell]
Command=2
IconFile=explorer.exe,3
[Taskbar]
Command=ToggleDesktop


Network Access After Norton Anti-Virus Install

Sometimes you can&#39;t access a WinXP computer after installing Norton Anti-Virus.
There might be a variety of errors at the other computer depending on the operating system.
On the XP computer, in the Event Viewer / System log, there will be the following error:
The server&#39;s configuration parameter &quot;irpstacksize&quot; is too small for the server to use a local device.
Start Regedit
Go to HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Servic es\lanmanserver\parameters
Edit the IRPStackSize
Give it a value of 15
Reboot the computer


Configure for Auto-Logon

If you are the only person using the computer and what to have it automatically log you on,
Start / Run / &quot;control userpasswords2&quot; - no quotes
Uncheck User must enter a user name and password to use this computer
Services You Can Disable
There are quite a few services you can disable from starting automatically.
This would be to speed up your boot time and free resources.
They are only suggestions so I suggestion you read the description of each one when you run Services
and that you turn them off one at a time.
Some possibilities are:
Alerter - Sends alert messages to specified users that are connected to the server computer.
Application Management - Allows software to tap directly into the Add/Remove Programs feature via the Windows Installer technology.
Background Intelligent Transfer Service - The Background Intelligent Transfer service is used by programs (such as Windows AutoUpdate) to download files by using spare bandwidth.
Clipbook - ClipBook permits you to cut and paste text and graphics over the network.
Error Reporting Service - Allows applications to send error reports to Microsoft in the event of an application fault.
Fast User Switching - Windows XP allows users to switch quickly between accounts, without requiring them to log off.
Help and Support - Allows the XP Built-in Help and Support Center to run.
IMAPI CD-Burning COM Service - You don&#39;t need this if you have other software to create CDs.
Indexing Service - Indexes contents and properties of files on local and remote computers; provides rapid access to files through flexible querying language.
IP SEC - Manages IP security policy and starts the ISAKMP/Oakley (IKE) and the IP security driver. If you are not on a domain, you likely don&#39;t need this running.
Messenger - Transmits net send and Alerter service messages between clients and servers. This is how a lot of pop-up windows start appearing on your desktop.
Net Logon - Supports pass-through authentication of account logon events for computers in a domain. If you are not on a domain, you don&#39;t need this running
Network DDE - Provides network transport and security for Dynamic Data Exchange (DDE) for programs running on the same computer or on different computers.
NT LM Security Support Provider - Provides security to remote procedure call (RPC) programs that use transports other than named pipes.
Performance Logs and Alerts - Collects performance data from local or remote computers based on preconfigured schedule parameters, then writes the data to a log or triggers an alert. If you don&#39;t need to monitor your performance logs, then you don&#39;t need this service.
Portable Media Serial Number - Retrieves the serial number of any portable music player connected to your computer
QOS RSVP - Provides network signaling and local traffic control setup functionality for QoS-aware programs and control applets.
Remote Desktop Help Session Manager - Manages and controls Remote Assistance. If you are not using Remote Desktop you don&#39;t need this service.
Remote Registry - Enables remote users to modify registry settings on this computer.
Routing &amp; Remote Access - Offers routing services to businesses in local area and wide area network environments. Allows dial-in access.
Secondary Login - Enables starting processes under alternate credentials. This is what allows you to run an application as another user.
Smart Card - Manages access to smart cards read by this computer.
Smart Card Helper - Enables support for legacy non-plug and play smart-card readers used by this computer.
SSDP Discovery Service - Enables discovery of UPnP devices on your home network.
TCP/IP NetBIOS Helper - Enables support for NetBIOS over TCP/IP (NetBT) service and NetBIOS name resolution. This should not be needed in today&#39;s network environment.
Telnet - Enables a remote user to log on to this computer and run programs, and supports various TCP/IP Telnet clients.
Uninterruptible Power Supply Service - Manages an uninterruptible power supply (UPS) connected to the computer.
Universal Plug and Play Device Host - Provides support to host Universal Plug and Play devices
Upload Manager - Manages synchronous and asynchronous file transfers between clients and servers on the network.
Volume Shadow Copy Service - Manages and implements Volume Shadow Copies used for backup and other purposes.
Web Client - Enables Windows-based programs to create, access, and modify non-local files across the Internet.
Wireless Zero Configuration - Provides automatic configuration for the 802.11 adapters
WMI Performance Adapter - Provides performance library information from WMI HiPerf providers.


Cleaning the Prefetch Directory

WindowsXP has a new feature called Prefetch. This keeps a shortcut to recently used programs.
However it can fill up with old and obsolete programs.
To clean this periodically go to:
Star / Run / Prefetch
Press Ctrl-A to highlight all the shorcuts
Delete them


Not Displaying Logon, Logoff, Startup and Shutdown Status Messages

To turn these off:
Start Regedit
Go to HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows\Curr entVersion\policies\system
If it is not already there, create a DWORD value named DisableStatusMessages
Give it a value of 1


Repair Install

If XP is corrupted to the point where none of the previous solutions get it to boot,
you can do a Repair Install that might work as well as keep the current settings.
Make sure you have your valid WindowsXP key.
The whole process takes about half an hour depending on your computer
If you are being prompted for the administrator&#39;s password, you need to choose the 2nd repair option, not the first.
Insert and boot from your WindowsXP CD
At the second R=Repair option, press the R key
This will start the repair
Press F8 for I Agree at the Licensing Agreement
Press R when the directory where WindowsXP is installed is shown. Typically this is C:\WINDOWS
It will then check the C: drive and start copying files
It will automatically reboot when needed. Keep the CD in the drive.
You will then see the graphic part of the repair that is like during a normal install of XP (Collecting Information, Dynamic Update, Preparing Installation, Installing Windows, Finalizing Installation)
When prompted, click on the Next button
When prompted, enter your XP key
Normally you will want to keep the same Workgroup or Domain name
The computer will reboot
Then you will have the same screens as a normal XP Install
Activate if you want (usually a good idea)
Register if you want (but not necessary)
Finish
At this point you should be able to log in with any existing accounts.


NTOSKRNL Missing or Corrupt

If you get an error that NTOSKRNL not found:
Insert and boot from your WindowsXP CD.
At the first R=Repair option, press the R key
Press the number that corresponds to the correct location for the installation of Windows you want to repair.
Typically this will be #1
Change to the drive that has the CD ROM.
CD i386
expand ntkrnlmp.ex_ C:\Windows\System32\ntoskrnl.exe
If WindowsXP is installed in a different location, just make the necessary change to C:\Windows
Take out the CD ROM and type exit


HAL.DLL Missing or Corrupt

If you get an error regarding a missing or corrupt hal.dll file, it might simply be the BOOT.INI file on the root of the C: drive that is misconfigured
Insert and boot from your WindowsXP CD.
At the first R=Repair option, press the R key
Press the number that corresponds to the correct location for the installation of Windows you want to repair.
Typically this will be #1
Type bootcfg /list to show the current entries in the BOOT.INI file
Type bootcfg /rebuild to repair it
Take out the CD ROM and type exit</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 08:38:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@darkilla darkilla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/darkilla">@darkilla</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>np juss helpin out my homies <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 08:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-95946-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946.rss">WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxchainxx xxchainxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxchainxx">@xxchainxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>very nice guide</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 15:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-95946-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946.rss">WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very interesting…</p>
<p>Thanks for sharing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 04:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-95946-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946.rss">WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@darkilla darkilla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/darkilla">@darkilla</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Corrupted or Missing \WINDOWS\SYSTEM32\CONFIG</p>
<p>If you get the error:<br>
Windows could not start because the following files is missing or corrupt<br>
\WINDOWS\SYSTEM32\CONFIG\SYSTEM or \WINDOWS\SYSTEM32\CONFIG\SOFTWARE<br>
Insert and boot from your WindowsXP CD.<br>
At the first R=Repair option, press the R key<br>
Press the number that corresponds to the correct location for the installation of Windows you want to repair.<br>
Typically this will be <span class="hashtag">#1</span><br>
Enter in the administrator password when requested<br>
cd \windows\system32\config<br>
Depending on which section was corrupted:<br>
ren software software.bad or ren system system.bad<br>
Depending on which section was corrupted<br>
copy \windows\repair\system<br>
copy \windows\repair\software<br>
Take out the CD ROM and type exit</p>
<p>NTLDR or <a href="http://NTDETECT.COM" rel="nofollow noopener">NTDETECT.COM</a> Not Found</p>
<p>If you get an error that NTLDR is not found during bootup,<br>
If you have FAT32 partitions, it is much simpler than with NTFS.<br>
Just boot with a Win98 floppy and copy the NTLDR or <a href="http://NTDETECT.COM" rel="nofollow noopener">NTDETECT.COM</a> files<br>
from the i386 directory to the root of the C:\ drive.<br>
For NTFS:<br>
Insert and boot from your WindowsXP CD.<br>
At the first R=Repair option, press the R key<br>
Press the number that corresponds to the correct location for the installation of Windows you want to repair.<br>
Typically this will be <span class="hashtag">#1</span><br>
Enter in the administrator password when requested<br>
Enter in the following commands (X: is replaced by the actual drive letter that is assigned to the CD ROM drive.<br>
COPY X:\i386\NTLDR C:<br>
COPY X:\i386\<a href="http://NTDETECT.COM" rel="nofollow noopener">NTDETECT.COM</a> C:<br>
Take out the CD ROM and type exit</p>
<p>Bringing Up the Shutdown Dialog Box</p>
<p>Create a new txt file somewhere on your system, open it and put in this one line:<br>
(new ActiveXObject(“Shell.Application”)).ShutdownWindow s();<br>
Save and Close the file. Change the extension to js and your got it.<br>
You can make a shortcut to that file to make it easy to shut down your system.</p>
<p>Hiding the Last User Logged On</p>
<p>If you use the standard NT style of login and want to hide the last user:<br>
Start the Group Policy Editor (gpedit.msc)<br>
Go to Computer Configuration / Windows Settings / Security Settings / Local Policies / Security Options<br>
Scroll down to Interactive logon: Do not display last user name<br>
Set it to Enable</p>
<p>Poweroff at Shutdown</p>
<p>If your computer does not turn off the power when doing a shutdown,<br>
you may need to edit the registry. I have all the correct BIOS and Power settings and still needed to do this.<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Control Panel\Desktop<br>
Edit the key PowerOffActive and give it a value of 1<br>
You can do the same in HKEY_USERS.DEFAULT\Control Panel\Desktop</p>
<p>Remembering Folder Settings</p>
<p>If XP does not remember your folder settings, delete or rename the following registry keys<br>
[HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\Shell NoRoam\BagMRU]<br>
[HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\Shell NoRoam\Bags]</p>
<p>Preventing Applications from Stealing the Focus</p>
<p>To prevent applications from stealing the focus from the window you are working<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_CURRENT_USER \ Control Panel \ Desktop<br>
Edit the key ForegroundLockTimeout<br>
Give it a value of 00030d40</p>
<p>Disable Explorer Thumbnail View</p>
<p>If you want disable the Explorer’s ability to show the Thumbnail View ,<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_CURRENT_USER \ Software \ Microsoft \ Windows \ CurrentVersion \ Explorer \ Advanced <br>
Change ClassicViewState to 1</p>
<p>Disable Shared Documents</p>
<p>To disable the Shared Documents folder that shows up on the network<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_CURRENT_USER \ Software \ Microsoft \ Windows \ CurrentVersion \ Policies \ Explorer <br>
Create a new DWORD Value<br>
Give it the name NoSharedDocuments<br>
Give it a value of 1<br>
Log off or reboot</p>
<p>Removing Thumbs.db Files</p>
<p>When viewing a folder with the Thumbnail view, WindowsXP creates a thumbs.db file.<br>
This is a cache of the current pictures in that directory.<br>
If you want to turn this feature off and save a little disk space<br>
Start the Windows Explorer<br>
Go to Tools / Folder Options / View<br>
In the first section under Files and Folders, check Do not cache thumbnails<br>
Now you can search for the thumbs.db file on your computer and remove them. No more should be created.</p>
<p>Enable / Disable the Task Manager</p>
<p>Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\Curre ntVersion\Policies\System<br>
Create the Dword value DisableTaskMgr<br>
Give it a value of 0 to enable it<br>
Give it a vaule of 1 to disable it</p>
<p>Clearing the Page File on Shutdown</p>
<p>Another way to set the computer to clear the pagefile without directly editing the registry is:<br>
Click on the Start button<br>
Go to the Control Panel<br>
Administrative Tools<br>
Local Security Policy<br>
Local Policies<br>
Click on Security Options<br>
Right hand menu - right click on “Shutdown: Clear Virtual Memory Pagefile”<br>
Select “Enable”<br>
Reboot<br>
If you want to clear the page file on each shutdown:<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Contro l\Session Manager\Memory Management\ClearPageFileAtShutdown<br>
Set the value to 1</p>
<p>No GUI Boot</p>
<p>If you don’t need to see the XP boot logo,<br>
Run MSCONFIG<br>
Click on the BOOT.INI tab<br>
Check the box for /NOGUIBOOT</p>
<p>Using the Classic Search in Explorer</p>
<p>If you prefer to use the classic search style in Explorer,<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\Curre ntVersion\Explorer\CabinetState<br>
Add a String Key called Use Search Asst<br>
Give it a value of no</p>
<p>Changing Drive Letters</p>
<p>If you want to change the letters assigned to your fixed or removable drives:<br>
Right Click on My Computer<br>
Select Manage<br>
Select Disk Management<br>
For a Fixed Disk:<br>
Select it<br>
Right click<br>
Select Change Drive Letter and Path<br>
Click on the Edit button<br>
Enter in the letter you want to use<br>
For a Removable Disk:<br>
In the lower, right hand panel, right click on the Disk or CD ROM #<br>
Select Change Drive Letter and Path<br>
Click on the Edit button<br>
Enter in the letter you want to use</p>
<p>Changing the Registered Owner</p>
<p>Start Regedit<br>
HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows NT\CurrentVersion<br>
From there you can edit the name in the Registered Owner key</p>
<p>Decreasing Boot Time</p>
<p>Microsoft has made available a program to analyze and decrease the time it takes to boot to WindowsXP<br>
The program is called BootVis<br>
Uncompress the file.<br>
Run BOOTVIS.EXE<br>
For a starting point, run Trace / Next Boot + Driver Delays<br>
This will reboot your computer and provide a benchmark<br>
After the reboot, BootVis will take a minute or two to show graphs of your system startup.<br>
Note how much time it takes for your system to load (click on the red vertical line)<br>
Then run Trace / Optimize System<br>
Re-Run the Next Boot + Drive Delays<br>
Note how much the time has decreased<br>
Mine went from approximately 39 to 30 seconds.</p>
<p>Hide/Unhide Logon Names</p>
<p>If you want to hide or unhide the names of users that are displayed on the initial logon screen:<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE \ SOFTWARE \ Microsoft \ Windows NT \ CurrentVersion \ Winlogon \ SpecialAccounts \ UserList<br>
Add a DWORD with the name of the user account you want to hide<br>
Make sure it has a value of 0<br>
If there is an existing account, you can unhide it by giving it a value of 1</p>
<p>WindowsXP Command Line Utilities</p>
<p>While there are a lot of command line utilities in WindowsXP, here are some that I have been using lately.<br>
bootcfg - Configures, queries, or changes Boot.ini file settings.<br>
driverquery - Displays a list of all installed device drivers and their properties.<br>
getmac - Returns the media access control (MAC) address and list of network protocols associated with each address for all network cards in each computer<br>
gpresult - Displays Group Policy settings and Resultant Set of Policy (RSOP) for a user or a computer<br>
netsh - You can use commands in the Netsh Interface IP context to configure the TCP/IP protocol<br>
schtasks - Schedules commands and programs to run periodically or at a specific time<br>
systeminfo - Displays detailed configuration information about a computer and its operating system</p>
<p>Disabling Hibernation</p>
<p>If you don’t want to use up the disk space taken by Hibernation, or don’t need to use it at all,<br>
you can easily disable it.<br>
Open up the Control Panel / Power Options icon<br>
Click on the Hibernation icon<br>
Uncheck Enable Hibernation</p>
<p>Increasing System Performance</p>
<p>If you have 512 megs or more of memory, you can increase system performance<br>
by having the core system kept in memory.<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Contro l\Session Manager\Memory Management\DisablePagingExecutive<br>
Set the value to be 1<br>
Reboot the computer</p>
<p>Common Command Console Utilities</p>
<p>WindowsXP comes with quite a few console utilities you can easily run from the command line:<br>
Computer Management - compmgmt.msc<br>
Disk Managment - diskmgmt.msc<br>
Device Manager - devmgmt.msc<br>
Disk Defrag - dfrg.msc<br>
Event Viewer - eventvwr.msc<br>
Shared Folders - fsmgmt.msc<br>
Group Policies - gpedit.msc<br>
Local Users and Groups - lusrmgr.msc<br>
Performance Monitor - perfmon.msc<br>
Resultant Set of Policies - rsop.msc<br>
Local Security Settings - secpol.msc<br>
Services - services.msc<br>
Component Services - comexp.msc</p>
<p>Automatically Ending Non-Responsive Tasks</p>
<p>Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Control Panel\Desktop\AutoEndTasks<br>
Set the value to be 1<br>
In the same section, change the WaitToKillAppTimeout to the number of milliseconds you want.</p>
<p>Changing Programs That Start Automatically</p>
<p>WindowsXP has a similar program, MSCONFIG, that was available in Windows98.<br>
This allows you to view and change what programs are automatically started each time you log in.<br>
The new version also allows you to view and edit the boot.ini file (as well as check for errors and use several advanced switches)</p>
<p>Creating an Automated Install of WindowsXP</p>
<p>On the WindowsXP CP, in the SUPPORT\TOOLS directory,<br>
there is a file called DEPLOY.CAB.<br>
Extract the programs DEPLOY.CHM (help file) and SETUPMGR.EXE (main program)<br>
Run SETUPMGR and answer the prompts.<br>
This will create both a unattend.bat and unattend.txt file you can use for automated installs.<br>
Note: The batch file might need some minor modification for file locations but it is fairly basic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 01:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-95946-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946.rss">WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@darkilla darkilla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/darkilla">@darkilla</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I havent made it… i got it from <a href="http://desimasalaforum.com" rel="nofollow noopener">desimasalaforum.com</a><br>
ENJOY <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
Opening Ports or Adding Allowed Programs with SP2’s Firewall</p>
<p>1.Click on Start / Run<br>
2.Enter in firewall.cpl<br>
3.Click on the Exceptions tab</p>
<p>Adding a Port for Internet Access:<br>
1.Click on the Add Port button<br>
2.Name it whatever you want<br>
3.Enter in the ports you want to open</p>
<p>Adding a Program for Internet Access<br>
1.Click on Add Program… button<br>
2.A list of all installed programs will be displayed<br>
3.Highlight the one you want to include for Internet access<br>
4.Click on the OK button</p>
<p>Autoexec.nt or Config.nt Errors</p>
<p>If you are getting errors similar to:<br>
The system file is not suitable for running MS-DOS and Microsoft Windows applications. Choose ‘Close’ to terminate the application.<br>
Try copying the file from \windows\repair directory to the one that is in the \windows\system32 directory.</p>
<p>Common Control Panel Applets</p>
<p>The follow are some common Control Panel Applets that are located in the \windows\system32 directory.<br>
If you find yourself using any of these frequently, then you can simply make shortcuts to them on your desktop.</p>
<p>appwiz.cpl &gt;&gt;Add/Remove Programs<br>
desk.cpl &gt;&gt; Display Properties<br>
firewall.cpl &gt;&gt; Firewall Settings<br>
inetcpl.cpl &gt;&gt; Internet Options<br>
mmsys.cpl &gt;&gt; Sound and Audio<br>
ncpa.cpl &gt;&gt; Network Connections<br>
nusrmgr.cpl &gt;&gt; User Accounts<br>
powercfg.cpl &gt;&gt; Power Options<br>
sysdm.cpl &gt;&gt;System Properties<br>
wscui.cpl &gt;&gt; Security Center<br>
wuaucpl.cpl &gt;&gt; Automatic Updates Configuration</p>
<p>Windows Explorer Opens Search Companion Rather than the Folder<br>
If the Windows Explorer opens up the Search Companion rather than opening up the actual folder, the default setting for opening a folder is changed.</p>
<p>To correct this:<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_CLASSES_ROOT \ Directory \ shell<br>
Edit the default value to be explorer or none</p>
<p>Guest Only Network Access</p>
<p>If you try and connect to an XP computer and are shown a logins screen with only the computername/Guest,<br>
You may need to change one of the Local Security Policies:<br>
Got to Control Panel - Administrative Tools<br>
Go to Local Policies - Security Options<br>
Check teh Network access: Sharing and security model for local accounts<br>
Set it to Classic - local users authenticate as themselves</p>
<p>Hiding a XP Computer from Network Neighborhood</p>
<p>If you want to share files from a XP computer,<br>
yet want to remove it from showing up in the Network Neighborhood,<br>
Run net config server /hidden:yes</p>
<p>Easy Way to Share Multiple Folders</p>
<p>If you need to share multiple folders, running the program SHRPUBW.EXE will bring up a simple dialog box to let you:<br>
Browse to the folder you want to share<br>
Enter in a Share name<br>
Ender in a Share description<br>
Set permissions. Several choices are available<br>
Restart the process from within the same program</p>
<p>Not Viewing Zip Files as Folders</p>
<p>If you want to turn of WindowsXP showing Zip files as folders,<br>
just run:<br>
regsvr32 /u zipfldr.dll</p>
<p>Setting Capslock, Numlock, Scroll Lock</p>
<p>If you want to set the startup state for any or all of these keys,<br>
you just need to edit the registry.<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_CURRENT_USER \ Control Panel \ Keyboard<br>
Open InitialKeyboardIndicators<br>
Change the value to one of the following numbers<br>
0 - All Keys off<br>
1 - Caps Lock on<br>
2 - Num Lock on<br>
4 - Scroll Lock on<br>
For multiple keys, add their values:<br>
3 - Caps Lock and Num Lock on<br>
5 - Caps Lock and Scroll Lock on<br>
6 - Num Lock and Scroll Lock on<br>
7 - Caps Lock, Num Lock, and Scroll Lock on<br>
Log off and back on again</p>
<p>Restoring Desktop Icon to the Quicklaunch Bar</p>
<p>If you mistakenly deleted the icon for the Desktop on the Quicklaunch toolbar<br>
Go to C:\Documents and Settings\user_name\Application Data\Microsoft\Internet Explorer\Quick Launch<br>
(where user_name is replaced by your login name)<br>
Create a Text file called ShowDesktop.SCF with the following contents:<br>
[Shell]<br>
Command=2<br>
IconFile=explorer.exe,3<br>
[Taskbar]<br>
Command=ToggleDesktop</p>
<p>Network Access After Norton Anti-Virus Install</p>
<p>Sometimes you can’t access a WinXP computer after installing Norton Anti-Virus.<br>
There might be a variety of errors at the other computer depending on the operating system.<br>
On the XP computer, in the Event Viewer / System log, there will be the following error:<br>
The server’s configuration parameter “irpstacksize” is too small for the server to use a local device.<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Servic es\lanmanserver\parameters<br>
Edit the IRPStackSize<br>
Give it a value of 15<br>
Reboot the computer</p>
<p>Configure for Auto-Logon</p>
<p>If you are the only person using the computer and what to have it automatically log you on,<br>
Start / Run / “control userpasswords2” - no quotes<br>
Uncheck User must enter a user name and password to use this computer<br>
Services You Can Disable<br>
There are quite a few services you can disable from starting automatically.<br>
This would be to speed up your boot time and free resources.<br>
They are only suggestions so I suggestion you read the description of each one when you run Services<br>
and that you turn them off one at a time.<br>
Some possibilities are:<br>
Alerter - Sends alert messages to specified users that are connected to the server computer.<br>
Application Management - Allows software to tap directly into the Add/Remove Programs feature via the Windows Installer technology.<br>
Background Intelligent Transfer Service - The Background Intelligent Transfer service is used by programs (such as Windows AutoUpdate) to download files by using spare bandwidth.<br>
Clipbook - ClipBook permits you to cut and paste text and graphics over the network.<br>
Error Reporting Service - Allows applications to send error reports to Microsoft in the event of an application fault.<br>
Fast User Switching - Windows XP allows users to switch quickly between accounts, without requiring them to log off.<br>
Help and Support - Allows the XP Built-in Help and Support Center to run.<br>
IMAPI CD-Burning COM Service - You don’t need this if you have other software to create CDs.<br>
Indexing Service - Indexes contents and properties of files on local and remote computers; provides rapid access to files through flexible querying language.<br>
IP SEC - Manages IP security policy and starts the ISAKMP/Oakley (IKE) and the IP security driver. If you are not on a domain, you likely don’t need this running.<br>
Messenger - Transmits net send and Alerter service messages between clients and servers. This is how a lot of pop-up windows start appearing on your desktop.<br>
Net Logon - Supports pass-through authentication of account logon events for computers in a domain. If you are not on a domain, you don’t need this running<br>
Network DDE - Provides network transport and security for Dynamic Data Exchange (DDE) for programs running on the same computer or on different computers.<br>
NT LM Security Support Provider - Provides security to remote procedure call (RPC) programs that use transports other than named pipes.<br>
Performance Logs and Alerts - Collects performance data from local or remote computers based on preconfigured schedule parameters, then writes the data to a log or triggers an alert. If you don’t need to monitor your performance logs, then you don’t need this service.<br>
Portable Media Serial Number - Retrieves the serial number of any portable music player connected to your computer<br>
QOS RSVP - Provides network signaling and local traffic control setup functionality for QoS-aware programs and control applets.<br>
Remote Desktop Help Session Manager - Manages and controls Remote Assistance. If you are not using Remote Desktop you don’t need this service.<br>
Remote Registry - Enables remote users to modify registry settings on this computer.<br>
Routing &amp; Remote Access - Offers routing services to businesses in local area and wide area network environments. Allows dial-in access.<br>
Secondary Login - Enables starting processes under alternate credentials. This is what allows you to run an application as another user.<br>
Smart Card - Manages access to smart cards read by this computer.<br>
Smart Card Helper - Enables support for legacy non-plug and play smart-card readers used by this computer.<br>
SSDP Discovery Service - Enables discovery of UPnP devices on your home network.<br>
TCP/IP NetBIOS Helper - Enables support for NetBIOS over TCP/IP (NetBT) service and NetBIOS name resolution. This should not be needed in today’s network environment.<br>
Telnet - Enables a remote user to log on to this computer and run programs, and supports various TCP/IP Telnet clients.<br>
Uninterruptible Power Supply Service - Manages an uninterruptible power supply (UPS) connected to the computer.<br>
Universal Plug and Play Device Host - Provides support to host Universal Plug and Play devices<br>
Upload Manager - Manages synchronous and asynchronous file transfers between clients and servers on the network.<br>
Volume Shadow Copy Service - Manages and implements Volume Shadow Copies used for backup and other purposes.<br>
Web Client - Enables Windows-based programs to create, access, and modify non-local files across the Internet.<br>
Wireless Zero Configuration - Provides automatic configuration for the 802.11 adapters<br>
WMI Performance Adapter - Provides performance library information from WMI HiPerf providers.</p>
<p>Cleaning the Prefetch Directory</p>
<p>WindowsXP has a new feature called Prefetch. This keeps a shortcut to recently used programs.<br>
However it can fill up with old and obsolete programs.<br>
To clean this periodically go to:<br>
Star / Run / Prefetch<br>
Press Ctrl-A to highlight all the shorcuts<br>
Delete them</p>
<p>Not Displaying Logon, Logoff, Startup and Shutdown Status Messages</p>
<p>To turn these off:<br>
Start Regedit<br>
Go to HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows\Curr entVersion\policies\system<br>
If it is not already there, create a DWORD value named DisableStatusMessages<br>
Give it a value of 1</p>
<p>Repair Install</p>
<p>If XP is corrupted to the point where none of the previous solutions get it to boot,<br>
you can do a Repair Install that might work as well as keep the current settings.<br>
Make sure you have your valid WindowsXP key.<br>
The whole process takes about half an hour depending on your computer<br>
If you are being prompted for the administrator’s password, you need to choose the 2nd repair option, not the first.<br>
Insert and boot from your WindowsXP CD<br>
At the second R=Repair option, press the R key<br>
This will start the repair<br>
Press F8 for I Agree at the Licensing Agreement<br>
Press R when the directory where WindowsXP is installed is shown. Typically this is C:\WINDOWS<br>
It will then check the C: drive and start copying files<br>
It will automatically reboot when needed. Keep the CD in the drive.<br>
You will then see the graphic part of the repair that is like during a normal install of XP (Collecting Information, Dynamic Update, Preparing Installation, Installing Windows, Finalizing Installation)<br>
When prompted, click on the Next button<br>
When prompted, enter your XP key<br>
Normally you will want to keep the same Workgroup or Domain name<br>
The computer will reboot<br>
Then you will have the same screens as a normal XP Install<br>
Activate if you want (usually a good idea)<br>
Register if you want (but not necessary)<br>
Finish<br>
At this point you should be able to log in with any existing accounts.</p>
<p>NTOSKRNL Missing or Corrupt</p>
<p>If you get an error that NTOSKRNL not found:<br>
Insert and boot from your WindowsXP CD.<br>
At the first R=Repair option, press the R key<br>
Press the number that corresponds to the correct location for the installation of Windows you want to repair.<br>
Typically this will be <span class="hashtag">#1</span><br>
Change to the drive that has the CD ROM.<br>
CD i386<br>
expand ntkrnlmp.ex_ C:\Windows\System32\ntoskrnl.exe<br>
If WindowsXP is installed in a different location, just make the necessary change to C:\Windows<br>
Take out the CD ROM and type exit</p>
<p>HAL.DLL Missing or Corrupt</p>
<p>If you get an error regarding a missing or corrupt hal.dll file, it might simply be the BOOT.INI file on the root of the C: drive that is misconfigured<br>
Insert and boot from your WindowsXP CD.<br>
At the first R=Repair option, press the R key<br>
Press the number that corresponds to the correct location for the installation of Windows you want to repair.<br>
Typically this will be <span class="hashtag">#1</span><br>
Type bootcfg /list to show the current entries in the BOOT.INI file<br>
Type bootcfg /rebuild to repair it<br>
Take out the CD ROM and type exit</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 01:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-95946-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winxp-tips-and-tricks-users-quick-reference/95946.rss">WinXP Tips and Tricks [ Users Quick Reference ]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
