<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] CloudScape</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-cloudscape/444491</link>
    <description>ONLINE!!! Cloudscape is online!!! 24/7 Webclient enabled!!! http://www.cloudscape.co.cc/playnow.html

Need co-owner that can code java.

Need staff.

I&#39;m working on a new server named CloudScape. It&#39;s going to be a really big long-term project. The base is [PI] RuneFX v1.

The website looks very nice and professional. When I&#39;m done coding it, it will feature a webclient, forums, snapshots, gameplay videos, chatroom, etc.

The game will feature everything from the RuneFX v1 base(525 graphics, all specs, corp, tormented beasts, full godwars, JAD, chaos elemental, warriors guild, etc.) and many other features that I plan on adding. So far I plan on improving the economy more, fixing most of the bugs, making a market area, changing up the starter, making the server seem even more professional to attract more players, if needed I will make the server more stable, look for cheats/dupes to fix, clean up the cache A LOT to reduce the cache file size, and much much more.

Right now what I need is another 1-2 coders but I&#39;m not going to go far into detail about that; I think that&#39;s only for the Development Teams thread.

The release date is sometime this month if everything goes well.

The main thing I have to wait on right now is getting cable internet. I think I&#39;m getting it this Wednesday. It will be 10mb/s download. The computer I am going to be hosting it from is around 4gb ram, and over 300GB HDD, I&#39;m not sure about the other specs.

Thanks for reading my post. If you have any advice about my future server just leave a comment. By advice, I don&#39;t mean advising a new base. Also, if you have ever used RuneFX v1 for a base, I&#39;d like to know anything I need to know about it, like any existing bugs/cheats/dupes, and whatever else.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 18:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-cloudscape/444491.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] CloudScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t think you understand what this section is for. It’s not an advertisement section.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-cloudscape/444491/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-cloudscape/444491/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 18:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444491-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-cloudscape/444491.rss">[PI] CloudScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] CloudScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ONLINE!!! Cloudscape is online!!! 24/7 Webclient enabled!!! <a href="http://www.cloudscape.co.cc/playnow.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.cloudscape.co.cc/playnow.html</a></p>
<p>Need co-owner that can code java.</p>
<p>Need staff.</p>
<p>I’m working on a new server named CloudScape. It’s going to be a really big long-term project. The base is [PI] RuneFX v1.</p>
<p>The website looks very nice and professional. When I’m done coding it, it will feature a webclient, forums, snapshots, gameplay videos, chatroom, etc.</p>
<p>The game will feature everything from the RuneFX v1 base(525 graphics, all specs, corp, tormented beasts, full godwars, JAD, chaos elemental, warriors guild, etc.) and many other features that I plan on adding. So far I plan on improving the economy more, fixing most of the bugs, making a market area, changing up the starter, making the server seem even more professional to attract more players, if needed I will make the server more stable, look for cheats/dupes to fix, clean up the cache A LOT to reduce the cache file size, and much much more.</p>
<p>Right now what I need is another 1-2 coders but I’m not going to go far into detail about that; I think that’s only for the Development Teams thread.</p>
<p>The release date is sometime this month if everything goes well.</p>
<p>The main thing I have to wait on right now is getting cable internet. I think I’m getting it this Wednesday. It will be 10mb/s download. The computer I am going to be hosting it from is around 4gb ram, and over 300GB HDD, I’m not sure about the other specs.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading my post. If you have any advice about my future server just leave a comment. By advice, I don’t mean advising a new base. Also, if you have ever used RuneFX v1 for a base, I’d like to know anything I need to know about it, like any existing bugs/cheats/dupes, and whatever else.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-cloudscape/444491/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-cloudscape/444491/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 18:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444491-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-cloudscape/444491.rss">[PI] CloudScape</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
