<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>You are all stupid seriously</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701</link>
    <description>What the fuck is your problem guys? All you do is fucking fight... You think you&#39;re cool because you can get away with being racist and making fun of other users... You get in fights over someone&#39;s critique... Stfu. There&#39;s no need for it... This is Graphics... Not Fight Club. If you wanna fight go elsewhere... Some people want critiques, Not spam and fights in there topic... I know getting along with people can be tough, But be the bigger man and stay the fuck out of shit that doesn&#39;t involve you, If you don&#39;t like a critique, Kindly say you disagree and get on with your life... You think you&#39;re all cool and shit? This is Mopar ffs... You&#39;re not cool... you&#39;re just like everyone else... considering most of you heard of this place from someone on MOPARSCAPE, you shouldn&#39;t make fun of the users who are originally from Mopar... So what it&#39;s private servers... Oh no. You probably play the original version of the game, Runescape... And you think you&#39;re cool? Okay... lol... Here&#39;s a tip; Shut up and stop fighting...
[center][img]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnwarn.gif[/img] Next time you have a problem with someone, take it to the staff.
Oh, and learn to use the enter button. It&#39;s not there for nothing.[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 22:36:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>You are all stupid seriously</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tico135 Tico]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tico135">@Tico135</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You aren’t much better posting this, are you?  You have quite obviously been flamed, so you are taking your anger out on <span class="bbcode-i">everyone</span> for no reason.  I think you need a reality check bud.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 22:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236701-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701.rss">You are all stupid seriously</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are all stupid seriously</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>How many …'s do you want?</p>
<p>Can’t be bothered to read it btw. YOU SUCK.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 22:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236701-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701.rss">You are all stupid seriously</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are all stupid seriously</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GMAN7 GMAN7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gman7">@GMAN7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What the fuck is your problem guys? All you do is fucking fight… You think you’re cool because you can get away with being racist and making fun of other users… You get in fights over someone’s critique… Stfu. There’s no need for it… This is Graphics… Not Fight Club. If you wanna fight go elsewhere… Some people want critiques, Not spam and fights in there topic… I know getting along with people can be tough, But be the bigger man and stay the fuck out of shit that doesn’t involve you, If you don’t like a critique, Kindly say you disagree and get on with your life… You think you’re all cool and shit? This is Mopar ffs… You’re not cool… you’re just like everyone else… considering most of you heard of this place from someone on MOPARSCAPE, you shouldn’t make fun of the users who are originally from Mopar… So what it’s private servers… Oh no. You probably play the original version of the game, Runescape… And you think you’re cool? Okay… lol… Here’s a tip; Shut up and stop fighting…<br>
[center]<img src="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnwarn.gif" alt width="" height=""> Next time you have a problem with someone, take it to the staff.<br>
Oh, and learn to use the enter button. It’s not there for nothing.[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 22:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236701-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-all-stupid-seriously/236701.rss">You are all stupid seriously</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
