<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Shops for a PVP server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shops-for-a-pvp-server/453058</link>
    <description>Hello my fellow Moparscapians! How are you all doing? Good!

So im working on a PVP server and i noticed, what you add in shops has a huge impact on the players you pull in. Im new to PVP server&#39;s, this is my first attempt. As i gave up on Eco servers(Because players are too lazy to do shit, or most likely because of my eco) i got the idea to start a PVP server, so i did!

I basically need huge help on my shops. What would you add? No spawning, thats just bullshit. 

Please throw in you&#39;re opinions, im pretty open minded. If you have no good information to provide, then shut the fuck up and don&#39;t post you&#39;re unnecessary kidshit.

One other question, what was/is YOUR favorite PVP server? 

Thanks guys. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 09:01:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shops-for-a-pvp-server/453058.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Shops for a PVP server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Grey_Cabbage Grey Cabbage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/grey_cabbage">@Grey_Cabbage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d say having the variety to be able to wear almost any equippable item is pretty awesome, as long as the items are statistically/situationally balanced. i.e. add every equippable item that isn’t a partyhat, separated into stores based on iconic NPCs like horvik or bob.</p>
<p>Sometimes I get the feeling of a black hole in my stomach when I go to the obby store and there’s no toktz kil ak which I 102% need for my 60 attack account, so try to avoid that.</p>
<ol>
<li>Items such as longbows, chainbodies and med helms are usually useless and often excluded, so never hesitate to do some configuration/exemel surgery:</li>
</ol>
<p>Some possibilities.cfg:<br>
-Make full helms have harsher negative ranged attack, meaning that tank rangers will prefer wearing med helms instead.<br>
-Buff chainbodies’ crush defense, or even give them a slight ranged attack bonus<br>
-Make longbows more accurate than shortbows<br>
-Give different items cool/ridic bonuses, e.g. wearing a gas mask makes you immune to poison<br>
-Make black dragonhide incredibly expensive to deter raggers, or alternatively make crossbows two handed<br>
-Top tier food like manta rays or saradomin brews should be super expensive<br>
-Don’t add teletabs</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>Also, item requirements are very important because they also keep lower tier items useful, e.g. forgetting to slap a 35 def and 40 attack requirement on barrows gloves will mean that everything under will be useless. Pures and mains are mutual in their interest to kill people on private servers, and having more and more types of accounts keeps the tomatoes in the fridge.<br>
“My stats? Oh yeah, I’m a 15 defence fremennik helm pure with skeletal armor and rune gloves, wearing this helmet gives me +5% damage when using crush attacks.”<br>
“Nice, I got 25 defence so I can wear white castlewars armor which gives a +12 stab attack bonus.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A fair share of items obtained from PvP rather than just coins will keep some items more valuable than others. I personally don’t like the stealing from stall action that exists in billions of private servers, because it feels like slavery and only encourages ghostmouse autobots.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>-One possible way to make making money fun could be to have a special chest in Edgeville or something, that fills up with GP whenever you deal damage, take damage, spend time in the wilderness or get multiple kills in a row, to keep the game competitive.</p>
<p>I usually look for replayability, variety, and no korasi’s swords. Hope this helps a bit, and gl</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shops-for-a-pvp-server/453058/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shops-for-a-pvp-server/453058/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 09:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453058-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shops-for-a-pvp-server/453058.rss">Shops for a PVP server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Shops for a PVP server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@best_shit_out best shit out]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/best_shit_out">@best_shit_out</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello my fellow Moparscapians! How are you all doing? Good!</p>
<p>So im working on a PVP server and i noticed, what you add in shops has a huge impact on the players you pull in. Im new to PVP server’s, this is my first attempt. As i gave up on Eco servers(Because players are too lazy to do shit, or most likely because of my eco) i got the idea to start a PVP server, so i did!</p>
<p>I basically need huge help on my shops. What would you add? No spawning, thats just bullshit.</p>
<p>Please throw in you’re opinions, im pretty open minded. If you have no good information to provide, then shut the fuck up and don’t post you’re unnecessary kidshit.</p>
<p>One other question, what was/is YOUR favorite PVP server?</p>
<p>Thanks guys. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shops-for-a-pvp-server/453058/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shops-for-a-pvp-server/453058/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 07:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453058-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shops-for-a-pvp-server/453058.rss">Shops for a PVP server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
