<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Standalone Game Engine</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822</link>
    <description>Hello, I was just wondering if it was possible for there to be a &quot;Standalone&quot; Game engine, that provides no method of gameplay, but simply allows you to &quot;test&quot; things in real time. So basically something that simulates server - client communications. HEre let me provide a better description of what I want to do.

I want to make an interface tester, among other things. Not to create new interfaces, but to &quot;explore&quot; the current interfaces. Like a server editor, but built into the client.

It&#39;s not very easy for me to explain, but the idea is clear in my mind. I guess I want to make a visual server editor. So like make a visual shop editor, that does not rely on pictures of all the different items and shop screen, but use jage&#39;x own game engine to displaythe interface screen, and then add the items to it in real time.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 22:05:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Standalone Game Engine</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No, like completely remove all gameplay functions. Just have cache functions. So like, I won’t be able to walk around, or player rendering or anything like that, but I’ll be able to open interfaces, send frames, stuff like that.</p>
<p>An example would be opening different interfaces, and testing how each works, like the shops interface, bank interface, stuff like that, without actualy playing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 22:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-303822-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822.rss">Standalone Game Engine</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Standalone Game Engine</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Runes_Are_Cool Runes Are Cool?]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runes_are_cool">@Runes_Are_Cool</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just use the same source on a different port if that’s what you mean?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 20:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-303822-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822.rss">Standalone Game Engine</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Standalone Game Engine</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I was just wondering if it was possible for there to be a “Standalone” Game engine, that provides no method of gameplay, but simply allows you to “test” things in real time. So basically something that simulates server - client communications. HEre let me provide a better description of what I want to do.</p>
<p>I want to make an interface tester, among other things. Not to create new interfaces, but to “explore” the current interfaces. Like a server editor, but built into the client.</p>
<p>It’s not very easy for me to explain, but the idea is clear in my mind. I guess I want to make a visual server editor. So like make a visual shop editor, that does not rely on pictures of all the different items and shop screen, but use jage’x own game engine to displaythe interface screen, and then add the items to it in real time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 03:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-303822-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standalone-game-engine/303822.rss">Standalone Game Engine</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
