<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help header send post data</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148</link>
    <description>no cURL&#39;s please, I need help with sending header data to a site that requires post variables.

The funny thing is, my script that did it was working in school... But when I brought it home, it doesnt...I think at home it may be sending it as get instead of post... Not sure though.

The real question, would the preferences of browser alter header data, or routers alter it, etc?
The code tries to take all colleges from collegeboard, enters them, their locs, and their collegids into db... Like I mentioned above, it works in the school comp, so I doubt its a syntax error... Id rather not release the code, because I dont want too many connections going to collegeboard...

any help will be appreciated. 
I used an array for the content and then used http_build_query(); to config the array into the parsing text for content for the header.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 03:54:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help header send post data</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Night26 Night26]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/night26">@Night26</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thats true, but you can still fopen the page and dispay its contents (the one with the post data)</p>
<p>Like I said, it works at school, but the same code doesnt work at home, does anyone know enough about routers, that might be masking the info to servers? dunno</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 03:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88148-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148.rss">Help header send post data</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help header send post data</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@S_ms S!ms]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/s_ms">@S_ms</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is what i found…</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I am in a situation where I need to redirect a user to another page but also<br>
send HTTP POST variables to that page using PHP (I’m assuming using the<br>
header() function).  I’m sure somebody out there knows how to do this.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>[i]I don’t think you can redirect to another page AND post to that page. You<br>
can, of course, stuff the information into the URL - but that maybe not be<br>
workable with the data you want to send. (Plus you’ll need to URL encode<br>
all the data.)</p>
<p>It’s because the browser is the one dealing with the new page. You (the<br>
server) says go “here” and the browser goes and gets that page. But posting<br>
to that page at the same time, is not part of the communication because all<br>
you have time to tell the browser is go “here”. The browser will ignore the<br>
rest.</p>
<p>One option maybe to post to the page “server to server” and deal with<br>
accordingly. Another option would be to save the information to a session<br>
object and then redirect. The target page can look for the session object<br>
and work on the data then.</p>
<p>(If I’m wrong some here will correct me. ;-)[/i]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 22:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88148-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148.rss">Help header send post data</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help header send post data</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Night26 Night26]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/night26">@Night26</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>no cURL’s please, I need help with sending header data to a site that requires post variables.</p>
<p>The funny thing is, my script that did it was working in school… But when I brought it home, it doesnt…I think at home it may be sending it as get instead of post… Not sure though.</p>
<p>The real question, would the preferences of browser alter header data, or routers alter it, etc?<br>
The code tries to take all colleges from collegeboard, enters them, their locs, and their collegids into db… Like I mentioned above, it works in the school comp, so I doubt its a syntax error… Id rather not release the code, because I dont want too many connections going to collegeboard…</p>
<p>any help will be appreciated.<br>
I used an array for the content and then used http_build_query(); to config the array into the parsing text for content for the header.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 05:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-88148-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-header-send-post-data/88148.rss">Help header send post data</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
