<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Runescape</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104</link>
    <description>Why has the player base for [i]317[/i] right up to [i]508[/i] dropped so much? 

[i]I remember a couple of years ago i had no problem getting 50 players if not more from little advertisement from Moparscape and other various sites, and without spending a cent. Nowadays you need like 300+ to even gain a decent player base buying sponsor&#39;s etc, this is really sad because it seems like everyone s just now greedy for the cash  :confused: I mean look how much soul spilit pays R-L for there sponsored spot, a few thousands of dollars and a written contract not liking this, i wonder how long 317 to 508 private servers will last now  :|[/i]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 17:59:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The sponsored servers make it harder to get players. But it’s still anyones game because if your server was truly awesome and appealed to the masses, word of mouth would get you players and maybe more than anyone else.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 17:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465104-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104.rss">Runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s due to the fact that no-one goes through trial and error. While remakes are and now always will be big; there’s so much more to offer for regular servers.</p>
<p>Many people asked me how I ran my server(s) and got so many players when all I done was leech a source and add in a few tutorials. The only tips I can give to anyone is focus more on the management and running of the server, forget about content for the minute; content can come at a later date. Work on keeping the server lagg-free with no random shutdowns or anything like that, including ddosing; get a ddos protected host. Then move on to your staff team and optimise that to be nothing but the best. People seem to have issues with people who own servers and have a tonne of moderators, I think it’s fine. For a 100 player server I had 10 mods from different timezones so that there would always be at least one mod on. I never even branched into administrators for quite some time just due to the fact that moderators were doing the job perfectly.</p>
<p>Once you have this then you can start working on content but never forget what you started with; keep the smooth and clean run server no matter what and players will build up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 09:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465104-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104.rss">Runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>While I’m sure there are many reasons people can pinpoint I would have to put it down to how the nature of advertising has changed, take Mopar for example, where in the past the potential traffic was spread out over equally placed servers. Now we have an environment where a lot of the traffic is going to the sponsored spots, which makes the non-sponsored servers fight it out even harder for traffic.</p>
<p>I believe the traffic is still there, I just think the nature of the SSP has changed quite a bit from what it used to be. It is a little unreasonable, especially on Mopar where the sponsored spots can cost so much meaning a lot of server can’t get a shot at having one * at all * and even if they could due to the bidding process the price of the spot would probably go up.</p>
<p>There have been calls to reduce the amount of spots, or even ideas such as introducing a silver server type purchase whereby the servers on the non-sponsored list get some form of notable indentation from the rest (Which could be sold at a lower static price, to show the more serious servers). I don’t really have a decided opinion on such an implementation, though.</p>
<p>I hold the opinion that these so call sponsored servers should be dropped back to the same list that every other server is in, except they have a golden box rather than the traditional whitey grey one. They can then be on the same playing field, and be expected to deliver good uptime and such rather than just sitting at the top of the page by default.</p>
<p>Alternately to the above, I could just hop on the bandwagon, and say the page is dying. Though there isn’t much fun in doing that. Though for the record I do think getting your server popular is still more than possible without large sums of money, it is just less burst traffic now than it used to be, so requires more establishment and reputation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 05:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465104-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104.rss">Runescape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Runescape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@loved loved]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loved">@loved</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why has the player base for <span class="bbcode-i">317</span> right up to <span class="bbcode-i">508</span> dropped so much?</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i">I remember a couple of years ago i had no problem getting 50 players if not more from little advertisement from Moparscape and other various sites, and without spending a cent. Nowadays you need like 300+ to even gain a decent player base buying sponsor’s etc, this is really sad because it seems like everyone s just now greedy for the cash  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> I mean look how much soul spilit pays R-L for there sponsored spot, a few thousands of dollars and a written contract not liking this, i wonder how long 317 to 508 private servers will last now  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 05:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465104-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape/465104.rss">Runescape</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
