<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Private Servers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers/458616</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been lurking in the shadows for some time now, took a fair amount of time off of the scene simply because of my full time work and personal schedule but none the less I keep looking around every now and then. I remember not the longest time ago there were constant changes to the RSPS scene in a way; different bases All-star Scape/Czar/Hyperion all that stuff in general.

Now it&#39;s gone? I mean as in the projects look the exact same - Delta is still thriving as a platform for a server to hold potentially hundreds of people from many different places in the work (can say the same for Project Insanity) but I understand from a learners prospective to learn from something simple/easy. But if this is the case why are people showing off the amount of players their PI/Delta servers can hold? As if there unique spawn pvp server is going to hit this amount anyway.

Maybe I&#39;m confusing you by attacking two points at once; just sad to see the progression lost and people learn from bad examples.. I don&#39;t know just having a dig I suppose. Your thoughts?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 02:55:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers/458616.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Private Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would say that private server’s have advanced far more than ever in the past 3 years. We know almost everything about the 317 client, just some of the work posted here isn’t impressive but there are people who are advancing fast.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers/458616/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers/458616/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 02:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458616-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers/458616.rss">Private Servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WW1 WW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ww1">@WW1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been lurking in the shadows for some time now, took a fair amount of time off of the scene simply because of my full time work and personal schedule but none the less I keep looking around every now and then. I remember not the longest time ago there were constant changes to the RSPS scene in a way; different bases All-star Scape/Czar/Hyperion all that stuff in general.</p>
<p>Now it’s gone? I mean as in the projects look the exact same - Delta is still thriving as a platform for a server to hold potentially hundreds of people from many different places in the work (can say the same for Project Insanity) but I understand from a learners prospective to learn from something simple/easy. But if this is the case why are people showing off the amount of players their PI/Delta servers can hold? As if there unique spawn pvp server is going to hit this amount anyway.</p>
<p>Maybe I’m confusing you by attacking two points at once; just sad to see the progression lost and people learn from bad examples… I don’t know just having a dig I suppose. Your thoughts?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers/458616/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers/458616/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 12:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-458616-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-servers/458616.rss">Private Servers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
