<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tricky Port Forwarding</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347</link>
    <description>Hello, I&#39;m a 20 year old college student majoring in computer programming(Definitely NOT networking). I really wanted to start messing around with private servers again, but I have a problem that I have spent weeks trying to solve, and I think it&#39;s time I asked for help lol.

I live in a house with two routers. Both routers are Netgear. We have several things that require internet, and for some reason, I can only change the settings in 1 of the routers, I&#39;m not sure how to log into the other router settings since they&#39;re both netgear, but basically, this is the scenario. Downstairs we have the first router, it powers all of the stuff downstairs, and then I have a really long cord running all the way upstairs to my room, which plugs from the first router into my router, giving my router internet access. Then my router powers all the stuff in my room.

What I&#39;m trying to do is forward my ports, and I&#39;m completely lost on how to do this, I feel as though I&#39;ve tried everything.

I&#39;ve gone into my router page and created a port forward that&#39;s set to 192.168.1.9, and created a static ip that&#39;s 10.0.0.9(Maybe I&#39;m doing it wrong?) and then set the ports to 43594. Then I went into my firewall and did all of the exceptions and stuff, and I created a no-ip account and all that good stuff. But every time I check, it says my port is still closed. Any help is GREATLY appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 19:59:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Tricky Port Forwarding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ultimatepkvillage ultimatepkvillage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ultimatepkvillage">@ultimatepkvillage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>fixed</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 19:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-433347-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347.rss">Tricky Port Forwarding</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tricky Port Forwarding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@spearo spearo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spearo">@spearo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why does everyone feel the need to mention how old they are, and that they are studying gaming/computer science… Makes no difference IMO.</p>
<p>Anyway…</p>
<ul>
<li>are their any changes ur ISP is blocking the port?</li>
<li>try disabling your firewall.</li>
<li>go to <a href="http://portforward.com" rel="nofollow noopener">portforward.com</a> like said above. Goodluck.</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 17:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-433347-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347.rss">Tricky Port Forwarding</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tricky Port Forwarding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ultimatepkvillage ultimatepkvillage]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ultimatepkvillage">@ultimatepkvillage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am guessing you probably have a modem which is connected to the computer/router downstairs try portforwarding on that one since the modem is connect to the router, and the computer is connected to the router?</p>
<p>Have you tried this website called <a href="http://portforward.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">portforward.com</a>?<br>
1.searched for your router model number?<br>
2.click on skip advertisement<br>
3.scroll down till you see runescape private server (click it)<br>
4.and follow the instructions from there?</p>
<p>Still need assist private message me or Add me on Skype: Ultimatepkvillage</p>
<p>-I’ll try and get it to work hopefully =D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 15:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-433347-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347.rss">Tricky Port Forwarding</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Tricky Port Forwarding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DrummerDavex DrummerDavex]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drummerdavex">@DrummerDavex</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I’m a 20 year old college student majoring in computer programming(Definitely NOT networking). I really wanted to start messing around with private servers again, but I have a problem that I have spent weeks trying to solve, and I think it’s time I asked for help lol.</p>
<p>I live in a house with two routers. Both routers are Netgear. We have several things that require internet, and for some reason, I can only change the settings in 1 of the routers, I’m not sure how to log into the other router settings since they’re both netgear, but basically, this is the scenario. Downstairs we have the first router, it powers all of the stuff downstairs, and then I have a really long cord running all the way upstairs to my room, which plugs from the first router into my router, giving my router internet access. Then my router powers all the stuff in my room.</p>
<p>What I’m trying to do is forward my ports, and I’m completely lost on how to do this, I feel as though I’ve tried everything.</p>
<p>I’ve gone into my router page and created a port forward that’s set to 192.168.1.9, and created a static ip that’s 10.0.0.9(Maybe I’m doing it wrong?) and then set the ports to 43594. Then I went into my firewall and did all of the exceptions and stuff, and I created a no-ip account and all that good stuff. But every time I check, it says my port is still closed. Any help is GREATLY appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 09:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-433347-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tricky-port-forwarding/433347.rss">Tricky Port Forwarding</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
