<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problems With 508 Client not connecting to Update Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-508-client-not-connecting-to-update-server/482297</link>
    <description>Okay, Well I&#39;ve had a few issues whilst trying to setup a 508, to make it public. The first problem i had was i couldn&#39;t connect to my host no-ip, on my client. It had previously only connected to the local host of (192.168.1.2(or)127.0.0.1(or)0.0.0.0). Now i have finally fixed that, so it now connects through the host i had specified on my no-ip account. Then i uploaded the client for a friend to try, so i could see if my ports were open. He received; Java not recognized Error. So we installed Jdk 7u13 (1.7 Update 13) That cleared up that problem. Now i am stuck I believe my ports aren&#39;t open, as he cannot connect, through the Specified host in no-ip, But i still can... I&#39;ve tried everything from port forwarding... to firewall inbound/outbound exceptions &amp; refreshing no-ip... but nothing has come of it.

I&#39;ve been trying to work this out all day... And i was highly determined when i set out. But 4 hours later. I come and ask the community, because i cant find any logical solution around this.

Thankyou in advance. Any solution will be a godsend :) Keep smiling! :D

i succesfully hosted a 508 on an internet dongle... mobile boradadbnadm so my biggest guess is that my port fowarding is the issue


[u][b]This issue is now fixed, I allowed port 443 through and this fixed my problem, I have also now moved to a 728.[/b][/u]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 18:40:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-508-client-not-connecting-to-update-server/482297.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problems With 508 Client not connecting to Update Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@warouxriot warouxriot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/warouxriot">@warouxriot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, Well I’ve had a few issues whilst trying to setup a 508, to make it public. The first problem i had was i couldn’t connect to my host no-ip, on my client. It had previously only connected to the local host of (192.168.1.2(or)127.0.0.1(or)0.0.0.0). Now i have finally fixed that, so it now connects through the host i had specified on my no-ip account. Then i uploaded the client for a friend to try, so i could see if my ports were open. He received; Java not recognized Error. So we installed Jdk 7u13 (1.7 Update 13) That cleared up that problem. Now i am stuck I believe my ports aren’t open, as he cannot connect, through the Specified host in no-ip, But i still can… I’ve tried everything from port forwarding… to firewall inbound/outbound exceptions &amp; refreshing no-ip… but nothing has come of it.</p>
<p>I’ve been trying to work this out all day… And i was highly determined when i set out. But 4 hours later. I come and ask the community, because i cant find any logical solution around this.</p>
<p>Thankyou in advance. Any solution will be a godsend <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Keep smiling! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>i succesfully hosted a 508 on an internet dongle… mobile boradadbnadm so my biggest guess is that my port fowarding is the issue</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">This issue is now fixed, I allowed port 443 through and this fixed my problem, I have also now moved to a 728.</span></span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-508-client-not-connecting-to-update-server/482297/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-508-client-not-connecting-to-update-server/482297/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 18:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-482297-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problems-with-508-client-not-connecting-to-update-server/482297.rss">Problems With 508 Client not connecting to Update Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
