<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Matrix 718 [ShopKeepers Stand Still]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/matrix-718-shopkeepers-stand-still/538806</link>
    <description>Hello, all I am wondering how to do is make it so the shop keepers can not move, and stand still. I have no troubles making the shops or changing npc spawns. I am using the different NPC&#39;s for the shops, and they are constantly walking around and annoying me, I would like to make them stand still.


Correction: Can someone please give me an example for object spawns in Matrix 718, this is how it tells me to use it, and this is what I do, Can someone give me a working example please? (I haven&#39;t touched anything Runescape related in over a year)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 15:57:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/matrix-718-shopkeepers-stand-still/538806.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Matrix 718 [ShopKeepers Stand Still]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lord0ftacos lord0ftacos]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lord0ftacos">@lord0ftacos</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, all I am wondering how to do is make it so the shop keepers can not move, and stand still. I have no troubles making the shops or changing npc spawns. I am using the different NPC’s for the shops, and they are constantly walking around and annoying me, I would like to make them stand still.</p>
<p>Correction: Can someone please give me an example for object spawns in Matrix 718, this is how it tells me to use it, and this is what I do, Can someone give me a working example please? (I haven’t touched anything Runescape related in over a year)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/matrix-718-shopkeepers-stand-still/538806/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/matrix-718-shopkeepers-stand-still/538806/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 15:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538806-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/matrix-718-shopkeepers-stand-still/538806.rss">Matrix 718 [ShopKeepers Stand Still]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
