<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Theclubsequence</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/theclubsequence/183836</link>
    <description>I wrote this, simply because I&#39;m too socially retarded to do anything useful with my time. It comes in three parts, three different sections to the night, three different approaches towards the event and a variation of genders.

SEQUENCE1
You guilt me into everything that requires a thought process
My mind is numb, captured by a stunning sight.
&quot;Beauty is skin deep&quot; but I&#39;m shallow enough to know what&#39;s in and what&#39;s not.
A spur of the moment act,
spontaneity is my strongest quality.
You&#39;re not quite my type,
but maybe after a few drinks i&#39;ll change my mind.
You waltz up to me like you do this regularly
Confidence is wasted on those who think they can dance.
A safe simple problem; soft to the touch
A safe simple problem; a heart to mistrust.

SEQUENCE2
City gentleman, 
Wont you show me how the street lights accentuate your eyes.
Raindrops are diamonds scattered across car windows.
Handprints linger and water smudged across my back.
This is romance at it&#39;s best, 
fuck the rest. It&#39;s glamour and avidity combined.
We thrive on the life of the night.
The scum that lines the street fall charmed at our feet.
You&#39;re beautiful but it doesn&#39;t make you clean.

SEQUENCE3
We stumble through the door and whats more is you don&#39;t leave much to the imagination do you?
I slip into my liquid coma while you slip into something more &#39;comfortable&#39;.
You shed your skin and crawl under mine.
Rusty fingers unhinge and embrace your waist.
Legs 
and 
bodies 
intertwined.
What happened next is simply classified.
Last nights stale vodka secretes inside my dreams.
This isn&#39;t love but this feelings taking over me.
When I wake I&#39;ll escape,
You&#39;re a face without a name.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 23:36:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/theclubsequence/183836.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Theclubsequence</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sammy25 sammy25]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sammy25">@sammy25</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wrote this, simply because I’m too socially retarded to do anything useful with my time. It comes in three parts, three different sections to the night, three different approaches towards the event and a variation of genders.</p>
<p>SEQUENCE1<br>
You guilt me into everything that requires a thought process<br>
My mind is numb, captured by a stunning sight.<br>
“Beauty is skin deep” but I’m shallow enough to know what’s in and what’s not.<br>
A spur of the moment act,<br>
spontaneity is my strongest quality.<br>
You’re not quite my type,<br>
but maybe after a few drinks i’ll change my mind.<br>
You waltz up to me like you do this regularly<br>
Confidence is wasted on those who think they can dance.<br>
A safe simple problem; soft to the touch<br>
A safe simple problem; a heart to mistrust.</p>
<p>SEQUENCE2<br>
City gentleman,<br>
Wont you show me how the street lights accentuate your eyes.<br>
Raindrops are diamonds scattered across car windows.<br>
Handprints linger and water smudged across my back.<br>
This is romance at it’s best,<br>
fuck the rest. It’s glamour and avidity combined.<br>
We thrive on the life of the night.<br>
The scum that lines the street fall charmed at our feet.<br>
You’re beautiful but it doesn’t make you clean.</p>
<p>SEQUENCE3<br>
We stumble through the door and whats more is you don’t leave much to the imagination do you?<br>
I slip into my liquid coma while you slip into something more ‘comfortable’.<br>
You shed your skin and crawl under mine.<br>
Rusty fingers unhinge and embrace your waist.<br>
Legs<br>
and<br>
bodies<br>
intertwined.<br>
What happened next is simply classified.<br>
Last nights stale vodka secretes inside my dreams.<br>
This isn’t love but this feelings taking over me.<br>
When I wake I’ll escape,<br>
You’re a face without a name.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/theclubsequence/183836/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/theclubsequence/183836/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 23:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-183836-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/theclubsequence/183836.rss">Theclubsequence</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
