<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>May--plans for summer 2012</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/may-plans-for-summer-2012/441128</link>
    <description>As per Frell&#39;s suggestion, we are going to do a summer-long contest for the next MGD award. This time, the contest is broken up into 3 small games, each one which needs to be submitted within a month. There will be one for June, one for July, and a third one for August. The winner of the overall contest will be determined from composite scores of each.

The themes (which are TBD) will be announced ahead of time, so each month will have a progressively more difficult challenge. This allows for people to design their games for each month ahead of time, and simply develop them within the month&#39;s limit.

More to come.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 20:00:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/may-plans-for-summer-2012/441128.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>May--plans for summer 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As per Frell’s suggestion, we are going to do a summer-long contest for the next MGD award. This time, the contest is broken up into 3 small games, each one which needs to be submitted within a month. There will be one for June, one for July, and a third one for August. The winner of the overall contest will be determined from composite scores of each.</p>
<p>The themes (which are TBD) will be announced ahead of time, so each month will have a progressively more difficult challenge. This allows for people to design their games for each month ahead of time, and simply develop them within the month’s limit.</p>
<p>More to come.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/may-plans-for-summer-2012/441128/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/may-plans-for-summer-2012/441128/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-441128-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/may-plans-for-summer-2012/441128.rss">May--plans for summer 2012</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
