<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[REQ] Clan Theatre Coords</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-clan-theatre-coords/548285</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been trying to search everywhere for the coordinates to the theater in the clan citadel, but I&#39;ve run into no luck finding it. I have all the map data up to this year, so it isn&#39;t the lack of data getting in the way of my search. I&#39;ve been able to find the giant area with all the base citadel pieces, but since the theater is instanced separately, it is much more difficult to locate. I&#39;ve tried using a command searching for an object&#39;s coordinates, but for an unknown reason a lot of the objects &quot;Don&#39;t exist&quot; according to my System.out results, in the way that the objects aren&#39;t being loaded into their positions, even though the model shows up in the right place. If anybody happens to know the location of the theater, it would be very helpful to me. 

Thanks in advance.

EDIT: I managed to find the DeathCon theater from the 2011 Halloween event after a little more searching at (4254 5208 0) I still need the original theater, but in case nobody is able to help I have this as a backup.

EDIT2: FINALLY found the citadel theater. It&#39;s (4683 4010 0) in case anybody cares to know.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 00:06:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-clan-theatre-coords/548285.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[REQ] Clan Theatre Coords</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@snbrx snbrx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/snbrx">@snbrx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been trying to search everywhere for the coordinates to the theater in the clan citadel, but I’ve run into no luck finding it. I have all the map data up to this year, so it isn’t the lack of data getting in the way of my search. I’ve been able to find the giant area with all the base citadel pieces, but since the theater is instanced separately, it is much more difficult to locate. I’ve tried using a command searching for an object’s coordinates, but for an unknown reason a lot of the objects “Don’t exist” according to my System.out results, in the way that the objects aren’t being loaded into their positions, even though the model shows up in the right place. If anybody happens to know the location of the theater, it would be very helpful to me.</p>
<p>Thanks in advance.</p>
<p>EDIT: I managed to find the DeathCon theater from the 2011 Halloween event after a little more searching at (4254 5208 0) I still need the original theater, but in case nobody is able to help I have this as a backup.</p>
<p>EDIT2: FINALLY found the citadel theater. It’s (4683 4010 0) in case anybody cares to know.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-clan-theatre-coords/548285/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-clan-theatre-coords/548285/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 00:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548285-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/req-clan-theatre-coords/548285.rss">[REQ] Clan Theatre Coords</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
