<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Complete guide to make a server :: works for any computer and any skill level</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099</link>
    <description>[size=20pt]THIS IS THE COMPLETE SILAB SERVER MAKING GUIDE. IT IS 100% ALL MINE, ABSOLUTELY [u]NO[/u] LEECH. THIS IS COMPLETE WITH FIREWALL SETTINGS, NO-IP HELP, DOWNLOADING A SOURCE, AND MOST IMPORTANTLY... [color=green]PORTFORWARDING!!!  :eek:[/color][/size]

Here it is. Just follow the steps [u]IN ORDER[/u] and it will make a completely working silab server without using hamachi. This silab server you create will be 100% yours and will not be running off of anyone&#39;s computer but your own. [color=navy](btw... I will also tell you how to get a 100% free system that will keep your server running [u]as long as your computer is on.)[/u] PLZ ENJOY THE SILAB SERVER YOU CREATE, PLZ COMMENT, AND PLZ REP IF YOU THINK THIS WORKS!!!     -Alpha 0nx[/color]




[size=7pt]** If necessary[/size]

**STEP 1 - Downloading Java 

Okay most of you probably have Java. But if you do not you must download before you continue to step 2. This is the link for the java download, .
If you want to make sure you have the most recent version of Java, Please do the following - 
[1] Go to [url=http://java.com/en/download/]http://java.com/en/download/[/url]. 
[2] Click &quot;Free Java Download&quot; (you may have to click this on two consecutive pages  :D). 
[3] Click &quot;Save&quot; (2 consecutive times again  ;))... (IF YOU [u]DO NOT[/u] HAVE WINRAR YOU MUST HAVE IT. Here is the link, [url=http://www.win-rar.com/download.html]http://www.win-rar.com/download.html[/url]
[b]NOTE: Please remember the version of java you downloaded, as you will need it for step 6.[/b]


STEP 2 - Downloading a Server Source

Okay, this is where your choice comes in. You will need to download a source for your server, but it is your choice on exactly what kind of source you want to use. This is a link for many different sources to use - [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,49.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,49.0.html[/url]. Please download a source off of this page (**also download the client if there is a link for it). If you dont exactly know if this is the source you want to use, you may want to download a few and try some out. When it comes to Silab servers there are many options for many different kinds of people (pk servers, skilling servers, spawning servers, etc.).



STEP 3 - Getting No-Ip

[b]Go to [url=http://www.no-ip.com]http://www.no-ip.com[/url] to start this step.[/b]
This step will be numbered to make it easier to follow, considering it may be slightly lengthly for explaining things.

[1] **You will need an account on this website to make it so you can create your server. These will be seperately numbered steps for creating an account on No-Ip.com.
          [01] On the right side of your computer screen you will see a place for registered users to log in (the title above this place is &quot;User              Login&quot;. If you look directly under the &quot;password&quot; box, there is a link named &quot;create account&quot;. Click it.
          [02] Please follow the steps on the website for creating a website to conclude this step.

[2] Login (located on the right side of the page). This process will automatically take you to a different page, [u]the page you need[/u]  :|

[3] Almost directly in the middle of the page are a set of buttons (manage domains, add domain, refer friend, add a host, manage hosts). Please click the button that says &quot;Add a Host&quot;.

[4] The first box says host name (this will be the IP of your server, [u]YOU WILL NEED THIS NAME FOR LATER USE. ALSO REMEMBER/WRITE DOWN IF IT&#39;S no-ip.biz, no-ip.org, etc.)[/u], this will be the IP that people enter to enter your server on any silab client. Name it whatever you feel like. Immediately right of this box is a drop down box, click it and select a no-ip.biz, no-ip.org, etc.

[5] Scroll down and select the &quot;create host&quot; button ([b][u]DO NOT REPLACE/ENTER ANYTHING IN ANY OF THE OTHER BOXES).[/u][/b]

[6] Enter www.no-ip.com into the url to get back to the home page.

[7] At the top of the page you will see a tab named &quot;download&quot;, CLICK THIS.

[8] follow the steps of downloading it that are on the website.

[9] [u]After you have downloaded the program[/u], please open it and make sure that the box next to your server&#39;s name is checked.

[10] Click the exit button after you finish and it will hide it but it will keep running, don&#39;t worry  :P



STEP 4 - PORTFORWARDING

[b]For the following step you will need to know your internet router&#39;s type AND model to complete this section[/b]
[1] Go to [url=http://www.portforward.com]http://www.portforward.com[/url]

[2] Scroll down until you find your EXACT model of router and click it.

[3] Once again, Scroll down until you find the program named &quot;Rune&quot;, and click it.

[4] You will need to know your Default Gateway. So do the following.
                [01] Click the start button (not on website, it is on your normal comp screen  ;))
                [02] Go to &quot;All Programs&quot;
                [03] Go to &quot;Accessories&quot;
                [04] Click &quot;Command Prompt&quot;
                [05] In your command prompt write &quot;ipconfig&quot; (without quotation marks  :D)
                [06] If you scroll down you will find something that says &quot;Default Gateway&quot; followed by a series of numbers and periods. You                      need to remember the series of numbers (ex. 192.168.0.1)

[5] Open a new tab and in the URL box enter your default gateway (ex. 192.168.0.1)
          **if you need a username and password it is usually,  USER - admin, PASS - admin. If not, you will need to find out on your own

[6] Go back to the portforward.com tab and follow the steps very precisly.
[b]Please note: Every place that you see &quot;7777&quot; replace that with 43594    [u]THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT!!![/u][/b]



STEP 5 - Firewall Settings

[1] Like before, Click &quot;start&quot;

[2] Go to &quot;Control Panel&quot;

[3] Click &quot;Security Center&quot;

[4] Click &quot;Windows Firewall&quot; (im not completely sure, but this may change between different computers. If it is changed just click whatever link deals with firewall settings  :o)

[5] At the top of the new page is a tab that says &quot;exceptions&quot;. CLICK IT   :eek:

[6] Then select &quot;Add Port&quot;

[7] The name will be your server&#39;s IP (whatever people enter to connect to your server), And the port will be 43594

[8] Make sure &quot;TCP&quot; is selected.

[9] Click &quot;OK&quot;



STEP 6 - Editing your compiler

[1] Open your source folder (The one you downloaded in step 2)

[2] Right click the thing in your folder named &quot;compile&quot; and select &quot;edit&quot;

[3] If you did what you should&#39;ve, you will remember the version of Java JDK you downloaded in STEP1  :|, if not, you must do as follows... (I really hate explaining this because you guys didn&#39;t listen ;))
          [01] Go to the &quot;start&quot; menu
          [02] Click &quot;my computer&quot;
          [03] Go to whatever is located in the &quot;hard disk drives&quot; section
          [04] One of the folders in this will be named &quot;program files&quot;, CLICK IT
          [05] Find and click the folder &quot;Java&quot;
          [06] Find the folder with a name like &quot;jdk1.6.0_14&quot;, that is the version of Java you have  :)

[4] In the document you opened when you clicked edit on your &quot;compile&quot; button, scroll down until you find the current version of Java the source is running on and change it to your version of Java (ex. jdk1.6.0_14)



STEP 7 - Server Runtime Management

I told you guys that I would tell you how to get a program that keeps your server up basically 24/7 as long as you leave your computer on. Well here is the section on downloading and setting up this program... Your Welcome ;D

[1] Go to [url=http://uppit.com/V0S5I3]http://uppit.com/V0S5I3[/url]

[2] Save the file to your documents, then open it.

[3] (after you open S.R.M.) At the top there is a tab called &quot;settings&quot;, Click it.

[4] Change the &quot;Jdk Directory&quot; to your version of Java (from step 6)

[5] In the &quot;Main Class&quot;, click &quot;browse&quot;.

[6] In the window that opens, select your source folder (from step 2), and CLICK IT

[7] Select the file named &quot;server&quot;

[8] In the S.R.M., go back to the &quot;main&quot; tab.

[9] Click &quot;Start&quot;




[size=20pt]YOU ARE OFFICIALLY DONE!!!! Go to this link, [url=http://www.client.silabsoft.com]www.client.silabsoft.com[/url], and then you can play on your server!!![/size]

[b][size=30pt]NOTE: To login to [u]YOUR[/u] server, you must use the IP 127.0.0.1[/size][/b]


Well there you go guys. YOU ARE DONE  :D    PLZ COMMENT. If you have any   :confused: QUESTIONS :confused:  Please ask and I promise I will go into greater detail or include a section on your question.



[center][size=25pt]-Alpha 0nx[/size][/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 06:15:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Complete guide to make a server :: works for any computer and any skill level</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NewbieNewty Newty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbienewty">@NewbieNewty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We appreciate your help but this is not the proper section and there is already a tutorial covering this subject.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 06:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-321099-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099.rss">Complete guide to make a server :: works for any computer and any skill level</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete guide to make a server :: works for any computer and any skill level</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lildude783 lildude783]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lildude783">@lildude783</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>if i was a mod i’d delete this -.-…</p>
<p>these “guides to turning on your server! 100% MY WORK!” are annoying…</p>
<p>did “you” figure out how to port forward? did “you” make your own wutevers that port forward differently than anything else… did “you” actually think all this up? or did you just steal it from silab or runelocus or another tut here on mopar?</p>
<p>close this or move it? its in wrong section… and i’ve seen too many of these “guide to make a server” things… theres ENOUGH of these already -.-</p>
<p>didnt need to read it… already knew what was gonna be in it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 04:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-321099-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099.rss">Complete guide to make a server :: works for any computer and any skill level</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete guide to make a server :: works for any computer and any skill level</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@icepkers icepkers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/icepkers">@icepkers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Umm… wouldn’t this go in the tutorial section?</p>
<p>if i was a mod i’d move this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 03:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-321099-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099.rss">Complete guide to make a server :: works for any computer and any skill level</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete guide to make a server :: works for any computer and any skill level</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@alpha_0nx alpha 0nx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/alpha_0nx">@alpha_0nx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=20pt]THIS IS THE COMPLETE SILAB SERVER MAKING GUIDE. IT IS 100% ALL MINE, ABSOLUTELY <span class="bbcode-u">NO</span> LEECH. THIS IS COMPLETE WITH FIREWALL SETTINGS, NO-IP HELP, DOWNLOADING A SOURCE, AND MOST IMPORTANTLY… [color=green]PORTFORWARDING!!!  :eek:[/color][/size]</p>
<p>Here it is. Just follow the steps <span class="bbcode-u">IN ORDER</span> and it will make a completely working silab server without using hamachi. This silab server you create will be 100% yours and will not be running off of anyone’s computer but your own. [color=navy](btw… I will also tell you how to get a 100% free system that will keep your server running <span class="bbcode-u">as long as your computer is on.)</span> PLZ ENJOY THE SILAB SERVER YOU CREATE, PLZ COMMENT, AND PLZ REP IF YOU THINK THIS WORKS!!!     -Alpha 0nx[/color]</p>
<p>[size=7pt]** If necessary[/size]</p>
<p>**STEP 1 - Downloading Java</p>
<p>Okay most of you probably have Java. But if you do not you must download before you continue to step 2. This is the link for the java download, .<br>
If you want to make sure you have the most recent version of Java, Please do the following -<br>
[1] Go to <a href="http://java.com/en/download/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.com/en/download/</a>.<br>
[2] Click “Free Java Download” (you may have to click this on two consecutive pages  :D).<br>
[3] Click “Save” (2 consecutive times again  ;))… (IF YOU <span class="bbcode-u">DO NOT</span> HAVE WINRAR YOU MUST HAVE IT. Here is the link, <a href="http://www.win-rar.com/download.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.win-rar.com/download.html</a><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">NOTE: Please remember the version of java you downloaded, as you will need it for step 6.</span></p>
<p>STEP 2 - Downloading a Server Source</p>
<p>Okay, this is where your choice comes in. You will need to download a source for your server, but it is your choice on exactly what kind of source you want to use. This is a link for many different sources to use - <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,49.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,49.0.html</a>. Please download a source off of this page (**also download the client if there is a link for it). If you dont exactly know if this is the source you want to use, you may want to download a few and try some out. When it comes to Silab servers there are many options for many different kinds of people (pk servers, skilling servers, spawning servers, etc.).</p>
<p>STEP 3 - Getting No-Ip</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Go to <a href="http://www.no-ip.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.no-ip.com</a> to start this step.</span><br>
This step will be numbered to make it easier to follow, considering it may be slightly lengthly for explaining things.</p>
<p>[1] **You will need an account on this website to make it so you can create your server. These will be seperately numbered steps for creating an account on <a href="http://No-Ip.com" rel="nofollow noopener">No-Ip.com</a>.<br>
[01] On the right side of your computer screen you will see a place for registered users to log in (the title above this place is “User              Login”. If you look directly under the “password” box, there is a link named “create account”. Click it.<br>
[02] Please follow the steps on the website for creating a website to conclude this step.</p>
<p>[2] Login (located on the right side of the page). This process will automatically take you to a different page, <span class="bbcode-u">the page you need</span>  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>[3] Almost directly in the middle of the page are a set of buttons (manage domains, add domain, refer friend, add a host, manage hosts). Please click the button that says “Add a Host”.</p>
<p>[4] The first box says host name (this will be the IP of your server, <span class="bbcode-u">YOU WILL NEED THIS NAME FOR LATER USE. ALSO REMEMBER/WRITE DOWN IF IT’S no-ip.biz, <a href="http://no-ip.org" rel="nofollow noopener">no-ip.org</a>, etc.)</span>, this will be the IP that people enter to enter your server on any silab client. Name it whatever you feel like. Immediately right of this box is a drop down box, click it and select a no-ip.biz, <a href="http://no-ip.org" rel="nofollow noopener">no-ip.org</a>, etc.</p>
<p>[5] Scroll down and select the “create host” button (<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">DO NOT REPLACE/ENTER ANYTHING IN ANY OF THE OTHER BOXES).</span></span></p>
<p>[6] Enter <a href="http://www.no-ip.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.no-ip.com</a> into the url to get back to the home page.</p>
<p>[7] At the top of the page you will see a tab named “download”, CLICK THIS.</p>
<p>[8] follow the steps of downloading it that are on the website.</p>
<p>[9] <span class="bbcode-u">After you have downloaded the program</span>, please open it and make sure that the box next to your server’s name is checked.</p>
<p>[10] Click the exit button after you finish and it will hide it but it will keep running, don’t worry  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>STEP 4 - PORTFORWARDING</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">For the following step you will need to know your internet router’s type AND model to complete this section</span><br>
[1] Go to <a href="http://www.portforward.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.portforward.com</a></p>
<p>[2] Scroll down until you find your EXACT model of router and click it.</p>
<p>[3] Once again, Scroll down until you find the program named “Rune”, and click it.</p>
<p>[4] You will need to know your Default Gateway. So do the following.<br>
[01] Click the start button (not on website, it is on your normal comp screen  ;))<br>
[02] Go to “All Programs”<br>
[03] Go to “Accessories”<br>
[04] Click “Command Prompt”<br>
[05] In your command prompt write “ipconfig” (without quotation marks  :D)<br>
[06] If you scroll down you will find something that says “Default Gateway” followed by a series of numbers and periods. You                      need to remember the series of numbers (ex. 192.168.0.1)</p>
<p>[5] Open a new tab and in the URL box enter your default gateway (ex. 192.168.0.1)<br>
**if you need a username and password it is usually,  USER - admin, PASS - admin. If not, you will need to find out on your own</p>
<p>[6] Go back to the <a href="http://portforward.com" rel="nofollow noopener">portforward.com</a> tab and follow the steps very precisly.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Please note: Every place that you see “7777” replace that with 43594    <span class="bbcode-u">THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT!!!</span></span></p>
<p>STEP 5 - Firewall Settings</p>
<p>[1] Like before, Click “start”</p>
<p>[2] Go to “Control Panel”</p>
<p>[3] Click “Security Center”</p>
<p>[4] Click “Windows Firewall” (im not completely sure, but this may change between different computers. If it is changed just click whatever link deals with firewall settings  :o)</p>
<p>[5] At the top of the new page is a tab that says “exceptions”. CLICK IT   :eek:</p>
<p>[6] Then select “Add Port”</p>
<p>[7] The name will be your server’s IP (whatever people enter to connect to your server), And the port will be 43594</p>
<p>[8] Make sure “TCP” is selected.</p>
<p>[9] Click “OK”</p>
<p>STEP 6 - Editing your compiler</p>
<p>[1] Open your source folder (The one you downloaded in step 2)</p>
<p>[2] Right click the thing in your folder named “compile” and select “edit”</p>
<p>[3] If you did what you should’ve, you will remember the version of Java JDK you downloaded in STEP1  :|, if not, you must do as follows… (I really hate explaining this because you guys didn’t listen ;))<br>
[01] Go to the “start” menu<br>
[02] Click “my computer”<br>
[03] Go to whatever is located in the “hard disk drives” section<br>
[04] One of the folders in this will be named “program files”, CLICK IT<br>
[05] Find and click the folder “Java”<br>
[06] Find the folder with a name like “jdk1.6.0_14”, that is the version of Java you have  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>[4] In the document you opened when you clicked edit on your “compile” button, scroll down until you find the current version of Java the source is running on and change it to your version of Java (ex. jdk1.6.0_14)</p>
<p>STEP 7 - Server Runtime Management</p>
<p>I told you guys that I would tell you how to get a program that keeps your server up basically 24/7 as long as you leave your computer on. Well here is the section on downloading and setting up this program… Your Welcome ;D</p>
<p>[1] Go to <a href="http://uppit.com/V0S5I3" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/V0S5I3</a></p>
<p>[2] Save the file to your documents, then open it.</p>
<p>[3] (after you open S.R.M.) At the top there is a tab called “settings”, Click it.</p>
<p>[4] Change the “Jdk Directory” to your version of Java (from step 6)</p>
<p>[5] In the “Main Class”, click “browse”.</p>
<p>[6] In the window that opens, select your source folder (from step 2), and CLICK IT</p>
<p>[7] Select the file named “server”</p>
<p>[8] In the S.R.M., go back to the “main” tab.</p>
<p>[9] Click “Start”</p>
<p>[size=20pt]YOU ARE OFFICIALLY DONE!!! Go to this link, <a href="http://www.client.silabsoft.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.client.silabsoft.com</a>, and then you can play on your server!!![/size]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=30pt]NOTE: To login to <span class="bbcode-u">YOUR</span> server, you must use the IP 127.0.0.1[/size]</span></p>
<p>Well there you go guys. YOU ARE DONE  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:">    PLZ COMMENT. If you have any   <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> QUESTIONS <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:">  Please ask and I promise I will go into greater detail or include a section on your question.</p>
<p>[center][size=25pt]-Alpha 0nx[/size][/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 03:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-321099-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-guide-to-make-a-server-works-for-any-computer-and-any-skill-level/321099.rss">Complete guide to make a server :: works for any computer and any skill level</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
