<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Interested in text based RTS?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443</link>
    <description>For the past 7 years I&#39;ve played a text based, real time strategy game called Planetarion. (It runs from your browser, so it&#39;s simple to use interface - if you&#39;ve heard of OGAME  it&#39;s an overly complicated ripoff of PA for kids)

Starting with over 100,000 players the game now has around 1500, it basically needs more and I thought I&#39;d come and give you an idea of what it&#39;s about. Bare in mind this is not everyones cup of tea, in fact most of the player base are working class adults above 20.

Planetarion is a space science fiction game, each player controlling a planet - within a galaxy. You can Buddy Pack galaxies with up to around 5 friends. There are also alliances allowing up to 75 members. This allows serious politics to take place, and I mean serious, you wouldn&#39;t believe the wars, backstabbing and power driven battles this game offers. The game runs by &quot;ticks&quot; a tick occurs once an hour, therefore you don&#39;t need to be playing for hours each day to be good, the more active you are the better you&#39;ll do though because you can be precise and literally never miss a tick. The game ticks in general for 7 weeks, then the universe resets and we start over. So we have rounds - some people don&#39;t like the idea of starting a fresh, but actually it&#39;s great for so many reasons and means you can say just play in winter or summer or whatever. Also each rounds ship stats and races (there are 5 balanced races with different specializations to choose from) are changed. Allowing new dynamics on attack fleets and the games combat system.

The game revolves around IRC - into programming? This game attracts developers on every level, since IRC is real time and it allows us to coordinate attacks and defence instantly. The bots developed by players are amazing and some even have webbies running simultaneously. My Alliance has a webbie and bot written all in Perl, and the guy releases it all open source. The game has parsers and does a &quot;planet dump&quot; every tick so you produce sites like www.sandmans.co.uk with universe stats on every planet. There also battle calculators and numerous other community resources it truly is a developers game ;) 

EDIT: Forgot to mention, it is very mathematical. Complex combat forumulae and ship stats. If you fear maths - stay away - even the login captcha is maths.

Sleepless nights, expect them! We attack in the early morning, although you can do something called pre-launch if you&#39;re a lazy fucker. If you don&#39;t have time to spare, then you can play very generally, if you have time to spare you can easily become a very good player. 

Hmm, I&#39;m just trying to ramble off lots of the features.. the galaxies and alliances you reside in will become great friends since you&#39;ll spend most of your time talking to them in private IRC channels. The community is very friendly and people are willing to help new players learn.

The current round is ticking till 22 December or so. You have no chance of winning or doing particular well signing up this late, but you&#39;ll get late signup bonuses and therefore have some research/constructions one done for you allowing you to get a feel for the game. Next round will be January some time, giving you plenty of time to decide.

This game requires commitment I wont lie. It&#39;s pretty hardcore and difficult to get into for a first timer. Which is why I&#39;m here making this so people can ask questions.

TBH I don&#39;t expect many of you to like it or play, but we need more players so I did it on the off chance some IRC regulars might give it a try.

www.planetarion.com
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Planetarion
http://www.clawofdarkness.com/pawiki/index.php/Main_Page

Forgive me for advertising, and this should be in Other games, but I want it to get attention :P

There is a manual ingame. By the way it is Free to play, but for £3 per round you can get a few bonuses - not needed by any of you unless you decide to play next round seriously.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 21:30:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Interested in text based RTS?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds interesting, I’ll probably sign up in January.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 21:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-248443-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443.rss">Interested in text based RTS?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Interested in text based RTS?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PeterMan PeterMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/peterman">@PeterMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I used to play something called Tribal Wars, and it was also a RTS.<br>
Got to time consuming after I got too many villages and playing on 4 or more servers though.<br>
I quit 4 months back :o</p>
<p>I’m not ready for another one yet   :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 02:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-248443-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443.rss">Interested in text based RTS?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Interested in text based RTS?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Fair enough, this came around just after MUDs died.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 19:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-248443-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443.rss">Interested in text based RTS?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Interested in text based RTS?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I thought you meant MUD-style when you said text-based. I don’t like browser-games.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 19:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-248443-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443.rss">Interested in text based RTS?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Interested in text based RTS?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For the past 7 years I’ve played a text based, real time strategy game called Planetarion. (It runs from your browser, so it’s simple to use interface - if you’ve heard of OGAME  it’s an overly complicated ripoff of PA for kids)</p>
<p>Starting with over 100,000 players the game now has around 1500, it basically needs more and I thought I’d come and give you an idea of what it’s about. Bare in mind this is not everyones cup of tea, in fact most of the player base are working class adults above 20.</p>
<p>Planetarion is a space science fiction game, each player controlling a planet - within a galaxy. You can Buddy Pack galaxies with up to around 5 friends. There are also alliances allowing up to 75 members. This allows serious politics to take place, and I mean serious, you wouldn’t believe the wars, backstabbing and power driven battles this game offers. The game runs by “ticks” a tick occurs once an hour, therefore you don’t need to be playing for hours each day to be good, the more active you are the better you’ll do though because you can be precise and literally never miss a tick. The game ticks in general for 7 weeks, then the universe resets and we start over. So we have rounds - some people don’t like the idea of starting a fresh, but actually it’s great for so many reasons and means you can say just play in winter or summer or whatever. Also each rounds ship stats and races (there are 5 balanced races with different specializations to choose from) are changed. Allowing new dynamics on attack fleets and the games combat system.</p>
<p>The game revolves around IRC - into programming? This game attracts developers on every level, since IRC is real time and it allows us to coordinate attacks and defence instantly. The bots developed by players are amazing and some even have webbies running simultaneously. My Alliance has a webbie and bot written all in Perl, and the guy releases it all open source. The game has parsers and does a “planet dump” every tick so you produce sites like <a href="http://www.sandmans.co.uk" rel="nofollow noopener">www.sandmans.co.uk</a> with universe stats on every planet. There also battle calculators and numerous other community resources it truly is a developers game <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>EDIT: Forgot to mention, it is very mathematical. Complex combat forumulae and ship stats. If you fear maths - stay away - even the login captcha is maths.</p>
<p>Sleepless nights, expect them! We attack in the early morning, although you can do something called pre-launch if you’re a lazy fucker. If you don’t have time to spare, then you can play very generally, if you have time to spare you can easily become a very good player.</p>
<p>Hmm, I’m just trying to ramble off lots of the features… the galaxies and alliances you reside in will become great friends since you’ll spend most of your time talking to them in private IRC channels. The community is very friendly and people are willing to help new players learn.</p>
<p>The current round is ticking till 22 December or so. You have no chance of winning or doing particular well signing up this late, but you’ll get late signup bonuses and therefore have some research/constructions one done for you allowing you to get a feel for the game. Next round will be January some time, giving you plenty of time to decide.</p>
<p>This game requires commitment I wont lie. It’s pretty hardcore and difficult to get into for a first timer. Which is why I’m here making this so people can ask questions.</p>
<p>TBH I don’t expect many of you to like it or play, but we need more players so I did it on the off chance some IRC regulars might give it a try.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.planetarion.com" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">www.planetarion.com</a><br>
<aside class="onebox wikipedia">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Planetarion" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">en.wikipedia.org</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    

<h3><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Planetarion" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Planetarion</a></h3>

<p>Planetarion (commonly referred to as PA) is a browser-based massively multiplayer online game. Created by Fifth Season AS in early 2000, then bought by Jolt in 2003, and then purchased by Renegade Games in 2009; it is now currently owned by Jagex. The game places players in control of a planet, with the ability to mine its asteroids for resources, enabling them to construct a fleet of spaceships to attack other player's planets. Although its popularity has declined with the emergence of other sim...</p>

  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<a href="http://www.clawofdarkness.com/pawiki/index.php/Main_Page" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.clawofdarkness.com/pawiki/index.php/Main_Page</a></p>
<p>Forgive me for advertising, and this should be in Other games, but I want it to get attention <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>There is a manual ingame. By the way it is Free to play, but for £3 per round you can get a few bonuses - not needed by any of you unless you decide to play next round seriously.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 18:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-248443-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/interested-in-text-based-rts/248443.rss">Interested in text based RTS?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
