<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Requesting a little help and information</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-little-help-and-information/59582</link>
    <description>I&#39;m extremely sorry if this has been asked before but is there anyway I can download the files needed to play runescape in it&#39;s entirety, I don&#39;t want an edited version besides commands because I&#39;d like to play the game in its entirety by myself with the original shops and quests and enjoy myself. I apologize if this question has been asked already but if anyone could point me in the right direction that would be much appreciated.

Thank you ahead of time.

(By the way my computer was acting screwy and I checked the first couple pages of this section of the forum and didn&#39;t see my post so if it is on here by some bizarre chain of events then forgive me please.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2007 22:05:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-little-help-and-information/59582.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Requesting a little help and information</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ramsus_Gallant Ramsus_Gallant]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ramsus_gallant">@Ramsus_Gallant</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m extremely sorry if this has been asked before but is there anyway I can download the files needed to play runescape in it’s entirety, I don’t want an edited version besides commands because I’d like to play the game in its entirety by myself with the original shops and quests and enjoy myself. I apologize if this question has been asked already but if anyone could point me in the right direction that would be much appreciated.</p>
<p>Thank you ahead of time.</p>
<p>(By the way my computer was acting screwy and I checked the first couple pages of this section of the forum and didn’t see my post so if it is on here by some bizarre chain of events then forgive me please.)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-little-help-and-information/59582/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-little-help-and-information/59582/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2007 22:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-59582-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-a-little-help-and-information/59582.rss">Requesting a little help and information</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
