<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;The conduct of three British military units in Afghanistan came under serious question tonight after the Ministry of Defence released unprecedented details of incidents in which troops attacked Afghan civilians.

The disclosure, in response to a request under the Freedom of Information Act made by the Guardian, revealed that of the casualties caused by British forces, two-thirds involved troops from the three units, triggering calls for an inquiry into their behaviour.

Releasing information about 21 incidents, the MoD revealed that the Coldstream Guards shot four civilians in Kabul over a period of three weeks; the Royal Marine commandos killed or wounded civilians eight times in six months; and the third unit, the Rifles, were involved in three incidents last year.

Among the casualties were children, and on one occasion a man with mental health problems.

Details of the attacks were not released at the time, but they were among thousands of incidents mentioned in US army logs posted by the whistle-blowing website WikiLeaks in the summer. Today&#39;s release came after the Guardian pressed for more details of those cases.

One cluster of incidents involved the Coldstream Guards in Kabul in autumn 2007. On 21 October, they killed one individual and wounded two others in a silver minibus while on patrol in Kabul.

The MoD says the minibus failed to stop when the soldiers signalled for it to do so, and the guardsmen shot at it.

In another incident, on 6 November 2007, the son of an Afghan general was killed. He was driving a Toyota car and was said to have accelerated towards a Coldstream Guards patrol. The soldiers could only shout a warning before shooting at the car; it skidded to a halt and the man fell out, the MoD said.

The Coldstream Guards&#39; unofficial blog described the mood within the detachment at the time: &quot;The overriding threat is that of suicide bombers, of which there have been a number in the recent past.&quot;

The second cluster of civilian casualties involved the Royal Marines, who were stationed in Helmand province.

On 19 November 2008 they shot dead a child in a white Toyota which they believed was driving towards them. &quot;There had been a report of a suicide bomber in the area,&quot; said the MoD.

On 4 December 2008, marines wounded a man who had been &quot;trying to locate his family as they had moved compounds&quot;. The marines thought he had been tracking them, the MoD says.

That month, a 12-year-old boy was wounded when a van sped towards a Royal Marines patrol and &quot;failed to stop after verbal warnings were given&quot;.

On 19 January 2009, two children were injured &quot;in their abdomens by shrapnel&quot; after missiles were fired from above by unmanned drones. The Royal Marines had called for the air strikes, fearing they were being threatened by Taliban insurgents.

A few days later, the marines shot a man and a child after they believed two men were &quot;reporting their progress&quot; in order to prepare a bomb attack.

A mentally ill man was shot in the last incident, on 26 March 2009. The marines had received a report of a bomb threat when a man on a motorcycle &quot;approached the patrol driving slowly and observing them&quot;. He disappeared after warning shots were fired. But he soon returned. The marines thought he was an &quot;imminent threat&quot; and shot him, according to the MoD.

The Rifles were involved in three incidents last year, including calling in RAF aircraft whose bomb killed an undisclosed number of civilians in Nad-e-Ali, Helmand last September.

Tonight, Labour MP Paul Flynn called for an inquiry into the conduct of the units in what he said could be &quot;atrocities in the name of the British people&quot;. &quot;Truth has a cleansing function,&quot; he added.

Royal Marine commandos were the last UK troops to be stationed in Sangin, one of the most dangerous areas of Afghanistan, before handing over to US forces earlier this year. The Rifles sustained particularly severe casualties when they were deployed in Sangin at the beginning of this year. The Coldstream Guards, the one of the oldest regiments in the British army, have been deployed in Afghanistan at regular intervals.

An MoD spokesman said: &quot;We deeply regret all civilian casualties. Protecting the Afghan civilian population is a cornerstone of ISAF&#39;s mission, and all British troops undergo comprehensive training on the strict rules of engagement. This contrasts directly with the attitude of the insurgents, whose indiscriminate use of suicide bombs, roadside explosive devices and human shields cause the majority of civilian deaths and injuries in Afghanistan. We will continue our efforts to prevent insurgents harming civilians and to develop the capacity of Afghan security forces to protect the population.&quot;

Meanwhile, today MEPs demanded that European leaders challenge the US president, Barack Obama, over WikiLeaks&#39; disclosures of alleged torture in Iraq. They want the issue to be raised at the EU-US summit agenda next month.

Guy Verhofstadt, leader of the liberals group in the European parliament, said that the Obama administration had to investigate the &quot;abuses&quot; revealed by WikiLeaks.

&quot;This will obviously be a sensitive topic for the US administration, but partners in the transatlantic alliance must be clear on common rules of engagement in times of conflict if we are to retain any moral standing in the world,&quot; Verhofstadt said.

&quot;Whilst the allegations concern actions undertaken during the previous Bush administration, it will be incumbent on the present one to investigate the abuses, pursue those complicit and lay down stricter guidelines for conduct in combat.&quot;

&quot;The US remains a hugely important ally in terms of security. We cannot afford to allow our standards to slip so far that respect for the rule of law is ignored.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

http://www.guardian.co.uk/world/2010/oct/26/afghanistan-civilians-ministry-defence-wikileaks?CMP=twt_gu</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 17:37:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:104, topic:366127”][quote author=Frell link=topic=462325.msg3388586#msg3388586 date=1288714385]<br>
Sweden survives because it doesnt spend alot on military and because of its banking system.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>In other words, because it’s run properly? :P[/quote]<br>
how u double post</p>
<p>And America survives off of internal industrialization, which socialism will ruin.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/105">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/105</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-105</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="100" data-topic="366127">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sweden survives because it doesnt spend alot on military and because of its banking system.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In other words, because it’s run properly? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/104">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/104</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 17:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-104</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="102" data-topic="366127">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But, theres no limit to how much you can succeed in America either. Capitalism is the reason why microsoft is here, apple is here, coca cola is here, the phone exists, the lightbulb exists etc. All these people knew that if they succeeded there was nothing holding them down from being insanely rich. That probably wasn’t their only motive, but it definitely motivated them. Something similar to this is the reason so many people complain about sports players making $7m a year from throwing a ball around and endorsements. I had a problem with it, until i realized American citizens paid them, they’re paid by the people coming to games etc.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But none of those things go away if you provide welfare, medical assistance etc. They’re not mutually exclusive. The light bulb is, after all, a British invention. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/103">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/103</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 17:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-103</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Speljohan, post:101, topic:366127”][quote author=Frell link=topic=462325.msg3388586#msg3388586 date=1288714385]<br>
Sweden survives because it doesnt spend alot on military and because of its banking system.<br>
[/quote]Ya, like i said, socialism works great here, but i doubt it would ever work for a super-country like USA[/quote]<br>
And this is the reason why all these Fox newscasters are always bashing Obama’s socialist policies. Right now our federal government provides too many things that it shouldnt, like social security, medicare, welfare, etc. These should all be funded by the state, our federal government forcing these things on all states is in a way, unconstitutional.</p>
<p>But, theres no limit to how much you can succeed in America either. Capitalism is the reason why microsoft is here, apple is here, coca cola is here, the phone exists, the lightbulb exists etc. All these people knew that if they succeeded there was nothing holding them down from being insanely rich. That probably wasn’t their only motive, but it definitely motivated them. Something similar to this is the reason so many people complain about sports players making $7m a year from throwing a ball around and endorsements. I had a problem with it, until i realized American citizens paid them, they’re paid by the people coming to games etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/102">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/102</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-102</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:100, topic:366127”]Sweden survives because it doesnt spend alot on military and because of its banking system.[/quote]Ya, like i said, socialism works great here, but i doubt it would ever work for a super-country like USA</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/101">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/101</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 16:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-101</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sweden survives because it doesnt spend alot on military and because of its banking system.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/100</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 16:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-100</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Erj Erj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/erj">@Erj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Civilian casualties are unaccepted!</p>
<p>“Bloody hell, we just got our arses kicked!”</p>
<p>Press X to try again.<br>
Press O to return to the Spec Ops Menu.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/99</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 15:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-99</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:97, topic:366127”][quote author=Speljohan link=topic=462325.msg3388458#msg3388458 date=1288691880]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Explain to me how, if someone is not mentally sick, not disabled, and they did decent in school and didnt drop out, they could be poor?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ignoring the other obvious idiocy… some people are sick, are disabled, or didn’t do decent_ly_ in school.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, if they nothing the poor will stay poor, and if the rich keep doing what they’re doing they will stay rich.  Where theres a will theres a way, but some people are in fact too lazy to cross the bridge.<br>
[/quote]Ya, it is the grinding-wheel of pure capitalism. There must be a huge poor working-class in order to accomodate for the rich, so essentially it is a very inhumane system. I believe that socialistic democracy is the best solution to this problem that we have today (Judging from the high living standards in scandinavia and other socialistic democracies).</p>
<p>The USA often brags about their Capitalistic system and success, and one of the many arguments i hear from the extremely conservative branch is “You are communists, we have thousands of products, what do you have?”. Well, first of all the USA isn’t even pure Capitalism (since there’s a few elite companies with way more power than they should have). Secondly, how much choice do you really have? Yeah, you got Dr Pepper, Coca Cola and Pepsi! The only problem here is that they are essentially the same thing, they are produced by the same big ol’ company, so you don’t really have that big and mighty choice you so prompty claim to have!</p>
<p>In a socialistic-democratic environment, Companies are allowed to exist, and are encouraged to thrive, but the essential things such as Healthcare and Education are either owned or funded by the state. (we have both private and public education that is equally good here, and both are free up until uni-level, where you start paying for things such as books and other neccessary materials for your education). Having drugs (Tobacco, Alcohol) government-regulated i feel is a good thing too, to ensure the taxes of these items are incredibly high and to stop oversupply and potential addictions leading to a bad life.</p>
<p>If you are going to work for the system, pay taxes all your life and fund the government, then it’s just fair that they give you the means to do so.</p>
<p>This prevents exploitation (assuming the state isn’t shit), and gives you a social security “web”, that protects you, should something go wrong.</p>
<p>I just woke up, so i have probably missed out on some things i wanted to say here, i think i got most of it down though.</p>
<p><img src="http://i51.tinypic.com/2iizlfl.jpg" alt></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>“The Constitution only gives people the right to pursue happiness. You have to catch it yourself.” - Benjamin Franklin.</p>
<p>Not everyone can be rich, and the rich people usually end up creating many middle class jobs for those who want to live well. The rich work with their mind, and in most cases they have it in a way that benefits the employees and the owner. But its not just the owner and then people working the machines, there is a whole hierarchy of people needed to be paid respected to their education, and shitton of more workers to pay. Why does McDonalds pay fast food workers minimum wage? I honestly don’t know, but would you give them any bigger of a cut without at least raising the experience requirements? I can see how your views would, in a way, protect everyone. But thats not how America was created to be.</p>
<p>America compared to many other countries is like a bike without training wheels. Its so easy to fall and so easy to stay up right.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.discountbookdistributors.com/images/products/detail/Socialism.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/quote]I wouldn’t want America to be a socialistic state at all tbh, lots of people enjoy what it offers. What i would like to see however, is that the government adds more restrictions aganist monopolies and massive corporations.</p>
<p>EDIT: Whilst my picture was an inaccurate one too, yours is a bit too much since the economy in Sweden for example, is way superior to the one of USA.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cia.gov/library/publications/the-world-factbook/rankorder/2187rank.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.cia.gov/library/publications/the-world-factbook/rankorder/2187rank.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/98</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 15:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-98</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Speljohan, post:95, topic:366127”][quote author=Frell link=topic=462325.msg3388318#msg3388318 date=1288672606]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Explain to me how, if someone is not mentally sick, not disabled, and they did decent in school and didnt drop out, they could be poor?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ignoring the other obvious idiocy… some people are sick, are disabled, or didn’t do decent_ly_ in school.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, if they nothing the poor will stay poor, and if the rich keep doing what they’re doing they will stay rich.  Where theres a will theres a way, but some people are in fact too lazy to cross the bridge.<br>
[/quote]Ya, it is the grinding-wheel of pure capitalism. There must be a huge poor working-class in order to accomodate for the rich, so essentially it is a very inhumane system. I believe that socialistic democracy is the best solution to this problem that we have today (Judging from the high living standards in scandinavia and other socialistic democracies).</p>
<p>The USA often brags about their Capitalistic system and success, and one of the many arguments i hear from the extremely conservative branch is “You are communists, we have thousands of products, what do you have?”. Well, first of all the USA isn’t even pure Capitalism (since there’s a few elite companies with way more power than they should have). Secondly, how much choice do you really have? Yeah, you got Dr Pepper, Coca Cola and Pepsi! The only problem here is that they are essentially the same thing, they are produced by the same big ol’ company, so you don’t really have that big and mighty choice you so prompty claim to have!</p>
<p>In a socialistic-democratic environment, Companies are allowed to exist, and are encouraged to thrive, but the essential things such as Healthcare and Education are either owned or funded by the state. (we have both private and public education that is equally good here, and both are free up until uni-level, where you start paying for things such as books and other neccessary materials for your education). Having drugs (Tobacco, Alcohol) government-regulated i feel is a good thing too, to ensure the taxes of these items are incredibly high and to stop oversupply and potential addictions leading to a bad life.</p>
<p>If you are going to work for the system, pay taxes all your life and fund the government, then it’s just fair that they give you the means to do so.</p>
<p>This prevents exploitation (assuming the state isn’t shit), and gives you a social security “web”, that protects you, should something go wrong.</p>
<p>I just woke up, so i have probably missed out on some things i wanted to say here, i think i got most of it down though.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i51.tinypic.com/2iizlfl.jpg" title="2iizlfl.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i51.tinypic.com/2iizlfl.jpg" alt width="428" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2iizlfl.jpg</span><span class="informations">600×700</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div>[/quote]<br>
“The Constitution only gives people the right to pursue happiness. You have to catch it yourself.” - Benjamin Franklin.</p>
<p>Not everyone can be rich, and the rich people usually end up creating many middle class jobs for those who want to live well. The rich work with their mind, and in most cases they have it in a way that benefits the employees and the owner. But its not just the owner and then people working the machines, there is a whole hierarchy of people needed to be paid respected to their education, and shitton of more workers to pay. Why does McDonalds pay fast food workers minimum wage? I honestly don’t know, but would you give them any bigger of a cut without at least raising the experience requirements? I can see how your views would, in a way, protect everyone. But thats not how America was created to be.</p>
<p>America compared to many other countries is like a bike without training wheels. Its so easy to fall and so easy to stay up right.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.discountbookdistributors.com/images/products/detail/Socialism.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/97</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 15:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-97</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MujaheD Radeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mujahed">@MujaheD</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In Australia, I get an interest-free government loan which pays for my <span class="bbcode-s">tuition</span> uni. If I don’t get a job which pays above a certain rate, I don’t ever have to pay back the loan.</p>
<p>tldr; Australia is the best place in the world.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/96</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 10:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-96</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:80, topic:366127”][quote author=Mopman link=topic=462325.msg3388303#msg3388303 date=1288671928]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Explain to me how, if someone is not mentally sick, not disabled, and they did decent in school and didnt drop out, they could be poor?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ignoring the other obvious idiocy… some people are sick, are disabled, or didn’t do decent_ly_ in school.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Yes, if they nothing the poor will stay poor, and if the rich keep doing what they’re doing they will stay rich.  Where theres a will theres a way, but some people are in fact too lazy to cross the bridge.[/quote]Ya, it is the grinding-wheel of pure capitalism. There must be a huge poor working-class in order to accomodate for the rich, so essentially it is a very inhumane system. I believe that socialistic democracy is the best solution to this problem that we have today (Judging from the high living standards in scandinavia and other socialistic democracies).</p>
<p>The USA often brags about their Capitalistic system and success, and one of the many arguments i hear from the extremely conservative branch is “You are communists, we have thousands of products, what do you have?”. Well, first of all the USA isn’t even pure Capitalism (since there’s a few elite companies with way more power than they should have). Secondly, how much choice do you really have? Yeah, you got Dr Pepper, Coca Cola and Pepsi! The only problem here is that they are essentially the same thing, they are produced by the same big ol’ company, so you don’t really have that big and mighty choice you so prompty claim to have!</p>
<p>In a socialistic-democratic environment, Companies are allowed to exist, and are encouraged to thrive, but the essential things such as Healthcare and Education are either owned or funded by the state. (we have both private and public education that is equally good here, and both are free up until uni-level, where you start paying for things such as books and other neccessary materials for your education). Having drugs (Tobacco, Alcohol) government-regulated i feel is a good thing too, to ensure the taxes of these items are incredibly high and to stop oversupply and potential addictions leading to a bad life.</p>
<p>If you are going to work for the system, pay taxes all your life and fund the government, then it’s just fair that they give you the means to do so.</p>
<p>This prevents exploitation (assuming the state isn’t shit), and gives you a social security “web”, that protects you, should something go wrong.</p>
<p>I just woke up, so i have probably missed out on some things i wanted to say here, i think i got most of it down though.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i51.tinypic.com/2iizlfl.jpg" title="2iizlfl.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i51.tinypic.com/2iizlfl.jpg" alt width="428" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2iizlfl.jpg</span><span class="informations">600×700</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/95</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-95</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Haha, yeah. You still do need one I believe for many payments here, but Jobseekers is one of the ones that will pay by Giro. And just by being on JSA you get things like free healthcare, so I guess we do OK.</p>
<p>For all the people that say our socialist system is shitty, at least our homeless people can be disease-free! hehe</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/94</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-94</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Actually, that issue with residency is one of the biggest obstacles (if not the biggest) in Australia too. Our shelters are always operating at full capacity too, and the result is that some people are turned away.<br>
Finally, some shelters only cater to women. This is good, because many women on the streets are there because they’re fleeing domestic violence. But with that being the case, that’s automatically a large list of shelters that any man can not make use of.</p>
<p>I can’t fathom the need for a residential address when it comes to receiving welfare payments; it’s like a kick in the teeth to those who need it most.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/93</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-93</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ah, OK. Well, that would be very useful. I’m not sure we even have anywhere like that near me, though. There’s a few places that will give you some food, if you’re lucky, and a place in the town centre that has residency, but they’re practically always full and give priority to people who are likely to be short term. Which is fair enough, since they’re always full. At least they get to help out some single mum who got kicked out of her home or whatever who will probably have somewhere to stay in a few weeks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/92</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-92</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>IIRC some shelters have residency. Dont get soup kitchen mixed up with shelter.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/91</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-91</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>How do you get a job at said fast food restaurant, with no fixed address?</p>
<p>That is, assuming there is a shelter like that near you, too.</p>
<p>In the UK, homeless people can still claim Jobseekers Allowance without a fixed address by Giro. So that’s £50 give or take a week to spend on bread or whatever (hopefully not booze, though I don’t doubt that it happens). That’s perhaps enough to live a somewhat meager life on, but it isn’t helping you get out of your situation anytime soon.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/90</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-90</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="87" data-topic="366127">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/lothy/40/51_1.png" class="avatar"> Lothy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think anyone who suggests that someone would choose to be poor is a moron. And for the record, most homeless people were homeless before they started taking drugs; they end up doing things such as chroming (paint sniffing) as a coping mechanism.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Im not talking about completely homeless people. Just poor people struggling. And i dont mean they go “hmm im going to be poor when i grow up”. But they’re decisions choose it for them.</p>
<p>[quote=“Mopman, post:88, topic:366127”][quote author=Frell link=topic=462325.msg3388352#msg3388352 date=1288675379]<br>
I sorta wonder how you actually become completely homeless. I used to live near DC and everyone homeless person we saw either had pills in his hand or on the bench next to him or a bottle of alcohol.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>You probably would, too. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>A large percentage of them took the drugs or alcohol up because of the homelessness, and not vice versa. But even for the ones that didn’t, is that not a failure of society to adequately deal with addicts, rather than “just their fault”? At least in some cases? I guess that depends on your outlook.[/quote]<br>
Id go to a shelter and talk to someone about giving me a haircut and a shave and some clean clothes, and then go to a fast food restaurant and apply. That is, if im sober.</p>
<p>[quote=“Lothy, post:87, topic:366127”]And for the record, everyone has thus far overlooked the simple fact that the rich aren’t expected to get off their arse – they can skip out on any real work just by virtue of lucking out.<br>
The best and brightest may never end up dying rich, despite doing their very best. On the flip side of the coin, some talentless hack, like the author of Twilight, writes a slop of shit romance novel which just so happened to appeal to most girls. Instant millionaire, and she’ll never have to work again should she choose not to.[/quote]<br>
True, America is the only place in the world where you can make the largest amounts of money in a matter of hours. Or lose it all…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/89</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-89</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="86" data-topic="366127">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I sorta wonder how you actually become completely homeless. I used to live near DC and everyone homeless person we saw either had pills in his hand or on the bench next to him or a bottle of alcohol.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You probably would, too. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>A large percentage of them took the drugs or alcohol up because of the homelessness, and not vice versa. But even for the ones that didn’t, is that not a failure of society to adequately deal with addicts, rather than “just their fault”? At least in some cases? I guess that depends on your outlook.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/88</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-88</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with Mopman; it’s very hard for homeless people to get out. They struggle to stay clean, which means interviewers for potential jobs write them off. They struggle to remain healthy, mentally and physically.</p>
<p>I think anyone who suggests that someone would choose to be poor is a moron. And for the record, most homeless people were homeless before they started taking drugs; they end up doing things such as chroming (paint sniffing) as a coping mechanism.</p>
<p>And for the record, everyone has thus far overlooked the simple fact that the rich aren’t expected to get off their arse – they can skip out on any real work just by virtue of lucking out.<br>
The best and brightest may never end up dying rich, despite doing their very best. On the flip side of the coin, some talentless hack, like the author of Twilight, writes a slop of shit romance novel which just so happened to appeal to most girls. Instant millionaire, and she’ll never have to work again should she choose not to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/87</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-87</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="85" data-topic="366127">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_1.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>To take it to the extreme, a homeless guy is basically fucked forever, currently.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I sorta wonder how you actually become completely homeless. I used to live near DC and everyone homeless person we saw either had pills in his hand or on the bench next to him or a bottle of alcohol.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="85" data-topic="366127">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_1.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The point I was trying to make (I think, I got lost halfway) is that the system as it is creates a situation where shit happening to people early in life (which may, like me, be out of my control, or I guess might just be some kid who was a delinquent when young but then grew up or whatever) makes it difficult to turn it around, regardless of drive or intelligence or whatever.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I wish i listened to older people when they told me to do good in school. I figured it out a little late but i still have enough time to fix it. Its true though, as you grow the less important your life becomes. You’re first 20 years will make it or break it.</p>
<p>You’ve made me more mad at our own system more than ever. All the holes really fuck it up for the ones who need it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/86</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-86</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thats kinda amusing, I felt bad for posting such a long reply. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>The point I was trying to make (I think, I got lost halfway) is that the system as it is creates a situation where shit happening to people early in life (which may, like me, be out of my control, or I guess might just be some kid who was a delinquent when young but then grew up or whatever) makes it difficult to turn it around, regardless of drive or intelligence or whatever.</p>
<p>To take it to the extreme, a homeless guy is basically fucked forever, currently.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/85</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-85</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Actually, you just reminded me that anything here that is ran by the government isn’t funded for shit. So if you are disabled or sick, you will pretty much stay poor. They wont hand you $20,000 a year at the least, theyll just give you scraps of whats left.</p>
<p>This is where we get mixed with the people who really need help, and the ones that are poor by choice that ruin the system. That, plus the shit funding just makes it worse. No one here ever does anything to deal with the ones who wont get off their asses. Those are the people i’ve been aiming at through this whole thread. The ones who spend welfare on drugs etc. I personally think if you arent sick or disabled you should have to do community service for welfare.</p>
<p>You said you aren’t asking for sympathy, but i still feel bad for posting such a short reply to that story <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/84</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-84</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OK, let’s use myself as an example. I currently cannot work or goto university, because I am sick. I cannot easily claim benefits, because the UK benefit system is not particularly helpful to people with my condition. This doesn’t really affect the argument much, though, because if I was in the US there wouldn’t be any to claim anyway as I understand it. I currently survive purely because of my Dad. He can’t help me much other than give me food and shelter, though, because he’s pretty piss poor himself.</p>
<p>When he left school he did what was expected of people who wanted to go into his profession - he got an apprenticeship at a respectable manufacturing firm, with a 2day release so that he could go to college at the same time. Got his City&amp;Guilds, had the job. Had a kid at 30 (me) and another one at 34. Somewhere around this time he got sick and was off work for a year (give or take a few months).</p>
<p>Couple of years ago, made redundant. Started his own business. Still paying off ridiculous amounts of debt from years ago, though, so he doesn’t have a lot of money.</p>
<p>I struggle to see where either of us have gone wrong. He didn’t have kids young (pretty late, really), didn’t squander money (he’s boring and didn’t party hard even when he was a kid :P). Just unfortunate, both in life circumstances and picking the “wrong” career in the first place (even when he worked, he wasn’t on very much, it’s not a good industry these days).</p>
<p>Don’t get me wrong, I’m not digging for sympathy, but the point is - we are nothing special. There are many, many people who are “poor” for reasons other than being lazy, and it’s incredibly short-sighted to assume otherwise. There’s a fuckton of people who have it a lot lot worse than I do, too. Though I do have to wonder what state my family would be in had we lived in the USA, at least there was some financial support available to my parents when we were younger.</p>
<p>EDIT: I also didn’t mean to imply that my family is poor now. We obviously do alright, I have internets and shit. Me personally, poor as fuck, but the household as whole does OK. We’ve had periods in the past where it has been a lot less certain though.</p>
<p>EDIT2: You also seem to imply that if people “fuck up their life early” by getting a criminal record or dropping out that that should spell doom for the rest of their life. I’m not sure if you meant that though - but if you didn’t, it’s precisely that effect that people take issue with.</p>
<p>Take me, for example - what the fuck do you think I’m gonna do, assuming I can have a life again in the next few years? I could go back to education now, possibly, if my dad can pay for it. If he can’t? I take menial jobs and live poor for the rest of my life. Which I’m not gonna cry about, too much, but would you tell me in 50 years time that I deserve it because I was too lazy to wave the magic wand and fix it? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/83</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 04:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-83</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:81, topic:366127”]You have a ridiculous attitude on why some people are rich and some people are poor.</p>
<p>I’d like to say that perhaps when you have a few more years under your belt you’ll understand, but I assume more of whoever taught you this bullshit will have poured in by then.[/quote]<br>
Give me the background of someone you think would be poor. This is different in all countries. If you’re disabled or sick you have people that will help you. If you dropped out of school, or did bad, or have a criminal record then you’ve screwed up your life before it practically started. And theres still people that can help you. If you did better than average in school but have a poor family, theres a good chance you can get a loan that will let you have a future where you can live comfortably.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="81" data-topic="366127">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_1.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d like to say that perhaps when you have a few more years under your belt you’ll understand</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is probably true, but im on the verge of graduating and i’ve developed this opinion after seeing all the options that are thrown in your face your last 2 years in high school.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/82</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 04:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-82</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You have a ridiculous attitude on why some people are rich and some people are poor.</p>
<p>I’d like to say that perhaps when you have a few more years under your belt you’ll understand, but I assume more of whoever taught you this bullshit will have poured in by then.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127/81</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 04:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-366127-81</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/british-forces-exposed-over-afghan-attacks/366127.rss">British forces exposed over Afghan attacks</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
