<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rune - Planet || NEW || OLD SCHOOL PKING || SPAWN</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-planet-new-old-school-pking-spawn/523776</link>
    <description>[center]


[url=http://www.rune-planet.com]WEBSITE - WEBCLIENT[/url]

[url=http://www.rune-planet.com/rune-planet.jar]DOWNLOADABLE .JAR[/url]


[size=10pt][b]
Starting Off[/b][/size]

When you first log into Rune-Planet, you will be greeted by the custom choose your class interface where players can choose between mage, archer, and warrior. after making their selection players will receive the appropriate starter and find themselves in the home of Draynor, but don&#39;t let this fool you, there are several other home locations on Salacious, the players may decide which one they like best. The shops are conveniently lined outside the bank in Draynor, make sure you check everything out because it all has a purpose.

[size=10pt][b]Training
[/b][/size]
One of the unique features found on Rune-Planet is its&#39; low XP rates, you may dislike how long it is taking to level, but at this rate it allows for players to accomplish there skills and makes skills serve more of a purpose. The nice thing about it is Rune-Planet is all carefully balanced, the low XP rates allows for a wide variety of methods for training in any skill!

[size=10pt][b]Making Money[/b][/size]

Money is challenging to make, but not impossible. Players can make money with a variety of methods such as, skilling,bossing,PvM,PvP, or even just by playing. While playing you will receive 100 Salacious point an hour as well as earn them while training, along with Rune-Planet Points players may earn mystery boxes, skill packages, and spins on the squeal of fortune. From time to time there is also a React mini-game that occasionally offers some really nice prizes.

[size=10pt][b]Summary[/b][/size]

Rune-Planet has all these great features to offer players including many more not mentioned in the guide, there&#39;s frequent content updates to keep the game exciting and challenging. The challenge is not for everyone, but if you enjoy a challenge Rune-Planet is the server for you!


[size=10pt][b]Some Features[/b][/size]

Realistic quality skilling
Difficult custom bosses
A full and exciting map
Perfect PvP
All kinds of gambling
Pets that work
React System
and MUCH more!



[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 01:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-planet-new-old-school-pking-spawn/523776.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rune - Planet || NEW || OLD SCHOOL PKING || SPAWN</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Server_Sniffer Server Sniffer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/server_sniffer">@Server_Sniffer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]</p>
<p><a href="http://www.rune-planet.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">WEBSITE - WEBCLIENT</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.rune-planet.com/rune-planet.jar" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">DOWNLOADABLE .JAR</a></p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Starting Off</span>[/size]</p>
<p>When you first log into Rune-Planet, you will be greeted by the custom choose your class interface where players can choose between mage, archer, and warrior. after making their selection players will receive the appropriate starter and find themselves in the home of Draynor, but don’t let this fool you, there are several other home locations on Salacious, the players may decide which one they like best. The shops are conveniently lined outside the bank in Draynor, make sure you check everything out because it all has a purpose.</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Training<br>
</span>[/size]<br>
One of the unique features found on Rune-Planet is its’ low XP rates, you may dislike how long it is taking to level, but at this rate it allows for players to accomplish there skills and makes skills serve more of a purpose. The nice thing about it is Rune-Planet is all carefully balanced, the low XP rates allows for a wide variety of methods for training in any skill!</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Making Money</span>[/size]</p>
<p>Money is challenging to make, but not impossible. Players can make money with a variety of methods such as, skilling,bossing,PvM,PvP, or even just by playing. While playing you will receive 100 Salacious point an hour as well as earn them while training, along with Rune-Planet Points players may earn mystery boxes, skill packages, and spins on the squeal of fortune. From time to time there is also a React mini-game that occasionally offers some really nice prizes.</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Summary</span>[/size]</p>
<p>Rune-Planet has all these great features to offer players including many more not mentioned in the guide, there’s frequent content updates to keep the game exciting and challenging. The challenge is not for everyone, but if you enjoy a challenge Rune-Planet is the server for you!</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Some Features</span>[/size]</p>
<p>Realistic quality skilling<br>
Difficult custom bosses<br>
A full and exciting map<br>
Perfect PvP<br>
All kinds of gambling<br>
Pets that work<br>
React System<br>
and MUCH more!</p>
<p>[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-planet-new-old-school-pking-spawn/523776/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-planet-new-old-school-pking-spawn/523776/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 01:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-523776-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rune-planet-new-old-school-pking-spawn/523776.rss">Rune - Planet || NEW || OLD SCHOOL PKING || SPAWN</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
