<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Election for 2012</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063</link>
    <description>I believe, that if I were able to vote, I would vote for Romney. For several reasons, too.
First of all, Obama is just a sweet-talker. He sugar coats everything and just makes people believe that what he says is true by the way he says things. I honestly don&#39;t think he&#39;s doing as much as he&#39;s capable of doing in office. He says one thing and then does another, then talks about it claiming he never said that. For instance: On the O&#39;Riley Factor, when Obama was campaigning for President the first time, him and Bill were discussing Capital Gains Tax. For those of you that don&#39;t know what that is, it&#39;s the profit you make from a sale of property of an investment. For example, when some people make money, they sometimes invest in other people, companies, businesses, and or things that, well, can be invested in. What people don&#39;t know is that that is a completely different tax from Capital Income Tax, which is the tax on your income, or how much you earn. So there are taxes on investing and taxes on earning. Anyway, just so you understood. So, when Bill and Obama were discussing Capital Gain Tax, he mentioned raising it. Now most people think, okay, just tax the rich so they pay more. They think they&#39;re taxing their INCOME, not who/what they&#39;re INVESTING in. Anyway, so Bill called him out on it saying. &quot;You&#39;re gonna raise it to 30%?!&quot; and Obama replied, &quot;No, no, I never mentioned raising it to 30%&quot; Implying that was too high of a tax. Now, about a year or so ago, maybe a couple months, he addressed the nation suggesting an increase to a 30% Capital Gain Tax. Now, our current tax percent for Capital Income is 35%, and for Capital Gains, it&#39;s 15%. So if we raised that even more, the risk of investing in other people/things will not be worth it and blahblahblah, small businesses will fail (like they are doing right now) and we will start to become a country run by only large businesses which is bad because private/small businesses help our country with jobs, keeping competition so that there aren&#39;t monopolies, etc. I could go into more detail and such but the point it, he DOESN&#39;T KEEP HIS WORD. and I mean, sure. people change their minds and stuff and that&#39;s okay. The point is that he gets so offended and sure that &quot;No, that&#39;s not going to happen&quot; then just completely turns around and decides the opposite is what worries me. He could just say something like &quot;Oh, we&#39;re unsure right now&quot; and provide more detail, etc. Anyway, this hasn&#39;t just happened once, it&#39;s just a solid example. Okay, wow so secondly.... ObamaCare. I know this is a touchy subject so I&#39;m just gonna say it out, straight. I&#39;m pretty sure it&#39;s violating our constitution, &quot;Distributing the wealth&quot; won&#39;t do anything once he&#39;s spent everyone else&#39;s money, our country can&#39;t afford any more debt, and it IS a problem. The bill is too socialist, I believe we need to be more conservative during this time with other countries going under such as Greece, ObamaCare: sure, it gives out free healthcare to everyone. Great. Who&#39;s money is that coming from? Middle class. And the middle class is being taxed and taken from way too much, soon we&#39;ll have a huge social class gap between wealthy and poor. Also, with ObamaCare, we will have a healthcare system like Canada, and many doctors will quit (my doctor is quitting) now that the government will pay them. (I&#39;m pretty sure that they all get paid the same, not a hundred percent sure, and here&#39;s some information on how our income tax will look now: http://www.smartmoney.com/taxes/inco...1335896160486/ Check it out if you wanna, but in short, Medicare tax will increase on Self-Employment income if you make more than $200,000 a year, for married couple ajoined if you make over $250,000, etc. More on the page, but the main things are that the maximum rate on dividends on long-term gains for people that invest is going to go from 15% to 39.6%! Quoting: &quot;But that&#39;s not all. Also starting in 2013, all or part of the net investment income, including long-term capital gains and dividends, collected by higher-income folks can get socked with an additional 3.8% &quot;Medicare contribution tax.&quot; Therefore, the maximum federal rate on long-term gains for 2013 and beyond will actually be 23.8% (versus the current 15%) and the maximum rate on dividends will be a whopping 43.4% (versus the current 15%). Yikes!&quot; Like. Seriously? People are getting penalized for making money and being successful. Isn&#39;t that the point? The make money, be successful and help other people reach where you got to and GIVE BACK? It&#39;s better to help somebody help themselves rather than just give people money? I&#39;d rather be independent than dependent on the government that is already over a five or six trillion in debt. I think we&#39;ve shown that spending more of what we don&#39;t have doesn&#39;t improve the economy. Okay, and two more things about Obama I know this is getting long. First, why do we separate parties so much and drastically? Like you&#39;re either REPUBLICAN, DEMOCRATIC, or I guess Independent is growing. The lines are so defined that there are stereotypes for each party. Obama is supposed to unite us as a nation, no matter what we believe in. He hasn&#39;t. He&#39;s just split us more apart and pointed out flaws. Lastly, Welfare. Okay, I understand there are people in bad situations that were born into poverty and really need help and are really looking for a job, but the fact of the matter is, I am paying (yes, I have a job) for someone else&#39;s life atm. Some jobs pay less than welfare gives. So why would you want to get a job and have to work when you get paid for doing nothing? Some people think that way. I would just live off welfare if I were in someone like that&#39;s shoes. Welfare was supposed to be a temporary thing. The government&#39;s just extended it for so long that people think that they&#39;re entitled to things now. Also, you get more money the more kids you have. So some people are just having kids when financially they can&#39;t even support themselves! then, those kids are put into poverty just like their parents. It&#39;s a viscous cycle. There are ways to fix this. Honestly, so many freaking opportunities. There are so many organizations that help with these kind of things (Example: I helped out at DRMM an organization in Detroit that give many different kinds of people help such as chronically homeless, abused, addicted, and teen moms shelter. Not just giving them things, but they are strongly encouraged to get an education, they are run on a strict schedule so that they learn to plan their time out, and they are offered religious opportunities) anyway, they have soup kitchens and Feed the hungry organization, blahblah etc. So I mean, Obama isn&#39;t reforming any part of that, he just keeps giving them money so that while we are getting money cut out of our salaries, it&#39;s sometimes going to someone who isn&#39;t doing anything with it. Ahh, just so stupid. And there is a way that could fix it, but more typing and I think I&#39;ve expressed my opinions. Okay, don&#39;t trash me hardcore, I respect your opinions and beliefs.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 15:12:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="36" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lostmyphat/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> lostmyphat:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>tldr; nial is a faggot that makes everyone sound stupid if you don’t have his views</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m sorry, I “make people sound stupid”? they’re quite capable of doing that themselves</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 15:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lostmyphat lostmyphat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lostmyphat">@lostmyphat</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Niall, post:8, topic:455063”]Note to ASDss - the following post will ‘trash you hardcore’ I hope, I spend the time to read your post and write a few somewhat abrasive arguments back, I do this not because I’m a cunt instead I do this because I think some of your thinking is flawed and close mined, I took the time to read and reply to your post and would appreciate it if you do the same</p>
<p>and fair warning I didn’t take the time to make this post polite and don’t expect the same in return, another fair warning I am generalising and do not necessarily mean to generalise, I am doing so for the sake of simplicity in referring to people or groups of people</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Middle class. And the middle class is being taxed and taken from way too much, soon we’ll have a huge social class gap between wealthy and poor.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>AHHAHAHA</p>
<p>no seriously, if you think that there is no income/social/whatever gap between the wealthy and middle class (not even poor) then you are SERIOUSLY DELUSIONAL, there is an extreme income gap between the wealthy and the middle class and the poor get the shit end of the stick in regards to taxes, taxing the rich who can afford to be taxed will result in less tax on the poor and lower middle classes who cannot afford to pay taxes</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Also, with ObamaCare, we will have a healthcare system like Canada, and many doctors will quit (my doctor is quitting) now that the government will pay them. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>it won’t be anything like canada or any other country with a national health system, it will be much less efficient but better than what you have now at least</p>
<p>in 2009 (keep in mind that this is the same policies from bush pretty much) the states paid almost double what a uk and france citizen pays for the same amount of healthcare, let that just sink in for a minute, me being a uk citizen, if I paid taxes (which I do not because I am unemployed) I would pay half of what you would pay and be entitled to the same amount of healthcare</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Like. Seriously? People are getting penalized for making money and being successful. Isn’t that the point? </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>they’re being taxed a fair amount for money they make, we’re not talking about placing a burden on small businesses and entrepreneur here, we’re talking about taxing multi-million dollar companies a fair amount and reinvesting it back into the country, it’s not socialism and it’s not communism it’s called government and it pays for everything you’d consider western culture</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>The make money, be successful and help other people reach where you got to and GIVE BACK? </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>except they don’t “give back”, want to know how mitt romney got rich? by buying companies, firing half the workforce and reducing pay and pensions for workers, does that seem like giving back to you? this is honestly literally how he got rich by the way, buying companies, firing the workers and fucking the rest of the workers over, jobs are outsourced and all additional revenue is NOT spent back into the company</p>
<p>but seriously, do you think mitt romney is giving back to people by hiding money in offshore accounts and investing it to avoid tax? do you think mitt romney is giving back to people when he has stated that releasing his tax returns would hurt him politically? john mccain in 2008 looked at mitt romneys tax returns and he saw something he didn’t like and went with sarah palin instead, do you think mitt romney is giving back to the people when mccain didn’t want him after seeing his taxes?</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>It’s better to help somebody help themselves rather than just give people money?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>yes because healthcare = giving people money</p>
<p>you’re talking about healthcare and now you’ve abruptly changed the topic to talking about welfare, maybe if you were more coherent and knew what a paragraph was you wouldn’t come off like someone who is merely parroting an opinion instead of forming one of his own</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>I’d rather be independent than dependent on the government that is already over a five or six trillion in debt. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well then good for you, maybe you can stop using the internet that the US government funded research for, maybe you can stop using public roads and stop drinking water from a tap, maybe you can kill yourself at 40 because those extra 30+ years of life expectancy are from medical gains funded in part by the government investment and legislation requiring medical companies to pay x back into research and development</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>I think we’ve shown that spending more of what we don’t have doesn’t improve the economy. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>seems to me like funding 2 wars for frivolous reasons doesn’t improve the economy</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>First, why do we separate parties so much and drastically? </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>because a 2 party system benefits everyone except the general public and the big organisations that benefit from a government they can control will pay a LOT of money to do so</p>
<p>and that isn’t a criticism of obama that’s a criticism of politics in the united states, obama has nothing to do with the 2 party system and its flaws</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Obama is supposed to unite us as a nation, no matter what we believe in. He hasn’t. He’s just split us more apart and pointed out flaws. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>because every president before obama united the nation and every president after obama will unite the nation</p>
<p>hint: multiple parties are there to represent the population, the united states political system is broken because of 2 parties who are almost identical but that’s another issue</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Lastly, Welfare. Okay, I understand there are people in bad situations that were born into poverty and really need help and are really looking for a job, but the fact of the matter is, I am paying (yes, I have a job) for someone else’s life atm. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>oh boo hoo you’re paying so the citizens of your country don’t go to absolute shit cry me a fucking river, that military tax you pay is likely going to go  on taking a life if you want some karmic retribution</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Some jobs pay less than welfare gives. So why would you want to get a job and have to work when you get paid for doing nothing? </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>except in that case they aren’t getting “welfare” they are getting several “welfares” for several reasons, the state of welfare in the united states may be in a bad spot but welfare is a necessity in a first would country</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Also, you get more money the more kids you have. So some people are just having kids when financially they can’t even support themselves! then, those kids are put into poverty just like their parents. It’s a viscous cycle. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>how about those people are having kids because people like you and your ilk want to ban abortion and create a social stigma on abortion so they can’t abort those children?</p>
<p>republican logic 101: hurr abortion is wrong lets ban abortion, hurr people are having kids to abuse welfare and not because abortion is illegal</p>
<p>and yes that is seriously how some of you people present yourselves, abortion banned = more children = more republicans cry about welfare families, and I know you aren’t talking about abortion but I’d bet my left testie that you are also against abortion</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>There are ways to fix this. Honestly, so many freaking opportunities. There are so many organizations that help with these kind of things (Example: I helped out at DRMM an organization in Detroit that give many different kinds of people help such as chronically homeless, abused, addicted, and teen moms shelter. </p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and how do you think those shelters are paid for? small organisations and charities help sure but welfare isn’t simply “giving money to the poor”, one thing welfare pays for is fucking food stamps and even little old me who isn’t a us citizen knows this, what, do you think cutting welfare = cutting foods stamps is a good idea?</p>
<p>like I said welfare in the states may be broken but it is an absolute god damn necessity for some people and I don’t think you necessarily appreciate how much so</p>
<p>yes you will get welfare cheats just like you will get people(read:mitt romney) who cheat small businesses by firing workers for personal gain, just because the system is broken doesn’t mean that destroying the system all together is the best idea</p>
<p>EDIT</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Is there anyone in here who likes Obama-/Romneycare?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>it’s definitely not the best solution but I guess it helps a hell of a lot of people, things like no more preexisting conditions and children being covered by their parents plan until age 26 are ridiculous breakthroughs from obamacare[/quote]</p>
<p>tldr; nial is a faggot that makes everyone sound stupid if you don’t have his views</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 05:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“t4, post:34, topic:455063”][quote author=hat trix link=topic=557930.msg4086487#msg4086487 date=1345913590]<br>
In the united states (health-care or not), you can walk into an ER and get seen that day, get surgery within a week, and get billed. If the bill is less then, lets say 2k (minor surgery or tests), they will just threaten to sue you for 7 years then you wont hear from them again (This is from multiple experiences).<br>
[/quote]<br>
you’ll spend a few hours (2-6) in the ER and not receive surgery unless it is an absolute emergency.[/quote]</p>
<p>Also: $2,500 bills for a C.T. scan you never had, $1,000 bills for walking into the Emergency Room Waiting Room area, $25 per seat used in the E.R. Waiting Room, them not doing jack shit unless you walk in carrying your head in your hands, ect. I SURE DO LOVE ME SOME HOSPITAL.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 19:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="26" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 hat trix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In the united states (health-care or not), you can walk into an ER and get seen that day, get surgery within a week, and get billed. If the bill is less then, lets say 2k (minor surgery or tests), they will just threaten to sue you for 7 years then you wont hear from them again (This is from multiple experiences).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you’ll spend a few hours (2-6) in the ER and not receive surgery unless it is an absolute emergency.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 18:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="28" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How good are the doctors in the UK?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>well, they give the same quality of care as americans for half the cost</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="28" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>How good are the doctors in the UK?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Shut up retard. No one gives a damn about your opinions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 10:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="26" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 hat trix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>that sounds like No health-care system I want to live in, Just saying.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="http://rplegalgroup.com/home/personal-injury/medical-malpractice-sc/" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://rplegalgroup.com/home/personal-injury/medical-malpractice-sc/</a></p>
<blockquote>According to the Institute of Medicine, medical errors kill at least 44,000 Americans each year and possibly as many as 98,000 people</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 14:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IcyyEffect IcyyEffect]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/icyyeffect">@IcyyEffect</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Idc… Obama did help people though…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“hat trix, post:26, topic:455063”][quote author=Niall link=topic=557930.msg4084996#msg4084996 date=1345735097]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Here in Canada it isn’t the responsibility of the federal government to provide health care. Health care is ran by the provincial(state) government. This is good because it allows different needs for different regions. For example, living in Ontario, I am given free OHIP (ontario health insurance plan) which covers basically everything except for drugs/dentist (any decent employer will cover the rest). When you walk out of the hospital, you never pay a cent. [/quote]</p>
<p>that’s pretty much how it’s ran in the uk, granted we don’t have states but eh</p>
<p>hospital healthcare is free (to citizens), dentist is free up until 16 or under certain conditions, prescription drugs all cost the same (about $12) and can be free under certain conditions (and if you’re an idiot and want non-generic drugs you can get them too)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>My girlfriend lived in the UK when she was about 14-15. She was put on a 6-12 month waiting list to get her braces fixed. The back brace had broken off and was destroying her inner lip. Her mom had a type of autoimmune liver disease that needed to be treated, but they were in no hurry to help. When they moved back to the united states, they found out that she was nearing stage 3 of 4 for the liver disease, and that It could have been fatal if not treated right away. From their point of view (all 3 of them living there), the healthcare was horrible compared to that of a middle-classed citizen of the united states.</p>
<p>that sounds like No health-care system I want to live in, Just saying.</p>
<p>In the united states (health-care or not), you can walk into an ER and get seen that day, get surgery within a week, and get billed. If the bill is less then, lets say 2k (minor surgery or tests), they will just threaten to sue you for 7 years then you wont hear from them again (This is from multiple experiences).[/quote]</p>
<p>The doctors in the United States made my grandmother live with appendicitis for a week, they told her she just wasn’t feeling well. That’s pretty pathetic for something as common and life threatening as appendicitis, which should be operated on the same day as diagnosis. After daily visits to the hospital they finally considered appendicitis, and by the time they flew her back to Canada her appendix had ruptured. As a result of the incompetent american doctors she had to get many organs and pieces of organs removed. Good thing she was in good hands in Canada. That surgery would have costed an American $700,000</p>
<p>I got appendicitis about a year later (in Canada). I went to the ER and they saw me within an hour, and diagnosed within a couple hours. Scheduled me for immediate surgery until a nurse stole the anesthetics haha. So I had to wait for the morning. That was hell and I cant imagine my grandmother living with that for a week.</p>
<p>My point is, shit happens. Neither of our stories are very representative of the overall healthcare of either country. There is no reasons for the quality to be any different. The only difference is that it’s paid by taxes, and there isn’t some fat cat at the top collecting the profits.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 00:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>How good are the doctors in the UK?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 18:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="26" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 hat trix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My girlfriend lived in the UK when she was about 14-15. She was put on a 6-12 month waiting list to get her braces fixed. The back brace had broken off and was destroying her inner lip. Her mom had a type of autoimmune liver disease that needed to be treated, but they were in no hurry to help. When they moved back to the united states, they found out that she was nearing stage 3 of 4 for the liver disease, and that It could have been fatal if not treated right away. From their point of view (all 3 of them living there), the healthcare was horrible compared to that of a middle-classed citizen of the united states.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>it definitely sucks that they had a bad experience but it is definitely not reflective of the nhs as a hole, and there would definitely have been options and courses of actions available to them when they needed them</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="26" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 hat trix:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In the united states (health-care or not), you can walk into an ER and get seen that day, get surgery within a week, and get billed.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>in the UK you can walk into an ER and get seen the same day(usually within the same hour, and definitely immediately if it’s an emergency), and get surgery within a week</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 18:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hat_trix hat trix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hat_trix">@hat_trix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Niall, post:20, topic:455063”][quote author=jme link=topic=557930.msg4084986#msg4084986 date=1345733934]<br>
Here in Canada it isn’t the responsibility of the federal government to provide health care. Health care is ran by the provincial(state) government. This is good because it allows different needs for different regions. For example, living in Ontario, I am given free OHIP (ontario health insurance plan) which covers basically everything except for drugs/dentist (any decent employer will cover the rest). When you walk out of the hospital, you never pay a cent. [/quote]</p>
<p>that’s pretty much how it’s ran in the uk, granted we don’t have states but eh</p>
<p>hospital healthcare is free (to citizens), dentist is free up until 16 or under certain conditions, prescription drugs all cost the same (about $12) and can be free under certain conditions (and if you’re an idiot and want non-generic drugs you can get them too)[/quote]</p>
<p>My girlfriend lived in the UK when she was about 14-15. She was put on a 6-12 month waiting list to get her braces fixed. The back brace had broken off and was destroying her inner lip. Her mom had a type of autoimmune liver disease that needed to be treated, but they were in no hurry to help. When they moved back to the united states, they found out that she was nearing stage 3 of 4 for the liver disease, and that It could have been fatal if not treated right away. From their point of view (all 3 of them living there), the healthcare was horrible compared to that of a middle-classed citizen of the united states.</p>
<p>that sounds like No health-care system I want to live in, Just saying.</p>
<p>In the united states (health-care or not), you can walk into an ER and get seen that day, get surgery within a week, and get billed. If the bill is less then, lets say 2k (minor surgery or tests), they will just threaten to sue you for 7 years then you wont hear from them again (This is from multiple experiences).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ggallin ggallin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ggallin">@ggallin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>note i wasn’t opposing or contradicting anyone, i was merely giving what i see from my perspective.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 16:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ggallin: I don’t want choices or alternatives. I want the best possible solution for a certain cost, and that the government should allocate enough resources that people get good enough health-care.</p>
<p>State own businesses and organizations should learn from the private, not become private. Because a successful governmental alternative would always be the cheapest alternative for you and me. (No need for giving away the profit)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 16:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="21" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ggallin/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> ggallin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the thing about any kind of government healthcare is that since the government’s paying for it (although you could use taxes to prove otherwise) they get to tell you what to do.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>just because it’s government ran(which doesn’t even need to be the case, the NHS in the UK is only government funded and is ran independently) doesn’t mean that the government has all the control, that’s the biggest load of bunk I’ve heard</p>
<p>it’s also not the case that you get told what to do or stuff it, in the uk for example you can change your GP for any reason at all and as far as I know if you require surgery you can get referred to another surgeon through your GP</p>
<p>of course this will greatly vary by country and the NHS has worked through all the kinks for the past 60 years but ‘free healthcare’ doesn’t automatically mean bad healthcare</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 16:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ggallin, post:21, topic:455063”][quote author=Niall link=topic=557930.msg4084996#msg4084996 date=1345735097]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Here in Canada it isn’t the responsibility of the federal government to provide health care. Health care is ran by the provincial(state) government. This is good because it allows different needs for different regions. For example, living in Ontario, I am given free OHIP (ontario health insurance plan) which covers basically everything except for drugs/dentist (any decent employer will cover the rest). When you walk out of the hospital, you never pay a cent. [/quote]</p>
<p>that’s pretty much how it’s ran in the uk, granted we don’t have states but eh</p>
<p>hospital healthcare is free (to citizens), dentist is free up until 16 or under certain conditions, prescription drugs all cost the same (about $12) and can be free under certain conditions (and if you’re an idiot and want non-generic drugs you can get them too)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>the thing about any kind of government healthcare is that since the government’s paying for it (although you could use taxes to prove otherwise) they get to tell you what to do. Whereas if you pay for insurance, you can actually tell the health provider what you want to do. Granted it’s not much difference, but the doctor/patient care differs. I’d know this because i had a ski accident back in 2003 in jackson hole wyoming which i’ve had to have several surgeries for my back and neck. I’ve seen the difference between medicare and Aetna for example. The differences would mainly be the treatment you receive from doctors, what the doctors are allowed to do, and the hospitals/doctors you can even go to.</p>
<p>So that’s something people need to take into account. The people on medicare are treated very poorly in my opinion.[/quote]</p>
<p>That is bullshit though. I get free health insurance and there is no way for me to lose it, nor am I told what to do. It doesn’t matter what my background is, it doesn’t matter what I was doing to get sick/injured, I am always covered for life, from the day I was born. You need to reform it because it works everywhere else. I’d know too since I’ve also had accidents, surgeries, illness and I am free to choose my doctor and hospital, and the quality is excellent.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 16:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ggallin ggallin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ggallin">@ggallin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Niall, post:20, topic:455063”][quote author=jme link=topic=557930.msg4084986#msg4084986 date=1345733934]<br>
Here in Canada it isn’t the responsibility of the federal government to provide health care. Health care is ran by the provincial(state) government. This is good because it allows different needs for different regions. For example, living in Ontario, I am given free OHIP (ontario health insurance plan) which covers basically everything except for drugs/dentist (any decent employer will cover the rest). When you walk out of the hospital, you never pay a cent. [/quote]</p>
<p>that’s pretty much how it’s ran in the uk, granted we don’t have states but eh</p>
<p>hospital healthcare is free (to citizens), dentist is free up until 16 or under certain conditions, prescription drugs all cost the same (about $12) and can be free under certain conditions (and if you’re an idiot and want non-generic drugs you can get them too)[/quote]<br>
the thing about any kind of government healthcare is that since the government’s paying for it (although you could use taxes to prove otherwise) they get to tell you what to do. Whereas if you pay for insurance, you can actually tell the health provider what you want to do. Granted it’s not much difference, but the doctor/patient care differs. I’d know this because i had a ski accident back in 2003 in jackson hole wyoming which i’ve had to have several surgeries for my back and neck. I’ve seen the difference between medicare and Aetna for example. The differences would mainly be the treatment you receive from doctors, what the doctors are allowed to do, and the hospitals/doctors you can even go to.</p>
<p>So that’s something people need to take into account. The people on medicare are treated very poorly in my opinion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 15:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/jme/40/55_1.png" class="avatar"> jme:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Here in Canada it isn’t the responsibility of the federal government to provide health care. Health care is ran by the provincial(state) government. This is good because it allows different needs for different regions. For example, living in Ontario, I am given free OHIP (ontario health insurance plan) which covers basically everything except for drugs/dentist (any decent employer will cover the rest). When you walk out of the hospital, you never pay a cent.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>that’s pretty much how it’s ran in the uk, granted we don’t have states but eh</p>
<p>hospital healthcare is free (to citizens), dentist is free up until 16 or under certain conditions, prescription drugs all cost the same (about $12) and can be free under certain conditions (and if you’re an idiot and want non-generic drugs you can get them too)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 15:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here in Canada it isn’t the responsibility of the federal government to provide health care. Health care is ran by the provincial(state) government. This is good because it allows different needs for different regions. For example, living in Ontario, I am given free OHIP (ontario health insurance plan) which covers basically everything except for drugs/dentist (any decent employer will cover the rest). When you walk out of the hospital, you never pay a cent.</p>
<p>So in my opinion, in the USA federal elections, it shouldn’t be up to Obama, or Romney, or the federal government to provide free healthcare. This should be a state matter.</p>
<p>USA should look to Canada for a health care model, as we are definitely the most similar country, and our health care system DOES work, and people are NOT complaining. Even our strong conservatives take pride in our free health care and they’re not whining about socialism on this issue.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 14:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Loveandpower, post:11, topic:455063”]Obamacare REQUIRES that everyone has healthcare. How is a  homeless person supposed to get that? hmm?  How is a person  who  is  making 7.50$ an hour supposed to afford that, plus car insurance, plus utilities. YOU CANT.</p>
<p>Romney Care can so smd as well. Romney claims that “the poor has a safety net” that is total bologna. I have been homeless before, and let me tell you there is no no bottom net. It’s pretty sad when homeless people already get declined for food stamps / etc[/quote]<br>
not to mention the government gets to tell you and the doctors what you can do about your health instead of you paying an insurance company who is there to server you a public service is now giving you something for free and you have to abide by their terms.<br>
[/quote]I didn’t know that :s</p>
<p>Is that with Obama or Romney?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 22:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ggallin, post:15, topic:455063”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=557930.msg4082663#msg4082663 date=1345500491]<br>
ggallin: So you’re communist, congratulations.<br>
[/quote]<br>
uhm… i dont think that’s what i meant. but whatever :)[/quote]<br>
If you don’t know what your stand point is, please just don’t speak.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 22:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ggallin, post:15, topic:455063”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=557930.msg4082663#msg4082663 date=1345500491]<br>
ggallin: So you’re communist, congratulations.<br>
[/quote]<br>
uhm… i dont think that’s what i meant. but whatever :)[/quote]<br>
Be clear in what you are saying.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 22:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ggallin ggallin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ggallin">@ggallin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="14" data-topic="455063">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>ggallin: So you’re communist, congratulations.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>uhm… i dont think that’s what i meant. but whatever <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 22:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ggallin: So you’re communist, congratulations.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 22:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Election for 2012</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ggallin ggallin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ggallin">@ggallin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Niall, post:12, topic:455063”][quote author=ggallin link=topic=557930.msg4082223#msg4082223 date=1345477857]</p>
<p>[quote]com·mu·nism<br>
noun /ˈkämyəˌnizəm/<br>
A political theory derived from Karl Marx, advocating class war and leading to a society in which all property is publicly owned and each person works and is paid according to their abilities and needs</p>
<p>Web definitions<br>
a form of socialism that abolishes private ownership</p>
<p>a political theory favoring collectivism in a classless society<br>
wordnetweb.princeton.edu/perl/webwn[/quote]<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>yes we know what communism means what is your point[/quote]</p>
<p>[quote=“Loveandpower, post:11, topic:455063”]Obamacare REQUIRES that everyone has healthcare. How is a  homeless person supposed to get that? hmm?  How is a person  who  is  making 7.50$ an hour supposed to afford that, plus car insurance, plus utilities. YOU CANT.</p>
<p>Romney Care can so smd as well. Romney claims that “the poor has a safety net” that is total bologna. I have been homeless before, and let me tell you there is no no bottom net. It’s pretty sad when homeless people already get declined for food stamps / etc[/quote]<br>
not to mention the government gets to tell you and the doctors what you can do about your health instead of you paying an insurance company who is there to server you a public service is now giving you something for free and you have to abide by their terms.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 22:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-455063-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/election-for-2012/455063.rss">Election for 2012</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
