<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Space Wars</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/space-wars/55460</link>
    <description>   One day while Captain Hoolaw was starting up his engine he heard a loud gunshot in the distant. Withdrawing his B94G Pistol and went to go check out what was happening.
&quot;A bank robbery.&quot; Said Captain Hoolaw. &quot;BOOM!&quot; Another gunshot. Captain Hoolaw found one of the robbers shooting  one of the police officers. &quot;Time to have some fun!&quot; Boasted Captain Hoolaw. &quot;BOOM!&quot; &quot;BOOM!&quot; &quot;BOOM!&quot; Captain Hoolaw Sneered at the robber he shot.
    It was only three hours ago when Captain Hoolaw had shot the robber and was now being paid. &quot;You gonna buy &#39;em new engines Hoolaw?&quot; Said Officer Kenny. &quot;Aye, might think &#39;bout it.&quot; Said Captain Hoolaw. &quot;Hey Hoolaw heard there was a huge &quot;Space Race.&quot;
in sector V. You going?&quot; Said Carl. &quot;Wow, a &quot;Space Race.&quot; i heard only &quot;L33T&quot; pilots were aloud.&quot;
    &quot;I can&#39;t believe they talked me into it.&quot; Muttered Captain Hoolaw. &quot;Ye know... There is a big reward on this right Hoolaw?&quot; Said His assistant Aaron. &quot;Don&#39;t go gettin&#39; any funny ideas!&quot; Snapped Captain Hoolaw. &quot;Okay okay okay... Geez i dun get ideas Hoot. heck, i harly know how t&#39; talk.&quot; Said Aaron. &quot;Oh in that case I&#39;ll put you in school.&quot; Mocked Captain Hoolaw. &quot;Okay! I&#39;ll shut up Kay?&quot; Said Aaron. &quot;You learn fast lad.&quot; Said Captain Hoolaw. &quot;I know you know that i hate being called &quot;Lad.&quot;!&quot; Yelled Aaron.
    &quot;Racers! Listen up! Follow me and you might not die during this race.&quot; Said the wife of the man who started the &quot;Space Race.&quot;. As the lady kept on repeating on how to survive the &quot;Space Race.&quot; Aaron Muttered. &quot;Does she ever shut up?&quot; &quot;I don&#39;t think so, she just wants to look good maybe.&quot; Whispered Captain Hoolaw. As Aaron kept on giggling while the lady kept on talking when she finally finished and when the racers were in their space ships Captain Hoolaw and Aaron laughed furiously.
    &quot;Racers! Start!-Your!-Engine!&quot; The Annoucer Yelled through the microphone.
&quot;VROOM!&quot; &quot;VROOM!!!!&quot; VROOOOOOM!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&quot; When all the ships started Captain Hoolaw wrote down for Aaron &quot;This is loud enuf 2 wake the ded!!&quot; Aaron wrote back
&quot;i bet the def can heer it 2&quot; Once all the engines died down they laughed and talked finally.
&quot;3!.............2!..............1!-GO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&quot; And they were off taking third place right away.
    &quot;Aaron start the boosters NOW!&quot; Yelled Captain Hoolaw. &quot;I&#39;m on it!&quot; Aaron yelled back.
Franticly Aaron searched for the &quot;Boosters&quot; &quot;Grr!&quot; Aaron growled &quot;I&#39;ll just do it manually&quot;
Aaron raced off the the manual gauge. But then he remembered he set it to remote control that was in his pocket he hit the button and fell back and hit the ground hard.
&quot;AARON!! YOU DID IT YOU GOT US FROM SIXTEENTH TO FIRST! WAY TO GO BUDDY!&quot; Captain Hoolaw yelled happily. Aaron raced off to his station and prepared for the living nightmare he was about to face.
    It was two days later Aaron was sleeping when he was awakened by a large shake
&quot;Wh-wh-what was that?&quot; Aaron said yawning. But then he heard groaning, Aaron was scared but he went to go check it out anyways &quot;Hooter? You there Hooter?&quot;
&quot;Oh my god, my leg! My leg! Aaron get over here&quot; Captain Hoolaw said. Aaron saw how scared Hooter was by his voice. &quot;Dude! What&#39;d you do!?&quot; Aaron was now panicking.
&quot;Shh! I think they&#39;re back onboard.&quot; Whispered Captain Hoolaw &quot;Who the crap did this to 
 you!? I&#39;m gonna kill &#39;em!&quot; Aaron was now mad. Aaron picked up Captain Hoolaws B94G
and went off to go see who was boarding their ship.
    Aaron saw a ship parked by their ship, this made him worry &quot;Hey boss i think i found one of &#39;em&quot; Said one of the men that had boarded the ship. &quot;Then kill them you idiot!&quot;
Said one of them. Thats probably their boss. Aaron thought. Aaron withdrew the pistol and opened fire on their boss. &quot;Holy crap! Take cover! Oh my god! They found us get your idiotic butts over here! Gah! I&#39;m hit! God dangit!&quot; Yelled their boss. Aaron was hit.
He swore at them and kept on firing.
    Captain Hoolaw heard gunshots. He picked up his assault rife and went to go help Aaron. He heard someone swear at someone. &quot;Sounds like Aaron&#39;s having fun&quot; Muttered Captain Hoolaw. He took aim and looked around and saw one person taken cover and three silhouettes shooting at Aaron. He took aim and fired. &quot;BAM!&quot; &quot;BOOM!&quot; &quot;BAM!&quot; He got all three of them.
    &quot;God, my leg still hurts.&quot; Said Captain Hoolaw. &quot;Not as much as my shoulder.&quot;
Said Aaron sadly. &quot;What&#39;d the police do to &#39;em?&quot; Asked Aaron. &quot;Hung &#39;em.&quot; Captain Hoolaw was not in a mood for questions. &quot;Okay.&quot; Aaron Muttered. &quot;They have allies, i bet they&#39;ll come after us since they&#39;re dead now.&quot; Muttered Captain Hoolaw. But they did not know this was only the beginning.
Will finish Later  ;D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2007 08:28:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/space-wars/55460.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Space Wars</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chipmunk_man chipmunk man]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chipmunk_man">@chipmunk_man</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>One day while Captain Hoolaw was starting up his engine he heard a loud gunshot in the distant. Withdrawing his B94G Pistol and went to go check out what was happening.<br>
“A bank robbery.” Said Captain Hoolaw. “BOOM!” Another gunshot. Captain Hoolaw found one of the robbers shooting  one of the police officers. “Time to have some fun!” Boasted Captain Hoolaw. “BOOM!” “BOOM!” “BOOM!” Captain Hoolaw Sneered at the robber he shot.<br>
It was only three hours ago when Captain Hoolaw had shot the robber and was now being paid. “You gonna buy 'em new engines Hoolaw?” Said Officer Kenny. “Aye, might think 'bout it.” Said Captain Hoolaw. “Hey Hoolaw heard there was a huge “Space Race.”<br>
in sector V. You going?” Said Carl. “Wow, a “Space Race.” i heard only “L33T” pilots were aloud.”<br>
“I can’t believe they talked me into it.” Muttered Captain Hoolaw. “Ye know… There is a big reward on this right Hoolaw?” Said His assistant Aaron. “Don’t go gettin’ any funny ideas!” Snapped Captain Hoolaw. “Okay okay okay… Geez i dun get ideas Hoot. heck, i harly know how t’ talk.” Said Aaron. “Oh in that case I’ll put you in school.” Mocked Captain Hoolaw. “Okay! I’ll shut up Kay?” Said Aaron. “You learn fast lad.” Said Captain Hoolaw. “I know you know that i hate being called “Lad.”!” Yelled Aaron.<br>
“Racers! Listen up! Follow me and you might not die during this race.” Said the wife of the man who started the “Space Race.”. As the lady kept on repeating on how to survive the “Space Race.” Aaron Muttered. “Does she ever shut up?” “I don’t think so, she just wants to look good maybe.” Whispered Captain Hoolaw. As Aaron kept on giggling while the lady kept on talking when she finally finished and when the racers were in their space ships Captain Hoolaw and Aaron laughed furiously.<br>
“Racers! Start!-Your!-Engine!” The Annoucer Yelled through the microphone.<br>
“VROOM!” “VROOM!!!” VROOOOOOM!!!" When all the ships started Captain Hoolaw wrote down for Aaron “This is loud enuf 2 wake the ded!!” Aaron wrote back<br>
“i bet the def can heer it 2” Once all the engines died down they laughed and talked finally.<br>
“3!..2!..1!-GO!!!” And they were off taking third place right away.<br>
“Aaron start the boosters NOW!” Yelled Captain Hoolaw. “I’m on it!” Aaron yelled back.<br>
Franticly Aaron searched for the “Boosters” “Grr!” Aaron growled “I’ll just do it manually”<br>
Aaron raced off the the manual gauge. But then he remembered he set it to remote control that was in his pocket he hit the button and fell back and hit the ground hard.<br>
“AARON!! YOU DID IT YOU GOT US FROM SIXTEENTH TO FIRST! WAY TO GO BUDDY!” Captain Hoolaw yelled happily. Aaron raced off to his station and prepared for the living nightmare he was about to face.<br>
It was two days later Aaron was sleeping when he was awakened by a large shake<br>
“Wh-wh-what was that?” Aaron said yawning. But then he heard groaning, Aaron was scared but he went to go check it out anyways “Hooter? You there Hooter?”<br>
“Oh my god, my leg! My leg! Aaron get over here” Captain Hoolaw said. Aaron saw how scared Hooter was by his voice. “Dude! What’d you do!?” Aaron was now panicking.<br>
“Shh! I think they’re back onboard.” Whispered Captain Hoolaw “Who the crap did this to<br>
you!? I’m gonna kill 'em!” Aaron was now mad. Aaron picked up Captain Hoolaws B94G<br>
and went off to go see who was boarding their ship.<br>
Aaron saw a ship parked by their ship, this made him worry “Hey boss i think i found one of 'em” Said one of the men that had boarded the ship. “Then kill them you idiot!”<br>
Said one of them. Thats probably their boss. Aaron thought. Aaron withdrew the pistol and opened fire on their boss. “Holy crap! Take cover! Oh my god! They found us get your idiotic butts over here! Gah! I’m hit! God dangit!” Yelled their boss. Aaron was hit.<br>
He swore at them and kept on firing.<br>
Captain Hoolaw heard gunshots. He picked up his assault rife and went to go help Aaron. He heard someone swear at someone. “Sounds like Aaron’s having fun” Muttered Captain Hoolaw. He took aim and looked around and saw one person taken cover and three silhouettes shooting at Aaron. He took aim and fired. “BAM!” “BOOM!” “BAM!” He got all three of them.<br>
“God, my leg still hurts.” Said Captain Hoolaw. “Not as much as my shoulder.”<br>
Said Aaron sadly. “What’d the police do to 'em?” Asked Aaron. “Hung 'em.” Captain Hoolaw was not in a mood for questions. “Okay.” Aaron Muttered. “They have allies, i bet they’ll come after us since they’re dead now.” Muttered Captain Hoolaw. But they did not know this was only the beginning.<br>
Will finish Later  ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/space-wars/55460/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/space-wars/55460/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2007 08:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-55460-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/space-wars/55460.rss">Space Wars</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
