<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Finch Head Color Affects Mating Outcome</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/finch-head-color-affects-mating-outcome/268872</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;[b]March 20, 2009[/b] -- Female finches from Northern Australia are controlling the sex of their offspring, according to the hair color of their male counterpart.

The finding, published today in the journal Science, is one of the first to clearly show that birds are capable of biasing the sex of their offspring to overcome genetic weaknesses.

Lead author Sarah Pryke, of the Department of Brain Behavior and Evolution at Macquarie University in Sydney, admits the mechanism by which the birds do this is not yet known.

The endangered Gouldian finch (Erythrura gouldiae), which is found in the northern savanna&#39;s of Australia, can have either black or red heads.

Pryke said some genetic incompatibility between the black and red-headed birds results in high mortality in the offspring when birds of different head colors mate.

With female offspring this mortality rate can be as much as 80 percent higher than in a same-head color pairing. Sons in a mixed pairing have a 40 percent mortality rate.

Pryke found that if the female mates with a finch of different head color, she attempts to overcome this genetic incompatability by over-producing sons -- as many as four males to one female.

&quot;This is the first time such a large effect has been shown,&quot; said Pryke. &quot;It is actually the female that is controlling the gender.&quot;

To reach this conclusion Pryke and colleague Simon Griffith took 100 red-headed and 100 black-headed female birds and mated them with a male of the same head color and a male with the different head color.

They found females in mixed pairs produced broods that were 82.1 percent male, whereas females in matched pairs produced an unbiased sex ratio with 45.9 percent males.

They then tested whether the females in mixed pairs were deliberately over-producing sons.

Female birds were tricked into thinking they were mating with an incompatible male.

The researchers did this by temporarily blackening the head color of red males and mating them with red and black-headed females.

The black females paired to red males with blackened heads produced a sex ratio that was roughly equal.

By contrast red females paired with red males that had blackened heads over-produced sons at a ratio similar to a mixed pairing. Pryke said there is no chemical or genetic interaction between the parents at work.

&quot;Gouldian finches wear their genes on their head so it is easy for a female to assess the genetic suitability of the male,&quot; she said.

&quot;Change the color of the male&#39;s head with dye and the sex ratio changes.&quot;

Through the study the researchers also found that females from mixed pairs produced fewer and smaller eggs.

Pryke said the finding is important because up to 30 percent of breeding pairs in the wild are mixed &quot;perhaps because of constraints on preferred mate availability.&quot;

Ben Sheldon, director of the University of Oxford&#39;s Edward Grey Institute of Field Ornithology, said the results demonstrate &quot;hitherto unsuspected degrees of control over reproductive investment by female birds.&quot;

&quot;This work opens new possibilities in unraveling the mechanisms behind these striking behaviors, something which has up to now remained an unsolved mystery,&quot; he said.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
sauce: http://dsc.discovery.com/news/2009/03/20/finch-color-mate.html

Quite interesting.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 12:08:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/finch-head-color-affects-mating-outcome/268872.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Finch Head Color Affects Mating Outcome</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uriko Uriko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uriko">@Uriko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>[b]March 20, 2009[/b] -- Female finches from Northern Australia are controlling the sex of their offspring, according to the hair color of their male counterpart.
<p>The finding, published today in the journal Science, is one of the first to clearly show that birds are capable of biasing the sex of their offspring to overcome genetic weaknesses.</p>
<p>Lead author Sarah Pryke, of the Department of Brain Behavior and Evolution at Macquarie University in Sydney, admits the mechanism by which the birds do this is not yet known.</p>
<p>The endangered Gouldian finch (Erythrura gouldiae), which is found in the northern savanna’s of Australia, can have either black or red heads.</p>
<p>Pryke said some genetic incompatibility between the black and red-headed birds results in high mortality in the offspring when birds of different head colors mate.</p>
<p>With female offspring this mortality rate can be as much as 80 percent higher than in a same-head color pairing. Sons in a mixed pairing have a 40 percent mortality rate.</p>
<p>Pryke found that if the female mates with a finch of different head color, she attempts to overcome this genetic incompatability by over-producing sons – as many as four males to one female.</p>
<p>“This is the first time such a large effect has been shown,” said Pryke. “It is actually the female that is controlling the gender.”</p>
<p>To reach this conclusion Pryke and colleague Simon Griffith took 100 red-headed and 100 black-headed female birds and mated them with a male of the same head color and a male with the different head color.</p>
<p>They found females in mixed pairs produced broods that were 82.1 percent male, whereas females in matched pairs produced an unbiased sex ratio with 45.9 percent males.</p>
<p>They then tested whether the females in mixed pairs were deliberately over-producing sons.</p>
<p>Female birds were tricked into thinking they were mating with an incompatible male.</p>
<p>The researchers did this by temporarily blackening the head color of red males and mating them with red and black-headed females.</p>
<p>The black females paired to red males with blackened heads produced a sex ratio that was roughly equal.</p>
<p>By contrast red females paired with red males that had blackened heads over-produced sons at a ratio similar to a mixed pairing. Pryke said there is no chemical or genetic interaction between the parents at work.</p>
<p>“Gouldian finches wear their genes on their head so it is easy for a female to assess the genetic suitability of the male,” she said.</p>
<p>“Change the color of the male’s head with dye and the sex ratio changes.”</p>
<p>Through the study the researchers also found that females from mixed pairs produced fewer and smaller eggs.</p>
<p>Pryke said the finding is important because up to 30 percent of breeding pairs in the wild are mixed “perhaps because of constraints on preferred mate availability.”</p>
<p>Ben Sheldon, director of the University of Oxford’s Edward Grey Institute of Field Ornithology, said the results demonstrate “hitherto unsuspected degrees of control over reproductive investment by female birds.”</p>
<p>“This work opens new possibilities in unraveling the mechanisms behind these striking behaviors, something which has up to now remained an unsolved mystery,” he said.</p>
</blockquote><br>
sauce: <a href="http://dsc.discovery.com/news/2009/03/20/finch-color-mate.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://dsc.discovery.com/news/2009/03/20/finch-color-mate.html</a>
<p>Quite interesting.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/finch-head-color-affects-mating-outcome/268872/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/finch-head-color-affects-mating-outcome/268872/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 12:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-268872-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/finch-head-color-affects-mating-outcome/268872.rss">Finch Head Color Affects Mating Outcome</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
