<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problem with all my source codes! need help please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-all-my-source-codes-need-help-please/350345</link>
    <description>i have a problem with all the source codes i try to use through moparscape...i delete hybridscape and then replace it with the source. the one i am using at the moment is mithscape. every time i try to run a compiler or anything else it says &quot;cannot find specified path&quot; or something like that....and the other thing i wanted to know is how i can play the server over LAN therefore having to have no internet connection because i am at boarding school and port 43594 is blocked so we are un-able to play online... so yeh if you can help thats a big THANKS</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 13:33:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-all-my-source-codes-need-help-please/350345.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problem with all my source codes! need help please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whatup722 whatup722]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whatup722">@whatup722</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i have a problem with all the source codes i try to use through moparscape…i delete hybridscape and then replace it with the source. the one i am using at the moment is mithscape. every time i try to run a compiler or anything else it says “cannot find specified path” or something like that…and the other thing i wanted to know is how i can play the server over LAN therefore having to have no internet connection because i am at boarding school and port 43594 is blocked so we are un-able to play online… so yeh if you can help thats a big THANKS</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-all-my-source-codes-need-help-please/350345/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-all-my-source-codes-need-help-please/350345/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 13:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-350345-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-with-all-my-source-codes-need-help-please/350345.rss">Problem with all my source codes! need help please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
