<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Thin clients</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thin-clients/376113</link>
    <description>Has anyone ever worked with something like this?  I can&#39;t use a true thin-client like LTSP because the network connection from this (ancient, and under-powered) laptop is wireless.  So I was thinking about a minimal install of debian, or maybe even arch or something, with only wireless drivers and a X server installed.  Then I can log into my desktop and do work.  VNC is an option, so is XDMCP, also Xnest over ssh.  Does anyone know any other options or have any suggestions in regards to this?  I would also like to have sound, which I don&#39;t think any of the options I listed would give me, but it&#39;s not a deal-breaker.

Does anyone know any nice tools to manage linux wireless connections via the command line?  Otherwise I&#39;ll probably write some scripts that run on boot to scan for known wireless networks to connect to.  I don&#39;t know how or if I can easily handle arbitrary networks, like those at coffee shops or houses I don&#39;t visit often.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 18:32:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thin-clients/376113.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Thin clients</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Has anyone ever worked with something like this?  I can’t use a true thin-client like LTSP because the network connection from this (ancient, and under-powered) laptop is wireless.  So I was thinking about a minimal install of debian, or maybe even arch or something, with only wireless drivers and a X server installed.  Then I can log into my desktop and do work.  VNC is an option, so is XDMCP, also Xnest over ssh.  Does anyone know any other options or have any suggestions in regards to this?  I would also like to have sound, which I don’t think any of the options I listed would give me, but it’s not a deal-breaker.</p>
<p>Does anyone know any nice tools to manage linux wireless connections via the command line?  Otherwise I’ll probably write some scripts that run on boot to scan for known wireless networks to connect to.  I don’t know how or if I can easily handle arbitrary networks, like those at coffee shops or houses I don’t visit often.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thin-clients/376113/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thin-clients/376113/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 18:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-376113-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/thin-clients/376113.rss">Thin clients</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
