<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450</link>
    <description>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T0abS0IdQtA

i literally fell out of my chair with the whole plates thing.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 22:31:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you’re not derailing it, we can bash anyone - mainstream republicans, unfortunately, say/do the darndest things (especially in the current GOP primaries).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 22:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="28" data-topic="436450">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 veer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]And command economy is more fitted to do it, when it has the necessary information and doesn’t take risks.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How do you plan for a bureaucracy to have the necessary information? That’s the whole point of markets i.e. decentralized approach to efficient resource allocation. You don’t face the problem of ~200 government workers trying to aggregate and interpret all the information of the populus; instead, the market price mechanism effectively solves this issue autonomically. However, pragmatically, there arise some issues which result in the contemporary use of collective bargaining and decentralized economic planning.[/quote]<br>
The bureaucracy already have the system to gather necessary information. Each store registers how much is bought of each item, so we have a measure of the consume. As a government owned store would have no competition, so it would have a stable consume, and the numbers could be trusted. And the Bureau of Statistics would know at any time how many people are living in each place, so any change in population could be adjusted for.</p>
<p>The real positive sides with a more planned economy is that you could easily persuade people to take more healthy choices by lowering the price on healthy food, and it would be in the government’s interest to keep products with poor quality out of the marked.  You don’t need to close a store that is not profitable, if it serve an important service to people in small places. In some places you would need less stores, as many stores are built close to each other without it serving a real need.</p>
<p>Anyway we have a too big consume in most countries in the western world, US’ ecological footprint is four times too high and need to be lowered. The free marked would NEVER try to reduce or consume.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">I feel I’m derailing this topic too far, so should we try to just bash republicans, and not the whole system? </span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 21:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@slavemaster veer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slavemaster">@slavemaster</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>And command economy is more fitted to do it, when it has the necessary information and doesn't take risks.</blockquote>
How do you plan for a bureaucracy to have the necessary information? That's the whole point of markets i.e. decentralized approach to efficient resource allocation. You don't face the problem of ~200 government workers trying to aggregate and interpret all the information of the populus; instead, the market price mechanism effectively solves this issue autonomically. However, pragmatically, there arise some issues which result in the contemporary use of collective bargaining and decentralized economic planning.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 18:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="25" data-topic="436450">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 R.I.P RSC:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I wouldn’t call the USSR a successful country. Looking at today’s unified Germany, it’s the East that still lacks behind the West. The former DDR is still a poor part of Germany, and a lot of the people there move to the west. And if you look at the video’s from 1989, you’ll see that everyone is happy they can go to the west. I doubt they were happy because they could spread their ideology or tell about their great Motherland.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Maybe people were happy in 1989, but this tell another story.<br>
<a href="http://mltoday.com/subject-areas/social-and-economic-conditions/life-was-better-under-socialism-say-eastern-germans-982.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://mltoday.com/subject-areas/social-and-economic-conditions/life-was-better-under-socialism-say-eastern-germans-982.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 16:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Radeon, post:20, topic:436450”]Ron Paul is a republican? He’s pretty much the best candidate. imo he’s the only chance America has to survive as a super power. If America doesn’t tone down its international efforts like the British empire did, it won’t last.[/quote]History repeats itself…  Good thing we teach it improperly to our youngin’s</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 16:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="23" data-topic="436450">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Authoritarian Socialism (USSR socialism) had its flaws, but on many fields it worked, we just need to remove the bad apples. It made Russia a super power and people were better off in East-Germany than modern Germany, without being a slave to big corporations. <span class="bbcode-b">As long as you didn’t complain or try to flee.</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So instead of being a slave to big corporations, you’ll be a slave to the government?</p>
<p>I wouldn’t call the USSR a successful country. Looking at today’s unified Germany, it’s the East that still lacks behind the West. The former DDR is still a poor part of Germany, and a lot of the people there move to the west. And if you look at the video’s from 1989, you’ll see that everyone is happy they can go to the west. I doubt they were happy because they could spread their ideology or tell about their great Motherland.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="20" data-topic="436450">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Radeon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ron Paul is a republican? He’s pretty much the best candidate. imo he’s the only chance America has to survive as a super power. If America doesn’t tone down its international efforts like the British empire did, it won’t last.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Funny. The British empire toned down its international efforts right as it lost the status.</p>
<p>I do agree though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 21:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="21" data-topic="436450">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 R.I.P RSC:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What do you see as the best system? Socialism? Communism? In theory these systems are great, but theory and practice are two different things. You need a hint of Socialism, but too much of it leaves a nasty taste.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Authoritarian Socialism (USSR socialism) had its flaws, but on many fields it worked, we just need to remove the bad apples. It made Russia a super power and people were better off in East-Germany than modern Germany, without being a slave to big corporations. As long as you didn’t complain or try to flee.</p>
<p>You say that theory and practice are different. Do you claim that the theory is wrong, or just hard to implement? I would say the later, and we just need to find the right way, even if that means trial and error.</p>
<p>I would not dictate exactly what the best system is, but abolishing private property is a great step in the right direction to equality.</p>
<blockquote>why are we using liberal as synonymous with liberalist - is that commonplace in other countries, because here they would mean very different things?</blockquote>
Excuse me for using the term Liberal incorrect, it just make sense for me that liberals support liberalism. If I were to translate the term we use in Norway, it would be "bourgeois", but that would include to many ideologies.
<blockquote>I don't know what problems you are talking about, but they aren't completely the fault of Liberalism. Looking at the Middle East, Liberalism is exactly the solution for their problems. A completely unregulated economy is wrong, but not every flavour of Liberalism preaches a free market.</blockquote>
I'm not saying the problem is liberalism in middle-east (Many of them have in fact a Arabic flavour of socialism). But the western world's liberalism, where we exploit workers in China and India in the name of profits. We are not able to provide decent healthcare for everyone, inhumane immigration politics, non-effective criminal care, an unstable economy, and a lot of poor people because they were unfortunate or we needed them to do the worst paid labour.
<p>The reason I think a flavour of Socialism can solve all of this is simple.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Removing greed from the system, and destroying the consumer culture would eliminate the reason for exploiting workers in other countries. We can afford to pay them a liveable wage.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>With everything in governmental control, we could have a much more effective economy and we would have no problem paying for health care.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>2b. I believe that cooperation, not competition is most effective for desired results. If the content of this article is correct: <a href="http://www.charleswarner.us/articles/competit.htm" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.charleswarner.us/articles/competit.htm</a>, then my view has also scientific evidence.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<p>If kill egoism, we would not deny people who need it to live in our country.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If everyone has what they need, nobody would become criminals because they fell outside society or doesn’t get what they need.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If the economy is under control and we abolish the credit economy we would have a much more stable economy without crisis because of some retards.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>5b. Command economy has its problem when it comes to production, but that that also applies to capitalism. And command economy is more fitted to do it, when it has the necessary information and doesn’t take risks.</p>
<ol start="6">
<li>
<p>If everyone get the same decent living standard, we wouldn’t have poor or rich.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I do not say we should let leachers leach, I would say that healthy people who deny working should get the same privileges that the rest of us.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>A last thing, I ask you how much socialism you can accept, and still call it liberal? For instance I would not include social democrats in that definition.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 20:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>why are we using liberal as synonymous with liberalist - is that commonplace in other countries, because here they would mean very different things?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="16" data-topic="436450">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>R.I.P RSC: Equal rights/possibilities and individual liberty does not go hand in hand, if you want equal rights/possibilities we need to limit the individual liberty and vice versa.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t see how they don’t go together. As long as people adhere to a basic set of rules, a Liberal society is capable of existing without any struggle. Add more complexity, and you add more laws. I’m not talking about a Utopian society here, where everyone is completely free. That would be impossible.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="16" data-topic="436450">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe I shouldn’t call all liberals stupid, ignorant would be a better word. It can’t fix anything, or else we wouldn’t have any problems in our liberal world.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t know what problems you are talking about, but they aren’t completely the fault of Liberalism. Looking at the Middle East, Liberalism is exactly the solution for their problems. A completely unregulated economy is wrong, but not every flavour of Liberalism preaches a free market.</p>
<p>What do you see as the best system? Socialism? Communism? In theory these systems are great, but theory and practice are two different things. You need a hint of Socialism, but too much of it leaves a nasty taste.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 15:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MujaheD Radeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mujahed">@MujaheD</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ron Paul is a republican? He’s pretty much the best candidate. imo he’s the only chance America has to survive as a super power. If America doesn’t tone down its international efforts like the British empire did, it won’t last.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 13:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>for us. it has nothing to do with taking care of the planet and everything to do with looking out for <span class="hashtag">#1</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Speljohan, post:17, topic:436450”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=539162.msg3945789#msg3945789 date=1331847653]<br>
Mopman: Ignore global warming and ignore that if everyone should have the same living standard as Americans, we would need some extra planets.<br>
[/quote]Global warming won’t kill the planet though.[/quote]<br>
I didn’t say kill it, just make it much less liveable.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 06:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:16, topic:436450”]Mopman: Ignore global warming and ignore that if everyone should have the same living standard as Americans, we would need some extra planets.[/quote]Global warming won’t kill the planet though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 05:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>R.I.P RSC: Equal rights/possibilities and individual liberty does not go hand in hand, if you want equal rights/possibilities we need to limit the individual liberty and vice versa.</p>
<p>Maybe I shouldn’t call all liberals stupid, ignorant would be a better word. It can’t fix anything, or else we wouldn’t have any problems in our liberal world.</p>
<p>Mopman: Ignore global warming and ignore that if everyone should have the same living standard as Americans, we would need some extra planets.</p>
<p>PS: There is of course some exception to this, if the church is friendly against homosexuality, then giving gays the right to marry wouldn’t step on the church right to marry whoever they want.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="436450">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/sinisoul/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> sinisoul:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>90% of the people on this forum are left wing librarians. Well, that test that people took was a bit botched so eh. Anyone else think that the republicans purposely promote idiots? Sarah Palin as vice president had to be a joke.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m not a librarian, although I do enjoy reading books.</p>
<p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:6, topic:436450”][quote author=t4 link=topic=539162.msg3945721#msg3945721 date=1331840117]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Liberals are just as stupid, they are not real left-wing, so you are stuck with two right-wing party.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>american liberals are indeed. i just found the rant to be humorous.<br>
[/quote]<br>
No, all liberals are stupid, not just the American ones.[/quote]</p>
<p>I don’t see anything wrong with individual liberty and equal rights. Please explain to me why I’m stupid, if you don’t mind.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nothing we do is destructive to the environment, the world has taken far worse beatings than us, we cannot destroy the world, only our ability to live in it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“the elve age, post:12, topic:436450”]Hahahahaha and you think Democrats are any better.</p>
<p>The people who actually have the talent to lead don’t, mainly because of having a bad past, money, ect.[/quote]<br>
wat</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hahahahaha and you think Democrats are any better.</p>
<p>The people who actually have the talent to lead don’t, mainly because of having a bad past, money, ect.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>90% of the people on this forum are left wing libertarian. Well, that test that people took was a bit botched so eh. Anyone else think that the republicans purposely promote idiots? Sarah Palin as vice president had to be a joke.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Speljohan, post:8, topic:436450”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=539162.msg3945710#msg3945710 date=1331838705]<br>
Liberals are just as stupid, they are not real left-wing, so you are stuck with two right-wing party.<br>
[/quote]Liberalism doesn’t neccessarily mean you are left wing though. You can be an ultra right-winger and still believe in liberal values. Just like you can be authoritarian and socialist.[/quote]<br>
Sorry, I never meant to claim that liberalism was left-wing. It is just that Americans claim that democrats/liberals are left wing.</p>
<p>t4: Yes, we live together in this world, so individual rights for a few people should not stand over the right of everyone to have a decent life, and our children’s right to have a decent planet.</p>
<p>The consumer culture we have is destructive on the globes resources and environment, liberalism cannot defeat the problem, just try a lost game to get some control.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:6, topic:436450”][quote author=t4 link=topic=539162.msg3945721#msg3945721 date=1331840117]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Liberals are just as stupid, they are not real left-wing, so you are stuck with two right-wing party.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>american liberals are indeed. i just found the rant to be humorous.<br>
[/quote]<br>
No, all liberals are stupid, not just the American ones.[/quote]<br>
individuality is stupid? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:4, topic:436450”]Liberals are just as stupid, they are not real left-wing, so you are stuck with two right-wing party.[/quote]Liberalism doesn’t neccessarily mean you are left wing though. You can be an ultra right-winger and still believe in liberal values. Just like you can be authoritarian and socialist.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>EVERYONE is STUPID. EVERYONE…</p>
<p>EVER.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s bash republicans</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“t4, post:5, topic:436450”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=539162.msg3945710#msg3945710 date=1331838705]<br>
Liberals are just as stupid, they are not real left-wing, so you are stuck with two right-wing party.<br>
[/quote]<br>
american liberals are indeed. i just found the rant to be humorous.[/quote]<br>
No, all liberals are stupid, not just the American ones.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436450-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lets-bash-republicans/436450.rss">Let&#39;s bash republicans</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
