<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking For A Coder</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-coder/542121</link>
    <description>Hello,

I am currently in the progress of making a private server, although no coding has been done. I am new to coding, I know a few basics but nothing much yet. I&#39;m also currently only using an HP Laptop so I am unable to host for long periods of time, plus I haven&#39;t been able to succeed with no-ip or port forwarding either. 

I am looking for somebody who can code a server for me and possible host it (you&#39;re not expected to host it so don&#39;t worry), you will receive co-owner on the server of course, and anything else can be discussed later on. I am willing to help as much as I can in the process as well, I would love to learn whatever I can about coding and if there is something that you would need me to do, just ask me.

As for my part in the process of creating the server, I will be designing and coding a website and forums. Along with doing some necessary prepping and what not that is needed for the release. 

I have a lot of ideas for customs including items, quests, bosses, drops, etc so I intend to make this server unique and top quality. If you want to help me out, I thank you ahead of time. Customs and all that will be discussed after the initial server is coded and ready to go.

Also if you can host or know somebody that can host please post here or pm me and we can talk further about that.

Contact me by replying here or through PM if you&#39;re interested in helping me and we&#39;ll discuss things further.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 03:20:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-coder/542121.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking For A Coder</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@adamgulka adamgulka]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/adamgulka">@adamgulka</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>add my skype:<br>
adam.122333</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-coder/542121/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-coder/542121/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 03:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542121-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-coder/542121.rss">Looking For A Coder</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking For A Coder</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mag3Rang3Pk3 Mag3Rang3Pk3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mag3rang3pk3">@Mag3Rang3Pk3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello,</p>
<p>I am currently in the progress of making a private server, although no coding has been done. I am new to coding, I know a few basics but nothing much yet. I’m also currently only using an HP Laptop so I am unable to host for long periods of time, plus I haven’t been able to succeed with no-ip or port forwarding either.</p>
<p>I am looking for somebody who can code a server for me and possible host it (you’re not expected to host it so don’t worry), you will receive co-owner on the server of course, and anything else can be discussed later on. I am willing to help as much as I can in the process as well, I would love to learn whatever I can about coding and if there is something that you would need me to do, just ask me.</p>
<p>As for my part in the process of creating the server, I will be designing and coding a website and forums. Along with doing some necessary prepping and what not that is needed for the release.</p>
<p>I have a lot of ideas for customs including items, quests, bosses, drops, etc so I intend to make this server unique and top quality. If you want to help me out, I thank you ahead of time. Customs and all that will be discussed after the initial server is coded and ready to go.</p>
<p>Also if you can host or know somebody that can host please post here or pm me and we can talk further about that.</p>
<p>Contact me by replying here or through PM if you’re interested in helping me and we’ll discuss things further.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-coder/542121/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-coder/542121/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 02:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542121-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-a-coder/542121.rss">Looking For A Coder</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
