<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NPC talking.. [508]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-talking-508/321108</link>
    <description>.. hey i want to know..

how i would make 1 npc speak several sentences..


like.. i get it to where when you click it it&#39;ll bring up the chat interface and you&#39;ll start talking, but when you click &#39;click to continue&#39; it&#39;ll close it, instead it should go to the other chat interface when you click &#39;click to continue&#39;


how would i make it so that when one chat part is done, it&#39;ll go to the other? 

can someone show me a tut or something? 


P.S. i&#39;m posting here becuz i dont have the time to look for a TUT or even try to think a little and figure it all out myself, i have to go to bed in 10 seconds, so i posted this quick, hopefully when i come back in 18 hours i&#39;ll have SOME answer?


pleeze help and give me an answer ASAP, i only have 18 hours left!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 04:08:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-talking-508/321108.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NPC talking.. [508]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lildude783 lildude783]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lildude783">@lildude783</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>… hey i want to know…</p>
<p>how i would make 1 npc speak several sentences…</p>
<p>like… i get it to where when you click it it’ll bring up the chat interface and you’ll start talking, but when you click ‘click to continue’ it’ll close it, instead it should go to the other chat interface when you click ‘click to continue’</p>
<p>how would i make it so that when one chat part is done, it’ll go to the other?</p>
<p>can someone show me a tut or something?</p>
<p>P.S. i’m posting here becuz i dont have the time to look for a TUT or even try to think a little and figure it all out myself, i have to go to bed in 10 seconds, so i posted this quick, hopefully when i come back in 18 hours i’ll have SOME answer?</p>
<p>pleeze help and give me an answer ASAP, i only have 18 hours left!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-talking-508/321108/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-talking-508/321108/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 04:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-321108-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npc-talking-508/321108.rss">NPC talking.. [508]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
