<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New to RSPS and I need help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-rsps-and-i-need-help/513186</link>
    <description>So basically, I am using the MezzyScape 384 client/source/cache. I&#39;m not new-new, as in my first time but new to creating my own. I somewhat know how to code and everything but I am having an error. After I changed the jdk version to mine, so I could run the client, it said &quot;client updated, please reload.&quot; So I tried to compile.. and I got this message:

&quot;Note: Recompile with Xlint:deprecation for details.&quot;

I googled that and everyone said it compiled but the code may break in the future relases of Java? I don&#39;t know, I still can&#39;t load the client. If anyone can help, that would be terrific. I apologize in advance if I sound stupid at all as I am a bit new to this. Thanks to anyone who can help though! :) I really want to play this, it looks pretty awesome.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 01:58:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-rsps-and-i-need-help/513186.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New to RSPS and I need help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That’s not an error, just a warning. (Boy, all hell will break loose when this is actually no longer available)</p>
<p>As for your client, the server is saying that there is most likely a UID or something like that, and your client is different, or their is a client version, and your client’s is different from the server’s.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-rsps-and-i-need-help/513186/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-rsps-and-i-need-help/513186/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-513186-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-rsps-and-i-need-help/513186.rss">New to RSPS and I need help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New to RSPS and I need help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aristeia Aristeia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aristeia">@Aristeia</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So basically, I am using the MezzyScape 384 client/source/cache. I’m not new-new, as in my first time but new to creating my own. I somewhat know how to code and everything but I am having an error. After I changed the jdk version to mine, so I could run the client, it said “client updated, please reload.” So I tried to compile… and I got this message:</p>
<p>“Note: Recompile with Xlint:deprecation for details.”</p>
<p>I googled that and everyone said it compiled but the code may break in the future relases of Java? I don’t know, I still can’t load the client. If anyone can help, that would be terrific. I apologize in advance if I sound stupid at all as I am a bit new to this. Thanks to anyone who can help though! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I really want to play this, it looks pretty awesome.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-rsps-and-i-need-help/513186/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-rsps-and-i-need-help/513186/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 19:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-513186-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-to-rsps-and-i-need-help/513186.rss">New to RSPS and I need help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
