<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073</link>
    <description>Alright guys, well today i&#39;am here to discuss something with each and everyone Moparian here. I have a question for you? Why exactly do you think people don&#39;t find the forums of moparscape good to advertise and post stuff on. In  my opinion the reason for this is the lack of content what i mean by this is that we don&#39;t have any events like Sotw, we don&#39;t have a nice shoutbox for people to discuss stuff in, we shouldn&#39;t just only have one theme it has been the same theme for so like. In my opinion if we change the forums theme, add a shoutbox, organize the boards, start more events and adding more usergroups we could have a lot more people active on the forums according to these images

[b]Moparscape[/b]

[img]http://puu.sh/1eCuG[/img]

[b]R*n*-S*rv*r
[/b][img]http://puu.sh/1eCvT[/img]

people actually like these type of features, and I don&#39;t mean start selling donator and such but i mean that we should add more usergroups such as; [b]Veterans, Global mod, Developer, Gfxer, Sotw winners[/b] the reason for this is that people actually would like a group that shows how respected they are here is a list of features i think we should add to the forums of Moparscape.


&lt;blockquote&gt;Stop using SMF and move onto Vbulletin 3.8.7 (4.x.x was the end of Vbulletin.)
If not then add more themes^
Add more User Groups
Add a shoutbox
Organize the boards and add a few more
Add a bit more stuff into the user Postbits&lt;/blockquote&gt;
If anyone has any more suggestions please reply with them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 21:15:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t even…</p>
<p>Why would you ever choose vbulletin over SMF?<br>
There are no themes better than the SMF core theme.<br>
There are several user groups and awards members can gain, work for it.<br>
There are several hidden boards the people who aren’t seasoned members can’t access.<br>
If you can’t access the IRC through our applet, download mIRC or another desktop client or just make a post/pm someone.<br>
That post bit thing that rune-server do is fucking hideous and tacky.</p>
<p>MoparScape has a reputation among the RSPS communities of which it is where the majority of the great programmers come from (which is complete shit, it’s only the mitb members they’re thinking of) so that makes them not come here because we’re not very beginner friendly. I’m happy with the community we have at the minute.</p>
<p>I also second what eyeownyew said, a lot of reports are taking longer and longer to be processed, it’d be an idea to bring in a few more sectionals if nothing else.</p>
<p>Do you have any other ideas besides turning us into rune-server?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 21:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kronixz kronikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kronixz">@kronixz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Honestly since we are talking about themes, there is this awesome smf theme called “gearbox”</p>
<p>would be awesome <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 18:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think the reason we are less active than the other communities is ‘retarded’ people. All of those people that post in the wrong section, all of the stupid people that post ‘leeched’ servers… It all happens here. Either we need to make sure that happens less, or we need to have more mods on top of it (not saying the mods are doing a bad job, but it’s impossible to keep watch 24/7).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 16:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="19" data-topic="464073">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 s1gma:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]Add a shoutbox</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>use irc, make irc easier to access for n00bs, <span class="bbcode-b">make them autojoin to <span class="hashtag">#mopar</span> for maximum buttrage</span>. irc should be a paid member feature. <span class="hashtag">#mopar</span> must collectively pay for noobs to be redirected to <span class="hashtag">#moparscape</span>.[/quote]<br>
Please no, I’m scared to go there :s</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 15:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_s11 s1gma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_s11">@_s11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Stop using SMF and move onto Vbulletin 3.8.7 (4.x.x was the end of Vbulletin.)</blockquote>
no
<blockquote>If not then add more themes^</blockquote>
yes, but only if i get one without styling/images/colours because fuck accessibility. people must pay for new themes.
<blockquote>Add more User Groups</blockquote>
yes, and remove privileges so no one complains about mods/admins. implement voteban instead, but people must pay to vote.
<blockquote>Add a shoutbox</blockquote>
use irc, make irc easier to access for n00bs, make them autojoin to #mopar for maximum buttrage. irc should be a paid member feature. #mopar must collectively pay for noobs to be redirected to #moparscape.
<blockquote>Organize the boards and add a few more</blockquote>
WIP... or just have one free-for-all board. new boards should have to be paid for.
<blockquote>Add a bit more stuff into the user Postbits</blockquote>
what is postbit? can mopar charge money for it? i say abolish postbits unless they're paid for.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 12:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>oh look this thread again.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 08:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Also semi on topic, Rune-Server isn’t censored here anymore.</p>
<p>Also, that number of 5k online is padded I believe. As in the ‘active’ time quota is longer than ours, and/or it includes crawlers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 07:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t believe the site is dying but is having a problem of keeping people here(and its evident-same old people, lack of content, etc) which is kind of changing how the forums work.</p>
<p>I agree with you on some points though. If I’m saying something that doesn’t make sense, my apologies as I’ve had a few.</p>
<ol>
<li>I would support a new attracting theme for newer users. Tbh, take a look at locus. Its built up very nice.</li>
<li>The usergroups are fine now, though the system behind them is not. Any awards from this side of the site should be re-evaluated imo. It might be a long-shot idea, but I think it would be cool to incorporate the help/tutorial/programming awards to people who actively contribute to the community, not just bail out once they receive it.</li>
<li>Shoutbox-No. Would be out of control, but the IRC we use is pretty ugly as well. I would honestly just use mibbit IRC  app. Easy to use and incorporate.</li>
<li>Boards-Seem to be a work in progress.</li>
</ol>
<p>last idea-Add the online list to past 24 hours. Make it look like we’re booming all the time to get people to stay</p>
<p>that is all</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 07:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>There is no reason to stop using SMF</li>
<li>Like Tom pointed out, if new themes are presented they do have the possibility to be added. I’m pretty sure I can disclose that there was actually a theme in the works to being put on here; been delayed because the admins are both very busy.</li>
<li>We have user groups.</li>
<li>A shoutbox is disgustingly ugly; we were talking about a theme that had a shoutbox that was hidden by default and you had to enable it on your profile, but I think the conclusion was it would be better to just find an IRC client that worked for more people instead of adding a blemish to the index.</li>
<li>The boards have already been re-organized. Adding boards is always an option, but it needs to be discussed and the need for the board needs to be apparent.</li>
<li>This is a simplistic site. We don’t have obtrusive avatars and images in signatures for a reason. It clutters up the page, and it looks unprofessional.</li>
</ol>
<p>Another thing I’d like to point out, especially for points 3 and 6, is that the type of people that these things attract are not the ones that we necessarily want on this site. You can look at most avatars/signatures on R-S and see what I mean. And a lot of the people that join just to get into a user group… well… yea.</p>
<p>This is not to say that this site is perfect, I don’t think anyone believes it is. There are things that could be done to make it more popular, but turning it into a cookie cutter VB site specifically formatted to please the 13 year old majority that have access to their parents credit cards to purchase an unban or a donator badge is not the solution.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 06:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Moparscape needs moar smart people. Hur hur.</p>
<p>Nothing wrong with mscp… well maybe one thing, we need more community contests.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 05:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve discussed the themes countless times with moparisthebest, he has always said if a particular theme gets enough attention then he will consider installing it. If you look at <a href="http://MoparCraft.net">MoparCraft.net</a> I originally wanted to completely change to another theme, but in the end we changed our mind and went with a customized version of the default theme. Of course there have been votes in the past for new themes, and he does forget at times but if there is that much support for the theme it will be impossible for him to avoid.</p>
<p>The idea of a chatbox has been discussed in the past, I personally didn’t mind but there were style concerns and such which eventually prevented it from becoming a reality. I can’t really remember the arguments as they were said but the idea was given a fair hearing. Though I don’t agree with the current IRC legend award, and culture which comes with it. We have situations where the cool dudes of the network are misleading people asking for help (which so happens to be the larger part of MSCP) which makes them go elsewhere.</p>
<p>The issue with your suggestions are that they’re unspecific, you want more boards but you fail to suggest what boards should be added so you’ve left it up to the staff to guess, the same applies for the post suggestion and award ideas. Veteran can mean anything, I can sign up to a site in 2006 and never appear again until now, can I claim the award/title?</p>
<p>Basing from the lack of detail, I’m to assume you’re emulating rune-server which doesn’t seem that appealing to be honest. All we will get is the rune-server folk which couldn’t cut it on the real thing, so come to us to achieve the goals they were denied on rune-server. Suggestions are good but when I was staff we spent a lot of time coming up with criteria for peoples suggestions and how they could work (which is often more time consuming than it sounds).</p>
<p>I also am skeptical to how you’ve managed to say the user groups (or whatever) are directly responsible for the popularity of rune-server. I’m not saying you’re all out wrong, but rather why couldn’t the harshness of the MSCP staff in the past be a major playing factor as well?</p>
<p>PS sorry for the lack of structure and possible mistakes (either in my reading of your post, or grammatically) it’s currently 5AM, heh.</p>
<p>EDIT: Forgot, the IRC applet is annoying yeh most people don’t realize they can download a separate IRC client, so perhaps in the future such information can be added.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 04:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lets not turn every thread into a flame war please.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 04:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah maybe that should be fixed, but thats a shit way to use IRC anyways. Much better off with an irc client like mirc or xchat.</p>
<p>I personally dislike vbulletin. I see no benefit in switching as we aren’t like other communities. We don’t need all the distracting clutter that other forums have and this is one thing that has always seperated us.</p>
<p>Pokemon awards have been used before the first private server was released, on the community where they began. This site has continued that tradition and will probably continue to do so.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>WHATS WRONG WITH DICK IN YOUR MOUTH HUH?</p>
<p>Shoutbox is just annoying, I don’t know why, it just seems irc is faster in a way, and shoutbox doesn’t even feel like actual chatting tbh</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Classic, post:8, topic:464073”]you’re an idiot, irc is 9999x better than a chat box</p>
<p>the commands are vast, and god way better to use and control then a chat box.</p>
<p>You have r-s views, not like moparscape is any better but you still suck for telling us this</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">I believe we should switch to vbulletin considering the fact that their are many more mods, better themes, and much better then SMF.</span><br>
I think we should get rid of the pokemon userbars and such and add better ones and anyways i don’t see how they relate to private servers in any way.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Holy fuck, somebody give me mod for just 5 minutes. That was the stupidest sentence I have ever read.</p>
<p>Also: This isn’t intellectual, it’s actually the exact opposite.</p>
<p>IRC IS WAYY BETTER than a shoutbox btw, you get that security error because you click yes on that second check box, L2Read those son.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you really shouldn’t talk, because you’re really stupid aswell[/quote]<br>
I’m surprised you can talk with all that dick in your mouth</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@classic mopmans little slave]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/classic">@classic</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you’re an idiot, irc is 9999x better than a chat box</p>
<p>the commands are vast, and god way better to use and control then a chat box.</p>
<p>You have r-s views, not like moparscape is any better but you still suck for telling us this</p>
<p>[quote=“tyb97, post:7, topic:464073”][quote author=rooneyscape link=topic=567862.msg4124244#msg4124244 date=1350185986]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">I believe we should switch to vbulletin considering the fact that their are many more mods, better themes, and much better then SMF.</span><br>
I think we should get rid of the pokemon userbars and such and add better ones and anyways i don’t see how they relate to private servers in any way.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Holy fuck, somebody give me mod for just 5 minutes. That was the stupidest sentence I have ever read.</p>
<p>Also: This isn’t intellectual, it’s actually the exact opposite.</p>
<p>IRC IS WAYY BETTER than a shoutbox btw, you get that security error because you click yes on that second check box, L2Read those son.[/quote]<br>
you really shouldn’t talk, because you’re really stupid aswell</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“rooneyscape, post:5, topic:464073”]<span class="bbcode-b">I believe we should switch to vbulletin considering the fact that their are many more mods, better themes, and much better then SMF.</span><br>
I think we should get rid of the pokemon userbars and such and add better ones and anyways i don’t see how they relate to private servers in any way.[/quote]<br>
Holy fuck, somebody give me mod for just 5 minutes. That was the stupidest sentence I have ever read.</p>
<p>Also: This isn’t intellectual, it’s actually the exact opposite.</p>
<p>IRC IS WAYY BETTER than a shoutbox btw, you get that security error because you click yes on that second check box, L2Read those son.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>I like smf more than vb, easier to use imo, simpler, and vb irritates me</li>
<li>I think its been decided that they want to keep one universal theme though I’m not 100% sure</li>
<li>Theres already alot, just people on the moparscape side don’t have that many, like different language master badges, etc, some badges only obtainable on moparcraft forum</li>
<li>We have IRC, which I think is alot better than shoutbox</li>
<li>Could be reorganized again later but for now I think it won’t be considering it was done somewhat recently</li>
<li>Rep was recently taken out, but they are going to add a new system once they find one that works good. As for avatars and user titles the forum gets way to crowded, laggy, etc with all those images, and it just makes it look sloppy imo</li>
</ol>
<p>You can use something like ice chat very simple to use the web client is just there for ease of access</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rooneyscape rooneyscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rooneyscape">@rooneyscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well could i ask why sotw was removed and i’am sure it drawed in many graphics related members, do you think the irc is better then a shoutbox? <img src="http://puu.sh/1eCZ9" alt width="" height="">, although we have themes i think we should have more.</p>
<p>I believe we should switch to vbulletin considering the fact that their are many more mods, better themes, and much better then SMF.<br>
I think we should get rid of the pokemon userbars and such and add better ones and anyways i don’t see how they relate to private servers in any way.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We used to have sotw which is nice but wasn’t drawing in crowds. shout box will never be added and we have irc to chat with. There are other themes, modify profile -&gt; Look and Layout. There’s not many but they are hard to add due to the forum being heavily modified. Tbh if you suggest good ones that the community likes they may be added at some point.</p>
<p>-Why vBulletin? SMF is great and free/open source<br>
-I’m not sure about user-groups, but we do have all sorts of badges/awards that serve the same purpose. I do think that we could use some new ones more related to private servers. <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,1766.0.html">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,1766.0.html</a><br>
-The boards are kind of in a confusing state since some of them from <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf">moparisthebest.com/smf</a> were moved here. I’m not any better at organizing them though so I have no suggestions</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rooneyscape rooneyscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rooneyscape">@rooneyscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“drubrkletern, post:2, topic:464073”]1. Better chances of catching lightning in a bottle than changing smf<br>
2. I don’t think that will happen soon either (Though I could be wrong on this one)<br>
3. Probably not going to happen<br>
4. Never going to happen<br>
5. Already happened might get organized some more, new ones probably won’t get added<br>
6. I think this is already being worked on[/quote]</p>
<p>Well would you agree with some of the suggestions or disagree? Please explain why.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>Better chances of catching lightning in a bottle than changing smf</li>
<li>I don’t think that will happen soon either (Though I could be wrong on this one)</li>
<li>Probably not going to happen</li>
<li>Never going to happen</li>
<li>Already happened might get organized some more, new ones probably won’t get added</li>
<li>I think this is already being worked on</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Moparscape needs a change</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rooneyscape rooneyscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rooneyscape">@rooneyscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright guys, well today i’am here to discuss something with each and everyone Moparian here. I have a question for you? Why exactly do you think people don’t find the forums of moparscape good to advertise and post stuff on. In  my opinion the reason for this is the lack of content what i mean by this is that we don’t have any events like Sotw, we don’t have a nice shoutbox for people to discuss stuff in, we shouldn’t just only have one theme it has been the same theme for so like. In my opinion if we change the forums theme, add a shoutbox, organize the boards, start more events and adding more usergroups we could have a lot more people active on the forums according to these images</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Moparscape</span></p>
<p><img src="http://puu.sh/1eCuG" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">R<em>n</em>-S<em>rv</em>r<br>
</span><img src="http://puu.sh/1eCvT" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>people actually like these type of features, and I don’t mean start selling donator and such but i mean that we should add more usergroups such as; <span class="bbcode-b">Veterans, Global mod, Developer, Gfxer, Sotw winners</span> the reason for this is that people actually would like a group that shows how respected they are here is a list of features i think we should add to the forums of Moparscape.</p>
<blockquote>Stop using SMF and move onto Vbulletin 3.8.7 (4.x.x was the end of Vbulletin.)
If not then add more themes^
Add more User Groups
Add a shoutbox
Organize the boards and add a few more
Add a bit more stuff into the user Postbits</blockquote>
If anyone has any more suggestions please reply with them.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 03:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-464073-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscape-needs-a-change/464073.rss">Moparscape needs a change</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
