<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Accessing non-static field with BCEL/Reflection</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been looking up information about BCEL and the Reflection API, including the two tutorials here. I&#39;ve successfully been able to retrieve values from static fields and print them to the console. While playing around with Reflection and RuneScape, I noticed that I was receiving minimal amounts of information that could actually be used in a helpful manner. Correct me if I&#39;m wrong, but I&#39;ve come to think that most information I would like to access is stored in an instance and held there non-static. I have found myself to be extremely lost when it comes to accessing fields that are part of the instance (non-static). I was able to implement accessor methods into a class - but I&#39;m left wondering [i]how do I call this method?[/i] More specifically, how do I specify instance I&#39;m trying to call the method of? Is this the proper way to do it? Is it even necessary?
I&#39;m left very confused and hope to find some information/guidance here, thank you.

Also, slightly off-topic, but what happened to rs-hacking.com? I&#39;ve seen many people link tutorials to the side but I&#39;ve been unable to view them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 17:27:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Accessing non-static field with BCEL/Reflection</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I just lurk here now man.  I really couldn’t tell you about what to do with the current client.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 17:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544905-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905.rss">Accessing non-static field with BCEL/Reflection</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Accessing non-static field with BCEL/Reflection</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Carazon Carazon ™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/carazon">@Carazon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Pwnd, post:2, topic:544905”]In regards to RS hacking, back in the day when BCEL first came around, you’d just insert your own methods into the classes that had fields you were interested in.  They’d literally just be an accessor method and that was how you retrieved the field.</p>
<p>Nowadays, fukifino[/quote]</p>
<p>Has it changed at all? Also, do you happen to have any information on finding the fields I’m interested in? I understand how to implement an accessor into a class, but how do I find that class in the first place?<br>
What I’m doing right now is just going through every single class in the gamepack.jar and printing out every static field value, limited to primitives and Strings. I’m not getting very much information. Stuff like inventory and skill XP doesn’t seem to be stored in any of these.<br>
Which is why I posted this thread - am I doing something wrong (inv stored in an iterable variant?) or are they simply within these non-static fields in some instance?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 08:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544905-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905.rss">Accessing non-static field with BCEL/Reflection</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Accessing non-static field with BCEL/Reflection</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In regards to RS hacking, back in the day when BCEL first came around, you’d just insert your own methods into the classes that had fields you were interested in.  They’d literally just be an accessor method and that was how you retrieved the field.</p>
<p>Nowadays, fukifino</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 08:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544905-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905.rss">Accessing non-static field with BCEL/Reflection</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Accessing non-static field with BCEL/Reflection</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Carazon Carazon ™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/carazon">@Carazon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve been looking up information about BCEL and the Reflection API, including the two tutorials here. I’ve successfully been able to retrieve values from static fields and print them to the console. While playing around with Reflection and RuneScape, I noticed that I was receiving minimal amounts of information that could actually be used in a helpful manner. Correct me if I’m wrong, but I’ve come to think that most information I would like to access is stored in an instance and held there non-static. I have found myself to be extremely lost when it comes to accessing fields that are part of the instance (non-static). I was able to implement accessor methods into a class - but I’m left wondering <span class="bbcode-i">how do I call this method?</span> More specifically, how do I specify instance I’m trying to call the method of? Is this the proper way to do it? Is it even necessary?<br>
I’m left very confused and hope to find some information/guidance here, thank you.</p>
<p>Also, slightly off-topic, but what happened to <a href="http://rs-hacking.com" rel="nofollow noopener">rs-hacking.com</a>? I’ve seen many people link tutorials to the side but I’ve been unable to view them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 08:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544905-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/accessing-non-static-field-with-bcel-reflection/544905.rss">Accessing non-static field with BCEL/Reflection</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
