<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688</link>
    <description>[b][size=20pt]Unfortunately this is now a SIDE Project, this is due to my research suggesting it was good but a little too different and people would rather have an excellent RSPS with the normal concepts but with some unique concepts included.

I plan on working on this project once my main project is completed and if it&#39;s a success I will release this too as a secondary option to play alongside my main project.

Your research has been far from a waste and I will still use a lot of concepts and a lot of the responses I&#39;ve collated in my new project.  Please refer to [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,667586.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,667586.0.html[/url] for my main project. [/size][/b]

[img]http://i.imgur.com/f38NgvL.png[/img]

[b][u]The 3 Isles[/u][/b]

[b][u]About me[/u][/b]

So I&#39;m 21, I currently help manage a large business with over 1,400 customers on &quot;memberships&quot;. I&#39;ve played Runescape since 2004 and honestly I can&#39;t remember exactly when I started RSPS&#39;s but it wasn&#39;t too long after. I&#39;ve got a lot of actual tangible real life experience with running projects and a business as well as having the more boring but very important knowlege too which came with an A at A-Level in the subject several years ago.

I have also recently invested £1,600 in a new computer so have the ability to host the server privately to begin and then move on to Dedi once it&#39;s required. I&#39;ve got experience running an RSPS before but it was more of a bit of fun back then, this to me is my baby of a project and I will treat it like a business for the most efficiency.

[b][u]My Research[/u][/b]

For the past 2 weeks I&#39;ve been collecting research for my unique and innovative RSPS idea that my research suggests could become a huge hit and change the game. (Contact me either on here or by Skype - Jamesbarker994 to ask about my research etc.) A lot of my research has been collated into 1 easy to read Excel Spreadsheet and anyone who helps me work on this server will have access to it in order to help them.

[b][u]My Servers Concept[/u][/b]

Here are the basic concepts of the RSPS in question.

[spoiler][b][u]The 3 Isles[/u][/b]

Rough First Draft of the Starter Dialog -

[i]&quot;A great war between the 3 gods of Runescape caused the population of Runescape to flee in fear of their lives, the homeland is in ruins and is no more.

A new era is upon us and you are one of the lucky survivors that has made it to this Desert Island and I will explain the new era of Runescape to you as we work to train you up!&quot;

&quot;Okay so here&#39;s your Starter Kit with everything you will need to start out.&quot;

[/i]... Player works through the tutorial and makes it to the end

[i]&quot;Okay, I have 3 Ships here and each will go to the Island of a God. You Sir must now choose which mighty god you will stand for? Will it be Guthix, Saradomin or Zamorak?...&quot;

&quot;Okay you have chosen the Island of X! I shall wish you goodbye and also good luck! Make the Island of X proud and if you ever need help then my brother is on the Island of Harmony and will help answer your questions!&quot;
[/i]
These are the 3 isles below. (Real RS names, look them up on the map)

Lunar Isle (Isle of Zamorak)
Fremennik Isles (Isle of Guthix)
Miscellania (Isle of Saradomin)

[b][u]Login Process[/u][/b]

1) Player logs in, must complete a Tutorial Island that explains the game without being too long and therefore boring.

2) After completion of the Tutorial Island the player now needs to choose an Isle to live. (Cannot choose an isle that is already over-populated)

[b][u]Basics[/u][/b]

Each village starts with the following...

1) Basic Shops
2) Basic Training Zones

[b][u]Basic Server Mechanics[/u][/b]

1) You must pay x amount to travel to another Isle via your port
2) When on another Isle you are hostile and so are they
3) Neutral zone to encourage trading and maybe some other features (&quot;Harmony&quot; look it up on the RS map, it&#39;s an island)
4) Each Isle has a Treasury (Refer to Treasury section for details)
5) 6 Isle Levels (To begin with, with time more levels will come, Refer to Isle Levels section for details)
6) You cannot buy from another Isles&#39; shops
7) 1 PvP Island (Yet to be chosen)
8) Neutral Minigames &amp; Boss Area&#39;s OR Different phases for different Isles? (No trading in these Minigames zones)
9) There are practically NO teleports, this is a Travel By Ship based server. (Refer to Ship System for details)

[b][u]Basic Treasury Mechanics[/u][/b]

1) Every 30 minutes a player is online they gain x amount of GP for their Isles treasury (Systems in place to stop people abusing this)
2) Players can donate to their treasury at any point, any amount of GP or even Item that will be converted into a &quot;Trade in value&quot; amount of GP. (&quot;Trade in&quot; worth much less than street price)

[b][u]Isle Levels[/u][/b]

1) Six levels to begin, each Isle starts at Level 1
2) With each level the Isle gains...

- More advanced Training Zones
- More items in shops (This will never become outrageous, player economy will be favoured)
- Cheaper items in certain shops
- More reliable ship to sail to other Isles (refer to ship system for details)

[b][u]Ship System[/u][/b]

When a player wishes to travel from their Isle to another there&#39;s a chance based on their Isles ship level that they may get stuck on the relevant [i]Pirate Island[/i].

If you check the actual RS map you will see that there&#39;s an island between each Isle (Miscellania is an Isle). These are called [i]Pirate Islands[/i].

Lunar Isle -&gt; Fremennik Isles = Pirates&#39; Cove [i](Pirate Island)[/i]
Fremennik Isles -&gt; Lunar Isle = Pirates&#39; Cove [i](Pirate Island)[/i]

Fremennik Isles -&gt; Miscellania = Waterbirth Island [i](Pirate Island)[/i]
Miscellania -&gt; Fremennik Isles = Waterbirth Island [i](Pirate Island)[/i]

If you travel from the far Western Isle to the far Eastern Isle or vice versa you may end up at either Pirate Island.

Also instead of teleporting anywhere this is an entirely ship based transportation system so if you want to travel to a Minigame such as the barrows, you will need to rely on your Isles ship! Whenever you travel to a minigame, based on the Isles&#39; ship level, you may end up at a random Pirate Island!

If you do end up on a [i]Pirate Island[/i] then you must complete a task such as cutting wood (Keeping it basic to begin with) to repair the ship! You will be rewarded an XP Lantern for this.

[u][b]Skills[/b][/u]

I&#39;ve thought up a basic starting plan where each Isle will have access to all the skills on their own Isle.

For example with the Woodcutting skill their would be certain trees in certain zones littered around the island (Or they could be in the same zone, this will of course be decided based on research from the RSPS community).

As the Isle&#39;s level increases more tree&#39;s appear and better axes appear in shops (Not too high as I wish to encourage player-made axes for the economy) therefore making it easier for the masses to cut down tree&#39;s and have access to the rich nectar that is GP which comes from selling those logs to the players or even shops for a lower &quot;Trade in value&quot; which should equal a vibrant economy.

Also when an Isle&#39;s level increases their could be a short time bonus for the Isle in terms of XP gained. This could be used to encourage players to use a skill that maybe isn&#39;t being as used as much as the others for whatever reason.

[size=8pt][b][i]Slayer[/i][/b][/size]

This would start off as a relatively easy skill but when they got to a certain level the player would start receiving tasks to go to another Isle and kill a certain monster or even as their level in Slayer increases even further - kill a certain player (of a similar level). This would be sort of like the Bounty Hunter system where you get a target. This could make Slayer much more than going to the same old Slayer Tower and killing the same old monsters etc which I see too often in RSPS&#39;s nowadays. (This concept it of course open for discussion and would be adjusted or depending on the feedback I receive.

People should even begin to enjoy slayer and for the PK&#39;ers, this is a skill which comes hand in hand with what they enjoy most!
[/spoiler]

[b][u]Budget[/u][/b]

I&#39;m willing to invest a fair amount into this project in order to get it working so the RSPS community can enjoy a new brilliant and unique server. Contact me over either Skype - Jamesbarker994 or over PM on here for further information.

Overall budget - £600 startup | £250/month running costs

This includes but is NOT limited too...

- Advertisement
- Developers
- VPS
- Forum

[u][b]Interested in being part of the Development Team that bring this revolutionary RSPS to light?[/b][/u]

Then please hop over to [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,667586.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,667586.0.html[/url].

Otherwise, any opinions on this concept would be great! Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 14:48:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Staff, you’re welcome to remove this now. It’s served a great purpose but is no longer required. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 14:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>once again I like the idea but does anyone else think that this might be too ‘different’ for a runescape server? i mean if you’re looking to do something you’ve always wanted to do that’s alright but if this is solely for business purposes then wouldn’t a normal server be more popular?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 05:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you guys, also Lare69 I’ve sent you a PM; if you’ve got a spare minute then please could you possibly read it. Thanks again.</p>
<p>Keep the responses coming in guys! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 15:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Like the overall concept best of luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2014 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you seem to be planning this all out very well, good luck man!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 07:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Vain_, post:4, topic:548688”]didnt read all that tbh am busy atm</p>
<p>just a thought make skills rely on other skills.</p>
<p><em>simply concept</em> farming: players plant seeds in pots. “plant pot in ground” cycle an event to slowly spawn objects in that tile (small fern, small bush,  small tree, normal tree, eventually a yew tree, then dead tree when cut/not cut after so long)</p>
<p>make plants not be able to be planted in such a close proximity,and chopping of dead trees would remove the object completely.</p>
<p>this <span class="bbcode-b">one idea</span> makes a demand for:<br>
miners must mine clay for crafters<br>
crafters must make pots for farmers<br>
pvms must collect seeds for farmers<br>
farmers must plant trees for wcs<br>
wcs must cut trees for fletchers<br>
fms must create fires for cookers</p>
<p>etc</p>
<p>make “roles” of each skill and make them interact with each other[/quote]</p>
<p>Yes I certainly agree with the general idea of making skills rely on other skills, it’s just about finding the correct balance of course. I love the idea though mate and I’ve noted it down. If you get a chance then please have a read of the new “Skills” section under the Spoiler and vote on the poll, Thank you. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>didnt read all that tbh am busy atm</p>
<p>just a thought make skills rely on other skills.</p>
<p><em>simply concept</em> farming: players plant seeds in pots. “plant pot in ground” cycle an event to slowly spawn objects in that tile (small fern, small bush,  small tree, normal tree, eventually a yew tree, then dead tree when cut/not cut after so long)</p>
<p>make plants not be able to be planted in such a close proximity,and chopping of dead trees would remove the object completely.</p>
<p>this <span class="bbcode-b">one idea</span> makes a demand for:<br>
miners must mine clay for crafters<br>
crafters must make pots for farmers<br>
pvms must collect seeds for farmers<br>
farmers must plant trees for wcs<br>
wcs must cut trees for fletchers<br>
fms must create fires for cookers</p>
<p>etc</p>
<p>make “roles” of each skill and make them interact with each other</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 02:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="548688">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Vain_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>again just wanna know what your thoughts are on skilling and how to plan to incorporate different skills into this concept.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well so far I’ve thought up a basic starting plan where each Isle will have access to all the skills on their own Isle.</p>
<p>For example with the Woodcutting skill their would be certain tree’s in certain zones littered around the island (Or they could be in the same zone, this will of course be decided based on research from the RSPS community). Maybe as the Isle’s level increases more tree’s appear or better axes appear in shops (Not too high to encourage player-made axes for the economy) therefore making it easier for the masses to cut down tree’s and have access to the rich nectar that is GP which comes from selling those logs to the players or even shops for a lower “Trade in value” which should equal a vibrant economy.</p>
<p>With one skill specifically though this could be slightly harder, so what I’ve thought could work well and be a very nice addition to the RSPS could be where Slayer has a PvP aspect to it. I shall elaborate further…</p>
<p>This is just a basic “first draft” concept but a player may have a task to go to another Isle and kill a certain monster or even as their level in Slayer increases - kill a certain player (of a similar level). This would be sort of like the Bounty Hunter system where you get a target. This could make Slayer much more than going to the same old Slayer Tower and killing the same old monsters etc which I see too often in RSPS’s nowadays. People may even begin to enjoy slayer and for the PK’ers, this is a skill which comes hand in hand with what they enjoy most!</p>
<p>Skill section added under Spoiler section. Thanks for your input Vain_ and if you have any further questions then please don’t hesitate to fire away!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 02:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>again just wanna know what your thoughts are on skilling and how to plan to incorporate different skills into this concept.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 02:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jarker994 Jarker994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jarker994">@Jarker994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[b][size=20pt]Unfortunately this is now a SIDE Project, this is due to my research suggesting it was good but a little too different and people would rather have an excellent RSPS with the normal concepts but with some unique concepts included.</p>
<p>I plan on working on this project once my main project is completed and if it’s a success I will release this too as a secondary option to play alongside my main project.</p>
<p>Your research has been far from a waste and I will still use a lot of concepts and a lot of the responses I’ve collated in my new project.  Please refer to <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,667586.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,667586.0.html</a> for my main project. [/size][/b]</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/f38NgvL.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">The 3 Isles</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">About me</span></span></p>
<p>So I’m 21, I currently help manage a large business with over 1,400 customers on “memberships”. I’ve played Runescape since 2004 and honestly I can’t remember exactly when I started RSPS’s but it wasn’t too long after. I’ve got a lot of actual tangible real life experience with running projects and a business as well as having the more boring but very important knowlege too which came with an A at A-Level in the subject several years ago.</p>
<p>I have also recently invested £1,600 in a new computer so have the ability to host the server privately to begin and then move on to Dedi once it’s required. I’ve got experience running an RSPS before but it was more of a bit of fun back then, this to me is my baby of a project and I will treat it like a business for the most efficiency.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">My Research</span></span></p>
<p>For the past 2 weeks I’ve been collecting research for my unique and innovative RSPS idea that my research suggests could become a huge hit and change the game. (Contact me either on here or by Skype - Jamesbarker994 to ask about my research etc.) A lot of my research has been collated into 1 easy to read Excel Spreadsheet and anyone who helps me work on this server will have access to it in order to help them.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">My Servers Concept</span></span></p>
<p>Here are the basic concepts of the RSPS in question.</p>
<p>[spoiler]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">The 3 Isles</span></span></p>
<p>Rough First Draft of the Starter Dialog -</p>
<p>[i]"A great war between the 3 gods of Runescape caused the population of Runescape to flee in fear of their lives, the homeland is in ruins and is no more.</p>
<p>A new era is upon us and you are one of the lucky survivors that has made it to this Desert Island and I will explain the new era of Runescape to you as we work to train you up!"</p>
<p>“Okay so here’s your Starter Kit with everything you will need to start out.”</p>
<p>[/i]… Player works through the tutorial and makes it to the end</p>
<p>[i]“Okay, I have 3 Ships here and each will go to the Island of a God. You Sir must now choose which mighty god you will stand for? Will it be Guthix, Saradomin or Zamorak?..”</p>
<p>“Okay you have chosen the Island of X! I shall wish you goodbye and also good luck! Make the Island of X proud and if you ever need help then my brother is on the Island of Harmony and will help answer your questions!”<br>
[/i]<br>
These are the 3 isles below. (Real RS names, look them up on the map)</p>
<p>Lunar Isle (Isle of Zamorak)<br>
Fremennik Isles (Isle of Guthix)<br>
Miscellania (Isle of Saradomin)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Login Process</span></span></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Player logs in, must complete a Tutorial Island that explains the game without being too long and therefore boring.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>After completion of the Tutorial Island the player now needs to choose an Isle to live. (Cannot choose an isle that is already over-populated)</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Basics</span></span></p>
<p>Each village starts with the following…</p>
<ol>
<li>Basic Shops</li>
<li>Basic Training Zones</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Basic Server Mechanics</span></span></p>
<ol>
<li>You must pay x amount to travel to another Isle via your port</li>
<li>When on another Isle you are hostile and so are they</li>
<li>Neutral zone to encourage trading and maybe some other features (“Harmony” look it up on the RS map, it’s an island)</li>
<li>Each Isle has a Treasury (Refer to Treasury section for details)</li>
<li>6 Isle Levels (To begin with, with time more levels will come, Refer to Isle Levels section for details)</li>
<li>You cannot buy from another Isles’ shops</li>
<li>1 PvP Island (Yet to be chosen)</li>
<li>Neutral Minigames &amp; Boss Area’s OR Different phases for different Isles? (No trading in these Minigames zones)</li>
<li>There are practically NO teleports, this is a Travel By Ship based server. (Refer to Ship System for details)</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Basic Treasury Mechanics</span></span></p>
<ol>
<li>Every 30 minutes a player is online they gain x amount of GP for their Isles treasury (Systems in place to stop people abusing this)</li>
<li>Players can donate to their treasury at any point, any amount of GP or even Item that will be converted into a “Trade in value” amount of GP. (“Trade in” worth much less than street price)</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Isle Levels</span></span></p>
<ol>
<li>Six levels to begin, each Isle starts at Level 1</li>
<li>With each level the Isle gains…</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>More advanced Training Zones</li>
<li>More items in shops (This will never become outrageous, player economy will be favoured)</li>
<li>Cheaper items in certain shops</li>
<li>More reliable ship to sail to other Isles (refer to ship system for details)</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Ship System</span></span></p>
<p>When a player wishes to travel from their Isle to another there’s a chance based on their Isles ship level that they may get stuck on the relevant <span class="bbcode-i">Pirate Island</span>.</p>
<p>If you check the actual RS map you will see that there’s an island between each Isle (Miscellania is an Isle). These are called <span class="bbcode-i">Pirate Islands</span>.</p>
<p>Lunar Isle -&gt; Fremennik Isles = Pirates’ Cove <span class="bbcode-i">(Pirate Island)</span><br>
Fremennik Isles -&gt; Lunar Isle = Pirates’ Cove <span class="bbcode-i">(Pirate Island)</span></p>
<p>Fremennik Isles -&gt; Miscellania = Waterbirth Island <span class="bbcode-i">(Pirate Island)</span><br>
Miscellania -&gt; Fremennik Isles = Waterbirth Island <span class="bbcode-i">(Pirate Island)</span></p>
<p>If you travel from the far Western Isle to the far Eastern Isle or vice versa you may end up at either Pirate Island.</p>
<p>Also instead of teleporting anywhere this is an entirely ship based transportation system so if you want to travel to a Minigame such as the barrows, you will need to rely on your Isles ship! Whenever you travel to a minigame, based on the Isles’ ship level, you may end up at a random Pirate Island!</p>
<p>If you do end up on a <span class="bbcode-i">Pirate Island</span> then you must complete a task such as cutting wood (Keeping it basic to begin with) to repair the ship! You will be rewarded an XP Lantern for this.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Skills</span></span></p>
<p>I’ve thought up a basic starting plan where each Isle will have access to all the skills on their own Isle.</p>
<p>For example with the Woodcutting skill their would be certain trees in certain zones littered around the island (Or they could be in the same zone, this will of course be decided based on research from the RSPS community).</p>
<p>As the Isle’s level increases more tree’s appear and better axes appear in shops (Not too high as I wish to encourage player-made axes for the economy) therefore making it easier for the masses to cut down tree’s and have access to the rich nectar that is GP which comes from selling those logs to the players or even shops for a lower “Trade in value” which should equal a vibrant economy.</p>
<p>Also when an Isle’s level increases their could be a short time bonus for the Isle in terms of XP gained. This could be used to encourage players to use a skill that maybe isn’t being as used as much as the others for whatever reason.</p>
<p>[size=8pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Slayer</span></span>[/size]</p>
<p>This would start off as a relatively easy skill but when they got to a certain level the player would start receiving tasks to go to another Isle and kill a certain monster or even as their level in Slayer increases even further - kill a certain player (of a similar level). This would be sort of like the Bounty Hunter system where you get a target. This could make Slayer much more than going to the same old Slayer Tower and killing the same old monsters etc which I see too often in RSPS’s nowadays. (This concept it of course open for discussion and would be adjusted or depending on the feedback I receive.</p>
<p>People should even begin to enjoy slayer and for the PK’ers, this is a skill which comes hand in hand with what they enjoy most!<br>
[/spoiler]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Budget</span></span></p>
<p>I’m willing to invest a fair amount into this project in order to get it working so the RSPS community can enjoy a new brilliant and unique server. Contact me over either Skype - Jamesbarker994 or over PM on here for further information.</p>
<p>Overall budget - £600 startup | £250/month running costs</p>
<p>This includes but is NOT limited too…</p>
<ul>
<li>Advertisement</li>
<li>Developers</li>
<li>VPS</li>
<li>Forum</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Interested in being part of the Development Team that bring this revolutionary RSPS to light?</span></span></p>
<p>Then please hop over to <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,667586.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,667586.0.html</a>.</p>
<p>Otherwise, any opinions on this concept would be great! Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 01:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548688-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-3-isles-unique-rsps-concept/548688.rss">[ The 3 Isles | Unique RSPS Concept ]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
