<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NPC&#39;s No-clip? [Delta]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npcs-no-clip-delta/506821</link>
    <description>When i attack NPC&#39;s on my server, my player will no-clip though walls and objects to reach that NPC, also if i attack an NPC and then run away, while the NPC is following me they no-clip through any walls and objects.

I&#39;ve been told that i need to add some sort of &quot;pathfinder&quot; to fix this error, but no-clipping only happens for me when i attack NPC&#39;s. When i&#39;m just walking somewhere, or i try to use an object that&#39;s in a place i can&#39;t reach, my player never no-clips. Doesn&#39;t this mean there has to be some sort of anti no-clip thing somewhere in my source? and that it&#39;s just not being applied for some reason when i attack NPC&#39;s?

If anyone understands my problem any help would really be appreciated  :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 05:31:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npcs-no-clip-delta/506821.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NPC&#39;s No-clip? [Delta]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Carnifex12 Carnifex12]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/carnifex12">@Carnifex12</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When i attack NPC’s on my server, my player will no-clip though walls and objects to reach that NPC, also if i attack an NPC and then run away, while the NPC is following me they no-clip through any walls and objects.</p>
<p>I’ve been told that i need to add some sort of “pathfinder” to fix this error, but no-clipping only happens for me when i attack NPC’s. When i’m just walking somewhere, or i try to use an object that’s in a place i can’t reach, my player never no-clips. Doesn’t this mean there has to be some sort of anti no-clip thing somewhere in my source? and that it’s just not being applied for some reason when i attack NPC’s?</p>
<p>If anyone understands my problem any help would really be appreciated  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npcs-no-clip-delta/506821/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npcs-no-clip-delta/506821/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 05:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506821-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/npcs-no-clip-delta/506821.rss">NPC&#39;s No-clip? [Delta]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
