<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Port help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-help/416866</link>
    <description>Hello, I recently reset my computer to factory default and now I cannot run a server. Even no-ip wont work it says error connecting to server. Before I did the reset I could run any server but now it says &quot;Cannot Assign Requested Adress: JVM_BIND&quot;. I have port forwarded and everything. I tried to run another server and it said &quot;Could not open the port 43594, it must be open in something else&quot; but I have no clue what it would be open in. I tried to find it on some port check websites but it said nothings open.

Any help is appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 01:36:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-help/416866.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Port help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@miller4 miller4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/miller4">@miller4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I recently reset my computer to factory default and now I cannot run a server. Even no-ip wont work it says error connecting to server. Before I did the reset I could run any server but now it says “Cannot Assign Requested Adress: JVM_BIND”. I have port forwarded and everything. I tried to run another server and it said “Could not open the port 43594, it must be open in something else” but I have no clue what it would be open in. I tried to find it on some port check websites but it said nothings open.</p>
<p>Any help is appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-help/416866/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-help/416866/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 01:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-416866-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-help/416866.rss">Port help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
