<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wow</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow/388776</link>
    <description>It&#39;s been a very long time for me, 4 years in fact, my past with Moparscape ranges over the very long years. Growing up with Moparscape was a real joy. I don&#39;t really do much or participate much anymore, but it&#39;s good to see that there is still a community of people here.

Anyhow, does anyone have any information on the server &quot;dds-specz&quot; which was shut down some months ago after some ups and downs, I&#39;ve just thought about it now and thats one of the only servers I was actually attatched to because of its community... Anyways, it was just a quick question to see if there is still a life within the community back at the server.

One of the all-time best servers was named &quot;Pk-Isles&quot; coded by the one and only bluurr. The finest server back in the OldSchool days. It really has left me some good memories which I hope to remember for a long time. I just wished I could go back and enjoy those times again. But I guess everything ends and you just have to move on.

Nowadays the servers a pretty much exactly the same. In my opinion, not being good as back in the old days where Dharoks Pking and the very first specials were introduced, without perfecting them such as the DDS not facing the right way ;) . I don&#39;t think MoparScape is at all the same what it used to be.

http://download.im1music.net/?link=http://mp3zee.com/btuznlv09tv4 - this helps me remember and does bring good old memories of my past here at MoparScape.

From the very first Skillcape to be released, to the new full screen HD clients. It&#39;s been a very exciting and quite impressive journey.

Cheers, if its not allowed/wrong section then just remove/move and message me please,

~ DoodleMan / Pure Str433</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 22:45:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow/388776.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Wow</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pure_str433 Pure str433]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure_str433">@Pure_str433</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s been a very long time for me, 4 years in fact, my past with Moparscape ranges over the very long years. Growing up with Moparscape was a real joy. I don’t really do much or participate much anymore, but it’s good to see that there is still a community of people here.</p>
<p>Anyhow, does anyone have any information on the server “dds-specz” which was shut down some months ago after some ups and downs, I’ve just thought about it now and thats one of the only servers I was actually attatched to because of its community… Anyways, it was just a quick question to see if there is still a life within the community back at the server.</p>
<p>One of the all-time best servers was named “Pk-Isles” coded by the one and only bluurr. The finest server back in the OldSchool days. It really has left me some good memories which I hope to remember for a long time. I just wished I could go back and enjoy those times again. But I guess everything ends and you just have to move on.</p>
<p>Nowadays the servers a pretty much exactly the same. In my opinion, not being good as back in the old days where Dharoks Pking and the very first specials were introduced, without perfecting them such as the DDS not facing the right way <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> . I don’t think MoparScape is at all the same what it used to be.</p>
<p><a href="http://download.im1music.net/?link=http://mp3zee.com/btuznlv09tv4" rel="nofollow noopener">http://download.im1music.net/?link=http://mp3zee.com/btuznlv09tv4</a> - this helps me remember and does bring good old memories of my past here at MoparScape.</p>
<p>From the very first Skillcape to be released, to the new full screen HD clients. It’s been a very exciting and quite impressive journey.</p>
<p>Cheers, if its not allowed/wrong section then just remove/move and message me please,</p>
<p>~ DoodleMan / Pure Str433</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow/388776/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow/388776/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 22:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-388776-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wow/388776.rss">Wow</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
