<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>~~I need a coder~~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-coder/225418</link>
    <description>Hey! Okay well, I&#39;m currently making my new server/client called MimzScape...
I&#39;m trying to make it look as good as possible, but I need some help on a few things.

All right, so, I&#39;ve been adding things to this server for about two or three days  and it looks alright...
I have two pk boxes, one is just flat, and the other has barriers for archers and mages.
But what I need help on is my Clan Wars minigame....
Here is a list of things that I need help with (listed from most important to least)

-Clan System (Create an official clan with your friends, and be able to give it points)
-Scoring/Winning System for Clan Wars (Gives points to the winners clan, and Will give them rewards)
-Time Limit for Clan Wars (I need a time limit to make the games short, also an alert system to let people know when the next game is starting)
-Player Limit/Just one clan limit (Right now, random people can just go through the portal and join any team that they want and there is no limit to how many people can join one team)
-Rewards for winning (I can probly do this myself, I just need a Scoring/Winning system)
-It would be cool if I could somehow create an upper level to my Clan Wars arena

~~Thats it for the list~~
I would really appreciate if someone would help me out, because once I finish this new Clan Wars system, I&#39;ll also be making other things to top the real Runescape, such as a Mod/Admin only minigame, maybe Mod/Admin wars (The same style as Clan Wars only with the restrictions of Mod/Admin only. Also I might add a new skill (probly not in this source though) and I might make an Assassin Minigame... but yeah I have a do-able ideas, so if you would like to help me please say so, if you have AIM that would totally help!


So yeah, would someone please help, it would be much appreciated  
Thanks -00ryn00 (Mimz)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 08:12:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-coder/225418.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>~~I need a coder~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@00rYn00 00rYn00]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/00ryn00">@00rYn00</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey! Okay well, I’m currently making my new server/client called MimzScape…<br>
I’m trying to make it look as good as possible, but I need some help on a few things.</p>
<p>All right, so, I’ve been adding things to this server for about two or three days  and it looks alright…<br>
I have two pk boxes, one is just flat, and the other has barriers for archers and mages.<br>
But what I need help on is my Clan Wars minigame…<br>
Here is a list of things that I need help with (listed from most important to least)</p>
<p>-Clan System (Create an official clan with your friends, and be able to give it points)<br>
-Scoring/Winning System for Clan Wars (Gives points to the winners clan, and Will give them rewards)<br>
-Time Limit for Clan Wars (I need a time limit to make the games short, also an alert system to let people know when the next game is starting)<br>
-Player Limit/Just one clan limit (Right now, random people can just go through the portal and join any team that they want and there is no limit to how many people can join one team)<br>
-Rewards for winning (I can probly do this myself, I just need a Scoring/Winning system)<br>
-It would be cool if I could somehow create an upper level to my Clan Wars arena</p>
<p><s>Thats it for the list</s><br>
I would really appreciate if someone would help me out, because once I finish this new Clan Wars system, I’ll also be making other things to top the real Runescape, such as a Mod/Admin only minigame, maybe Mod/Admin wars (The same style as Clan Wars only with the restrictions of Mod/Admin only. Also I might add a new skill (probly not in this source though) and I might make an Assassin Minigame… but yeah I have a do-able ideas, so if you would like to help me please say so, if you have AIM that would totally help!</p>
<p>So yeah, would someone please help, it would be much appreciated<br>
Thanks -00ryn00 (Mimz)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-coder/225418/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-coder/225418/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 08:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-225418-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-a-coder/225418.rss">~~I need a coder~~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
