<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My complaint to Jagex</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665</link>
    <description>What do pretentious crumbums, audacious, meretricious backbiters, and Jagex have in common? If you answered, &quot;They all advocate pertinacious perorations,&quot; then pat yourself on the back. The rest of this letter is focused exclusively on Jagex, not because I harbor any ill-will towards it but because repeating something over and over does not make it true. The logical consequences of that are clear: The facts as I see them simply do not support the false, but widely accepted, notion that 75 million years ago, a galactic tyrant named Xenu solved the overpopulation problem of his 76-planet federation by transporting the excess people to Earth, chaining them to volcanoes, and dropping H-bombs on them. Something recently occurred to me that might occur to Jagex, as well, if it would just turn down the volume of its voice for a moment: Jagex likes actions that make us the helpless puppets of our demographic labels. Could there be a conflict of interest there? If you were to ask me, I&#39;d say that it keeps trying to deceive us into thinking that all major world powers are controlled by a covert group of &quot;insiders&quot;. The purpose of this deception may be to infringe upon our most important constitutional rights. Or maybe the purpose is to lay all of society open to the predations of organized criminality. Oh what a tangled web Jagex weaves when first it practices to deceive.

But I digress. You might have heard the story that Jagex once agreed to help us protect little children from dictatorial scroungers like it. No one has located the document in which Jagex said that. No one has identified when or where Jagex said that. That&#39;s because it never said it. As you might have suspected, I have a tendency to report the more sensational things that Jagex is up to, the more shocking things, things like how it wants to convince others that phlegmatic troublemakers are the &quot;chosen people&quot; of scriptural prophecy. And I realize the difficulty that the average person has in coming to grips with that, but one can consecrate one&#39;s life to the service of a noble idea or a glorious ideology. Jagex, however, is more likely to commit all sorts of mortal sins -- not to mention an uncountable number of venial ones. I can reword my point as follows. Jagex exudes the foul odor of philistinism.

Jagex&#39;s criticisms of my letters have never successfully disproved a single fact I ever presented. Instead, its criticisms are based solely on its emotions and gut reactions. Well, I refuse to get caught up in Jagex&#39;s &quot;I think … I believe … I feel&quot; game. Although the Gospel According to Jagex says that Jagex is a perpetual victim of injustice, I maintain that if we place blame where it belongs -- in the hands of Jagex and its imprudent patsies -- then the sea of phallocentrism, on which Jagex so heavily relies, will begin to dry up. Before I move on, I just want to state once more that we wouldn&#39;t currently have a problem with larrikinism if it weren&#39;t for Jagex. Although it created the problem, aggravated the problem, and escalated the problem, Jagex insists that it can solve the problem if we just grant it more power. How naïve does it think we are? Truly, when I&#39;m through with Jagex, it&#39;ll think twice before attempting to trample into the mud all that is fine and noble and beautiful. The more I think about humorless, garrulous rakes, the more troubled I become by Jagex&#39;s animadversions. That&#39;s it for this letter. I sincerely hope that typing it was not a complete waste of energy. Unfortunately, I do realize that my words will probably trigger no useful response in the flabby synapses of Jagex&#39;s brain. I just felt obligated to go through the motions because remaining silent and inactive in the face of Jagex&#39;s squibs negates our duty as civilized members of the community.
this is a joke.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 01:59:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My complaint to Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@philip_l_g philip_l_g]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/philip_l_g">@philip_l_g</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“DeadBird, post:1, topic:67665”]What do pretentious crumbums, audacious, meretricious backbiters, and Jagex have in common? If you answered, “They all advocate pertinacious perorations,” then pat yourself on the back. The rest of this letter is focused exclusively on Jagex, not because I harbor any ill-will towards it but because repeating something over and over does not make it true. The logical consequences of that are clear: The facts as I see them simply do not support the false, but widely accepted, notion that 75 million years ago, a galactic tyrant named Xenu solved the overpopulation problem of his 76-planet federation by transporting the excess people to Earth, chaining them to volcanoes, and dropping H-bombs on them. Something recently occurred to me that might occur to Jagex, as well, if it would just turn down the volume of its voice for a moment: Jagex likes actions that make us the helpless puppets of our demographic labels. Could there be a conflict of interest there? If you were to ask me, I’d say that it keeps trying to deceive us into thinking that all major world powers are controlled by a covert group of “insiders”. The purpose of this deception may be to infringe upon our most important constitutional rights. Or maybe the purpose is to lay all of society open to the predations of organized criminality. Oh what a tangled web Jagex weaves when first it practices to deceive.</p>
<p>But I digress. You might have heard the story that Jagex once agreed to help us protect little children from dictatorial scroungers like it. No one has located the document in which Jagex said that. No one has identified when or where Jagex said that. That’s because it never said it. As you might have suspected, I have a tendency to report the more sensational things that Jagex is up to, the more shocking things, things like how it wants to convince others that phlegmatic troublemakers are the “chosen people” of scriptural prophecy. And I realize the difficulty that the average person has in coming to grips with that, but one can consecrate one’s life to the service of a noble idea or a glorious ideology. Jagex, however, is more likely to commit all sorts of mortal sins – not to mention an uncountable number of venial ones. I can reword my point as follows. Jagex exudes the foul odor of philistinism.</p>
<p>Jagex’s criticisms of my letters have never successfully disproved a single fact I ever presented. Instead, its criticisms are based solely on its emotions and gut reactions. Well, I refuse to get caught up in Jagex’s “I think<br>
I believe<br>
I feel” game. Although the Gospel According to Jagex says that Jagex is a perpetual victim of injustice, I maintain that if we place blame where it belongs – in the hands of Jagex and its imprudent patsies – then the sea of phallocentrism, on which Jagex so heavily relies, will begin to dry up. Before I move on, I just want to state once more that we wouldn’t currently have a problem with larrikinism if it weren’t for Jagex. Although it created the problem, aggravated the problem, and escalated the problem, Jagex insists that it can solve the problem if we just grant it more power. How naïve does it think we are? Truly, when I’m through with Jagex, it’ll think twice before attempting to trample into the mud all that is fine and noble and beautiful. The more I think about humorless, garrulous rakes, the more troubled I become by Jagex’s animadversions. That’s it for this letter. I sincerely hope that typing it was not a complete waste of energy. Unfortunately, I do realize that my words will probably trigger no useful response in the flabby synapses of Jagex’s brain. I just felt obligated to go through the motions because remaining silent and inactive in the face of Jagex’s squibs negates our duty as civilized members of the community.<br>
this is a joke.&lt;-- there just to point it out to people retarted enough to see it[/quote]<br>
there you go just for people who dont see it:D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 01:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-67665-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665.rss">My complaint to Jagex</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My complaint to Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exe626 exe626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exe626">@exe626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I got a feeling he didn’t type all of that…<br>
I think I’ve seen it before  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-67665-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665.rss">My complaint to Jagex</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My complaint to Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wyn10 wyn10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wyn10">@wyn10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>deadbird…all i can saw is you like typing alot…and you like making people like me read :S</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 17:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-67665-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665.rss">My complaint to Jagex</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My complaint to Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DeadBird DeadBird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deadbird">@DeadBird</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Jagex’s scribblings are completely disgusting – so much so, that if there are any children or sensitive people reading this letter, I suggest that they stop now and not read what I am about to describe. For complete details, I refer you to my forthcoming book on the subject. I shall here mention only a few random items that may be new or especially interesting to you. For instance, Jagex’s favorite buzzword these days is “crisis”. It likes to tell us that we have a crisis on our hands. It then argues that the only reasonable approach to combat this crisis is for it to construct the spectre of a terrible armed threat. In my opinion, the real crisis is the dearth of people who understand that Jagex’s latest manifesto, like all the ones that preceded it, is a consummate anthology of disastrously bad writing teeming with misquotations and inaccuracies, an odyssey of anecdotes that are occasionally entertaining, but certainly not informative. What do we owe Jagex? Nothing, absolutely nothing. If it claims otherwise, we have to stand firm and point out that Jagex has gotten away with so much for so long that it’s lost all sense of caution, all sense of limits. If you think about it, only an organization without any sense of limits could desire to defend Trotskyism, simplism, and notions of racial superiority. In such a brief letter as this, I certainly cannot refute all the endeavors of empty-headed charlatans, but perhaps I can brush away some of their most deliberate and flagrant arguments.</p>
<p>It appears that, for Jagex, “open-mindedness” isn’t a policy or a belief, but a flag to wave when it feels like it, and one to hide when it doesn’t suit its purposes. Once we realize that, what do we do? The appropriate thing, in my judgment, is to show principle, gumption, verve, and nerve. I say that because I am fed up with its loquacious and macabre behavior. We can therefore extrapolate that it is doing everything in its power to make me turn to a life of crime. The only reason I haven’t yet is that I believe in the four P’s: patience, prayer, positive thinking, and perseverance.</p>
<p>It may seem to many people, maybe even the majority, that what we’re involved in with Jagex is not a game. It’s the most serious possible business, and every serious person – every person with any shred of a sense of responsibility – must concern himself with it. Jagex will reap a harvest of death before the year is over – not necessarily by direct action, but by convincing its supporters to ransack people’s homes. Jagex’s views occasionally differ in terms of how headstrong can they are, but generally share one fundamental tendency: They move increasingly towards the establishment of a totalitarian Earth. For Jagex’s hate-filled plans to succeed, it needs to “dumb down” our society. An uninformed populace is easier to control and manipulate than an educated populace. Before long, schoolchildren will stop being required to learn the meanings of words like “galvanocauterization” and “premisrepresentation”. They will be incapable of comprehending that Jagex used to complain about being persecuted. Now it is our primary persecutor. This reversal of roles reminds me that honest people will admit that it is cowardice on Jagex’s part to fill the air with recrimination and rancor. Concerned people are not afraid to face our problems realistically, get to the root of our problems, and be determined to solve them. And sensible people know that whenever Jagex is blamed for conspiring to turn the social order upside-down so that the dregs on the bottom become the scum on the top, it blames its vicegerents. Doing so reinforces their passivity and obedience and increases their guilt, shame, terror, and conformity, thereby making them far more willing to help Jagex make nearby communities victims of environmental degradation and toxic waste dumping. Jagex doesn’t use words for communication or for exchanging information. It uses them to disarm, to hypnotize, to mislead, and to deceive.</p>
<p>Due to the power relationship between the dominator and the dominated, if Jagex had even a shred of intellectual integrity, it’d admit that I correctly predicted that it would attack the very fabric of this nation. Alas, I didn’t think it’d do that so effectively – or so soon. We must reach out to people with the message that Jagex’s adulators, when they are taken seriously at all, are considered by most scholars to be of questionable credibility. We must alert people of that. We must educate them. We must inspire them. And we must encourage them to create a world in which gnosticism, communism, and factionalism are all but forgotten.</p>
<p>It seems clear that Jagex has gone way too far with its no-compromise attitude. But we ought to look at the matter in a broader framework before we draw final conclusions on the subject: We see that Jagex is extraordinarily brazen. We’ve all known that for a long time. However, its willingness to resolve a moral failure with an immoral solution sets a new record for brazenness. Considering that Jagex never misses an opportunity to indulge its preoccupation with its alleged victimization, I find it almost laughable how it remains oblivious to the fact that by provoking its opponents to irrational rage, it makes them look like incontinent devil-worshippers – and Jagex knows it. Why Jagex would even pretend that its reinterpretations of historic events can give us deeper insights into the nature of reality is beyond me. Jagex’s toadies have been staggering around like punch-drunk fighters hit too many times – stunned, confused, betrayed, and trying desperately to rationalize Jagex’s feeble-minded, debauched squibs. It is not a pretty sight.</p>
<p>Much of our nation’s history stands as shameful testament to the danger inherent in allowing Jagex to concoct a version of reality that fully contradicts real life. I put that observation into this letter just to let you see that I, having repeatedly witnessed it make individuals indifferent to the survival of their families, insist that I have every right to refer to it as a longiloquent, rude clunk. But there is a further-reaching implication: Illiterate marauders ought to be worshipping at a higher altar than the bottom line of a balance sheet. That said, let me continue. I cannot emphasize enough how much I resent Jagex’s theories. I am tired of hearing or reading that Jagex can dissolve the bonds that join individuals to their natural communities and get away with it. You know that that is simply not true. Now the surprising news: The acid test for Jagex’s “kinder, gentler” new monographs should be, “Do they still discourage us from expressing our doctrines in whatever way we damn well please?” If the answer is yes, then we can conclude that Jagex’s beliefs (as I would certainly not call them logically reasoned arguments) have experienced a considerable amount of evolution (or perhaps more accurately, genetic drift) over the past few weeks. They used to be simply clumsy. Now, not only are they both purblind and oligophrenic, but they also serve as unequivocal proof that there’s an important difference between me and Jagex. Namely, I myself am willing to die for my cause. Jagex, in contrast, is willing to kill for its – or, if not to kill, at least to scapegoat easy, unpopular targets, thereby diverting responsibility from more culpable parties.</p>
<p>Jagex is not only immoral, but amoral. For your information, if Jagex can give us all a succinct and infallible argument proving that national-security interests can and should be sidestepped whenever its institutional interests are at stake, I will personally deliver its Nobel Prize for Pompous Rhetoric. In the meantime, Jagex insists that profits come before people. This fraud, this lie, is just one among the thousands they perpetrates. Given Jagex’s propensity for repression in the service of paradigmatic integrity, it is little wonder that I cannot compromise with Jagex; it is without principles. I cannot reason with it; it is without reason. But I can warn it, and with a warning it must definitely take to heart: Jagex will probably never understand why it scares me so much. And it really does scare me: Its practices are scary, its slurs are scary, and most of all, it will skewer me over a pit barbecue because it possesses a hatred that defies all logic and understanding, that cannot be quantified or reasoned away, and that savagely possesses what I call intellectually challenged prigs with anti-democratic and uncontrollable rage.</p>
<p>Jagex’s hypnopompic insights are a cancer that gnaws away at the national psyche, and everyone with half a brain understands that. If you can make any sense out Jagex’s shameless rantings, then you must have gotten higher marks in school than I did. There are few certainties in life. I have counted only three: death, taxes, and Jagex announcing some drugged-out thing every few weeks. Jagex is totally gung-ho about statism because it lacks more pressing soapbox issues. You won’t find many of Jagex’s cringers who will openly admit that they favor Jagex’s schemes to burn its opponents at the stake. In fact, their declamations are characterized by a plethora of rhetoric to the contrary. If you listen closely, though, you’ll hear how carefully they cover up the fact that if hedonism were an Olympic sport, Jagex would clinch the gold medal.</p>
<p>Let’s face it: Jagex spouts a lot of numbers whenever it wants to make a point. It then subjectively interprets those numbers to support its flimflams while ignoring the fact that its criticisms are in conflict with accepted morality. In reaching that conclusion, I have made the usual assumption that I stand by what I’ve written before, that Jagex commonly appoints ineffective people to important positions. It then ensures that these people stay in those positions because that makes it easy for Jagex to break down the industrial-technological system. I am cognizant that this is one letter that Jagex doesn’t want you to read, but I’m not a malodorous person. I’d like nothing more than to extend my hand in friendship to Jagex’s apostles and convey my hope that in the days to come we can work together to reinforce the contentions of all reasonable people and confute those of the most unpleasant mob bosses you’ll ever see. Unfortunately, knowing them, they’d rather rewrite and reword much of humanity’s formative works to favor Marxism because that’s what Jagex wants. Jagex says that everyone would be a lot safer if it were to monitor all of our personal communications and financial transactions – even our library records. Why on Earth does Jagex need to monitor our library records? I’ve never gotten a clear and honest answer to that question from Jagex. But what is clear is that some people think it’s a bit extreme of me to lead the way to the future, not to the past, – a bit over the top, perhaps. Well, what I ought to remind such people is that Jagex’s tractates do not represent progress. They represent insanity masquerading as progress.</p>
<p>Think about how easy it’s become for predaceous crumbums to make conditions far worse than could ever have been the case without Jagex’s huffy efforts. Jagex demands obeisance from its satraps. Then, once they prove their loyalty, Jagex forces them to generate an epidemic of corruption and social unrest. I have a T-shirt emblazoned with the following inscription: “The popularity of Jagex’s revenge fantasies among insipid radicals is a harbinger of daft things to come.” I like to wear that T-shirt to make a point about how Jagex has never gotten ahead because of its hard work or innovative ideas. Rather, all of Jagex’s successes are due to kickbacks, bribes, black market double-dealing, outright thuggery, and unsavory political intrigue. Jagex’s lynch mob appears to be growing in number. I doubtlessly pray that this is analogous to the flare-up of a candle just before extinction yet I keep reminding myself that there are three fairly obvious problems with Jagex’s ideas, each of which needs to be addressed by any letter that attempts to pave the way for people of every sex, race, and socioeconomic status to fulfill their own spiritual destiny. First, the limitation and final abolition of vigilantism presuppose the elimination of innumerable preconditions. Second, Jagex should not be allowed to operate heavy machinery, specifically, its ego. And third, Jagex has two imperatives. The first is to turn our country into an ugly cesspool overrun with scum, disease, and crime. The second imperative is to draw unsuspecting social outcasts into the orbit of prolix perverts. Jagex argues that courtesy and manners don’t count for anything. To maintain this thesis, Jagex naturally has had to shovel away a mountain of evidence, which it does by the desperate expedient of claiming that war is peace, freedom is slavery, and ignorance is strength. I have now said everything there is to say. So, to summarize it all, reason, not make-believe, is the best way to deal with the real evils of our world.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 15:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-67665-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665.rss">My complaint to Jagex</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My complaint to Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@YourDistracted YourDistracted]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yourdistracted">@YourDistracted</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Highlight as you read :). Lol. You will get it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 14:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-67665-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665.rss">My complaint to Jagex</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My complaint to Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Using a thesaurus cannot polish a turd, in fact it makes it look even more absurd - like a turd in a fluffy pink dress dancing a waltz.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 14:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-67665-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665.rss">My complaint to Jagex</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My complaint to Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exe626 exe626]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exe626">@exe626</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Is all of it a joke or did you really send that letter? lols</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 11:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-67665-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665.rss">My complaint to Jagex</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My complaint to Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DeadBird DeadBird]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deadbird">@DeadBird</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What do pretentious crumbums, audacious, meretricious backbiters, and Jagex have in common? If you answered, “They all advocate pertinacious perorations,” then pat yourself on the back. The rest of this letter is focused exclusively on Jagex, not because I harbor any ill-will towards it but because repeating something over and over does not make it true. The logical consequences of that are clear: The facts as I see them simply do not support the false, but widely accepted, notion that 75 million years ago, a galactic tyrant named Xenu solved the overpopulation problem of his 76-planet federation by transporting the excess people to Earth, chaining them to volcanoes, and dropping H-bombs on them. Something recently occurred to me that might occur to Jagex, as well, if it would just turn down the volume of its voice for a moment: Jagex likes actions that make us the helpless puppets of our demographic labels. Could there be a conflict of interest there? If you were to ask me, I’d say that it keeps trying to deceive us into thinking that all major world powers are controlled by a covert group of “insiders”. The purpose of this deception may be to infringe upon our most important constitutional rights. Or maybe the purpose is to lay all of society open to the predations of organized criminality. Oh what a tangled web Jagex weaves when first it practices to deceive.</p>
<p>But I digress. You might have heard the story that Jagex once agreed to help us protect little children from dictatorial scroungers like it. No one has located the document in which Jagex said that. No one has identified when or where Jagex said that. That’s because it never said it. As you might have suspected, I have a tendency to report the more sensational things that Jagex is up to, the more shocking things, things like how it wants to convince others that phlegmatic troublemakers are the “chosen people” of scriptural prophecy. And I realize the difficulty that the average person has in coming to grips with that, but one can consecrate one’s life to the service of a noble idea or a glorious ideology. Jagex, however, is more likely to commit all sorts of mortal sins – not to mention an uncountable number of venial ones. I can reword my point as follows. Jagex exudes the foul odor of philistinism.</p>
<p>Jagex’s criticisms of my letters have never successfully disproved a single fact I ever presented. Instead, its criticisms are based solely on its emotions and gut reactions. Well, I refuse to get caught up in Jagex’s “I think … I believe … I feel” game. Although the Gospel According to Jagex says that Jagex is a perpetual victim of injustice, I maintain that if we place blame where it belongs – in the hands of Jagex and its imprudent patsies – then the sea of phallocentrism, on which Jagex so heavily relies, will begin to dry up. Before I move on, I just want to state once more that we wouldn’t currently have a problem with larrikinism if it weren’t for Jagex. Although it created the problem, aggravated the problem, and escalated the problem, Jagex insists that it can solve the problem if we just grant it more power. How naïve does it think we are? Truly, when I’m through with Jagex, it’ll think twice before attempting to trample into the mud all that is fine and noble and beautiful. The more I think about humorless, garrulous rakes, the more troubled I become by Jagex’s animadversions. That’s it for this letter. I sincerely hope that typing it was not a complete waste of energy. Unfortunately, I do realize that my words will probably trigger no useful response in the flabby synapses of Jagex’s brain. I just felt obligated to go through the motions because remaining silent and inactive in the face of Jagex’s squibs negates our duty as civilized members of the community.<br>
this is a joke.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-67665-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-complaint-to-jagex/67665.rss">My complaint to Jagex</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
