<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[need help] distances</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-distances/105954</link>
    <description>hey.
i need a code of distances, for multi of ancients to work properly.
so far, what ive done with it, was making the gfx start from the player, contact from player to one target (doesnt need multi) and making the finish gfx at all of the mobs/players that are being attacked. e.g, ice burst, starting like ice blitz, then theres a gfx of ice in the air from the player to the mob/other player, and finally land on the mob/other player as a cube.

but, there is something bad which fucks it all. (sorry for the language :P)
when i set the range at attacknpcswithin to any low number, it doesnt attack from that distance, lets say i put range as 5, if im far from the monster, it does the animation but the gfx&#39;s and damage are not done. also, the npc still &quot;recognizes&quot; that as an attack, and fights me back. if i set the range to a large number, lets say 20, and attack it from that far, it does the gfx, it damages the mobs BUT it also attacks mobs from 20 coords away from me, like if im in the middle of a map, and at the south of me theres a mob 20 coords away from me, and also in the north a mob 20 coords away from me, it attacks both.

so, what im looking for, is a better attacknpcswithin, one that makes the player attack a mob from any range, then any mobs X coords away from the mob that was targeted by the player will be attacked. X = any range i decide it to be, or the 8 squares around the targeted mob. mostly like real runescape, yeah..

well if you got whats above, please post it, ill even credit it at my source (if you still havent gave credits yourself),  please. 

Thanks

======
P.S
mobs, monsters and npcs are the same (at least for me :P)[br][size=1]Posted on: June 04, 2007, 08:05:37 AM[/size][hr]bump plox:\</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 23:41:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-distances/105954.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[need help] distances</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Adidishen Adidishen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/adidishen">@Adidishen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hey.<br>
i need a code of distances, for multi of ancients to work properly.<br>
so far, what ive done with it, was making the gfx start from the player, contact from player to one target (doesnt need multi) and making the finish gfx at all of the mobs/players that are being attacked. e.g, ice burst, starting like ice blitz, then theres a gfx of ice in the air from the player to the mob/other player, and finally land on the mob/other player as a cube.</p>
<p>but, there is something bad which fucks it all. (sorry for the language :P)<br>
when i set the range at attacknpcswithin to any low number, it doesnt attack from that distance, lets say i put range as 5, if im far from the monster, it does the animation but the gfx’s and damage are not done. also, the npc still “recognizes” that as an attack, and fights me back. if i set the range to a large number, lets say 20, and attack it from that far, it does the gfx, it damages the mobs BUT it also attacks mobs from 20 coords away from me, like if im in the middle of a map, and at the south of me theres a mob 20 coords away from me, and also in the north a mob 20 coords away from me, it attacks both.</p>
<p>so, what im looking for, is a better attacknpcswithin, one that makes the player attack a mob from any range, then any mobs X coords away from the mob that was targeted by the player will be attacked. X = any range i decide it to be, or the 8 squares around the targeted mob. mostly like real runescape, yeah…</p>
<p>well if you got whats above, please post it, ill even credit it at my source (if you still havent gave credits yourself),  please.</p>
<p>Thanks</p>
<p>======<br>
P.S<br>
mobs, monsters and npcs are the same (at least for me :P)[br][size=1]Posted on: June 04, 2007, 08:05:37 AM[/size][hr]bump plox:\</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-distances/105954/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-distances/105954/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 23:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-105954-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-distances/105954.rss">[need help] distances</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
