<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Shortbow Bug - A Simple Model Issue</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shortbow-bug-a-simple-model-issue/329200</link>
    <description>Right, now I know some people have posted this in the past, but both they and the people who replied were [B]very[/B] vague. So I&#39;m posting this to get a nice and precise answer, since I will supply detail on my issue.

OK, well the Bug is a problem with shortbows on my server. They display as a some sort of sword on the ground beneath the characters feet as shown in Image #1:


[IMG]http://img514.imageshack.us/img514/1712/swordf.jpg[/img]
[I]Image #1 - Magic Shortbow[/I]


[IMG]http://img85.imageshack.us/img85/7782/inventg.jpg[/img]
[I]Image #1 - Magic Shortbow in Inventory[/I]


[IMG]http://img11.imageshack.us/img11/5153/dropi.jpg[/img]
[I]Image #1 - Magic Shortbow When dropped[/I]


Right, now what I do know.. or think, is that the problem is within the client, that it is to do with the models and that it is pain in the ass. BUT, after attempting to solve the problem myself, by re-adding the appropriate models, I found that it made.. no difference and I am still left with this problem, so here I am supplying some knowledge into what my client is showing.

[CODE]====================
Item Name: Shortbow
Item ID: 842
anInt174 = 2429
class8.anInt181 = 760
class8.anInt190 = 552
class8.anInt198 = 28
class8.anInt204 = 0
class8.anInt169 = 0
class8.anInt194 = 2
class8.anInt165 = -1
class8.anInt200 = -1
class8.anInt188 = -1
class8.anInt164 = -1
class8.anInt175 = -1
class8.anInt197 = -1
====================
Item Name: Oak shortbow
Item ID: 843
Original model colors: 6674
Changed model colors: 8111
anInt174 = 2562
class8.anInt181 = 1200
class8.anInt190 = 508
class8.anInt198 = 124
class8.anInt204 = 0
class8.anInt169 = 7
class8.anInt194 = 2
class8.anInt165 = 512
class8.anInt200 = 512
class8.anInt188 = -1
class8.anInt164 = -1
class8.anInt175 = -1
class8.anInt197 = -1
====================[/CODE]
[I]This is within my &quot;itemdump.txt&quot;[/I]

Now I have been looking through other clients, and I haven&#39;t found anything about the shortbows being declared, and I am aware that .txt files usually do nothing but supply information to the person reading. As you probably can guess, I am not the very best at coding clients... but this is usually the case server side, since .txt don&#39;t appear to do anything at all that I am aware of.

So I&#39;ve guessed that the model ID is 512, with recolours if necessary, but I have found and added that model using RSMV as you can see below in image #2. Now as you can probably see, there are two 512&#39;s one of which Gzipped, well ok the one highlighted in red is the shortbow model, the one in green is some random model that has caused the shortbows to be bugged (as they have replaced the model) I have in fact removed that model, yet still no luck.

[IMG]http://img651.imageshack.us/img651/1976/dats.jpg[/img]
[I]Image #2 - Models Folder[/I]

I would love it if someone would point me in the right direction as I&#39;m clearly going very wrong somewhere. Perhaps link a declared version of the shortbows for the client or perhaps a working model, I&#39;m not asking to be spoonfed, as you can see I have attempted to solve the problem and now I&#39;m at the point where I need to be assisted by someone with superior knowledge of clients.

Thanks in advance,
-Hawk</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 20:52:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shortbow-bug-a-simple-model-issue/329200.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Shortbow Bug - A Simple Model Issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Hawk_I I Hawk I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_hawk_i">@I_Hawk_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Right, now I know some people have posted this in the past, but both they and the people who replied were <span class="bbcode-b">very</span> vague. So I’m posting this to get a nice and precise answer, since I will supply detail on my issue.</p>
<p>OK, well the Bug is a problem with shortbows on my server. They display as a some sort of sword on the ground beneath the characters feet as shown in Image <span class="hashtag">#1:</span></p>
<p><img src="http://img514.imageshack.us/img514/1712/swordf.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Image <span class="hashtag">#1</span> - Magic Shortbow</span></p>
<p><img src="http://img85.imageshack.us/img85/7782/inventg.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Image <span class="hashtag">#1</span> - Magic Shortbow in Inventory</span></p>
<p><img src="http://img11.imageshack.us/img11/5153/dropi.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Image <span class="hashtag">#1</span> - Magic Shortbow When dropped</span></p>
<p>Right, now what I do know… or think, is that the problem is within the client, that it is to do with the models and that it is pain in the ass. BUT, after attempting to solve the problem myself, by re-adding the appropriate models, I found that it made… no difference and I am still left with this problem, so here I am supplying some knowledge into what my client is showing.</p>
<h1>[CODE]====================<br>
Item Name: Shortbow<br>
Item ID: 842<br>
anInt174 = 2429<br>
class8.anInt181 = 760<br>
class8.anInt190 = 552<br>
class8.anInt198 = 28<br>
class8.anInt204 = 0<br>
class8.anInt169 = 0<br>
class8.anInt194 = 2<br>
class8.anInt165 = -1<br>
class8.anInt200 = -1<br>
class8.anInt188 = -1<br>
class8.anInt164 = -1<br>
class8.anInt175 = -1<br>
class8.anInt197 = -1</h1>
<p>Item Name: Oak shortbow<br>
Item ID: 843<br>
Original model colors: 6674<br>
Changed model colors: 8111<br>
anInt174 = 2562<br>
class8.anInt181 = 1200<br>
class8.anInt190 = 508<br>
class8.anInt198 = 124<br>
class8.anInt204 = 0<br>
class8.anInt169 = 7<br>
class8.anInt194 = 2<br>
class8.anInt165 = 512<br>
class8.anInt200 = 512<br>
class8.anInt188 = -1<br>
class8.anInt164 = -1<br>
class8.anInt175 = -1<br>
class8.anInt197 = -1<br>
====================[/CODE]<br>
<span class="bbcode-i">This is within my “itemdump.txt”</span></p>
<p>Now I have been looking through other clients, and I haven’t found anything about the shortbows being declared, and I am aware that .txt files usually do nothing but supply information to the person reading. As you probably can guess, I am not the very best at coding clients… but this is usually the case server side, since .txt don’t appear to do anything at all that I am aware of.</p>
<p>So I’ve guessed that the model ID is 512, with recolours if necessary, but I have found and added that model using RSMV as you can see below in image <span class="hashtag">#2</span>. Now as you can probably see, there are two 512’s one of which Gzipped, well ok the one highlighted in red is the shortbow model, the one in green is some random model that has caused the shortbows to be bugged (as they have replaced the model) I have in fact removed that model, yet still no luck.</p>
<p><img src="http://img651.imageshack.us/img651/1976/dats.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Image <span class="hashtag">#2</span> - Models Folder</span></p>
<p>I would love it if someone would point me in the right direction as I’m clearly going very wrong somewhere. Perhaps link a declared version of the shortbows for the client or perhaps a working model, I’m not asking to be spoonfed, as you can see I have attempted to solve the problem and now I’m at the point where I need to be assisted by someone with superior knowledge of clients.</p>
<p>Thanks in advance,<br>
-Hawk</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shortbow-bug-a-simple-model-issue/329200/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shortbow-bug-a-simple-model-issue/329200/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 20:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-329200-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/shortbow-bug-a-simple-model-issue/329200.rss">Shortbow Bug - A Simple Model Issue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
