<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Starting a RSPS with delta</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041</link>
    <description>[left]Ok so you can flame me all you like I know there are about 1 million trillion tutorials on how to start a server using delta but do I care? no I do not.
The reason for me doing this pointless tutorial is because I&#39;m going to progress through a various of amount of little things you can do on delta but I have to start somewhere.
 if you would prefer a video to this tutorial feel free - [youtube]http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fG2dKc6IfDI&amp;context=C4c23c8aADvjVQa1PpcFPVuGx3ORoxnm773Q7SEAo-hrh9qKUkKIw=[/youtube]

As of the written part that begins now in a semi-detailed tutorial on how to lets say start a server.
Now this tutorial will cover starting up your server changing the ip and changing your character rights as these are the main subjected things that the majority of people like to do when they first start up there server,
So assuming you have downloaded

winrar - http://www.rarlab.com/download.htm

And

JDK - http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/javase/downloads/index.html

We can go ahead with downloading a delta source and client which ever one you choose is entirely up to you, just try to make sure it&#39;s one you like and can enjoy because making a server can be very boring at times and you don&#39;t want to give up because you can&#39;t get something done. 

Ok so go ahead and download a source and client, next thing you want to do is extract the files to a location of your choice lets say.. your desktop? or even a new folder named &quot;rsps stuff&quot; haha I know i&#39;m imaginative, so once you have downloaded your source and client and extracted the files you want to start changing the ip&#39;s about, Now in this tutorial we&#39;re going to be using the local ip &quot;127.0.0.1&quot; so only you will be able to connect to your server at the moment.

Now i&#39;m going to put these two parts into CLIENT and SOURCE sections to help clear up confusion ok so now we&#39;re going to start with..[/left]

[center][size=14pt]CLIENT[/size][/center]
[center]Ok so first of all we want to check the jdk you are using will be compatible with your Compiler.bat, now to do this we simply right click the run.bat and select edit, now your going to see a piece of coding but the part we are interested in is the part that says JDK1.0.6 or something along those lines because we need to change this to fit our JDK version &quot;if you don&#39;t know what it is go to MY COMPUTER/LOCAL DISK(c)/PROGRAM FILES/JAVA then it should appear&quot; simple replace the digits 1.0.6 with the ones on your JDK,
Now we have our jdk sorted we can begin with changing our IP that we are connecting to, So lets go ahead and do that so first of all we are still in the client folder so we need to locate the file named &quot;GUI.java or EGUI.java&quot; and we open that up in notepad.
Next we press ctrl+F and search for &quot;no-ip&quot; till we find our no-ip to change E.G &quot;TESTER.no-ip.biz&quot; so we would erase all of that with in the quotations and change it to &quot;127.0.0.1&quot; now we do this till there are no &quot;no-ip&quot; address&#39;s left we next save and compile and you have successfully change the ip on your client WELL DONE![/center]

[center][size=14pt]SOURCE[/size][/center]
[center]This is pretty much the same except a different file in a different folder also don&#39;t forget to check your compiler to make sure it&#39;s fitted for your needs, ok so this time we&#39;re looking for &quot;client.java&quot; within the source and we are going to open that with notepad as-well as we do with all .java files and yes again we search up &quot;no-ip&quot; and change the &quot;no-ip&quot; into the local ip &quot;127.0.0.1&quot; do that till there are no &quot;no-ip&quot; address&#39;s left, save and compile and you have now completed the first section of this tutorial well done to you![/center] 

[left]Now we&#39;re going to focus on the staff rights, to change this we&#39;re going to need to make a new account with in the game so start up your client and your source.
next log in with a new account and log straight back out so the account is saved and make sure to stay logged off at this part or the changes won&#39;t be put into effect,So now we go into the source folder and then into the folder named &quot;characters&quot; you then open up the file with the account name on it e.g &quot;TEST&quot; it will bring down a bunch of menus but the one we&#39;re going to focus on is &quot;playerrights = 0&quot; now we&#39;re going to change this little &quot;0&quot; on the end of that to a different digit i&#39;m going to make it an owner just for an example you can choose which one you want, to change it into an owner/co-owner account simply change the &quot;0&quot; into a &quot;3&quot; save it and log back in you will now see your changes in effect.
You can also make it into a various amount of other things for example
0 - regular player
1 - moderator
2 - administrator
3 - owner/co-owner
4 - hidden admin

These are the most common in delta based servers.

Tho i&#39;m afraid to say this is the end of this little tutorial I&#39;ve not helped many but i hope I&#39;ve helped some and will be writing more in the future![/left]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 07:15:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Starting a RSPS with delta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@smeego smeego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/smeego">@smeego</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="437041">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 arham 4:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No need for this. Thank you so much for the contribution.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<blockquote>Ok so you can flame me all you like I know there are about 1 million trillion tutorials on how to start a server using delta but do I care? no I do not.
The reason for me doing this pointless tutorial is because I'm going to progress through a various of amount of little things you can do on delta but I have to start somewhere.</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 07:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437041-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041.rss">Starting a RSPS with delta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Starting a RSPS with delta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“JavaTC, post:3, topic:437041”][quote author=arham 4 link=topic=539756.msg3951282#msg3951282 date=1332296771]<br>
No need for this. Thank you so much for the contribution.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Sadly the help section spam says otherwise.  I’m thinking of making my own.[/quote]</p>
<p>There may or may not be a need for this. Only one truth remains: People don’t search.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 05:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437041-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041.rss">Starting a RSPS with delta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Starting a RSPS with delta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="437041">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 arham 4:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No need for this. Thank you so much for the contribution.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sadly the help section spam says otherwise.  I’m thinking of making my own.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 05:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437041-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041.rss">Starting a RSPS with delta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Starting a RSPS with delta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No need for this. Thank you so much for the contribution.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 02:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437041-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041.rss">Starting a RSPS with delta</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Starting a RSPS with delta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@smeego smeego]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/smeego">@smeego</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[left]Ok so you can flame me all you like I know there are about 1 million trillion tutorials on how to start a server using delta but do I care? no I do not.<br>
The reason for me doing this pointless tutorial is because I’m going to progress through a various of amount of little things you can do on delta but I have to start somewhere.<br>
if you would prefer a video to this tutorial feel free - [youtube]<a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fG2dKc6IfDI&amp;context=C4c23c8aADvjVQa1PpcFPVuGx3ORoxnm773Q7SEAo-hrh9qKUkKIw=%5B/youtube%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fG2dKc6IfDI&amp;context=C4c23c8aADvjVQa1PpcFPVuGx3ORoxnm773Q7SEAo-hrh9qKUkKIw=[/youtube]</a></p>
<p>As of the written part that begins now in a semi-detailed tutorial on how to lets say start a server.<br>
Now this tutorial will cover starting up your server changing the ip and changing your character rights as these are the main subjected things that the majority of people like to do when they first start up there server,<br>
So assuming you have downloaded</p>
<p>winrar - <a href="http://www.rarlab.com/download.htm" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rarlab.com/download.htm</a></p>
<p>And</p>
<p>JDK - <a href="http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/javase/downloads/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/javase/downloads/index.html</a></p>
<p>We can go ahead with downloading a delta source and client which ever one you choose is entirely up to you, just try to make sure it’s one you like and can enjoy because making a server can be very boring at times and you don’t want to give up because you can’t get something done.</p>
<p>Ok so go ahead and download a source and client, next thing you want to do is extract the files to a location of your choice lets say… your desktop? or even a new folder named “rsps stuff” haha I know i’m imaginative, so once you have downloaded your source and client and extracted the files you want to start changing the ip’s about, Now in this tutorial we’re going to be using the local ip “127.0.0.1” so only you will be able to connect to your server at the moment.</p>
<p>Now i’m going to put these two parts into CLIENT and SOURCE sections to help clear up confusion ok so now we’re going to start with…[/left]</p>
<p>[center][size=14pt]CLIENT[/size][/center]<br>
[center]Ok so first of all we want to check the jdk you are using will be compatible with your Compiler.bat, now to do this we simply right click the run.bat and select edit, now your going to see a piece of coding but the part we are interested in is the part that says JDK1.0.6 or something along those lines because we need to change this to fit our JDK version “if you don’t know what it is go to MY COMPUTER/LOCAL DISK©/PROGRAM FILES/JAVA then it should appear” simple replace the digits 1.0.6 with the ones on your JDK,<br>
Now we have our jdk sorted we can begin with changing our IP that we are connecting to, So lets go ahead and do that so first of all we are still in the client folder so we need to locate the file named “GUI.java or EGUI.java” and we open that up in notepad.<br>
Next we press ctrl+F and search for “no-ip” till we find our no-ip to change E.G “TESTER.no-ip.biz” so we would erase all of that with in the quotations and change it to “127.0.0.1” now we do this till there are no “no-ip” address’s left we next save and compile and you have successfully change the ip on your client WELL DONE![/center]</p>
<p>[center][size=14pt]SOURCE[/size][/center]<br>
[center]This is pretty much the same except a different file in a different folder also don’t forget to check your compiler to make sure it’s fitted for your needs, ok so this time we’re looking for “client.java” within the source and we are going to open that with notepad as-well as we do with all .java files and yes again we search up “no-ip” and change the “no-ip” into the local ip “127.0.0.1” do that till there are no “no-ip” address’s left, save and compile and you have now completed the first section of this tutorial well done to you![/center]</p>
<p>[left]Now we’re going to focus on the staff rights, to change this we’re going to need to make a new account with in the game so start up your client and your source.<br>
next log in with a new account and log straight back out so the account is saved and make sure to stay logged off at this part or the changes won’t be put into effect,So now we go into the source folder and then into the folder named “characters” you then open up the file with the account name on it e.g “TEST” it will bring down a bunch of menus but the one we’re going to focus on is “playerrights = 0” now we’re going to change this little “0” on the end of that to a different digit i’m going to make it an owner just for an example you can choose which one you want, to change it into an owner/co-owner account simply change the “0” into a “3” save it and log back in you will now see your changes in effect.<br>
You can also make it into a various amount of other things for example<br>
0 - regular player<br>
1 - moderator<br>
2 - administrator<br>
3 - owner/co-owner<br>
4 - hidden admin</p>
<p>These are the most common in delta based servers.</p>
<p>Tho i’m afraid to say this is the end of this little tutorial I’ve not helped many but i hope I’ve helped some and will be writing more in the future![/left]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 02:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437041-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/starting-a-rsps-with-delta/437041.rss">Starting a RSPS with delta</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
