<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Question regarding threads</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702</link>
    <description>A little while ago i posted the basic idea of what I&#39;m now working on... which can be found here: http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,426688.0.html

more to the question: On the client end what is the rule of thumb for the number of threads you should not exceed? I am currently on 3 threads (1 for communications, 1 for rendering + main thread) however in my planning I have felt that I will need to get to 5 threads to really give the users the experience I am looking for. If performance is the only issue and the number of threads do not matter, then I guess I would be okay with 5 or so threads because its barely taking up any memory and cpu with the way I have the entire project structured. I&#39;m just a bit hesitant when it comes to networking and concurrency in java so I&#39;m seeking some helpful feedback on the topic.

side note; Client and server and are both in java.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 09:45:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hayley1 Hayley;]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hayley1">@Hayley1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What’s the matter with a single thread for game logic and a thread pool for networking?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 09:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jython super_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jython">@Jython</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="15" data-topic="344702">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 c|p:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>why not just use an EventManager and ScheduledExecutorServices with resource pooling and cached thread stacks in an overclocked jvm hypervising runtime?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>EventManager is outdated you should use javax.swing.Timer</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 19:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“repacsenur, post:2, topic:344702”]use threads only where you have loops which are nearly forever because without threads it won’t be able to do multi-tasking since code just goes in one direction and it will never leave that loop[/quote]Bahah what.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 18:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cheese_Police c|p]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheese_police">@Cheese_Police</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>why not just use an EventManager and ScheduledExecutorServices with resource pooling and cached thread stacks in an overclocked jvm hypervising runtime?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 16:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DarKcookie DarKcookie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/darkcookie">@DarKcookie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why not use a synchronized queue to handle incoming events,<br>
and forget about the entire timestamp comparison?</p>
<p>Have your client-server communication thread(-pool)<br>
store events into a queue (LinkedBlockingQueue for example),<br>
then have another thread(-pool) handle those events one by one.<br>
For optimal cpu usage, you would probably want to use<br>
a single thread for all events that require ‘timestamping’,<br>
and have a thread-pool handle the rest of the queue.</p>
<p>You shouldn’t think of threads as “something I need X amount of”.<br>
Less threads means less thinking about synchronization and (dead)locks,<br>
more threads means better cpu usage (up to a certain threads/core ratio).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 15:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@abraham2119 abraham2119]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/abraham2119">@abraham2119</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="12" data-topic="344702">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 quest rs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the pid I’m avoiding</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is actually something you should use. Let it be a value derived from the username or based on slot availability, it doesn’t matter. It’s much better to have an identification system based on a single integral value than on a full username. Primarily because you send x amount of bytes (I’d go with two) instead of the length of each username for each packet pertaining to a specific player. Secondly, assuming you want your game to not be as easily reversed, you don’t want to send packets containing the full ASCII usernames as any packet sniffer setup to listen on the game connection will be able reverse the protocol without even having to reverse engineer the client itself. This is also a reason to avoid TEXT-based networking protocols.</p>
<p>Additionally, although your professor is right about increasing potential bugs in your application with more threads, that in itself is not a particularly good reason to refrain from using them, as with the help of the Concurrent API, multi-threaded applications that share class members are easily written. The real reason is because, as I said before, it’s a huge waste of resources.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 18:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@quest_rs quest rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/quest_rs">@quest_rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sorry if I am sounding obnoxious but I am really not ignoring any feedback from you guys. And I’m sorry if it’s offensive but this foum is a troll center now adays where people who have opened up the runescape client and changed a few ints call themselves programmer. I’m sure that’s not the case for the people who has posted on here.</p>
<p>Back on track; repac the pid I’m avoiding, I asked my prof at uni about this and he said the design I had was good however the increased num of threads meant chances of errors increasing, I’m guessing he wAs reffering to thread management and sync, deadlocks etc. And Abraham you almost got it right, the players do race but the order does not matter to the user, but to the client. So your timestamps idea just may work, I’m typing up the pseduo code atm.</p>
<p>Also repac; it’s a bubble chat type thing where the chat will just scroll off screen where the player stands, but I guess putting all the rendering in one section will be easier to manage, though it will greatly increase render timeand I will need to make up for it by reducing thread sleep times even when idle (when there’s no updates) to continue processing the chat</p>
<p>thanks for the constructive feed backs, I really appreciate the diacussion, as I originally posted I was lookig for either agreement or alternatives, which I’m getting here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 18:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@abraham2119 abraham2119]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/abraham2119">@abraham2119</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As for your runescape-classic analogy, I’m not very familiar with the game since I haven’t played in around 6 years, but I’m assuming that it’s some kind of competition to whoever opens the chest first. If that’s the case, then clearly, there can’t be two that open it at a same time.Therefore you have to have some sort of prioritization system. The fact that it’s unfair for the other player doesn’t make a difference, as the player will not recognize that they both sent it at the same exact time (the chances of them clicking at the exact same moment is also quite unlikely). Regardless, if time precision is such an important matter, you can include a time stamp in your packet header and then compare with other packets in the queue.</p>
<p>There are better alternatives over a crappy design.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 14:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@repacsenur repacsenur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/repacsenur">@repacsenur</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>think about the days back on runescape classic the person with the lowest pid (playerId) no matter if both users sent packets at 200 milliseconds each on nature rune theiving chest. the person with the lowest playerId Always opened the chest first no matter how hard you tried.</p>
<p>Because in runescape all players connections are assigned to a array not a thread then they are iterated by playerId’s and handled in occurrence then packets sent out in just a for loop or something</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">for(pid=0;pid&lt;maxPlayers;pid++) {
  if(player[pid] != null) {
    doServerSideLogic(pid); //which builds up on some packet stream
    doMoreLogic(pid); //builds up more if anything to build could be nothing
    sendPacket(pid);
  }
}</code></pre>
<p>Or you can use a for each loop and then you can avoid the null check because it will go by existing players only but then again a null may exist too.</p>
<p>Then again this approach may be bad too what if some user adds too much processing logic with one huge packet and it will lag the server for everybody cause a DDoS because everyone will have to wait until this one user is fully processed so some smart fix should be thought of to fix that issue maybe some kind of timer which checks how long processing is taking if too long spawn a new thread</p>
<p>lol as for the chat you don’t need a thread for that if you got a thread to handle incoming packets then when a chat packet comes in just add it to queue list for rendering when the render thread is ready to render player chat’s, same with all other graphic related packets.</p>
<p>Just set a boolean flag saying updateReady but if you have multiple updates then a boolean flag wont cut it have to use a queue of some kind of array or something then just check length if greater then 0 copy all values it (idk if this best way because if you don’t there is risk of new updates getting added by packet thread as you are processing them) so after copied then process it then using removeAll remove all the updates you already processed from packet update array then finally clear/destroy the copied array…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 14:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@abraham2119 abraham2119]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/abraham2119">@abraham2119</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>quest rs, unless you are using an asynchronous server approach, there won’t be a time when two packets are sent at the same time since the server’s packet system should be synchronous. Therefore, the thread-per-client is deemed to be useless. Yes, if two users click at the same time one will be handled first, but the difference will not be noticeable <span class="bbcode-b">at all</span> from the player’s perspective. It’s not worth it to waste so much useful resources on such a useless task.</p>
<p>Stop being so obnoxious and listen to people that have more experience than yourself regarding game design, and basic design in general.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ollie Ollie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ollie">@Ollie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yo i have a 5 core cpu so program me a 5 core program. thanks. please.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 08:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@quest_rs quest rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/quest_rs">@quest_rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>that maybe so, but do you have something better to suggest which will get the same result?</p>
<p>the p1 p2 example i posted above will be occurring very frequently so I have chosen to keep the feature. This way, user to click first will always be gaurenteed the position instead of the user who joined first.</p>
<p>Just because thread per client is poorly implemented and used by “idiots”  doesn’t mean its a bad choice in every situation ?</p>
<p>p.s I know that ultimately it will come down to first come first serve because of how instructions are executed, but the user wont be able to notice that kind of a difference where if I updated each character in the list first before updating the next. Another thing to keep in mind is that I am keeping in mind of other factors such as user’s network speed, OS, hardware, JVM etc.</p>
<p>edit:<br>
but it seems perhaps we got a little off topic, I just need to know what may be the concerns of having so many threads so I may tackle each one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 07:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Speljohan Speljohan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/speljohan">@Speljohan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“quest rs, post:5, topic:344702”]well abraham perhaps you could help me out.</p>
<p>The point of thread per player is that the client can constantly keep the player in a state of “alive” competition. The users do not get to  share the same location so when they pick their destination, they do not have to wait in a line up to be updated.</p>
<p>ex: P1 is index 1 and P2 is index 2 in the list.</p>
<p>P2 and P1 click at the same time on the same location, player 1’s coordinated would be updated first resulting in p2 being blocked out.</p>
<p>Personally because this is client sided I wont have to worry about it performance because i know my target audience can handle the required. If you have any suggestions on being able to get the same results in another approach i’d love to give it a try. I prefer the minimum thread count myself but its the only way I can see it written in the way I want it.[/quote]Only idiots do thread per client, i doubt any game out there does it at all tbh.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 07:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@quest_rs quest rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/quest_rs">@quest_rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well abraham perhaps you could help me out.</p>
<p>The point of thread per player is that the client can constantly keep the player in a state of “alive” competition. The users do not get to  share the same location so when they pick their destination, they do not have to wait in a line up to be updated.</p>
<p>ex: P1 is index 1 and P2 is index 2 in the list.</p>
<p>P2 and P1 click at the same time on the same location, player 1’s coordinated would be updated first resulting in p2 being blocked out.</p>
<p>Personally because this is client sided I wont have to worry about it performance because i know my target audience can handle the required. If you have any suggestions on being able to get the same results in another approach i’d love to give it a try. I prefer the minimum thread count myself but its the only way I can see it written in the way I want it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 05:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@abraham2119 abraham2119]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/abraham2119">@abraham2119</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“quest rs, post:1, topic:344702”]A little while ago i posted the basic idea of what I’m now working on… which can be found here: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,426688.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,426688.0.html</a></p>
<p>more to the question: On the client end what is the rule of thumb for the number of threads you should not exceed? I am currently on 3 threads (1 for communications, 1 for rendering + main thread) however in my planning I have felt that I will need to get to 5 threads to really give the users the experience I am looking for. If performance is the only issue and the number of threads do not matter, then I guess I would be okay with 5 or so threads because its barely taking up any memory and cpu with the way I have the entire project structured. I’m just a bit hesitant when it comes to networking and concurrency in java so I’m seeking some helpful feedback on the topic.</p>
<p>side note; Client and server and are both in java.[/quote]Five threads is fine. The concern with threads comes into place because of their memory occupancy; the default stack size per thread differs per operating system, but if I recall correctly, it’s 265 KB on Windows/Linux x86. You can change this setting by passing the ‘-Xss’ argument to the JVM. Regardless, I don’t see why you need anymore threads than the ones you are using. You can use the rendering thread as an “all-around” thread and handle everything else there too. You should leave the main thread idling, as it carries a preferential thread priority status, and end up just using two.</p>
<p>[quote=“quest rs, post:3, topic:344702”]well I was hoping to get:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>updates the entire graphics</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>used for communicating with server</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>update game logic for each player OR I could break up the graphics thread to have a thread for each player (aprox 25 - but idk if thats such a good design however EXTREMELY EASY to implement thread / player on screen  ----**only 25 players are allowed in one visible section of the map) which just carries details about any users in the area and draws them</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>backup / misc tasks</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I personally prefer the 4 thread design but i am tempted to pull the 25 threads just to see what will happen.[/quote]<br>
As I said above, tasks ‘3 and 4’ should just be executed on the rendering thread. The reason for this is that game logic should be handled at par with rendering since variations in systems’ processing power will affect the rate of the game, and because of this, rendering should not be unsynchronized with game status.</p>
<p>As for the thread-per-player design, that’s the stupidest approach you can take. Again, have a list of players and iterate through them in the “game thread” and process them respectively.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 05:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@quest_rs quest rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/quest_rs">@quest_rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well I was hoping to get:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>updates the entire graphics</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>used for communicating with server</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>update game logic for each player OR I could break up the graphics thread to have a thread for each player (aprox 25 - but idk if thats such a good design however EXTREMELY EASY to implement thread / player on screen  ----**only 25 players are allowed in one visible section of the map) which just carries details about any users in the area and draws them</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>backup / misc tasks</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I personally prefer the 4 thread design but i am tempted to pull the 25 threads just to see what will happen.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 05:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@repacsenur repacsenur]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/repacsenur">@repacsenur</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>use threads only where you have loops which are nearly forever because without threads it won’t be able to do multi-tasking since code just goes in one direction and it will never leave that loop</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 04:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Question regarding threads</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@quest_rs quest rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/quest_rs">@quest_rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A little while ago i posted the basic idea of what I’m now working on… which can be found here: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,426688.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,426688.0.html</a></p>
<p>more to the question: On the client end what is the rule of thumb for the number of threads you should not exceed? I am currently on 3 threads (1 for communications, 1 for rendering + main thread) however in my planning I have felt that I will need to get to 5 threads to really give the users the experience I am looking for. If performance is the only issue and the number of threads do not matter, then I guess I would be okay with 5 or so threads because its barely taking up any memory and cpu with the way I have the entire project structured. I’m just a bit hesitant when it comes to networking and concurrency in java so I’m seeking some helpful feedback on the topic.</p>
<p>side note; Client and server and are both in java.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 04:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344702-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-regarding-threads/344702.rss">Question regarding threads</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
