<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617</link>
    <description>Alot of my friends asked me how i pay for real rs membership since i don&#39;t have a job or credit card, or anything really :P
and since free-trade might be back, i thought i&#39;d share this way with some of you incase you want to play rs again once in a while for the sake of remembering your child hood.

Anyways, i&#39;ll give a brief description on how i make some money for rs membership:
   [u]First[/u] off, i use this advertising program that shortens my links and adds a 5 second waiting period to skip the add, it doesn&#39;t make too much that the beginning, but the more clicks you get then each further click will give you more money then the one before. now it&#39;s not like you can live off of this, but if you post links on forums and stuff often, then you could use this so that you get a little something and save for a thing like rs membership. Now here&#39;s the link to where you can register: *  as you can see, the link is kind of weird, and here&#39;s an example of a shortened link: * now that&#39;s just a link to a different thread that i made on this forum. Me telling you this is also a positive thing for myself, because for each referral, i get a small amount of cash too, (but the referral has to get some clicks on their shortened links too)

  My [u]Second way[/u] of making a small amount of extra cash for things like rs membership is by using a thing called &quot;google&quot; it&#39;s basically a search engine like Google, but for searching you sometimes get these points, for which you may eventually exchange for things like paypal cash, ultimate game cards, amazon gift cards, etc.  here&#39;s the link for registration: *    and once again, this link is good for me, cause if you use it, i get a referral, and whenever you search and get points, i get some too. 

you might think it&#39;s pointless, and it might be if you have a nice steady job and have a way of paying online, but for me, it&#39;s just a win-win situation, because i have no in-come, and by doing the things i normally do (post links on forums, use search engine) i get paid a small amount of cash, i don&#39;t really pay attention to how much i make, i don&#39;t try hard, you should just go about your everyday activities, and just use these as a part of a habit, well that&#39;s hat i do.

Anyways, thanks for reading, i hope this is helpful to some people, i don&#39;t know whether what i&#39;m doing is against regulations, but i was requested this by some friends so i thought i&#39;d just share it with all you :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 17:46:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="377617">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/reyx7/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> reyx7:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re not allowed to have your referral as the only link available…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><span class="mention">@OP</span> Anyone could google this and come up with the same results, all you’re doing is trying to make some money off this topic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 17:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377617-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617.rss">How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WhiteWolves WhiteWolves]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whitewolves">@WhiteWolves</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xxlukexx, post:3, topic:377617”][quote]<br>
Or you could Develop a RSPS and kindly accept donations.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>why would you do that? weeks/months of development, when all you need is 3 pounds…[/quote]<br>
i think what he meant was, if you already have a server open, then just ask for some donations, not make one from scratch just for the money (and i do not own a rsps any longer)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="377617">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/reyx7/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> reyx7:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re not allowed to have your referral as the only link available…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>first of all, the sites are easy to find,<br>
and why wouldn’t i be allowed? it’s a win-win situation, they get to start making some money and i get a little too, it’s not like they get less because i referred them. i don’t see why you would even state this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 17:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377617-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617.rss">How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You’re not allowed to have your referral as the only link available…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 16:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377617-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617.rss">How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlukexx xxlukexx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlukexx">@xxlukexx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Or you could Develop a RSPS and kindly accept donations.</blockquote>
<p>why would you do that? weeks/months of development, when all you need is 3 pounds…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 15:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377617-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617.rss">How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlukexx xxlukexx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlukexx">@xxlukexx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Or you could go in your mums purse and take the card.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377617-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617.rss">How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WhiteWolves WhiteWolves]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whitewolves">@WhiteWolves</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alot of my friends asked me how i pay for real rs membership since i don’t have a job or credit card, or anything really <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
and since free-trade might be back, i thought i’d share this way with some of you incase you want to play rs again once in a while for the sake of remembering your child hood.</p>
<p>Anyways, i’ll give a brief description on how i make some money for rs membership:<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">First</span> off, i use this advertising program that shortens my links and adds a 5 second waiting period to skip the add, it doesn’t make too much that the beginning, but the more clicks you get then each further click will give you more money then the one before. now it’s not like you can live off of this, but if you post links on forums and stuff often, then you could use this so that you get a little something and save for a thing like rs membership. Now here’s the link to where you can register: *  as you can see, the link is kind of weird, and here’s an example of a shortened link: * now that’s just a link to a different thread that i made on this forum. Me telling you this is also a positive thing for myself, because for each referral, i get a small amount of cash too, (but the referral has to get some clicks on their shortened links too)</p>
<p>My <span class="bbcode-u">Second way</span> of making a small amount of extra cash for things like rs membership is by using a thing called “google” it’s basically a search engine like Google, but for searching you sometimes get these points, for which you may eventually exchange for things like paypal cash, ultimate game cards, amazon gift cards, etc.  here’s the link for registration: *    and once again, this link is good for me, cause if you use it, i get a referral, and whenever you search and get points, i get some too.</p>
<p>you might think it’s pointless, and it might be if you have a nice steady job and have a way of paying online, but for me, it’s just a win-win situation, because i have no in-come, and by doing the things i normally do (post links on forums, use search engine) i get paid a small amount of cash, i don’t really pay attention to how much i make, i don’t try hard, you should just go about your everyday activities, and just use these as a part of a habit, well that’s hat i do.</p>
<p>Anyways, thanks for reading, i hope this is helpful to some people, i don’t know whether what i’m doing is against regulations, but i was requested this by some friends so i thought i’d just share it with all you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 15:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377617-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-make-money-through-links-save-enough-for-rs-membership/377617.rss">How to make money through links (save enough for rs membership)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
