<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My life sucks</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911</link>
    <description>Hey everyone, I needed a place to vent about how much of a fail my life is, and since I haven&#39;t posted on here in a long, long time, I figured here&#39;s the place.

I&#39;m 17 years old. I haven&#39;t had any relationships what-so-ever. Excluding a 5th grade &quot;girl friend&quot;. I&#39;ve never even kissed someone else.

Right after 5th grade, I moved to a completely new place from where I lived before. It was a 3 hour drive from where I used to live. Day one of my new school I was labeled as weird. I sat with the weird kids, and couldn&#39;t do anything about it. I was picked and joked on until around 8th grade.

In 8th grade, the bullying and labeling went away. I didn&#39;t really make any friends, I actually started alienating myself from people. I stopped trying to talk to other people. I just did my work, and talked with the few friends I had. I wasn&#39;t labeled as weird anymore. But, I was too scared to speak up and try to make friends because I didn&#39;t want to go back to when I was getting picked and joked on.

Since then, I&#39;ve done the same thing. I haven&#39;t talked to many people, excluding people that I already knew, and people friends have introduced me to. I was friendzoned last year by an ugly chick, which makes me feel bad too. I&#39;m glad I didn&#39;t go out with her, now that I look at her, but it was like a kick in the face.

So now here we are. I&#39;ve lied to friends about experiences just to keep from getting joked on. I hate lying about that kind of shit, but it&#39;s for the better. Don&#39;t get me wrong, I would talk to people, but I&#39;m so fucking scared about fucking up. I choke and say the wrong words. It&#39;s not just girls I have a problem talking to. It&#39;s anyone. I even quit playing Baseball my freshman year because I was too scared of being rejected by the &quot;jocks&quot; of my school. I was actually decent at the sport, but I&#39;m so fucking scared that I&#39;m just going to get labeled weird like before, and I&#39;m going to get joked on and bullied like before. I&#39;m a junior in highschool, and I haven&#39;t even kissed a girl yet. There are girls in my school who fucking have children.

If I was to rate myself looks-wise, I&#39;d rate myself a 4.5/10. I&#39;m not a great looking guy, and I&#39;m not nearly in the physical shape I should be in. I&#39;m not fat, but I&#39;m 150lbs and haven&#39;t had much physical activity for 3 years. 

I&#39;ve been thinking for so long on what I should do to try to improve my situation. The key to doing anything that I want requires confidence, which I have absolutely none of. I&#39;m going to try to spend all of my summer getting in shape. I&#39;m going to be dieting and going to the gym every day. I feel like if I can look at myself with confidence, then maybe I can fix all this shit. For the few people who actually read through this shit, add the word lemon in your response. Thank you very much for reading if you did.


TL;DR:
My life sucks.
OP&#39;s a fag.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 20:06:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="30" data-topic="438911">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>DO NOT, lie to your friends about experiences</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Over exaggerate them for epicness.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 20:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Try these:</p>
<p>Exercise - run 10-20 minutes a day AT LEAST, and weight lift if you can &gt; confidence x300% You said youre going to the gym, follow one of these routines: <a href="http://scoobysworkshop.com/teen-workout-plan/">http://scoobysworkshop.com/teen-workout-plan/</a> and once that gets easy go to <a href="http://scoobysworkshop.com">http://scoobysworkshop.com</a> and on the right look at intermediate or advanced. And drink whey protein when youre done working out, and stay away from creatine or youll look freakish. Youll notice results almost immediately both physically and mentally and start seeing major changes in 2 more weeks. Goes by fast though <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Get a haircut - People who hate their own life tend to have scruffy bowl cuts or faggy emo dickloving hair and arent usually higenic . Get a short haircut and clean up. If you have hair between your eyebrows pluck it once every two weeks (im not saying pluck your entire eyebrows to look penciled in) If you wear glasses try new frames or try contacts.</p>
<p>Wear normal clothes - Dont wear short shorts, shirts that are huge or shirts that look super faded or stained. Wear shirts that fit, if you have to try aeropostal or abercrombie because they fit very well youll just look like a walking billboard. Dont wear skinny jeans and dont wear supper baggy jeans. Dont wear sweat pants unless you look like eminem.</p>
<p>DO NOT, lie to your friends about experiences (if theyre good friends) unless its something truly degrading that you want to erase. In most cases theyll help you get in the loop of things if they know youre new to something, no biggy.</p>
<p>Whenever I see people in your situation I always ask myself what they can do to start and reverse that, and exercise is probably the <span class="hashtag">#1</span>, but when the rest of those suggestions all come together itll affect how you look as a whole. More people wont mind being around you and they wont isolate themselves from you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 20:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@time_of_rune time of rune]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/time_of_rune">@time_of_rune</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:12, topic:438911”]This is sad, why don’t you just grow up and act like a man should (if you’re a man). I have few friends i am close to but then there are friends i talk to regularly. I’m not the kind of person to be ‘out there’ but when i want to be heard i am, i don’t like people pushing me around. Why don’t you get out of your comfort zone, and go find people who will like your ‘weirdness’ because if they don’t like it then you aren’t really friends. You cannot live your life in fear of being labelled because in the end everyone is, you need to get over it.</p>
<p>Is it just me or does this sound kinda like a troll? Stereotypical nerd online ftw?[/quote]</p>
<p>I really don’t appreciate the derogatory comments. If you knew how it felt to be in my shoes, and think the way I do, you’d understand it’s so hard to just completely forget what life has “taught” me. If you think I’m trolling, so be it.</p>
<p>[quote=“Muroth, post:14, topic:438911”]i’m just generally shy in person, until you get to know me, then you’ll find me fucking hyper. i used to ignore the ‘popular’ crowd as  i saw them as douches, but once i got to know them, they’re not all that bad. everybody can feel lonely at one point, doesn’t mean you can’t fix that. you’ll find friends, maybe not in highschool with that attitude.</p>
<p>if troll, congratulations, i gave a troll advice.[/quote]</p>
<p>Thanks for the advice. Like I said before, you can think I’m a troll if you want. I just needed a place to vent.</p>
<p>[quote=“xdeathstarsx, post:15, topic:438911”]You think you’re special you little faggot, 99% of this community are 20 year old virgins, shut the fuck up whining cunt.</p>
<p>You have no friends because you’re a little 12 year old who cries that he’s never got his willy wet, here’s an idea, go and fuck a silicone egg like Lawl and then try go outside instead of crying on a private server community about how much of a little bitch you are. Man the fuck up you wet anal fart.[/quote]</p>
<p>Love you too bro.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="17" data-topic="438911">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/_vengeance/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> _Vengeance:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We don’t care. Some words of advice, though, if you think a forum full of 13 year olds is a good place to seek counsel, you have a fucking long way to go before you’ll be worth anything to anyone. Go to some pickup artist forums, read all of the advice you can find. You’ll become one of those “douches” that you never would have liked (because you were a jealous moron and they picked on you), but you’ll become everything that you claim you want to be - providing you can grow some fucking balls. At least you realise you’re a pussy/fagot/loser. Most people don’t.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The point of this thread was to vent my frustration, not to seek advice or feels.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 19:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frozon566 frozon566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frozon566">@frozon566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="25" data-topic="438911">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Miss Silabsoft:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>and as long as you don’t do what tree does you will get an opportunity.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lol.</p>
<hr>
<p>just decide right now EXACTLY what you want to become/do/say and then watch this:</p>
<p>[youtube]<a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_7I7iasuIdw&amp;feature=pyv%5B/youtube%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_7I7iasuIdw&amp;feature=pyv[/youtube]</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 19:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Eh Pretty Easy, post:26, topic:438911”][quote author=t4 link=topic=541617.msg3967819#msg3967819 date=1333896501]<br>
as long as you’re not a complete aspie you’ll fit into uni assuming you’re entering a science major<br>
[/quote]Doing a science major further isolates him from the rest of the world as it is common sense that people with such a career end up being hermits.[/quote]<br>
perhaps, but your associates will most likely befriend you</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 18:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“t4, post:16, topic:438911”]as long as you’re not a complete aspie you’ll fit into uni assuming you’re entering a science major[/quote]Doing a science major further isolates him from the rest of the world as it is common sense that people with such a career end up being hermits.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 18:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just be yourself and not care too much about it for everyone it comes at different times, and as long as you don’t do what tree does you will get an opportunity.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 16:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xdeathstarsx, post:20, topic:438911”][quote author=reyx7 link=topic=541617.msg3967833#msg3967833 date=1333898042]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>You think you’re special you little faggot, 99% of this community are 20 year old virgins, shut the fuck up whining cunt.</p>
<p>You have no friends because you’re a little 12 year old who cries that he’s never got his willy wet, here’s an idea, go and fuck a silicone egg like Lawl and then try go outside instead of crying on a private server community about how much of a little bitch you are. Man the fuck up you wet anal fart.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The words of a sad, lonely little boy.</p>
<ol>
<li>99% of this community isn’t 20</li>
<li>A decent portion of these forums don’t fuck around with private servers</li>
<li>Cussing does not make you cool</li>
</ol>
<p>I’m sure on the other side I’m talking to a lost, weak person with no friends and sits in his tiny apartment living a pathetic life between your shit job at McDonalds and coming home browsing /b/ with the other people who are lost with no soul. May hell continue to reign upon you.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Fuck off you fucking fuck wit, you fuck yourself you little fucking moron before i fucking fuck your mother up the fucking fuckhole.[/quote]</p>
<p>I think I proved my point. Better yet, you proved it for me. Thanks, asshole.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 15:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>^ I reported his post anyway.  Even if he isn’t trolling, he shouldn’t even be allowed to post shit like that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 15:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xdeathstarsx, post:20, topic:438911”][quote author=reyx7 link=topic=541617.msg3967833#msg3967833 date=1333898042]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>You think you’re special you little faggot, 99% of this community are 20 year old virgins, shut the fuck up whining cunt.</p>
<p>You have no friends because you’re a little 12 year old who cries that he’s never got his willy wet, here’s an idea, go and fuck a silicone egg like Lawl and then try go outside instead of crying on a private server community about how much of a little bitch you are. Man the fuck up you wet anal fart.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The words of a sad, lonely little boy.</p>
<ol>
<li>99% of this community isn’t 20</li>
<li>A decent portion of these forums don’t fuck around with private servers</li>
<li>Cussing does not make you cool</li>
</ol>
<p>I’m sure on the other side I’m talking to a lost, weak person with no friends and sits in his tiny apartment living a pathetic life between your shit job at McDonalds and coming home browsing /b/ with the other people who are lost with no soul. May hell continue to reign upon you.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Fuck off you fucking fuck wit, you fuck yourself you little fucking moron before i fucking fuck your mother up the fucking fuckhole.[/quote]<br>
You’re either really bad at trolling or so self absorbed that you’re delusional.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 15:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xdeathstarsx, post:20, topic:438911”][quote author=reyx7 link=topic=541617.msg3967833#msg3967833 date=1333898042]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>You think you’re special you little faggot, 99% of this community are 20 year old virgins, shut the fuck up whining cunt.</p>
<p>You have no friends because you’re a little 12 year old who cries that he’s never got his willy wet, here’s an idea, go and fuck a silicone egg like Lawl and then try go outside instead of crying on a private server community about how much of a little bitch you are. Man the fuck up you wet anal fart.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The words of a sad, lonely little boy.</p>
<ol>
<li>99% of this community isn’t 20</li>
<li>A decent portion of these forums don’t fuck around with private servers</li>
<li>Cussing does not make you cool</li>
</ol>
<p>I’m sure on the other side I’m talking to a lost, weak person with no friends and sits in his tiny apartment living a pathetic life between your shit job at McDonalds and coming home browsing /b/ with the other people who are lost with no soul. May hell continue to reign upon you.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Fuck off you fucking fuck wit, you fuck yourself you little fucking moron before i fucking fuck your mother up the fucking fuckhole.[/quote]<br>
protroll or typical 13yo</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 15:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xdeathstarsx x Albi x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xdeathstarsx">@xdeathstarsx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“reyx7, post:19, topic:438911”][quote author=xdeathstarsx link=topic=541617.msg3967812#msg3967812 date=1333895659]<br>
You think you’re special you little faggot, 99% of this community are 20 year old virgins, shut the fuck up whining cunt.</p>
<p>You have no friends because you’re a little 12 year old who cries that he’s never got his willy wet, here’s an idea, go and fuck a silicone egg like Lawl and then try go outside instead of crying on a private server community about how much of a little bitch you are. Man the fuck up you wet anal fart.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>The words of a sad, lonely little boy.</p>
<ol>
<li>99% of this community isn’t 20</li>
<li>A decent portion of these forums don’t fuck around with private servers</li>
<li>Cussing does not make you cool</li>
</ol>
<p>I’m sure on the other side I’m talking to a lost, weak person with no friends and sits in his tiny apartment living a pathetic life between your shit job at McDonalds and coming home browsing /b/ with the other people who are lost with no soul. May hell continue to reign upon you.[/quote]</p>
<p>Fuck off you fucking fuck wit, you fuck yourself you little fucking moron before i fucking fuck your mother up the fucking fuckhole.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 15:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xdeathstarsx, post:15, topic:438911”]You think you’re special you little faggot, 99% of this community are 20 year old virgins, shut the fuck up whining cunt.</p>
<p>You have no friends because you’re a little 12 year old who cries that he’s never got his willy wet, here’s an idea, go and fuck a silicone egg like Lawl and then try go outside instead of crying on a private server community about how much of a little bitch you are. Man the fuck up you wet anal fart.[/quote]</p>
<p>The words of a sad, lonely little boy.</p>
<ol>
<li>99% of this community isn’t 20</li>
<li>A decent portion of these forums don’t fuck around with private servers</li>
<li>Cussing does not make you cool</li>
</ol>
<p>I’m sure on the other side I’m talking to a lost, weak person with no friends and sits in his tiny apartment living a pathetic life between your shit job at McDonalds and coming home browsing /b/ with the other people who are lost with no soul. May hell continue to reign upon you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 15:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Quite simple. Don’t look like someone who would be picked on. I noticed this in about 8-9th grade that my obsessiveness over runescape made me realize how frail and pale I was, I’ve since worked out for the past 3 years and tan ever so often to get the major paleness away.</p>
<p>Now people are surprised to find out I play WoW ololol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 15:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Vengeance _Vengeance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_vengeance">@_Vengeance</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We don’t care. Some words of advice, though, if you think a forum full of 13 year olds is a good place to seek counsel, you have a fucking long way to go before you’ll be worth anything to anyone. Go to some pickup artist forums, read all of the advice you can find. You’ll become one of those “douches” that you never would have liked (because you were a jealous moron and they picked on you), but you’ll become everything that you claim you want to be - providing you can grow some fucking balls. At least you realise you’re a pussy/fagot/loser. Most people don’t.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 14:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>as long as you’re not a complete aspie you’ll fit into uni assuming you’re entering a science major</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 14:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xdeathstarsx x Albi x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xdeathstarsx">@xdeathstarsx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You think you’re special you little faggot, 99% of this community are 20 year old virgins, shut the fuck up whining cunt.</p>
<p>You have no friends because you’re a little 12 year old who cries that he’s never got his willy wet, here’s an idea, go and fuck a silicone egg like Lawl and then try go outside instead of crying on a private server community about how much of a little bitch you are. Man the fuck up you wet anal fart.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Muroth Muroth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/muroth">@Muroth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i’m just generally shy in person, until you get to know me, then you’ll find me fucking hyper. i used to ignore the ‘popular’ crowd as  i saw them as douches, but once i got to know them, they’re not all that bad. everybody can feel lonely at one point, doesn’t mean you can’t fix that. you’ll find friends, maybe not in highschool with that attitude.</p>
<p>if troll, congratulations, i gave a troll advice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 13:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Super sad. Mate, you should get some spirit. I got picked on when I was in 1st grade because I cried in the first day of school (cause I switched schools). If there is an expertise, embrace it. In 2nd grade, I got the guts to go and embrace my knowledge of meteorology at such a young age. To put my situation to yours, I got the guts in 1st grade to play basketball.</p>
<p>Just, the thing is to not worry about how many friends you have, or if you have gotten a kiss, etc. You only have to remember:</p>
<blockquote>A pack of 10 friends is worse than 2 friends.</blockquote>
<p>In third grade, I became one of the most popular kids, even though I only had 2 good and loyal friends.</p>
<p>Less friends follows,</p>
<blockquote>Good things come in small packages</blockquote>
<p>Don’t act like a <span class="bbcode-b">lemon</span> and stay squashed, go out!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 13:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is sad, why don’t you just grow up and act like a man should (if you’re a man). I have few friends i am close to but then there are friends i talk to regularly. I’m not the kind of person to be ‘out there’ but when i want to be heard i am, i don’t like people pushing me around. Why don’t you get out of your comfort zone, and go find people who will like your ‘weirdness’ because if they don’t like it then you aren’t really friends. You cannot live your life in fear of being labelled because in the end everyone is, you need to get over it.</p>
<p>Is it just me or does this sound kinda like a troll? Stereotypical nerd online ftw?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 13:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Please, for gods sake, stop acting like getting a girlfriend or a million friends is the most important aspect of your life.  The most important thing you have to do at this age is learn as much as you can for the life ahead.  I know people at my school with 6 packs, that are masculine, etc and have no friends because they treat people like shit.  I personally only talk to around 6 or 7 people, weigh somewhere above 250 or so, have acne, and people still enjoy talking to me and I love my life.</p>
<p>I typically avoid talking to most people from where I live because they are very arrogant and belligerent.  The thing is, if you sit here and just think to yourself that you’re doing terrible, then you will.</p>
<p>One thing I did when being bullied in school, I stopped it by trolling before I even knew what it was.  The stupid thing about bullies is that they insult you pointing out one or two of your flaws, when in reality they have many flaws themselves.  I just agree to what they shout at me, calmly insult them, and walk away.  Fairly recently, I met a kid who used to hate me and make me feel bad, he walked up and said “wow your still a fucking fatass” and I said “You know it, man”.<br>
They can say anything they want about you, that doesn’t means it’s true.  Just agree with them and walk away, they’ll either get bored, mad, or eventually get called out by their peers because you aren’t doing anything, and he’s bashing you for no reason.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 11:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Welcome to the general life of Moparscape!</p>
<p>In all honesty though your taking it out of proportion. In reality EVERYONE only has a few friends. Those who have hundreds of friends are not really friends with anybody just knows how to network. It’s like  people with oodles of facebook friends. They may get like  20k facebook likes on a random  wall post but only about five or six of those members will they talk to  on a personal/friendship level.</p>
<p>As long as you have those close friends you will be okay. It’s fairly common to  not really have female companions until after high school actually. I can’t speak for everyone but I didn’t start  my long term relationship with my now beloved ex  until the ending of my 12th grade year.</p>
<p>When the right woman comes a long you will know it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 10:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@time_of_rune time of rune]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/time_of_rune">@time_of_rune</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="438911">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Eh Pretty Easy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Don’t be yourself. Be more than yourself. The only problem you have is that you keep bashing yourself, which in turn results in low self-esteem and poor self-image. No one will like you unless you like yourself first.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, that’s what I think getting in shape will help. I’ll actually feel confident about myself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 09:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Don’t be yourself. Be more than yourself. The only problem you have is that you keep bashing yourself, which in turn results in low self-esteem and poor self-image. No one will like you unless you like yourself first.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 09:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My life sucks</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@time_of_rune time of rune]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/time_of_rune">@time_of_rune</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="438911">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/yz85racer/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Yz85Racer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Doesn’t everyone? Why do you need to not be alone?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s not that I don’t need to be alone, but I doubt more seclusion is going to help my issue any.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 09:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438911-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-life-sucks/438911.rss">My life sucks</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
