<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Few bugs i ran into</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334</link>
    <description>Bug 1. Adding friends to the friend list who are online doesn&#39;t show them online until you log out then back in

Bug 2. Well, the easiest way to explain this would be if you were to have let&#39;s say 20M GP in your inventory, and let&#39;s say for the sake of this 25 bandages, in total that would be 26 slots in your inventory out of 28. If you were to go into a shop and attempt to buy &#39;100&#39; wolf bones then it would charge you for 100 bones but only infact give you &#39;2&#39; bones. Do you understand where I am coming from? It essentially charges you for the amount of 100 bones when in fact only giving you 2 as that&#39;s the full inventory space, the game in theory should only give you 2 bones and then you have a full inventory space and not be able to charge for you for the others.


any help please?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 23:04:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Few bugs i ran into</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>
<p>When you add a player, re-send the friends list (like x-j-k-x said). When a player logs in, update everyone’s friends list again.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Re-write your buying code. Make sure it checks for both noted and un-noted. Make sure it does price checks before any money is removed. If the price is above what the player has:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">int buyAmt = COINS / PRICE_FOR_ONE;
int price = COINS * buyAmt;</code></pre>
<p>Noted/stackable items will have a different set of checks than non-stackables. Stackables need a minimal of 1 inventory space unless the amount purchased will remove all coins, or if the player already has the item and the amount purchased won’t send the value above Integer.MAX_VALUE (Which would actually send it to the negatives). Non-stackables need as many spaces as they’re purchasing, - 1 if it removes all coins.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 23:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555334-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334.rss">Few bugs i ran into</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Few bugs i ran into</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@X-J-K-X X-J-K-X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x-j-k-x">@X-J-K-X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>1: rebuild the fl when you add someone</p>
<p>2: instead of deducting the money for the amount they tried to buy, deduct the money for the amount they were ABLE to buy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 22:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555334-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334.rss">Few bugs i ran into</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Few bugs i ran into</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@neevbc neevbc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/neevbc">@neevbc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bug 1. Adding friends to the friend list who are online doesn’t show them online until you log out then back in</p>
<p>Bug 2. Well, the easiest way to explain this would be if you were to have let’s say 20M GP in your inventory, and let’s say for the sake of this 25 bandages, in total that would be 26 slots in your inventory out of 28. If you were to go into a shop and attempt to buy ‘100’ wolf bones then it would charge you for 100 bones but only infact give you ‘2’ bones. Do you understand where I am coming from? It essentially charges you for the amount of 100 bones when in fact only giving you 2 as that’s the full inventory space, the game in theory should only give you 2 bones and then you have a full inventory space and not be able to charge for you for the others.</p>
<p>any help please?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555334-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-bugs-i-ran-into/555334.rss">Few bugs i ran into</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
