<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Galaxy Warfare</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/galaxy-warfare/555456</link>
    <description>Hello All.  

Galaxy warfare is a browser based, grid 2d style game that takes place out in space.  you join a faction, and explore the galaxy, collect items, capture planets, get in ship battles and try and level up to get bigger and better ships and system updates to become even more powerful.  The game has been out for a little bit but is still developed more and more each day.  The game is completely free to play, you just have to register.  You can, However, Donate and subscribe to help further the games development.

After level 10, you can join a fleet within your faction, or at level 15 create your own fleet and try and become the best and most feared fleet out there!  

Some features of the game

Fleets
Active Chat
Daily, weekly, and monthly missions
Multiple types of ships to select from
massive grid to explore. 
Most wanted
Lots of leaderboards (For daily best, and over all best)


Fleets - Fleets are kinda like your clan per-say, it can have up to 32 members in a single fleet and is created at level 15 or joined at level 10.  You can level up your fleet by getting into ship battles against other players and AI&#39;s.  Fleets can also send distress singles if they need help and store items that you don&#39;t wanna use or that you wanna give to your fleet members.

Daily, Weekly, and monthly missions - each day, two new daily missions are released that once completed can be redeemed for credits, or EXP and sometimes items.  Weekly&#39;s are released each week and like dailys can be redeemed for items, but usually are better items or bigger amounts of credits and EXP.  Same with monthly.

Multiple types of ships - there are 4 factions but currently only 3 can be played right off the bat, the last one needs to be unlocked.  But all 4 factions have 6 different ships that you unlock and once unlocked lets you upgrade your ships systems.

Most wanted - As players roam the galaxy and collect planets and kill AI&#39;s and other players, their bounty goes up, which means you will eventually get put on the most wanted list with a credit amount on your head that players will try and collect, an vice versa, you can try and hunt players as well.

 

Check out the site

[url=http://game.galaxywarfare.com/?section=register&amp;refcode=BE0807DF]Use this link to register and it also helps me directly :)[/url]

 


 

Thanks for reading and considering.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 15:19:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/galaxy-warfare/555456.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Galaxy Warfare</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@alex4ever alex4ever]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/alex4ever">@alex4ever</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello All.</p>
<p>Galaxy warfare is a browser based, grid 2d style game that takes place out in space.  you join a faction, and explore the galaxy, collect items, capture planets, get in ship battles and try and level up to get bigger and better ships and system updates to become even more powerful.  The game has been out for a little bit but is still developed more and more each day.  The game is completely free to play, you just have to register.  You can, However, Donate and subscribe to help further the games development.</p>
<p>After level 10, you can join a fleet within your faction, or at level 15 create your own fleet and try and become the best and most feared fleet out there!</p>
<p>Some features of the game</p>
<p>Fleets<br>
Active Chat<br>
Daily, weekly, and monthly missions<br>
Multiple types of ships to select from<br>
massive grid to explore.<br>
Most wanted<br>
Lots of leaderboards (For daily best, and over all best)</p>
<p>Fleets - Fleets are kinda like your clan per-say, it can have up to 32 members in a single fleet and is created at level 15 or joined at level 10.  You can level up your fleet by getting into ship battles against other players and AI’s.  Fleets can also send distress singles if they need help and store items that you don’t wanna use or that you wanna give to your fleet members.</p>
<p>Daily, Weekly, and monthly missions - each day, two new daily missions are released that once completed can be redeemed for credits, or EXP and sometimes items.  Weekly’s are released each week and like dailys can be redeemed for items, but usually are better items or bigger amounts of credits and EXP.  Same with monthly.</p>
<p>Multiple types of ships - there are 4 factions but currently only 3 can be played right off the bat, the last one needs to be unlocked.  But all 4 factions have 6 different ships that you unlock and once unlocked lets you upgrade your ships systems.</p>
<p>Most wanted - As players roam the galaxy and collect planets and kill AI’s and other players, their bounty goes up, which means you will eventually get put on the most wanted list with a credit amount on your head that players will try and collect, an vice versa, you can try and hunt players as well.</p>
<p>Check out the site</p>
<p><a href="http://game.galaxywarfare.com/?section=register&amp;refcode=BE0807DF" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Use this link to register and it also helps me directly <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></a></p>
<p>Thanks for reading and considering.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/galaxy-warfare/555456/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/galaxy-warfare/555456/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 15:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555456-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/galaxy-warfare/555456.rss">Galaxy Warfare</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
