<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Which is it?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/which-is-it/157533</link>
    <description>Recently I was reading up on the impeachment proceedings against Dick Cheney. For a different perspective I read a Fox News article. The last line, a quote from Bush&#39;s press secretary, stuck with me:

http://www.foxnews.com/story/0,2933,308738,00.html
&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;It is this behavior that leaves the American people shaking their head in wonder at this Congress,&quot; Perino said.&lt;/blockquote&gt;



Hmmm. It is true that Congress has a lower approval rating than Bush. But...maybe, just maybe, people are pissed off because Bush and Cheney [b]haven&#39;t[/b] been impeached. Are people really pissed off at the Congress because they aren&#39;t bowing down to Bush enough? Or is it because anybody with even a marginal knowledge of US government knows that Congress can end the war anytime they want, even without a large majority?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 18:44:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/which-is-it/157533.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Which is it?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Recently I was reading up on the impeachment proceedings against Dick Cheney. For a different perspective I read a Fox News article. The last line, a quote from Bush’s press secretary, stuck with me:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.foxnews.com/story/0,2933,308738,00.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.foxnews.com/story/0,2933,308738,00.html</a></p>
<blockquote>"It is this behavior that leaves the American people shaking their head in wonder at this Congress," Perino said.</blockquote>
<p>Hmmm. It is true that Congress has a lower approval rating than Bush. But…maybe, just maybe, people are pissed off because Bush and Cheney <span class="bbcode-b">haven’t</span> been impeached. Are people really pissed off at the Congress because they aren’t bowing down to Bush enough? Or is it because anybody with even a marginal knowledge of US government knows that Congress can end the war anytime they want, even without a large majority?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/which-is-it/157533/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/which-is-it/157533/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 18:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-157533-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/which-is-it/157533.rss">Which is it?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
