<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Linux] Project Backup Utility</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-project-backup-utility/491181</link>
    <description>This is a very small and simple backup utility that made it easier for me to create backups of my chatroom. Since I have JAR&#39;s setup to be run via the terminal by default I can easily just double-click this and let my backups go. I decided to release it just to help anybody else out who might find it useful. It took me 20 seconds to make so No, I do not say this was hard. It was by far the easiest tool I have ever made.

[Q]Why is it not compatible with Windows or Mac OSX?
[A]Simple, because I have not tested it so I am saying it is incompatible. As long as the ZIP command is available in your OS, with the same way to be executed as it is in Ubuntu it should work fine.

[Q]What does it do?
[A]This creates a backup of the given folder (assigned in settings.conf) in the ZIP format.

[Q]How do I run this?
[A]It should be ran via the terminal (shell).

[Q]Where do I download it from?
[A]This link: http://up.ht/13hHrpM

EDIT: On a side note so nobody gets confused. The &#39;NAME=&#39; property in settings.conf is not going to be the exact name used. For example, I left it as &quot;chatroom&quot;. The actual saved file will be (if for example, ran on 1-19-2013 would be &quot;chatroom-2-20-2013.zip&quot;. This helps you keep track of your backups better. If request (it will take two seconds) I can add in support via settings.conf for a custom date format.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 21:27:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-project-backup-utility/491181.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Linux] Project Backup Utility</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CoonHunter CoonHunter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coonhunter">@CoonHunter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is a very small and simple backup utility that made it easier for me to create backups of my chatroom. Since I have JAR’s setup to be run via the terminal by default I can easily just double-click this and let my backups go. I decided to release it just to help anybody else out who might find it useful. It took me 20 seconds to make so No, I do not say this was hard. It was by far the easiest tool I have ever made.</p>
<p>[Q]Why is it not compatible with Windows or Mac OSX?<br>
[A]Simple, because I have not tested it so I am saying it is incompatible. As long as the ZIP command is available in your OS, with the same way to be executed as it is in Ubuntu it should work fine.</p>
<p>[Q]What does it do?<br>
[A]This creates a backup of the given folder (assigned in settings.conf) in the ZIP format.</p>
<p>[Q]How do I run this?<br>
[A]It should be ran via the terminal (shell).</p>
<p>[Q]Where do I download it from?<br>
[A]This link: <a href="http://up.ht/13hHrpM" rel="nofollow noopener">http://up.ht/13hHrpM</a></p>
<p>EDIT: On a side note so nobody gets confused. The ‘NAME=’ property in settings.conf is not going to be the exact name used. For example, I left it as “chatroom”. The actual saved file will be (if for example, ran on 1-19-2013 would be “chatroom-2-20-2013.zip”. This helps you keep track of your backups better. If request (it will take two seconds) I can add in support via settings.conf for a custom date format.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-project-backup-utility/491181/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-project-backup-utility/491181/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 21:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-491181-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-project-backup-utility/491181.rss">[Linux] Project Backup Utility</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
