<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RSPS Quest Tab Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-quest-tab-help/415807</link>
    <description>Hey guys I&#39;ve been coding this server for quite a while and i&#39;m curious as how to add the words in the quest tab to click on and the prompt comes up. I already have the quests coded and npcs set i just need to place the &quot;button&quot; in the quest tab? What folder do i go into inorder to add the clickable button. I thought it was ClickingButtons.java but idk. Here is a picture. Of what im talking about
[IMG]http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x402/modzillascape/Capture-3.jpg[/img]

basically where the blue is, is where i want words that i can click and the quest prompt comes up. My action button is 66112. The ring of incar.. is 66111. If that helps. Thanks!! for helpin!!



[b][size=36pt]NEVER MIND I FOUND IT IN THE CLIENT FOLDER IN RS INTERFACE! :p SORRY[/size][/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 17:37:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-quest-tab-help/415807.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RSPS Quest Tab Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@modzilla modzilla]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/modzilla">@modzilla</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys I’ve been coding this server for quite a while and i’m curious as how to add the words in the quest tab to click on and the prompt comes up. I already have the quests coded and npcs set i just need to place the “button” in the quest tab? What folder do i go into inorder to add the clickable button. I thought it was ClickingButtons.java but idk. Here is a picture. Of what im talking about<br>
<img src="http://i1180.photobucket.com/albums/x402/modzillascape/Capture-3.jpg" alt width="254" height="252"></p>
<p>basically where the blue is, is where i want words that i can click and the quest prompt comes up. My action button is 66112. The ring of incar… is 66111. If that helps. Thanks!! for helpin!!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=36pt]NEVER MIND I FOUND IT IN THE CLIENT FOLDER IN RS INTERFACE! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> SORRY[/size]</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-quest-tab-help/415807/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-quest-tab-help/415807/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 17:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-415807-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-quest-tab-help/415807.rss">RSPS Quest Tab Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
