<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need some input on what i should do in this script</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-input-on-what-i-should-do-in-this-script/181386</link>
    <description>I&#39;m still working on that solitaire script. Right now i&#39;ve got most the procedures i&#39;m going to need to call on later.

Dealing w/ aces
Moving cards from one slot to another
Drawing new cards
Flipping cards

now i need to make it smart :P 

One issue i do have is flipping my aces, when i have more than 1 ace up it sends them to the top and flips new cards, but it continues to try to flip cards a few more times. I figure thats due to the variables i&#39;m using to count how many aces there are(I&#39;m sure theres a better way than what i&#39;m using). I could use some help with that to see what i&#39;m doing wrong.


For the main procedure for figuring out what cards to move and such i know i can simply use a shit load of If statements, but i want to slim it down and make it faster than that. I goofed around with numbering each card 1-52, say(for instance) the 5 of hearts is number 18, well if the 6 of spades or clubs are up i could simply see if either of their numbers are up, i.e. 24, 47*random numbers* then i could use cases to set the variables for the MoveCard; procedure

Thats the most compact and quick way i can think of.

also i have to go through and re-do the FindCardSlotOne; into cases and seperate each slot up so i can just call on the one i need to re-read instead of wasting time reading all 7.

If somebody can help me think of a better way for the main procedure that would be awesome :) 

Remember, this script is kind of haggard at the moment i&#39;m just trying to get theory into pratice then i&#39;ll refine it later, so don&#39;t be too harsh ;)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 21:54:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-input-on-what-i-should-do-in-this-script/181386.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need some input on what i should do in this script</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dgc2002 Dgc2002]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dgc2002">@Dgc2002</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m still working on that solitaire script. Right now i’ve got most the procedures i’m going to need to call on later.</p>
<p>Dealing w/ aces<br>
Moving cards from one slot to another<br>
Drawing new cards<br>
Flipping cards</p>
<p>now i need to make it smart <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>One issue i do have is flipping my aces, when i have more than 1 ace up it sends them to the top and flips new cards, but it continues to try to flip cards a few more times. I figure thats due to the variables i’m using to count how many aces there are(I’m sure theres a better way than what i’m using). I could use some help with that to see what i’m doing wrong.</p>
<p>For the main procedure for figuring out what cards to move and such i know i can simply use a shit load of If statements, but i want to slim it down and make it faster than that. I goofed around with numbering each card 1-52, say(for instance) the 5 of hearts is number 18, well if the 6 of spades or clubs are up i could simply see if either of their numbers are up, i.e. 24, 47<em>random numbers</em> then i could use cases to set the variables for the MoveCard; procedure</p>
<p>Thats the most compact and quick way i can think of.</p>
<p>also i have to go through and re-do the FindCardSlotOne; into cases and seperate each slot up so i can just call on the one i need to re-read instead of wasting time reading all 7.</p>
<p>If somebody can help me think of a better way for the main procedure that would be awesome <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Remember, this script is kind of haggard at the moment i’m just trying to get theory into pratice then i’ll refine it later, so don’t be too harsh <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-input-on-what-i-should-do-in-this-script/181386/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-input-on-what-i-should-do-in-this-script/181386/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 21:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-181386-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-some-input-on-what-i-should-do-in-this-script/181386.rss">Need some input on what i should do in this script</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
