<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What goes in this board?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-goes-in-this-board/544995</link>
    <description>This board is designed to be a more relaxed area for those looking to kick their feet back and have some fun. We&#39;ve decided to trial this board. The rules are considerably more relaxed here meaning you can worry less about receiving an infraction for not taking a topic super seriously. Let&#39;s make a few things clear though, while this forum is relaxed there will be absolutely no illegal content in the form of downloads, viruses, porn or anything that&#39;s illegal. Rules that involve the harassment or attacking of another member are still withstanding. Please don&#39;t take this board seriously and be reasonable so we can all enjoy it. Anybody who abuses this board will be met with a board based ban which will revoke your access to post here.

Feel free to play games, have a joke, and troll. If you&#39;re going to post any NSFW content please use the spoiler tag (if you&#39;re going to post politically sensitive material, or anything related to nazis like a flag for example). If you post anything NSFW that breaks the site rules on porn or grotesquely illicit content even with a spoiler tag you will be banned from this board. This topic may be updated with further information in the future.

Have fun :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 16:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-goes-in-this-board/544995.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What goes in this board?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This board is designed to be a more relaxed area for those looking to kick their feet back and have some fun. We’ve decided to trial this board. The rules are considerably more relaxed here meaning you can worry less about receiving an infraction for not taking a topic super seriously. Let’s make a few things clear though, while this forum is relaxed there will be absolutely no illegal content in the form of downloads, viruses, porn or anything that’s illegal. Rules that involve the harassment or attacking of another member are still withstanding. Please don’t take this board seriously and be reasonable so we can all enjoy it. Anybody who abuses this board will be met with a board based ban which will revoke your access to post here.</p>
<p>Feel free to play games, have a joke, and troll. If you’re going to post any NSFW content please use the spoiler tag (if you’re going to post politically sensitive material, or anything related to nazis like a flag for example). If you post anything NSFW that breaks the site rules on porn or grotesquely illicit content even with a spoiler tag you will be banned from this board. This topic may be updated with further information in the future.</p>
<p>Have fun <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-goes-in-this-board/544995/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-goes-in-this-board/544995/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 16:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544995-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-goes-in-this-board/544995.rss">What goes in this board?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
