<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rooting/Hardware Issue</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rooting-hardware-issue/527160</link>
    <description>I&#39;m sure all you Android users know what rooting is and what it does.  I bought my phone a little over a year ago (Motorola Droid 4, Verizon) and haven&#39;t had a problems with it at all, and wasn&#39;t too worried about it breaking since I have the Total Equipment Coverage for a few extra bucks a month.  However, I recently ran into a hardware problem: the screen is completely black when I slide open the keyboard.  I think it has to do with a wire that is loose or just not working properly (a problem sliding phones tend to have).  I believe this is the problem because when opening the keyboard the backlight for the keys stay on, and the screen stays on if the keyboard is pulled out very little, but it I pull it out more, the screen turns completely black (with the Android buttons below the screen still on).  Every once in a while, I will actually be able to open the keyboard fully and have the screen stay on, but after a bit, it starts malfunctioning again.

So that&#39;s the hardware problem I&#39;m encountering, but the question is, if I have rooted my phone in the past (I&#39;ve unrooted it now, however) will Verizon be able to tell?  I worry due to the fact that rooting could void your warranty and then I&#39;m pretty much screwed right over.  A factory reset is an option, but not an option I&#39;m willing to do unless need be.


Please no idiotic posts from L&amp;P, ty.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 03:37:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rooting-hardware-issue/527160.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rooting/Hardware Issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Null_Amount N_A]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/null_amount">@Null_Amount</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="http://www.droidforums.net/favicon-196x196.png" class="site-icon" width="196" height="196">
      <a href="http://www.droidforums.net/threads/225452/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DroidForums.net | Android Forums &amp; News</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="http://www.droidforums.net/data/avatars/m/120/120199.jpg?1404219682" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="96" height="96">

<h3><a href="http://www.droidforums.net/threads/225452/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Will verizon know if my phone is rooted for warranty if i cant even turn on?</a></h3>

<p>I got the white led problem but unlike the other times i have had it, the power vol down doesnt do anything, plugging into any charger just shows the...</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
Specifically the third post down. I can’t verify the accuracy of it, however.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rooting-hardware-issue/527160/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rooting-hardware-issue/527160/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 03:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527160-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rooting-hardware-issue/527160.rss">Rooting/Hardware Issue</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rooting/Hardware Issue</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m sure all you Android users know what rooting is and what it does.  I bought my phone a little over a year ago (Motorola Droid 4, Verizon) and haven’t had a problems with it at all, and wasn’t too worried about it breaking since I have the Total Equipment Coverage for a few extra bucks a month.  However, I recently ran into a hardware problem: the screen is completely black when I slide open the keyboard.  I think it has to do with a wire that is loose or just not working properly (a problem sliding phones tend to have).  I believe this is the problem because when opening the keyboard the backlight for the keys stay on, and the screen stays on if the keyboard is pulled out very little, but it I pull it out more, the screen turns completely black (with the Android buttons below the screen still on).  Every once in a while, I will actually be able to open the keyboard fully and have the screen stay on, but after a bit, it starts malfunctioning again.</p>
<p>So that’s the hardware problem I’m encountering, but the question is, if I have rooted my phone in the past (I’ve unrooted it now, however) will Verizon be able to tell?  I worry due to the fact that rooting could void your warranty and then I’m pretty much screwed right over.  A factory reset is an option, but not an option I’m willing to do unless need be.</p>
<p>Please no idiotic posts from L&amp;P, ty.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rooting-hardware-issue/527160/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rooting-hardware-issue/527160/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 01:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-527160-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rooting-hardware-issue/527160.rss">Rooting/Hardware Issue</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
