<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Xbox 360 Sound Commits Suicide When Playing Wolfenstein: TNO</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-360-sound-commits-suicide-when-playing-wolfenstein-tno/547160</link>
    <description>Alright so recently I got a copy of Wolfenstein: The New Order for my Xbox 360, and was fine until I hit the third level. Recently I can only get anywhere from 1min - 15min into to it, because the sound cuts out and I have to restart the Xbox, and the mission because reloading the checkpoint makes the sound immediately go out. This isn&#39;t the game sound cutting out, the WHOLE system cuts out, no menu noise, game or anything else. I unplug my turtle beaches and play through the TV, and I reach the same fate. This also only occurs when playing Wolfenstein, nothing else, and this has never happened before, any help?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 01:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-360-sound-commits-suicide-when-playing-wolfenstein-tno/547160.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Xbox 360 Sound Commits Suicide When Playing Wolfenstein: TNO</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright so recently I got a copy of Wolfenstein: The New Order for my Xbox 360, and was fine until I hit the third level. Recently I can only get anywhere from 1min - 15min into to it, because the sound cuts out and I have to restart the Xbox, and the mission because reloading the checkpoint makes the sound immediately go out. This isn’t the game sound cutting out, the WHOLE system cuts out, no menu noise, game or anything else. I unplug my turtle beaches and play through the TV, and I reach the same fate. This also only occurs when playing Wolfenstein, nothing else, and this has never happened before, any help?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-360-sound-commits-suicide-when-playing-wolfenstein-tno/547160/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-360-sound-commits-suicide-when-playing-wolfenstein-tno/547160/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 01:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547160-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xbox-360-sound-commits-suicide-when-playing-wolfenstein-tno/547160.rss">Xbox 360 Sound Commits Suicide When Playing Wolfenstein: TNO</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
