<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[2010-2011] Full Screen Hi-Def Webclient (Skill 3D Productions)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310</link>
    <description>I&#39;m going to be talking some about a webclient that i have been working on since November 2010, I&#39;ve decided to post about it now to show the progress that i have made over the past year working on this client. When you first start the client it will be a standard sized webclient size (765 x 503) it will take 20-40 seconds to download the necessary files, it will only do this the first start-up of the client, every time after that when you start the client it takes about 10 seconds to get to the main screen (that is if there aren&#39;t any updates). Also upon first time of starting up the client you will need to set up a few settings, then your settings will be saved and ready to go for next time, the few settings that you&#39;ll need to set-up:


[ul][li]Screen Dimensions (At least 800x600)[/li]
[li]Low-Def or Hi-Def[/li]
[li]Other General Settings[/li][/ul]


The owner of the server and webclient will also have to do some setting up of the client, you&#39;ll be able to select different client versions that all can be run in full screen. I currently have 317 and 508 working in full screen without it being distorted. I&#39;m hoping to have this client released by Spring 2012, what is coming up in a few months..! Stuff that i still need to work on:


[ul][li]More client versions[/li]
[li]Fix the auto-updater[/li]
[li]In-game option to select from different worlds (This can be toggled on/off by the owner)[/li]
[li]Small Varrock bug when client is full screen with 317[/li]
[li]Resizeable Webclient (In Browser, Drag corners of client to re-size. Almost Completed.)[/li]
[li]Option to pop-out the Web Client from the browser to use as if its a computer Window, and pop back into the browser at anytime. Need to fix the bug with this where if you close the webclient window the popped-out client freezes and stays open and you need to manually close.[/li][/ul]


Keep in mind that when i mean full screen this is not a windowed version it takes up your whole computer screen as a game like Fallout, Call of Duty, Medal of Honor would do so. You can exit full screen and go back to the resizeable or adjusted in-browser client at any time by pressing Esc in full screen mode. 

I have spent quite a long time on this project and ill be releasing it soon for others to enjoy it. The reason i started this is because i got into runescape private servers back in 2007 when real Runescape was getting boring after a while, i didn&#39;t get into any server or client coding until 2009 and i haven&#39;t released any projects until 2010. I have been doing Website Design and Coding for the past 4 years and Java program coding for the past 2 years, plus RSPS clients the past 3 years, I thought that i could implement the Website Coding, Java Coding, and RSPS clients together to make something that no one has seen before. Thats the sole purpose of this client release is to amaze others and hopefully have some include this webclient with their RSPS. I will for sure meet my deadline and may possibly have it ready to release before the deadline, as i am working on it quite a bit on the weekends when i don&#39;t have school. I&#39;m just a 14 year old kid that loves to code websites, rsps&#39;s, and java. Not some major developer, i taught myself how to code by using the internet (its amazing how much you can learn) yes i&#39;m 14 and here to release a fullscreen hi-def webclient with all of the features that you have read from above, Don&#39;t let my age fool you.. 

I&#39;ll be uploading pictures and videos of the client later tonight or tomorrow for all to see,

[i][b]Please though, do me a favor.. I like honest opinions when i come to my work, There&#39;s nothing i dislike more then having someone i&#39;m doing a goodjob just to findout they were just trying to be nice. I want your honest opinion Moparscapers, do you like this project idea and the thoughts that i have listed so far? Let me know in a comment section below. Good or Bad feedback your feedback is greatly appreciated. [/b][/i]

PS: I haven&#39;t logged onto Mopar for a long time and i had deleted the email that my old account had been linked to, thats why i have created this new account with my new email, I have been a Moparscape member for years and ill remain one for years to come.

[center]Best Regards,
-Skill3d; Owner of Skill 3D Coding[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:09:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[2010-2011] Full Screen Hi-Def Webclient (Skill 3D Productions)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pot_up_pls pot up pls]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pot_up_pls">@pot_up_pls</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thread looks nice and tidy, goodluck mate. i will be sure too be checking up on this.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="420310">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/riipiinftw/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> RiiPiiNFtW:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Media plox</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420310-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310.rss">[2010-2011] Full Screen Hi-Def Webclient (Skill 3D Productions)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[2010-2011] Full Screen Hi-Def Webclient (Skill 3D Productions)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RiiPiiNFtW RiiPiiNFtW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/riipiinftw">@RiiPiiNFtW</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Media plox</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 17:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420310-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310.rss">[2010-2011] Full Screen Hi-Def Webclient (Skill 3D Productions)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[2010-2011] Full Screen Hi-Def Webclient (Skill 3D Productions)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Native1 Native^]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/native1">@Native1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looking good, but you will need pictures to get this allowed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 17:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420310-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310.rss">[2010-2011] Full Screen Hi-Def Webclient (Skill 3D Productions)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[2010-2011] Full Screen Hi-Def Webclient (Skill 3D Productions)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skill_3D Skill 3D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skill_3d">@Skill_3D</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m going to be talking some about a webclient that i have been working on since November 2010, I’ve decided to post about it now to show the progress that i have made over the past year working on this client. When you first start the client it will be a standard sized webclient size (765 x 503) it will take 20-40 seconds to download the necessary files, it will only do this the first start-up of the client, every time after that when you start the client it takes about 10 seconds to get to the main screen (that is if there aren’t any updates). Also upon first time of starting up the client you will need to set up a few settings, then your settings will be saved and ready to go for next time, the few settings that you’ll need to set-up:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Screen Dimensions (At least 800x600)[/li]<br>
[li]Low-Def or Hi-Def[/li]<br>
[li]Other General Settings[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>The owner of the server and webclient will also have to do some setting up of the client, you’ll be able to select different client versions that all can be run in full screen. I currently have 317 and 508 working in full screen without it being distorted. I’m hoping to have this client released by Spring 2012, what is coming up in a few months…! Stuff that i still need to work on:</p>
<p>[ul][li]More client versions[/li]<br>
[li]Fix the auto-updater[/li]<br>
[li]In-game option to select from different worlds (This can be toggled on/off by the owner)[/li]<br>
[li]Small Varrock bug when client is full screen with 317[/li]<br>
[li]Resizeable Webclient (In Browser, Drag corners of client to re-size. Almost Completed.)[/li]<br>
[li]Option to pop-out the Web Client from the browser to use as if its a computer Window, and pop back into the browser at anytime. Need to fix the bug with this where if you close the webclient window the popped-out client freezes and stays open and you need to manually close.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>Keep in mind that when i mean full screen this is not a windowed version it takes up your whole computer screen as a game like Fallout, Call of Duty, Medal of Honor would do so. You can exit full screen and go back to the resizeable or adjusted in-browser client at any time by pressing Esc in full screen mode.</p>
<p>I have spent quite a long time on this project and ill be releasing it soon for others to enjoy it. The reason i started this is because i got into runescape private servers back in 2007 when real Runescape was getting boring after a while, i didn’t get into any server or client coding until 2009 and i haven’t released any projects until 2010. I have been doing Website Design and Coding for the past 4 years and Java program coding for the past 2 years, plus RSPS clients the past 3 years, I thought that i could implement the Website Coding, Java Coding, and RSPS clients together to make something that no one has seen before. Thats the sole purpose of this client release is to amaze others and hopefully have some include this webclient with their RSPS. I will for sure meet my deadline and may possibly have it ready to release before the deadline, as i am working on it quite a bit on the weekends when i don’t have school. I’m just a 14 year old kid that loves to code websites, rsps’s, and java. Not some major developer, i taught myself how to code by using the internet (its amazing how much you can learn) yes i’m 14 and here to release a fullscreen hi-def webclient with all of the features that you have read from above, Don’t let my age fool you…</p>
<p>I’ll be uploading pictures and videos of the client later tonight or tomorrow for all to see,</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Please though, do me a favor… I like honest opinions when i come to my work, There’s nothing i dislike more then having someone i’m doing a goodjob just to findout they were just trying to be nice. I want your honest opinion Moparscapers, do you like this project idea and the thoughts that i have listed so far? Let me know in a comment section below. Good or Bad feedback your feedback is greatly appreciated. </span></span></p>
<p>PS: I haven’t logged onto Mopar for a long time and i had deleted the email that my old account had been linked to, thats why i have created this new account with my new email, I have been a Moparscape member for years and ill remain one for years to come.</p>
<p>[center]Best Regards,<br>
-Skill3d; Owner of Skill 3D Coding[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 13:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-420310-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/2010-2011-full-screen-hi-def-webclient-skill-3d-productions/420310.rss">[2010-2011] Full Screen Hi-Def Webclient (Skill 3D Productions)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
