<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016</link>
    <description>[center][size=12pt][u][b]Tutorial: How to Adapt to a 508 Server[/b][/u]
By: Davidi2[/size][/center]

Many people now are switching from 317 servers to 508 and beyond. This switch is very large, and can take a long time to get used to. In a 317, almost everything you need to edit is in client.java, the main file for the server. When you first download a 508, you notice there is no client.java, or any main file at all. 508 servers use many different files all linked together in some way to run the server. This image should help you understand:[img]http://davidscape.com/508Chart.gif[/img]



As you can see, this is much more complicate then a 317. Now Ill walk you through some of the major things you might want to know about 508s:

[size=12pt][b]1. The Server and Engine[/b][/size]
So what happens when you click run.bat? Its pretty amazing. A ripple effect of methods and classes all work in unison to create what we know as a private server, with the ability to accept connections and then send packets to display a character on the screen of the client. But what players dont usually see is whats behind the scenes; whats running everything? The answer: [b]Server.java[/b]. This small java file puts everything together. It starts the engine, the socket listener(or connection manager) and many other individual files. It is also where banned users are usually found. Once it starts everything, the Server then hands the work over to the Engine. The Engine takes EVERY file in your server and puts them together, like putting different cogs into a machine. It starts the packet manager, file manager (for logging in ect), NPC, Players. Combat, everything. It also holds server-wide variables. Such as minigame timers and some shop data. The Engine relates to its Mopar counterpart, and runs everything.

[size=12pt][b]2. Packets: Commands, Clicking, and WHAT?![/b][/size]
If you want to change something related to the client, such as clicking on things, or typing, you go to the packets folder. The packets folder is inside the io folder. In there are a bunch of files with pretty obvious names. 

[ul][li]ActionButtons - For clicking buttons on interfaces[/li]
[li]Commands - For typing commands and what they do[/li]
[li]ItemOperate - When you operate certain items[/li]
[li]PublicChat - What happens when someone talks[/li]
[li]Walking - What happens when someone walks[/li][/ul]

There are plenty of them, and they all relate to a packet sent to/from the client through the Stream (see below) in varying packet sizes. When the server picks up a packet, it sends it to the PacketManager, where it is identified and executed. For example, in PacketManager:
[code]case 222:  
[/code] 
Would indicate that the client send a packet of size 222, and to execute whatever packet 222 does. In this case, 222 is Public chatting. 
[code]case 222:

            /*
             * Public chatting.
             */
            publicChat.handlePacket(p, packetId, packetSize);
            break;[/code]
So the packet manager &quot;handles&quot; the 222 packet by executing the public chat method &quot;handlePacket.&quot;  The method handlePacket is in all of the different packet files, because it makes it easier to identify which packet is which. Here is the default layout of a packet:[code]

package SOURCENAME.io.packets;

import SOURCENAME.players.Player;

public class PACKETNAME implements Packet {

    /**
     * Default setup for all packets.
     * @param p The Player which the frame should be handled for.
     * @param packetId The packet id this belongs to.
     * @param packetSize The amount of bytes being recieved for this packet.
     */
    void handlePacket(Player p, int packetId, int packetSize);
//This is what the server should do when the packet is received. It could be to move, or to teleport, or almost anything.
}
[/code]

[size=12pt][b]3. World[/b][/size]
Depending on your source, this folder may contain, but is not limited to: minigames, mapdata, items, grandexchangedata, and npcmovement. I will cover the ones that the typical Palidino base has, which are mapdata, items, and minigames.

[b]Mapdata[/b]
In a 317 server, the mapdata is stored in the cache and client, not in separate files. However, a typical MapData java file looks something like this: [code]package SOURCENAME.world.mapdata;


import java.io.BufferedReader;
import java.io.FileReader;
import java.io.File;
import SOURCENAME.util.Misc;


public class MapData {

    /**
     * Each list contains the region and 4 pieces of data.
     */
    public MapList[] mapLists = new MapList[2000];

    /**
     * Constructs a new MapData class.
     */
    public MapData() {
        loadMapAreaData();
    }

    /**
     * Load the map data into memory for faster load time.
     */
    public void loadMapAreaData() {
        int curId = 0;

        for (int i = 0; i &lt; 16000; i++) {
if ((i != 12351) &amp;&amp; (i != 12352)){
            try {
                File file = new File(&quot;./data/mapdata/&quot; + i + &quot;.txt&quot;);

                if (file.exists()) {
                    MapList list = mapLists[curId++] = new MapList();
                    BufferedReader in = new BufferedReader(
                            new FileReader(&quot;./data/mapdata/&quot; + i + &quot;.txt&quot;));
                    String str;
                    int regionId = 0;

                    list.region = i;
                    while ((str = in.readLine()) != null) {
                        if (!str.equals(&quot;&quot;)) {
                            list.data[regionId++] = Integer.parseInt(str.trim());
                        }
                    }
                    in.close();
                    in = null;
                }
                file = null;
            } catch (Exception e) {
                e.printStackTrace();
            }
        }
    }
}

    /**
     * Returns the four pieces of map data from a region.
     * @param myRegion The region to get data from.
     * @return Returns the four mapdata.
     */
    public int[] getData(int myRegion) {
        for (MapList list : mapLists) {
            if (list == null) {
                continue;
            }
            if (list.region == myRegion) {
                return list.data;
            }
        }
        Misc.println(&quot;Missing map data: &quot; + myRegion);
        return new int[4];
    }
}
[/code]
As you can see, this loads each map region separately, and stores it into an array. This provides limitations to 508 servers, as there are certain places that cannot be visited without the correct mapdata. If you are playing your server and your screen goes white, chances are you are missing mapdata.

[b]Items[/b]
The items folder [i]usually[/i] contains the following java files: GroundItem, ItemList, and Items. The ground item file handles, you guessed it, ground items. These are items that are dropped, by NPCs, Players, or just created, such as a party room putting items on the floor.  The code for a ground item is: [code]public GroundItem(int _index, int id, int amt, int x, int y, int h, String owner) {
        index = _index;
        itemId = id;
        itemAmt = amt;
        itemX = x;
        itemY = y;
        itemHeight = h;
        itemDroppedBy = owner;
    }[/code]
Each variable is fairly obvious, but Ill explain a few of them. Index is which ground item we are talking about. Such as in an array, if we want to talk about the second value of the array we say: [code]System.out.println(&quot;&quot; + ourArray[1]);[/code] 
The item dropped by variable stores who can see the drop. For example, you could say David and only the user David could see the drop. Setting the value to &quot;&quot; makes it so everyone can see it.

The item list file stores each item in its own array, one of the few things a 317 and 508 have in common. Its fairly simple and doesn&#39;t need much explaining.

The main item file is the main file for handling all items in the game. It stores all of the item methods, such as: [code]getDiscription(int itemId)[/code]
and puts the other item files together.

[b]Minigame[/b]
This is one of the least important of all your folders. In it are the files for your minigames, depending on your source. The normal and most common is bountyHunter. It is for leaving and entering the craters, and setting skulls ect. Not much to do here but make and edit minigames.

[size=12pt][b]4. Players[/b][/size]
If you have ever seen a 317, you know that a lot of things are handled in Client.java. 508&#39;s are packaged, but Player.java is still the main &#39;Entity&#39; class. In other words, you start a new instance of the class &#39;Player&#39; every time a new player connects and logs into the server. This is how you can send a specific person a message, and not have it go to everyone on the server.  There are many things Player.java handles, such as player specific methods, and player variables that are different for everyone. (Such as x,y coords and height, as well as things like skill levels and items) 

In a packaged 508 Player.java might not handle as much as a Client.java, but it still handles a lot, and it is important to understand what it is.

[size=12pt][b]5. Login[/b][/size]
Login.java is usually in the IO folder in a 508 server. This is the class that handles a connection and reads all the information sent from the client. During the process you verify the users client version, as well as their username and password. You also load the characters file and send that information. Depending on what happens during the login process, the server sends a return code back to the client that tells it what to tell the player. For example, if the password sent does not match the one that your server has stored, it returns a code telling the client to give the message the passwords don&#39;t match. The same thing happens if the server sends the code for the player being banned. If you are ever going to have the server check for a correct client version, this is where it would happen. (I might release a tutorial for adding auto update to 508 clients and servers soon) 

This is also where login messages happen, as well as player right checking and sending.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 13:42:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“boomer216, post:26, topic:326016”]God you are an idiot.  That flow chart you display is nothing different then what 317 servers have.  This does not explain anything about 508, rather it is about your game engine ideas.[/quote]Actually it is the layout of most packaged 508 file paths.</p>
<p>I just replaced the main index with ‘Engine’ because most have those are different. For example, mine is ‘DavidScape’, while others might be ‘RS2’ or ‘Bulby’.</p>
<p>I suggest you download a 508 before making accusations.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 13:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>God you are an idiot.  That flow chart you display is nothing different then what 317 servers have.  This does not explain anything about 508, rather it is about your game engine ideas.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 08:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@justinxg27 justinxg27]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/justinxg27">@justinxg27</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks, now I can code 508’s.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 02:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Manu0238, post:23, topic:326016”]hey pretty well done , i always like your source’s and stuff keep going on like this :D[/quote]Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 21:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Manu0238 Manu0238]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/manu0238">@Manu0238</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hey pretty well done , i always like your source’s and stuff keep going on like this <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 19:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very Goooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooood.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2010 01:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“licorish55, post:20, topic:326016”]Quick question.<br>
Although this is a good tut etc etc…</p>
<p>Do you like cheesecake?[/quote]<br>
Yes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 21:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Quick question.<br>
Although this is a good tut etc etc…</p>
<p>Do you like cheesecake?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 20:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Angel Ranqes, post:17, topic:326016”]My 508 is  most likely better than all the other ones right now (in my opinion), and i did not no half of this. Love the way you explained it and broke it down. This is sexy if i could rep you i would :)[/quote]Thanks.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="18" data-topic="326016">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mental Piracy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hopefully this will make more people comfortable moving forward and people will stop cramming updated shit in my beloved 317s, just because 508s scare them. Gj</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s my goal <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mental_Piracy Mental Piracy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mental_piracy">@Mental_Piracy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hopefully this will make more people comfortable moving forward and people will stop cramming updated shit in my beloved 317s, just because 508s scare them. Gj</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 01:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Angel_Ranqes Angel Ranqes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/angel_ranqes">@Angel_Ranqes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My 508 is  most likely better than all the other ones right now (in my opinion), and i did not no half of this. Love the way you explained it and broke it down. This is sexy if i could rep you i would <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 01:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="15" data-topic="326016">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Soul:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Not bad David. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thank you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 18:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_soul The Soul]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_soul">@the_soul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not bad David. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 18:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Primadude, post:13, topic:326016”]This is only for the shit Palidino76 base. I suggest you explain the RS2HD base as well, since it’s far better than Palidino’s.</p>
<p>However, good job.[/quote]<br>
TBH I have never looked at a rs2hd base :S</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 18:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@primadude Primadude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/primadude">@primadude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is only for the shit Palidino76 base. I suggest you explain the RS2HD base as well, since it’s far better than Palidino’s.</p>
<p>However, good job.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 18:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the positive feedback guys.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 06:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@killer117 killer117]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/killer117">@killer117</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very nice, I read it all. Good explanations and everything. I really like the picture at the top.<br>
And now, I want to look into 508’s   <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>~Thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 05:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@glestrts glestrts]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/glestrts">@glestrts</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol nice, at first when i saw the tile i thought this was about changing a 317 into a 508, i was like “holy shit” delta on a 508…</p>
<p>O.T. isn’t rs2hd more stable than pali’s base?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 04:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@P_I_M_P_3_D_Tut `Lewk_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/p_i_m_p_3_d_tut">@P_I_M_P_3_D_Tut</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can see you put some time into this.</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
I forgot to put good job. wat</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 04:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="7" data-topic="326016">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lin/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Lin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nice job, hopefully this helps some people.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s the plan <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 04:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice job, hopefully this helps some people.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 04:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Uh, thanks I think.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 04:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>MAKE A HUGE FLOW CHART WITH PICTURES AND COLORFUL WORDS SO PEOPLE WITH DOWN SYNDROM FOLLOW ALONG.</p>
<p>And people who only scim over stuff, they see the big bold colorful world and are like ooooohhh… im’a read this…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 04:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>YAY, Its somewhere other than your server download now =]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 04:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="326016">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/jc22493/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Jc22493:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The visual is pretty helpful to beginners. Also, nicely explained. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thank you.</p>
<p>I plan to write the biggest section (players) soon.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2010 03:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326016-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-adapt-from-a-317-to-508/326016.rss">How to Adapt From a 317 to 508</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
