<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>508 Localhost Client! -- Need help!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-localhost-client-need-help/286806</link>
    <description>I have no clue where to post this question, and it isn&#39;t server-related.

It&#39;s about my Client. I&#39;m not very good with clients, I&#39;m more about servers, and stuff. 2 Weeks ago I lost my Internet, and at the very night before I was playing my source, with a standard Localhost Client, and right when I woke up, I got a phone call saying my Internet got shut off, and plus my Client all of a sudden stopped working. (I&#39;m currently using my friends computer), So I thought to myself, maybe it&#39;s a sign from God telling me to do more with my life? I have nothing to do, everyday, I can&#39;t figure out what the problem is with the client, theres never nothing on T.V, it&#39;s to fucking hot outside to go anywhere, I don&#39;t have no money to go swimming, it&#39;s absolutley boaring.

Please, can somone please explain thoroughly as of what might be the problem? Don&#39;t be all nerdish about it, and stuff, I don&#39;t know much about Clients. Below are the stuff that I made sure were working, and other Miscellaneous information that might help.



---------------------------------------------------------------------

1.) I checked my Cache, it was working fine. (C:\cache508/rs2).

2.) I havn&#39;t made any updates on my source for the passed 4 weeks, so it can&#39;t be my source.

3.) I used the &#39;Z-File Searcher&#39; and found that the directory for the cache was working correctly.

4.) The IPs for 127.0.0.1, which the server connects to are working perfectly (The file looks the same as it does this client i&#39;m using, except for that client isn&#39;t connecting)


My suggestion is that when I changed the 127.0.0.1, when I was editing my client, it must of got messed up, and I didn&#39;t fix it properly. It stays at &#39;Connecting to Update Server&#39;, so it&#39;s the connection problem.

Can somone please help, I really need help.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 03, 2009, 04:27:20 am[/size][hr]Can somone please help me, and tell me how to do this without having to download an IP-Changer.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 10:26:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-localhost-client-need-help/286806.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>508 Localhost Client! -- Need help!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ServerSoft ServerSoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/serversoft">@ServerSoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have no clue where to post this question, and it isn’t server-related.</p>
<p>It’s about my Client. I’m not very good with clients, I’m more about servers, and stuff. 2 Weeks ago I lost my Internet, and at the very night before I was playing my source, with a standard Localhost Client, and right when I woke up, I got a phone call saying my Internet got shut off, and plus my Client all of a sudden stopped working. (I’m currently using my friends computer), So I thought to myself, maybe it’s a sign from God telling me to do more with my life? I have nothing to do, everyday, I can’t figure out what the problem is with the client, theres never nothing on T.V, it’s to fucking hot outside to go anywhere, I don’t have no money to go swimming, it’s absolutley boaring.</p>
<p>Please, can somone please explain thoroughly as of what might be the problem? Don’t be all nerdish about it, and stuff, I don’t know much about Clients. Below are the stuff that I made sure were working, and other Miscellaneous information that might help.</p>
<hr>
<p>1.) I checked my Cache, it was working fine. (C:\cache508/rs2).</p>
<p>2.) I havn’t made any updates on my source for the passed 4 weeks, so it can’t be my source.</p>
<p>3.) I used the ‘Z-File Searcher’ and found that the directory for the cache was working correctly.</p>
<p>4.) The IPs for 127.0.0.1, which the server connects to are working perfectly (The file looks the same as it does this client i’m using, except for that client isn’t connecting)</p>
<p>My suggestion is that when I changed the 127.0.0.1, when I was editing my client, it must of got messed up, and I didn’t fix it properly. It stays at ‘Connecting to Update Server’, so it’s the connection problem.</p>
<p>Can somone please help, I really need help.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 03, 2009, 04:27:20 am[/size][hr]Can somone please help me, and tell me how to do this without having to download an IP-Changer.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-localhost-client-need-help/286806/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-localhost-client-need-help/286806/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 10:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-286806-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-localhost-client-need-help/286806.rss">508 Localhost Client! -- Need help!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
