<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Year 11 English: Othello VS O, Text and context</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/year-11-english-othello-vs-o-text-and-context/142561</link>
    <description>ok, i have a major exam in 33 hours that i have done almost no study for, hell, i have never even read the book &quot;othello&quot;, although i was present when it was being studied in class, and i did study alot of it, so i grasp all the basic concepts being brought across:
-othello is a black man in white mans society
-othello only attained his present position because of military superiority
-venetians viewed othello as being primal and &quot;below&quot; them in a sense.
-the thinly shrouded veil of othello&#39;s equality with the venetians is ripped away when he marries desdamona.
-othello is too trusting of others
-Othello descends into madness from iago&#39;s baiting

and i also have watched the movie O plenty of times:
-odin is a black kid at an all white school
-odin only attained his present position because of his sporting prowess
-white people view othello as being &quot;different&quot;
-the dean gets pissed at odin for gettin wiv his daughta(sorry for this line, but i cant think of any other way of putting it. in contrast to othello, the rest of the community still accepts him)
-odin trusts hugo too much
-odin descends into madness from hugo&#39;s baiting. the cocaine doesnt help either.

basically, what im after is as much information as possible that someone can give me about the relationships between the 2 texts when it comes to &quot;text and context&quot;
im really after a band 6(i think its the equivalent of a GPA of 4.0) which is basically the highest mark possible.
according to the board of studies website, to attain a band 6, one must:
[code]
· displays a highly developed ability to describe and analyse a broad range of language forms,
features and structures of texts and explain the ways these shape meaning and influence
responses in a variety of texts and contexts.
· presents a critical, refined personal response showing highly developed skills in
interpretation, analysis, synthesis and evaluation of texts and textual detail.
· exhibits an ability to compose imaginatively, interpretively and critically with sustained
precision, flair, originality and sophistication for a variety of audiences, purposes and
contexts in order to explore and communicate ideas, information and values.
[/code]

http://www.boardofstudies.nsw.edu.au/syllabus_hsc/pdf_doc/english_syl.pdf
around page 45 is the stuff i gotta worry about. im advanced english.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2007 19:23:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/year-11-english-othello-vs-o-text-and-context/142561.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Year 11 English: Othello VS O, Text and context</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@elementalelf elementalelf]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/elementalelf">@elementalelf</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok, i have a major exam in 33 hours that i have done almost no study for, hell, i have never even read the book “othello”, although i was present when it was being studied in class, and i did study alot of it, so i grasp all the basic concepts being brought across:<br>
-othello is a black man in white mans society<br>
-othello only attained his present position because of military superiority<br>
-venetians viewed othello as being primal and “below” them in a sense.<br>
-the thinly shrouded veil of othello’s equality with the venetians is ripped away when he marries desdamona.<br>
-othello is too trusting of others<br>
-Othello descends into madness from iago’s baiting</p>
<p>and i also have watched the movie O plenty of times:<br>
-odin is a black kid at an all white school<br>
-odin only attained his present position because of his sporting prowess<br>
-white people view othello as being “different”<br>
-the dean gets pissed at odin for gettin wiv his daughta(sorry for this line, but i cant think of any other way of putting it. in contrast to othello, the rest of the community still accepts him)<br>
-odin trusts hugo too much<br>
-odin descends into madness from hugo’s baiting. the cocaine doesnt help either.</p>
<p>basically, what im after is as much information as possible that someone can give me about the relationships between the 2 texts when it comes to “text and context”<br>
im really after a band 6(i think its the equivalent of a GPA of 4.0) which is basically the highest mark possible.<br>
according to the board of studies website, to attain a band 6, one must:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">· displays a highly developed ability to describe and analyse a broad range of language forms,
features and structures of texts and explain the ways these shape meaning and influence
responses in a variety of texts and contexts.
· presents a critical, refined personal response showing highly developed skills in
interpretation, analysis, synthesis and evaluation of texts and textual detail.
· exhibits an ability to compose imaginatively, interpretively and critically with sustained
precision, flair, originality and sophistication for a variety of audiences, purposes and
contexts in order to explore and communicate ideas, information and values.</code></pre>
<p><a href="http://www.boardofstudies.nsw.edu.au/syllabus_hsc/pdf_doc/english_syl.pdf" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.boardofstudies.nsw.edu.au/syllabus_hsc/pdf_doc/english_syl.pdf</a><br>
around page 45 is the stuff i gotta worry about. im advanced english.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/year-11-english-othello-vs-o-text-and-context/142561/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/year-11-english-othello-vs-o-text-and-context/142561/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2007 19:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142561-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/year-11-english-othello-vs-o-text-and-context/142561.rss">Year 11 English: Othello VS O, Text and context</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
