<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A few problems :S</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-problems-s/419313</link>
    <description>Right, so basically, i have added 4 more whip recolours into the client.
I have changed their stats, so they give bonuses in different areas etc (item.cfg)

Now, all that is wrong is that when i go to my &#39;Owner Whip&#39; ig, and attack with it, is that it attacks like a longsword, even thought it looks exactly like a recoloured whip.
Also, when i go onto the weapon tab, it has the &quot;slash&quot; &quot;stab&quot; etc... like this :
[URL=http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/12/attackx.jpg/][IMG]http://img12.imageshack.us/img12/1185/attackx.jpg[/img][/URL]

You see? It all seems to be wrong, and my question (1) is, how do i change that to the normal whip... interface?
Thanks.

And, question 2...hehe :)

I&#39;m thinking about recolouring a godsword, (i know recolours look gay and stupid, and mess everything up etc etc, but it&#39;s all experience, and i just want to get my head around iit..)

I have the ints, for an arma godsword, and i understand that Array156, and Array160 are recolours and everything to do with that...

I just want to know how i could recolour it, say... red, and black or purple and black, and then give it a different id, so i can keep the original, and the new one?

Thankyou again :)

EDIT,
I have made the godsword, a different id, and spawned it IG, but, as expected, it isn&#39;t held like the godswords, and doesn&#39;t remove my shield.
I&#39;m wondering how and were i edit that, for it.
Just incase you&#39;re wondering, i&#39;ve changed the id, to a bronze 2h... which(for me) is id; 1307.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 23:31:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-problems-s/419313.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A few problems :S</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CoreVersion CoreVersion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coreversion">@CoreVersion</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Right, so basically, i have added 4 more whip recolours into the client.<br>
I have changed their stats, so they give bonuses in different areas etc (item.cfg)</p>
<p>Now, all that is wrong is that when i go to my ‘Owner Whip’ ig, and attack with it, is that it attacks like a longsword, even thought it looks exactly like a recoloured whip.<br>
Also, when i go onto the weapon tab, it has the “slash” “stab” etc… like this :<br>
<a href="http://imageshack.us/photo/my-images/12/attackx.jpg/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img12.imageshack.us/img12/1185/attackx.jpg" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>You see? It all seems to be wrong, and my question (1) is, how do i change that to the normal whip… interface?<br>
Thanks.</p>
<p>And, question 2…hehe <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I’m thinking about recolouring a godsword, (i know recolours look gay and stupid, and mess everything up etc etc, but it’s all experience, and i just want to get my head around iit…)</p>
<p>I have the ints, for an arma godsword, and i understand that Array156, and Array160 are recolours and everything to do with that…</p>
<p>I just want to know how i could recolour it, say… red, and black or purple and black, and then give it a different id, so i can keep the original, and the new one?</p>
<p>Thankyou again <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>EDIT,<br>
I have made the godsword, a different id, and spawned it IG, but, as expected, it isn’t held like the godswords, and doesn’t remove my shield.<br>
I’m wondering how and were i edit that, for it.<br>
Just incase you’re wondering, i’ve changed the id, to a bronze 2h… which(for me) is id; 1307.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-problems-s/419313/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-problems-s/419313/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 23:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-419313-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-few-problems-s/419313.rss">A few problems :S</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
