<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>TheRealPleasure Presents, &quot;E28&quot;</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/therealpleasure-presents-e28/553025</link>
    <description>G&#39;Day Guys,

Used to run a client Back in the day, am making my return slowly integrating my past knowledge and present knowledge, I won&#39;t reveal my old forum name ever, But do not let this deter you from what is coming, starting from a reworked P.I client and source, I&#39;ll keep this space updated regularly and as I always used to do, provide any and all source code I use upon request, no images as of yet, what can you expect from a clean client though, this all said and done will provide images shortly.

*Admin feel free to delete if necessary, we all know you&#39;re nazi&#39;s anyway! seriously though, I can re-write this when I provide content.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 13:25:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/therealpleasure-presents-e28/553025.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>TheRealPleasure Presents, &quot;E28&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TheRealPleasure TheRealPleasure]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/therealpleasure">@TheRealPleasure</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>G’Day Guys,</p>
<p>Used to run a client Back in the day, am making my return slowly integrating my past knowledge and present knowledge, I won’t reveal my old forum name ever, But do not let this deter you from what is coming, starting from a reworked P.I client and source, I’ll keep this space updated regularly and as I always used to do, provide any and all source code I use upon request, no images as of yet, what can you expect from a clean client though, this all said and done will provide images shortly.</p>
<p>*Admin feel free to delete if necessary, we all know you’re nazi’s anyway! seriously though, I can re-write this when I provide content.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/therealpleasure-presents-e28/553025/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/therealpleasure-presents-e28/553025/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 13:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553025-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/therealpleasure-presents-e28/553025.rss">TheRealPleasure Presents, &quot;E28&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
