<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432</link>
    <description>This guide will be based on personal experiences so if you want something added to the guide you are weary about. post the topic and i will add it.

[size=12pt][u]Public Server General Risks[/u][/size]

So you have created a public server, and your first few members are flocking in. You do not know these people, but at this stage, your just happy having them here, that is what blinds you from this point i would like to make.

Those people have an established connection to your computer. They are allowed through the router, and now you are close to being completely vunerable to attack, if one was a hacker. You may be thinking to yourself, &quot;oh crap im screwed&quot; , this shouldnt be the case, because some handy tools can help keep your players, your server, and most importantly, YOU safe from harm.


[size=12pt][u]Password Inspection and Changing[/u][/size]

If you are using a admin account or mod account, make your password something no one would guess, including numbers and letters, and atleast 9 characters long. That should ensure temporary safety to brute force attacks. Also, you should change the password often. (once a week) This also goes for your username and password on your router and Computer.

[size=12pt][u]Firewall and Antivirus[/u][/size]

These two things will be your primary tools to defending your computer. You are foolish to be without both of them. But only some are recommendable for this occasion.

Firewalls are your last resort before a hacker can get into your computer and corrupt and change your data. Make sure you have one with limitation options preferably options that allow you to block an IP and protect open ports.

[size=12pt][u]Some recommended Firewalls are:[/u][/size]

ZoneAlarm [i](Highly Recommended)[/i] - [url=http://www.zonealarm.com]http://www.zonealarm.com[/url]

Pctools Firewall - [url=http://www.pctools.com/firewall/]http://www.pctools.com/firewall/[/url]

Norton Personal Firewall - [url=http://www.symantec.com]http://www.symantec.com[/url]

McAfee Firewall - [url=http://www.mcafee.com]http://www.mcafee.com[/url]

An Antivirus is your clean up tool. If your hacker gets in and implants his programs to do his bidding, this is your only way to clean up what he has dumped on your harddrive.

[size=12pt][u]Some recommended Anti-virus&#39;s are:[/u][/size]

Avast [i](Highly Recommended)[/i] - [url=http://avast.com]http://avast.com[/url]

Norton Internet security - [url=http://www.symantec.com]http://www.symantec.com[/url]

AVG - [url=http://www.grisoft.com]http://www.grisoft.com[/url]

These are great for picking up known viruses, i suggest using more than one.

With these tools you should be well armed for battle against a hacker. But if you want near perfect protection, i suggest looking into a router.

[size=12pt][u]Online Virus Scan (Dose Not Remove)[/u][/size]

This tool is very very useful because you can scan zip, rar, exe, and othere files before you open them so
that the virus dose not get to you. Don&#39;t ever extract a file without scaning it so a good place for that would be these places below.

Jotti Online - [url=http://virusscan.jotti.org]http://virusscan.jotti.org[/url]

Kaspersky - [url=http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus]http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus[/url]

Ca - [url=http://ca.com/us/securityadvisor/virusinfo/scan.aspx]http://ca.com/us/securityadvisor/virusinfo/scan.aspx[/url]

[size=12pt][u]Spy Sweepers - Kill them keyloggers on your pc[/u][/size]

Well i Spy Sweeper, Sweeps them Keyloggers that record every thing you do. They can get all your pass words every thing now you dont want that do you? Did think so so i have made a list of some Spy Sweepers to remove them from your computer!

Pc Tools Spy Doctor - [url=http://www.pctools.com/spyware-doctor/]http://www.pctools.com/spyware-doctor/[/url]

[size=12pt][u]Router Protection - The Ultimate Firewall[/u][/size]

A router is a supreme solution to keeping your computer safe from malicious attacks. The main reason they are near bulletproof. Nothing can get through without ports being open.

On routers their are a few default ports that are always open. for example port 80 for internet browsing. but if you want people to connect to your computer. Lets say play on your private server, you will have to open more ports) for them to be able to connect. This leaves those ports vunerable for attack. but thats 1-2 ports out of 99999. So the hacker would have to know what hes hacking before he could get inside (or he would do a port scan)

So there, this limits the hackers possibilities to virtually none if he wasnt attacking your private server. But in this thread we will pretend he is, and at this point in the game. You would be hijacked. So lets continue to find out what we can do to keep those people out.

[size=12pt][u]How To Respond To an Attack, and What You Should Do.[/u][/size]

So lets say this hacker got through, made it into your database, banned all your admins, made himself one, and enlisted a few more to help his cause. You would be just about ready to give up, rolling on the floor sucking your thumb knowing your computers going down slowly. Dont panic, this is what you can do to protect yourself.

Using Antivirus and Firewall protection, as well as the command prompt. We can find the person connected to your computer&#39;s IP, Block it from your computer, delete his virus he probably left to get back in, and in the end save your computer!

Here is the battle plan.

[size=12pt][u]The Battle Plan - A Defensive Alternative[/u][/size]

So the hacker proboly has admin on your server and probably banned you and took away your powers. Dont fear, you won&#39;t forget, you have control over the database. when you see him enter your server. quickly make a admin account. get on the server, and before he kicks and bans you, do a player info command (or connected from, or look at your runserver window if you are hosting). at the bottom of the message, it will display his IP. write it down, this part is vital.

With that IP in hand you are now ready to launch your defensive manuaver. Bring up your firewall, and pray it can block IP&#39;s. if it can, put in his IP, if it requires a network LAN IP, open up command prompt (start &gt; Run &gt;CMD) and type in ipconfig, your lan IP will be the Ip address shown, then either wait for him to Disconnect from your server, or kill the connection with a command. now he will be barred from your system without any means of getting back in. His IP is blocked (Be careful, this only works with STATIC IPs).

The hacker, however, could of deployed a few viruses for him to gain entry again. (examples include backdoor.trojan or a RAT program). use a few antiVirus&#39;s to scan for them. use more than one however, most antivirus&#39;s dont pick up everything.

When your done the clean up. You are now safe from the hacker. For now. And I guarantee he will try to attack again, just remain smart, remember the battle plan. and know how to use your tools effectively to get that low life back out of your computer.


Note: your computer is never going to be 100% safe. so make a public server at your own expense. Thank you for reading my guide, I hope it has given you an Idea on how to protect yourself.

If you see an error in the guide please point it out and I will fix it the best I can (please dont flame)
[size=12pt][u]
FAQ and reader concerns and personal issues[/u][/size]

This is a section to help readers with there personal experiences and concerns. I will try to give the best answer I can so i can keep the Rune-Server members safe.

Q: Will Jagex ban me?
A: Probably, if they ever find out, but I highly doubt they will while doing legal things.

Q: Can you teach me how to make a private server please?
A: No, this guide merely points out the risk of running one, and how to protect yourself.

Becareful and have fun on your servers!

Credits - To some guy on rune-server and some to me for adding on to it with more stuff</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 19:59:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@b15 b15]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b15">@b15</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>NICE POST THIS WILL HELP LOTS. IDK IF U LEACHED OR WHATEVER, BY SPREADING THE WORD AROUND IT WILL HELP LOADS OF SERVERS TO BECOME MORE SAFE! if u did leach u should have added his name in the credits but besides that you helped a lot! Thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 19:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@grimreaper61 grimreaper61]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/grimreaper61">@grimreaper61</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wow this helped me alot…my 1 character password really isnt cutting it. I am glad i read this before i got hacked/sarcasm</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 15:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="167432">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/coalman58/40/2486_1.png" class="avatar"> coalman58:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Thanks for the info.Once I had a few people trying to log onto my computer but cause of my 5 really good firewalls and anti virus programs and scanners it let me choose for some reason if I want to give this person some,full,or no controll of my computer.I know it’s weird but it did and thanks to my firewalls and my spybots it got rid of my trogens.Thanks to my mom’s computer junky friend and thanks to you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> O and don’t let it get to you that people are making fun of you,they do it to me alot in school.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It let you choose? LOL?!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 15:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@coalman58 coalman58]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coalman58">@coalman58</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the info.Once I had a few people trying to log onto my computer but cause of my 5 really good firewalls and anti virus programs and scanners it let me choose for some reason if I want to give this person some,full,or no controll of my computer.I know it’s weird but it did and thanks to my firewalls and my spybots it got rid of my trogens.Thanks to my mom’s computer junky friend and thanks to you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> O and don’t let it get to you that people are making fun of you,they do it to me alot in school.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 14:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gnarly1 gnarly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gnarly1">@gnarly1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks barrage time</p>
<p>This is for them people who make post about players impersonating them and “OMg somE GuY maDe HIm Self A Admin ON My sErVer WHAT DO i dO??!?!?!” People liek that</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 12:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@barrage_time barrage time]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/barrage_time">@barrage_time</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Not really, better to be safe then sorry?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 12:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@For For ( ; ; )]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/for">@For</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is quite sad lol. This post makes it sound like it’s some big battle, it’s funny because the majority of people on private servers can’t program simple java and yet, you think one of them is going to be clever enough to implant viruses to allow themselves access to your computer ?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 12:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gnarly1 gnarly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gnarly1">@gnarly1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow you just made a fool of your self</p>
<p>““Credits - To some guy on rune-server and some to me for adding on to it with more stuff””</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 12:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@For For ( ; ; )]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/for">@For</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah didn’t someone else post this ? I remember laughing at it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 12:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@snowycards snowycards]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/snowycards">@snowycards</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>umm i saw this posted by someone else a while ago so i think this is leeched</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 12:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gnarly1 gnarly]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gnarly1">@gnarly1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This guide will be based on personal experiences so if you want something added to the guide you are weary about. post the topic and i will add it.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">Public Server General Risks</span>[/size]</p>
<p>So you have created a public server, and your first few members are flocking in. You do not know these people, but at this stage, your just happy having them here, that is what blinds you from this point i would like to make.</p>
<p>Those people have an established connection to your computer. They are allowed through the router, and now you are close to being completely vunerable to attack, if one was a hacker. You may be thinking to yourself, “oh crap im screwed” , this shouldnt be the case, because some handy tools can help keep your players, your server, and most importantly, YOU safe from harm.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">Password Inspection and Changing</span>[/size]</p>
<p>If you are using a admin account or mod account, make your password something no one would guess, including numbers and letters, and atleast 9 characters long. That should ensure temporary safety to brute force attacks. Also, you should change the password often. (once a week) This also goes for your username and password on your router and Computer.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">Firewall and Antivirus</span>[/size]</p>
<p>These two things will be your primary tools to defending your computer. You are foolish to be without both of them. But only some are recommendable for this occasion.</p>
<p>Firewalls are your last resort before a hacker can get into your computer and corrupt and change your data. Make sure you have one with limitation options preferably options that allow you to block an IP and protect open ports.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">Some recommended Firewalls are:</span>[/size]</p>
<p>ZoneAlarm <span class="bbcode-i">(Highly Recommended)</span> - <a href="http://www.zonealarm.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.zonealarm.com</a></p>
<p>Pctools Firewall - <a href="http://www.pctools.com/firewall/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.pctools.com/firewall/</a></p>
<p>Norton Personal Firewall - <a href="http://www.symantec.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.symantec.com</a></p>
<p>McAfee Firewall - <a href="http://www.mcafee.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.mcafee.com</a></p>
<p>An Antivirus is your clean up tool. If your hacker gets in and implants his programs to do his bidding, this is your only way to clean up what he has dumped on your harddrive.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">Some recommended Anti-virus’s are:</span>[/size]</p>
<p>Avast <span class="bbcode-i">(Highly Recommended)</span> - <a href="http://avast.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://avast.com</a></p>
<p>Norton Internet security - <a href="http://www.symantec.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.symantec.com</a></p>
<p>AVG - <a href="http://www.grisoft.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.grisoft.com</a></p>
<p>These are great for picking up known viruses, i suggest using more than one.</p>
<p>With these tools you should be well armed for battle against a hacker. But if you want near perfect protection, i suggest looking into a router.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">Online Virus Scan (Dose Not Remove)</span>[/size]</p>
<p>This tool is very very useful because you can scan zip, rar, exe, and othere files before you open them so<br>
that the virus dose not get to you. Don’t ever extract a file without scaning it so a good place for that would be these places below.</p>
<p>Jotti Online - <a href="http://virusscan.jotti.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://virusscan.jotti.org</a></p>
<p>Kaspersky - <a href="http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus</a></p>
<p>Ca - <a href="http://ca.com/us/securityadvisor/virusinfo/scan.aspx" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://ca.com/us/securityadvisor/virusinfo/scan.aspx</a></p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">Spy Sweepers - Kill them keyloggers on your pc</span>[/size]</p>
<p>Well i Spy Sweeper, Sweeps them Keyloggers that record every thing you do. They can get all your pass words every thing now you dont want that do you? Did think so so i have made a list of some Spy Sweepers to remove them from your computer!</p>
<p>Pc Tools Spy Doctor - <a href="http://www.pctools.com/spyware-doctor/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.pctools.com/spyware-doctor/</a></p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">Router Protection - The Ultimate Firewall</span>[/size]</p>
<p>A router is a supreme solution to keeping your computer safe from malicious attacks. The main reason they are near bulletproof. Nothing can get through without ports being open.</p>
<p>On routers their are a few default ports that are always open. for example port 80 for internet browsing. but if you want people to connect to your computer. Lets say play on your private server, you will have to open more ports) for them to be able to connect. This leaves those ports vunerable for attack. but thats 1-2 ports out of 99999. So the hacker would have to know what hes hacking before he could get inside (or he would do a port scan)</p>
<p>So there, this limits the hackers possibilities to virtually none if he wasnt attacking your private server. But in this thread we will pretend he is, and at this point in the game. You would be hijacked. So lets continue to find out what we can do to keep those people out.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">How To Respond To an Attack, and What You Should Do.</span>[/size]</p>
<p>So lets say this hacker got through, made it into your database, banned all your admins, made himself one, and enlisted a few more to help his cause. You would be just about ready to give up, rolling on the floor sucking your thumb knowing your computers going down slowly. Dont panic, this is what you can do to protect yourself.</p>
<p>Using Antivirus and Firewall protection, as well as the command prompt. We can find the person connected to your computer’s IP, Block it from your computer, delete his virus he probably left to get back in, and in the end save your computer!</p>
<p>Here is the battle plan.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u">The Battle Plan - A Defensive Alternative</span>[/size]</p>
<p>So the hacker proboly has admin on your server and probably banned you and took away your powers. Dont fear, you won’t forget, you have control over the database. when you see him enter your server. quickly make a admin account. get on the server, and before he kicks and bans you, do a player info command (or connected from, or look at your runserver window if you are hosting). at the bottom of the message, it will display his IP. write it down, this part is vital.</p>
<p>With that IP in hand you are now ready to launch your defensive manuaver. Bring up your firewall, and pray it can block IP’s. if it can, put in his IP, if it requires a network LAN IP, open up command prompt (start &gt; Run &gt;CMD) and type in ipconfig, your lan IP will be the Ip address shown, then either wait for him to Disconnect from your server, or kill the connection with a command. now he will be barred from your system without any means of getting back in. His IP is blocked (Be careful, this only works with STATIC IPs).</p>
<p>The hacker, however, could of deployed a few viruses for him to gain entry again. (examples include backdoor.trojan or a RAT program). use a few antiVirus’s to scan for them. use more than one however, most antivirus’s dont pick up everything.</p>
<p>When your done the clean up. You are now safe from the hacker. For now. And I guarantee he will try to attack again, just remain smart, remember the battle plan. and know how to use your tools effectively to get that low life back out of your computer.</p>
<p>Note: your computer is never going to be 100% safe. so make a public server at your own expense. Thank you for reading my guide, I hope it has given you an Idea on how to protect yourself.</p>
<p>If you see an error in the guide please point it out and I will fix it the best I can (please dont flame)<br>
[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><br>
FAQ and reader concerns and personal issues</span>[/size]</p>
<p>This is a section to help readers with there personal experiences and concerns. I will try to give the best answer I can so i can keep the Rune-Server members safe.</p>
<p>Q: Will Jagex ban me?<br>
A: Probably, if they ever find out, but I highly doubt they will while doing legal things.</p>
<p>Q: Can you teach me how to make a private server please?<br>
A: No, this guide merely points out the risk of running one, and how to protect yourself.</p>
<p>Becareful and have fun on your servers!</p>
<p>Credits - To some guy on rune-server and some to me for adding on to it with more stuff</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 11:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-167432-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-a-public-server-and-how-to-protect-yourself/167432.rss">Hosting a Public Server, And How to Protect Yourself!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
