<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266</link>
    <description>There are many problems with Rack Steady&#39;s actions. The one that&#39;s the most blatant, and the one that I will limit my discussion to, is related to its overt support of interventionism. But first, let me pose you a question: Is Rack Steady actually concerned about any of us or does it just want to allow federally funded research to mushroom into a randy, grossly inefficient system, hampered by viperine babblers and the worst types of naive crooks there are? After reading this letter, you&#39;ll certainly find it&#39;s the latter. Rack Steady is extremely contemptuous. In fact, my handy-dandy Contemptuous-O-Meter confirms that Rack Steady&#39;s goal is to prey on people&#39;s fear of political and economic instability. This is abject sensationalism!

Someone needs to build a true community of spirit and purpose based on mutual respect and caring. Who&#39;s going to do it? Rack Steady? I think not. What do you think of this: It would be a work of supererogation to study the problem and recommend corrective action at a time when every week there transpires news of officious degenerates following Rack Steady&#39;s orders to destroy all tradition, all morality, and the entire democratic system?

Without a doubt, however, Rack Steady cannot be tamed by &quot;tolerance&quot; and &quot;accommodation&quot; but is actually spurred on by such gestures. It sees such gestures as a sign of weakness on our part and is thereby encouraged to continue displacing meaningful discussion of an issue&#39;s merit or demerit with hunch and emotion. As a general rule, Rack Steady keeps repeating over and over again that people prefer &quot;cultural integrity&quot; and &quot;multicultural sensitivity&quot; to health, food, safety, and the opportunity to choose their own course through life. This verbigeration is symptomatic of an excessive love of statism and indicates to me that if we don&#39;t acquire the input of a representative cross-section of the community in a non-threatening, inclusive environment right now, then Rack Steady&#39;s metanarratives will soon start to metastasize until they carve out space in the mainstream for unholy politics. While Rack Steady puts on a good dog-and-pony show, its legatees are merely ciphers. Rack Steady is the one who decides whether or not to perpetuate myths that glorify antinomianism. Rack Steady is the one who gives out the orders to smear people of impeccable character and reputation. And Rack Steady is the one trying to conceal how it irritates all and sundry. Don&#39;t make the mistake of thinking otherwise. Rack Steady does, and that&#39;s why Machiavellianism is the principal ingredient in the ideological flypaper it uses to attract the most whiney champions of deceit, lies, theft, plunder, and rapine you&#39;ll ever see into its club. Well, that&#39;s another story. To get back to my main point, I ought to mention that I&#39;m not writing this letter for your entertainment. I&#39;m not even writing it for your education. I&#39;m writing it for our very survival.

Honor means nothing to Rack Steady. Principles mean nothing to Rack Steady. All it cares about is how best to acquire public acceptance of its selfish false-flag operations.

Rack Steady has blood on its hands. Naturally, it pretends to be an innocent lamb who has our best interests at heart. We all know the reality: If Rack Steady really had our best interests at heart, it wouldn&#39;t turn back the clock and repeal all the civil rights and anti-discrimination legislation now on the books. Rack Steady uses heathenism to invent a new moral system that legitimizes its desire to reinforce the impression that blathering leeches—as opposed to Rack Steady&#39;s apple-polishers—are striving to teach beggarly concepts to children. That&#39;s the large elephant in the room that nobody talks about. Nevertheless, I unquestionably think that people really ought to start talking about it because then they&#39;d realize that Rack Steady really shouldn&#39;t replicate the most self-aggrandizing structures of contemporary life. That&#39;s just common sense. Of course, the people who appreciate its litanies are those who eagerly root up common sense, prominently hold it out, and decry it as poison with astonishing alacrity.

Are you beginning to get the picture here? If Rack Steady honestly believes that some of my points are not valid, I would love to get some specific feedback from it. Some meretricious, malign hoodlums have raised objections to my indiscretions but their objections are all politically motivated. Rack Steady&#39;s ruminations provide a vivid example of how Rack Steady oppresses its rivals by crushing them, expelling them, pauperizing them, and cutting them off from families and friends. With this central point cleared up, the rest of its arguments are rendered moot, as I want you to know that comments like that don&#39;t sit well with reckless nitwits. Knowing, as they say, is half the battle. What remains is to lay out some ideas and interpretations that hold the potential for insight.

I am not mistaken when I say that unless you define success using the sort of loosey-goosey standards by which Rack Steady abides you&#39;ll realize that true measures of success involve avoiding the extremes of a pessimistic naturalism and an optimistic humanism by combining the truths of both. Success is getting the world to see that Rack Steady appears to have found a new tool to use to help it control, manipulate, and harm other people. That tool is racism, and if you watch it wield it you&#39;ll honestly see why one of the great mysteries of modern life is, How much longer can we tolerate its insensate practices before the whole country collectively throws up? I have asked God for answers, but it appears that this is a closed-book test. Let me simply suggest, therefore, that whenever Rack Steady attempts to panic irrationally and overreact completely, it looks around waiting for applause as if it&#39;s done something decent and moral rather than illogical and mephitic.

Fortunately, if you ever get into an argument with some of Rack Steady&#39;s attendants about whether or not its wheelings and dealings are counterproductive to society, I have an excellent sockdolager for you. Simply inform the other party that this is not the first time we&#39;ve had trouble with otiose malingerers, and it won&#39;t be the last. There&#39;s no need here to present any evidence of that; examples can be found all over the World Wide Web. In fact, a simple search will quickly reveal that if Rack Steady&#39;s thinking were cerebral rather than glandular, it wouldn&#39;t consider it such a good idea to use both overt and covert deceptions to quash other people&#39;s opinions.

You are, I&#39;m sure, well aware that the pragmatist position is that Rack Steady&#39;s standard operating procedure is to trick our children into adopting unconventional, disapproved-of opinions and ways of life. But did you know that there will be public outrage if it tries to block streets and traffic to the extent that ambulances can&#39;t get through? Regardless of what philanthropic enthusiasts or visionary dreamers may say about corporate perfectibility, Rack Steady&#39;s sole purpose in life seems to be to influence the attitudes of dominant culture towards any environment or activity that is predominantly complacent. This is not what I think; this is what I know. I additionally know that I will never give up. I will never stop trying. And I will use every avenue possible to think outside the box.

Now let&#39;s go back to what I was saying earlier about how Rack Steady clings to cronyism like a drowning man clings to a life preserver. As I previously stated, at the heart of the problem is its obliviousness to history, its moral cowardice masked in bold rhetoric, and its overwhelmingly shallow political posturing. An obvious parallel from a different context is that Rack Steady cheers acts of wanton slaughter. Once we realize that, what do we do? The appropriate thing, in my judgment, is to hold Rack Steady responsible for the hatred it so furtively expresses. I say that because its true colors have finally come out. That&#39;s something you won&#39;t find in your local newspaper because it&#39;s the news that just doesn&#39;t fit. Okay, there&#39;s no reason for me to be closed-minded, so I&#39;ll leave you with this concept: Rack Steady loves everybody so much, it wants to rip out the guts of everybody who doesn&#39;t love everybody as much as it does.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 22:58:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>k</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 22:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466266-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266.rss">Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xdeathstarsx x Albi x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xdeathstarsx">@xdeathstarsx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>FUCK U ALL CUINTS FUCK U</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 22:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466266-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266.rss">Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/CeSLc.gif" alt width="161" height="81"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 17:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466266-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266.rss">Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/7DzPH.gif" alt width="350" height="193"><br>
<img src="http://i1256.photobucket.com/albums/ii482/miscgifz/store-didnt-read-lol.gif" alt width="320" height="320"><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/xPiWp.gif" alt width="368" height="230"><br>
<img src="http://i55.tinypic.com/1z68w0i.gif" alt width="352" height="288"><br>
<img src="http://oi39.tinypic.com/2d7yja0.jpg" alt width="265" height="244"><br>
<img src="http://i.imgur.com/lbOtp.gif" alt width="400" height="299"><br>
<img src="http://i125.photobucket.com/albums/p75/jalamb86/gifs/didntread.gif" alt width="320" height="320"><br>
<img src="http://gifsforum.com/images/gif/did%20not%20read/grand/did-not-read-eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3-927.gif" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i718.photobucket.com/albums/ww185/danceloversteph/no1curr.gif" alt width="320" height="320"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 01:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466266-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266.rss">Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>cool Markov chain story bro.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 00:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466266-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266.rss">Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xdeathstarsx x Albi x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xdeathstarsx">@xdeathstarsx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There are many problems with Rack Steady’s actions. The one that’s the most blatant, and the one that I will limit my discussion to, is related to its overt support of interventionism. But first, let me pose you a question: Is Rack Steady actually concerned about any of us or does it just want to allow federally funded research to mushroom into a randy, grossly inefficient system, hampered by viperine babblers and the worst types of naive crooks there are? After reading this letter, you’ll certainly find it’s the latter. Rack Steady is extremely contemptuous. In fact, my handy-dandy Contemptuous-O-Meter confirms that Rack Steady’s goal is to prey on people’s fear of political and economic instability. This is abject sensationalism!</p>
<p>Someone needs to build a true community of spirit and purpose based on mutual respect and caring. Who’s going to do it? Rack Steady? I think not. What do you think of this: It would be a work of supererogation to study the problem and recommend corrective action at a time when every week there transpires news of officious degenerates following Rack Steady’s orders to destroy all tradition, all morality, and the entire democratic system?</p>
<p>Without a doubt, however, Rack Steady cannot be tamed by “tolerance” and “accommodation” but is actually spurred on by such gestures. It sees such gestures as a sign of weakness on our part and is thereby encouraged to continue displacing meaningful discussion of an issue’s merit or demerit with hunch and emotion. As a general rule, Rack Steady keeps repeating over and over again that people prefer “cultural integrity” and “multicultural sensitivity” to health, food, safety, and the opportunity to choose their own course through life. This verbigeration is symptomatic of an excessive love of statism and indicates to me that if we don’t acquire the input of a representative cross-section of the community in a non-threatening, inclusive environment right now, then Rack Steady’s metanarratives will soon start to metastasize until they carve out space in the mainstream for unholy politics. While Rack Steady puts on a good dog-and-pony show, its legatees are merely ciphers. Rack Steady is the one who decides whether or not to perpetuate myths that glorify antinomianism. Rack Steady is the one who gives out the orders to smear people of impeccable character and reputation. And Rack Steady is the one trying to conceal how it irritates all and sundry. Don’t make the mistake of thinking otherwise. Rack Steady does, and that’s why Machiavellianism is the principal ingredient in the ideological flypaper it uses to attract the most whiney champions of deceit, lies, theft, plunder, and rapine you’ll ever see into its club. Well, that’s another story. To get back to my main point, I ought to mention that I’m not writing this letter for your entertainment. I’m not even writing it for your education. I’m writing it for our very survival.</p>
<p>Honor means nothing to Rack Steady. Principles mean nothing to Rack Steady. All it cares about is how best to acquire public acceptance of its selfish false-flag operations.</p>
<p>Rack Steady has blood on its hands. Naturally, it pretends to be an innocent lamb who has our best interests at heart. We all know the reality: If Rack Steady really had our best interests at heart, it wouldn’t turn back the clock and repeal all the civil rights and anti-discrimination legislation now on the books. Rack Steady uses heathenism to invent a new moral system that legitimizes its desire to reinforce the impression that blathering leeches—as opposed to Rack Steady’s apple-polishers—are striving to teach beggarly concepts to children. That’s the large elephant in the room that nobody talks about. Nevertheless, I unquestionably think that people really ought to start talking about it because then they’d realize that Rack Steady really shouldn’t replicate the most self-aggrandizing structures of contemporary life. That’s just common sense. Of course, the people who appreciate its litanies are those who eagerly root up common sense, prominently hold it out, and decry it as poison with astonishing alacrity.</p>
<p>Are you beginning to get the picture here? If Rack Steady honestly believes that some of my points are not valid, I would love to get some specific feedback from it. Some meretricious, malign hoodlums have raised objections to my indiscretions but their objections are all politically motivated. Rack Steady’s ruminations provide a vivid example of how Rack Steady oppresses its rivals by crushing them, expelling them, pauperizing them, and cutting them off from families and friends. With this central point cleared up, the rest of its arguments are rendered moot, as I want you to know that comments like that don’t sit well with reckless nitwits. Knowing, as they say, is half the battle. What remains is to lay out some ideas and interpretations that hold the potential for insight.</p>
<p>I am not mistaken when I say that unless you define success using the sort of loosey-goosey standards by which Rack Steady abides you’ll realize that true measures of success involve avoiding the extremes of a pessimistic naturalism and an optimistic humanism by combining the truths of both. Success is getting the world to see that Rack Steady appears to have found a new tool to use to help it control, manipulate, and harm other people. That tool is racism, and if you watch it wield it you’ll honestly see why one of the great mysteries of modern life is, How much longer can we tolerate its insensate practices before the whole country collectively throws up? I have asked God for answers, but it appears that this is a closed-book test. Let me simply suggest, therefore, that whenever Rack Steady attempts to panic irrationally and overreact completely, it looks around waiting for applause as if it’s done something decent and moral rather than illogical and mephitic.</p>
<p>Fortunately, if you ever get into an argument with some of Rack Steady’s attendants about whether or not its wheelings and dealings are counterproductive to society, I have an excellent sockdolager for you. Simply inform the other party that this is not the first time we’ve had trouble with otiose malingerers, and it won’t be the last. There’s no need here to present any evidence of that; examples can be found all over the World Wide Web. In fact, a simple search will quickly reveal that if Rack Steady’s thinking were cerebral rather than glandular, it wouldn’t consider it such a good idea to use both overt and covert deceptions to quash other people’s opinions.</p>
<p>You are, I’m sure, well aware that the pragmatist position is that Rack Steady’s standard operating procedure is to trick our children into adopting unconventional, disapproved-of opinions and ways of life. But did you know that there will be public outrage if it tries to block streets and traffic to the extent that ambulances can’t get through? Regardless of what philanthropic enthusiasts or visionary dreamers may say about corporate perfectibility, Rack Steady’s sole purpose in life seems to be to influence the attitudes of dominant culture towards any environment or activity that is predominantly complacent. This is not what I think; this is what I know. I additionally know that I will never give up. I will never stop trying. And I will use every avenue possible to think outside the box.</p>
<p>Now let’s go back to what I was saying earlier about how Rack Steady clings to cronyism like a drowning man clings to a life preserver. As I previously stated, at the heart of the problem is its obliviousness to history, its moral cowardice masked in bold rhetoric, and its overwhelmingly shallow political posturing. An obvious parallel from a different context is that Rack Steady cheers acts of wanton slaughter. Once we realize that, what do we do? The appropriate thing, in my judgment, is to hold Rack Steady responsible for the hatred it so furtively expresses. I say that because its true colors have finally come out. That’s something you won’t find in your local newspaper because it’s the news that just doesn’t fit. Okay, there’s no reason for me to be closed-minded, so I’ll leave you with this concept: Rack Steady loves everybody so much, it wants to rip out the guts of everybody who doesn’t love everybody as much as it does.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-466266-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rack-steady-shitty/466266.rss">Rack steady (shitty! :@@@)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
