<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Storyline</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920</link>
    <description>
I&#39;m going to keep this short, since I&#39;m serious about my new soon to be released game, and since I&#39;m planning to earn some money with it I thought it would be interesting to include a storyline.


[b]Description of the game:[/b]

With your mouse you control some guy with guns in first person.


With WASD/Arrows you control a fish.


Your fish is basicly dumped in the sea with other fishes with different sizes, and you have to eat smaller fishes, and avoid bigger fishes or else you&#39;ll die. The more fish you eat, the bigger your fish gets. Much like the original Fishy.
Now, with the first person guy, you basicly can shoot fish in the sea to help your fish. If you kill a fish your fish gets bigger aswell because your fish eats the dead meat. Now, this is because of the fact that your fish alone could not survive, the game is random generated and gives sometimes combinations like 2 Big fishes from the left and 2 from the right. A combo that our fish could not survive on it&#39;s own. This is where our guy comes in, and shoots the f out of those fishes. So with the guy, it does not matter if the enemy fishes are bigger than our fish or not.


This may sound cheesy but it&#39;s a pretty fun game from what I&#39;ve heard, and people did play 30+ minutes (Pre-Alpha builds).


And yes, I have systems integrated within the game that give me a list of the gameplay lengts, the host where the game is being hosted,...


It&#39;s a 2D game, if this turns out to be something, then the next version will be 3D.


[b]As you can see...[/b]

It is quite hard to find a matching storyline to this game.


After some fast thinking, I&#39;ve came to this:


Basicly, there was this guy Vreg and he was extremely smart.
One day he was bored and took a sample of his DNA and cloned a fish version of him.
He named him Vreggie.
He went fishing one day with Vreggie next to him but landed into a storm.
The storm got worse and basicly he and Vreggie got overboard.
He was able to swim back to land but Vreggie was lost.
Now this was tragic because I forgot to mention that while cloning himself he made a mistake,
one that kills Vreg when Vreggie dies.
Wich is why he integrated a GPS system and manual control into Vreggie&#39;s brain incase of emergensies.
He ran home really quick and activated the GPS system, after he received a signal with the location of Vreggie
he took his scuba diving outfit and his guns and went after Vreggie. 
Once he finally reached Vreggie under water he activated manual control.
His goal was to make Vreggie the biggest of all fishes so that he could turn off manual control without Vreggie getting killed. 


It is up to you to define the fate of Vreg and Vreggie.


-----------------------------------------------------------


So that&#39;s it I guess, I tried to make it funny because I can&#39;t think of anything serious that matches the gameplay.




Opinions and improvements are welcome.


Extra: the game has 10 levels (waves) of 3 minutes. It get&#39;s harder the longer you play, but you get money from killing fishes wich allows you to upgrade your weapons, buy all sorts of items such as God Fish, Double Guns,....
I&#39;ve made 8 guns and 10 items for the first release of the game. /notthatanyonecares.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 23:40:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Storyline</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“CoonHunter, post:2, topic:402920”]Sounds like a weird version of the bacteria level of Spore.[/quote]Lol, it’s fun, and I don’t play Spore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 23:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-402920-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920.rss">Storyline</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Storyline</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CoonHunter CoonHunter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/coonhunter">@CoonHunter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds like a weird version of the bacteria level of Spore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 23:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-402920-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920.rss">Storyline</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Storyline</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MistaBigBoss MistaBigBoss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mistabigboss">@MistaBigBoss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m going to keep this short, since I’m serious about my new soon to be released game, and since I’m planning to earn some money with it I thought it would be interesting to include a storyline.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Description of the game:</span></p>
<p>With your mouse you control some guy with guns in first person.</p>
<p>With WASD/Arrows you control a fish.</p>
<p>Your fish is basicly dumped in the sea with other fishes with different sizes, and you have to eat smaller fishes, and avoid bigger fishes or else you’ll die. The more fish you eat, the bigger your fish gets. Much like the original Fishy.<br>
Now, with the first person guy, you basicly can shoot fish in the sea to help your fish. If you kill a fish your fish gets bigger aswell because your fish eats the dead meat. Now, this is because of the fact that your fish alone could not survive, the game is random generated and gives sometimes combinations like 2 Big fishes from the left and 2 from the right. A combo that our fish could not survive on it’s own. This is where our guy comes in, and shoots the f out of those fishes. So with the guy, it does not matter if the enemy fishes are bigger than our fish or not.</p>
<p>This may sound cheesy but it’s a pretty fun game from what I’ve heard, and people did play 30+ minutes (Pre-Alpha builds).</p>
<p>And yes, I have systems integrated within the game that give me a list of the gameplay lengts, the host where the game is being hosted,…</p>
<p>It’s a 2D game, if this turns out to be something, then the next version will be 3D.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">As you can see…</span></p>
<p>It is quite hard to find a matching storyline to this game.</p>
<p>After some fast thinking, I’ve came to this:</p>
<p>Basicly, there was this guy Vreg and he was extremely smart.<br>
One day he was bored and took a sample of his DNA and cloned a fish version of him.<br>
He named him Vreggie.<br>
He went fishing one day with Vreggie next to him but landed into a storm.<br>
The storm got worse and basicly he and Vreggie got overboard.<br>
He was able to swim back to land but Vreggie was lost.<br>
Now this was tragic because I forgot to mention that while cloning himself he made a mistake,<br>
one that kills Vreg when Vreggie dies.<br>
Wich is why he integrated a GPS system and manual control into Vreggie’s brain incase of emergensies.<br>
He ran home really quick and activated the GPS system, after he received a signal with the location of Vreggie<br>
he took his scuba diving outfit and his guns and went after Vreggie.<br>
Once he finally reached Vreggie under water he activated manual control.<br>
His goal was to make Vreggie the biggest of all fishes so that he could turn off manual control without Vreggie getting killed.</p>
<p>It is up to you to define the fate of Vreg and Vreggie.</p>
<hr>
<p>So that’s it I guess, I tried to make it funny because I can’t think of anything serious that matches the gameplay.</p>
<p>Opinions and improvements are welcome.</p>
<p>Extra: the game has 10 levels (waves) of 3 minutes. It get’s harder the longer you play, but you get money from killing fishes wich allows you to upgrade your weapons, buy all sorts of items such as God Fish, Double Guns,…<br>
I’ve made 8 guns and 10 items for the first release of the game. /notthatanyonecares.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 20:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-402920-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/storyline/402920.rss">Storyline</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
