<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need urgent help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-urgent-help/449922</link>
    <description>I have a server and everyody plays fine, it was just posted on the status page. My one friend, irl, who is going to be co-owner, can&#39;t connect. He tries the client and the webclient, on his win 7 laptop and vista PC.  Both times he gets Error Loading Please Report. The cache properly downloaded for him and I copy and pasted it into his USER file along with his C DRIVE. I updated his JRE to 7, which I compiled with, and  set it so notepad opens the class file, not flash player. What else could be the problem? This happens for the webclient and the desktop client. This hasn&#39;t happened for my other players.

HybridPVP v3 Source and Client</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 02:03:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-urgent-help/449922.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need urgent help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Turmoilz1337x Turmoilz1337x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/turmoilz1337x">@Turmoilz1337x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have a server and everyody plays fine, it was just posted on the status page. My one friend, irl, who is going to be co-owner, can’t connect. He tries the client and the webclient, on his win 7 laptop and vista PC.  Both times he gets Error Loading Please Report. The cache properly downloaded for him and I copy and pasted it into his USER file along with his C DRIVE. I updated his JRE to 7, which I compiled with, and  set it so notepad opens the class file, not flash player. What else could be the problem? This happens for the webclient and the desktop client. This hasn’t happened for my other players.</p>
<p>HybridPVP v3 Source and Client</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-urgent-help/449922/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-urgent-help/449922/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 02:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-449922-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-urgent-help/449922.rss">Need urgent help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
