<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server hosting</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting/547607</link>
    <description>i wasn&#39;t sure where to post this because i have not used the website for awhile. anyways i was using a ubuntu 14.04 server to host my hidden service but it didn&#39;t pan out so it never got past the nginx and tor. So i came to moparscape hoping i could host a 317 server. I have hosted quite a few servers really none that have panned out. I left because of school stuff but i&#39;m back and hoping to host a rsps server.

I&#39;m really not looking for something that&#39;s over project insanity because the higher revisions aren&#39;t really my thing.

None the less. I can show and allow root access to my ubuntu 14.04 Server. i done a clean reinstall and installed java among all the other stuff needed for rsps. So the specifications are.

Ubuntu 14.04 LTS
Ram: 8GB
VCores: 4
Bandwidth: 3TB
Connection: 100mbs
ddos protect included.
VPN SETUP: i have a vpn that could be setup to run under but i never really tried it besides on my lubuntu laptop. not sure how it would work running an rsps server. we can talk about it if you want.


I have been around awhile i&#39;m not known to really anyone that plays anymore. I will do any of the system administrator tasks because most don&#39;t know how to use it for some un-godly reason they use windows. Anyways.

Contact me on skype. at.

SchoolEncryption  or you can pm me here. it&#39;s complety up to you but i&#39;m always on skype.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 04:24:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting/547607.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server hosting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@D3i7y D3i7y]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/d3i7y">@D3i7y</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i wasn’t sure where to post this because i have not used the website for awhile. anyways i was using a ubuntu 14.04 server to host my hidden service but it didn’t pan out so it never got past the nginx and tor. So i came to moparscape hoping i could host a 317 server. I have hosted quite a few servers really none that have panned out. I left because of school stuff but i’m back and hoping to host a rsps server.</p>
<p>I’m really not looking for something that’s over project insanity because the higher revisions aren’t really my thing.</p>
<p>None the less. I can show and allow root access to my ubuntu 14.04 Server. i done a clean reinstall and installed java among all the other stuff needed for rsps. So the specifications are.</p>
<p>Ubuntu 14.04 LTS<br>
Ram: 8GB<br>
VCores: 4<br>
Bandwidth: 3TB<br>
Connection: 100mbs<br>
ddos protect included.<br>
VPN SETUP: i have a vpn that could be setup to run under but i never really tried it besides on my lubuntu laptop. not sure how it would work running an rsps server. we can talk about it if you want.</p>
<p>I have been around awhile i’m not known to really anyone that plays anymore. I will do any of the system administrator tasks because most don’t know how to use it for some un-godly reason they use windows. Anyways.</p>
<p>Contact me on skype. at.</p>
<p>SchoolEncryption  or you can pm me here. it’s complety up to you but i’m always on skype.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting/547607/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting/547607/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 04:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547607-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-hosting/547607.rss">Server hosting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
