<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Now I need a path</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980</link>
    <description>[center]Hello, my name is Brandon. I&#39;m 16 years old and I&#39;ve been dropped out of school for a few months now. When I dropped out, I started working. I&#39;ve been doing things that involve carpentry, painting, and other things that would try my strength and endurance. Now I may be forced to go back to school, but the 2nd semester will be over in about a month, and if I go to school in fall, I will be a freshmen again (I&#39;m supposed to be a junior in fall).
I&#39;ve been living poor for years now, so I know how it feels to stress about groceries (even with food-stamps), etc. I realize I&#39;m much too intelligent to have myself and my future family stranded in poverty, and it scares the fuck out of me.

You&#39;ve likely already noticed, I&#39;m a big bitch about school. However, I do have sufficient reasoning. My schooling has pretty much always been screwed up. I&#39;ve always missed more days than allowed, in fact I went to truancy court for the first time in kindergarten. In the past 2 years, I&#39;ve been to 4 different high schools, of various peoples. In order, I went to a school with a total of approx. 800 that were all country (so I&#39;m an outcast), another which was 75% black (hood black) and the white people were so childish that I had to leave, a large one that I consider to be a cluster fuck, and the last school I attended was in the middle of a hood, with around 300 students, and only 4, yes 4, other whites.
On top of this, my personal life has been a train wreck for years. I don&#39;t have much family. My mom &amp; dad aren&#39;t doing well at all, and it of course hurts me to even know that. Any other family I have is only &#39;family&#39;, and doesn&#39;t even know anything about me. I&#39;m simply not focused when I&#39;m in school on account of all the other bullshit that&#39;s going around, and I can easily find myself ditching classes to smoke some dank or a cigarette on account of my personal issues.

I feel if I went to one of those special schools, where you just go for 4-5 hours a day and do work on a computer, I would try my hardest and succeed. It&#39;s my belief that those schools were originally created with the intent to help those who couldn&#39;t take the conventional approach to an education, however I was told back in fall that in order to get in I would either need to be sent there for being an uncontrollable pest, or I would need to have 10+ credits. I have 2.
I&#39;ve no idea what career field I desire, but I&#39;m well aware that many jobs (like oil field worker) pay great for young people, offer good benefits, but age your body exceedingly fast. I&#39;m hesitant of this. I&#39;d like to be 50 when I&#39;m 50, and not 80 when I&#39;m 50.

I really need some advice, preferably from someone who&#39;s already succeeded. Any ideas or suggestions?[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 08:24:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NewbieNewty Newty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbienewty">@NewbieNewty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You need to get back in school and tough it out man. Its just a couple years, it may seem like an eternity now, but it isn’t. Your highschool diploma is the foundation of the rest of your working life. If you really can’t tough it out you need to get enrolled in a GED program. Talk with a school counselor about getting enrolled in one.</p>
<p>I strongly suggest you finish high school the traditional way though. It leaves a few more doors open for you should life throw you another curveball. If it interests you I would suggest joining the Air Force (assuming your in the US). It’s decent pay but more importantly it is a secure job, a warm bed at night and food in your stomach.</p>
<p>Message me on the IRC if you have any questions.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 08:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A lot of the skills you gain here propel people to careers in CS. I skipped working restaurants and went straight to being an engineer at a reputable streaming company. You just need to stick with it. Talking to people about how to get your foot in the door will help you blaze your way at a faster rate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 03:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Start looking towards the future.  This is a long-term type of situation, I would think.  Why are you here at MSCP?  Do you like to program? (or to the standards of this website, “program”)  If you take interest in that and can really dedicate yourself, you should really work at it.</p>
<p>tl;dr, focus on something you love that will make money.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 03:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PI_Developer PI_Developer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pi_developer">@PI_Developer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Vain_, post:5, topic:542980”]if you’re struggling with money and cant afford groceries - sell computer / get rid of internet.<br>
you need to get your priorities fixed mate.</p>
<p>also try online/alternative schooling.[/quote]<br>
Won’t sell comp, mom uses it.<br>
Internet is from my phone, I tether it. I have unlimited plan no longer offered by my carrier, only extended because I haven’t switched my plan.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“PI_Developer, post:4, topic:542980”][quote author=TabbyKiller link=topic=661855.msg4423860#msg4423860 date=1399767575]<br>
I fudgeed up in school last year as well, I decided to play around more than I should have and when it came around to doing exams, I scrapped by and passed most but it wasn’t enough credits to pass the year. It shouldn’t be hard to find a good school where people actually care about their education, go on a search, make some appointments, and get a tour during school hours.</p>
<p>When I was young, before NCEA, I never really understood how important school was, and in order to do what you like, you’re going to need a plan b which is where your education comes into play. For example, I want to go into the movie business, it’s a hard deal and it’s not 100% guaranteed, so while I work towards my goal I will need to get a decent job (that you or I may not even like) to pay the bills. Even the army requires a good literacy and numeracy level, so don’t expect to get any jobs if you don’t have a background in any education. Schooling is the very very minimum requirement, succeeding with anything (if anything) below that is just a miracle.</p>
<p>If you’re really stuck up on not going to school then the only thing I can think of is correspondence, you should be able to find something near you. It really is just school online, I’m doing it right now to get the small amount of credits I need to NCEA level 3.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Are there any qualifications for online school?[/quote]<br>
There are no requirements, if you’re lucky like me, there will be no cost for anyone under the age of 18.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vain1 Vain_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vain1">@Vain1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>if you’re struggling with money and cant afford groceries - sell computer / get rid of internet.<br>
you need to get your priorities fixed mate.</p>
<p>also try online/alternative schooling.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PI_Developer PI_Developer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pi_developer">@PI_Developer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“TabbyKiller, post:3, topic:542980”]I fudgeed up in school last year as well, I decided to play around more than I should have and when it came around to doing exams, I scrapped by and passed most but it wasn’t enough credits to pass the year. It shouldn’t be hard to find a good school where people actually care about their education, go on a search, make some appointments, and get a tour during school hours.</p>
<p>When I was young, before NCEA, I never really understood how important school was, and in order to do what you like, you’re going to need a plan b which is where your education comes into play. For example, I want to go into the movie business, it’s a hard deal and it’s not 100% guaranteed, so while I work towards my goal I will need to get a decent job (that you or I may not even like) to pay the bills. Even the army requires a good literacy and numeracy level, so don’t expect to get any jobs if you don’t have a background in any education. Schooling is the very very minimum requirement, succeeding with anything (if anything) below that is just a miracle.</p>
<p>If you’re really stuck up on not going to school then the only thing I can think of is correspondence, you should be able to find something near you. It really is just school online, I’m doing it right now to get the small amount of credits I need to NCEA level 3.[/quote]</p>
<p>Are there any qualifications for online school?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I fudgeed up in school last year as well, I decided to play around more than I should have and when it came around to doing exams, I scrapped by and passed most but it wasn’t enough credits to pass the year. It shouldn’t be hard to find a good school where people actually care about their education, go on a search, make some appointments, and get a tour during school hours.</p>
<p>When I was young, before NCEA, I never really understood how important school was, and in order to do what you like, you’re going to need a plan b which is where your education comes into play. For example, I want to go into the movie business, it’s a hard deal and it’s not 100% guaranteed, so while I work towards my goal I will need to get a decent job (that you or I may not even like) to pay the bills. Even the army requires a good literacy and numeracy level, so don’t expect to get any jobs if you don’t have a background in any education. Schooling is the very very minimum requirement, succeeding with anything (if anything) below that is just a miracle.</p>
<p>If you’re really stuck up on not going to school then the only thing I can think of is correspondence, you should be able to find something near you. It really is just school online, I’m doing it right now to get the small amount of credits I need to NCEA level 3.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My advice: Don’t consult Moparscape.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Now I need a path</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PI_Developer PI_Developer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pi_developer">@PI_Developer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Hello, my name is Brandon. I’m 16 years old and I’ve been dropped out of school for a few months now. When I dropped out, I started working. I’ve been doing things that involve carpentry, painting, and other things that would try my strength and endurance. Now I may be forced to go back to school, but the 2nd semester will be over in about a month, and if I go to school in fall, I will be a freshmen again (I’m supposed to be a junior in fall).<br>
I’ve been living poor for years now, so I know how it feels to stress about groceries (even with food-stamps), etc. I realize I’m much too intelligent to have myself and my future family stranded in poverty, and it scares the fuck out of me.</p>
<p>You’ve likely already noticed, I’m a big bitch about school. However, I do have sufficient reasoning. My schooling has pretty much always been screwed up. I’ve always missed more days than allowed, in fact I went to truancy court for the first time in kindergarten. In the past 2 years, I’ve been to 4 different high schools, of various peoples. In order, I went to a school with a total of approx. 800 that were all country (so I’m an outcast), another which was 75% black (hood black) and the white people were so childish that I had to leave, a large one that I consider to be a cluster fuck, and the last school I attended was in the middle of a hood, with around 300 students, and only 4, yes 4, other whites.<br>
On top of this, my personal life has been a train wreck for years. I don’t have much family. My mom &amp; dad aren’t doing well at all, and it of course hurts me to even know that. Any other family I have is only ‘family’, and doesn’t even know anything about me. I’m simply not focused when I’m in school on account of all the other bullshit that’s going around, and I can easily find myself ditching classes to smoke some dank or a cigarette on account of my personal issues.</p>
<p>I feel if I went to one of those special schools, where you just go for 4-5 hours a day and do work on a computer, I would try my hardest and succeed. It’s my belief that those schools were originally created with the intent to help those who couldn’t take the conventional approach to an education, however I was told back in fall that in order to get in I would either need to be sent there for being an uncontrollable pest, or I would need to have 10+ credits. I have 2.<br>
I’ve no idea what career field I desire, but I’m well aware that many jobs (like oil field worker) pay great for young people, offer good benefits, but age your body exceedingly fast. I’m hesitant of this. I’d like to be 50 when I’m 50, and not 80 when I’m 50.</p>
<p>I really need some advice, preferably from someone who’s already succeeded. Any ideas or suggestions?[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2014 23:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542980-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/now-i-need-a-path/542980.rss">Now I need a path</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
