<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mokeys and hamlet</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mokeys-and-hamlet/20799</link>
    <description>i did not type this, this is from a different forum. but i find this a funny argument. &quot;
QUOTE(Chongablonga @ Oct 28 2006, 04:32 PM)
I have not once said &#39;monkeys will never type hamlet&#39;. I have said, and this is correct, that there is no scientifically or mathematically provable way of saying for certain that they will or will not type hamlet, which is what all of this debate has been based off. I&#39;m not agreeing or disagreeing with the idea that monkeys will type hamlet, I&#39;m just saying you can neither check, or speculate either way.


You can use math. Watch, it&#39;s very simple.

(1-(1/26)^(number of letters in Hamlet))^(inf) = 0. That is the probability that the monkeys will not type Hamlet. It is ZERO.

Let me ask you this. If you flip a coin infinity times, can you be sure that you will eventually get heads? The answer is yes; you have a probability of 100%. The exact same mathematics hold for typing hamlet, and also for molecules randomly rearranging to form Earth.

They will type Hamlet, eventually. At a given point in time, they probably will not be typing Hamlet, but taking an entire infinite timeline as a whole, they will have typed Hamlet. (As a matter of fact, they will have typed it infinity times.)

Hamlet will be written in any sort of language, code, or form. Literally every combination of words and letters will be typed. This exact forum discussion will be written by the monkeys infinity times. It&#39;s all a matter of probability.&quot;

also this is my thing..

I don&#39;t know if anyone else thought of this, but because the spectrum of light(red being the lowest frequency, purple/indego being the highest.) and light is emmited by photons with energy. and light is caused by the vibration of atoms/molecules.
blood that is oxydized(i don&#39;t know if that is the correct term) or is carrying oxygen, while blood in our veins that have released the oxygen are blue. would the oxygen, when being carried slow down the frequency to a red color because it has more mass? And when there is less mass in the blood cell the color is blue?(vibrating faster) Would that show any explanation to this? (I was thinking of this while in the car going home.) Because I think this might be the explanation of why blood is colored like that. But that is up to you to judge.



-forgive me for my spelling if there are any errors.


GIVE your oppinion!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2006 23:00:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mokeys-and-hamlet/20799.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mokeys and hamlet</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kloplop321 kloplop321]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kloplop321">@kloplop321</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i did not type this, this is from a different forum. but i find this a funny argument. "<br>
QUOTE(Chongablonga @ Oct 28 2006, 04:32 PM)<br>
I have not once said ‘monkeys will never type hamlet’. I have said, and this is correct, that there is no scientifically or mathematically provable way of saying for certain that they will or will not type hamlet, which is what all of this debate has been based off. I’m not agreeing or disagreeing with the idea that monkeys will type hamlet, I’m just saying you can neither check, or speculate either way.</p>
<p>You can use math. Watch, it’s very simple.</p>
<p>(1-(1/26)^(number of letters in Hamlet))^(inf) = 0. That is the probability that the monkeys will not type Hamlet. It is ZERO.</p>
<p>Let me ask you this. If you flip a coin infinity times, can you be sure that you will eventually get heads? The answer is yes; you have a probability of 100%. The exact same mathematics hold for typing hamlet, and also for molecules randomly rearranging to form Earth.</p>
<p>They will type Hamlet, eventually. At a given point in time, they probably will not be typing Hamlet, but taking an entire infinite timeline as a whole, they will have typed Hamlet. (As a matter of fact, they will have typed it infinity times.)</p>
<p>Hamlet will be written in any sort of language, code, or form. Literally every combination of words and letters will be typed. This exact forum discussion will be written by the monkeys infinity times. It’s all a matter of probability."</p>
<p>also this is my thing…</p>
<p>I don’t know if anyone else thought of this, but because the spectrum of light(red being the lowest frequency, purple/indego being the highest.) and light is emmited by photons with energy. and light is caused by the vibration of atoms/molecules.<br>
blood that is oxydized(i don’t know if that is the correct term) or is carrying oxygen, while blood in our veins that have released the oxygen are blue. would the oxygen, when being carried slow down the frequency to a red color because it has more mass? And when there is less mass in the blood cell the color is blue?(vibrating faster) Would that show any explanation to this? (I was thinking of this while in the car going home.) Because I think this might be the explanation of why blood is colored like that. But that is up to you to judge.</p>
<p>-forgive me for my spelling if there are any errors.</p>
<p>GIVE your oppinion!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mokeys-and-hamlet/20799/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mokeys-and-hamlet/20799/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2006 23:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20799-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mokeys-and-hamlet/20799.rss">Mokeys and hamlet</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
