<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280</link>
    <description>My project had been lost and I discontinued working on this for quite some while.  In fact, I stopped programming any form of documentation with java since the closing of this project.  Since then I have moved onto Python and Delphi..  But I&#39;m hoping to jump right back into this sever.

Special thanks to Adem70 for keeping my backup base files from over a year ago.

It&#39;s based on one of Palidino76&#39;s early releases, so it&#39;s quite outdated.  I have managed to spruce up the code to be stable and reliable with many modifications added.  There might be a gap in my logs, because I started working on code that&#39;s under the hood and wouldn&#39;t effect anything noticeably in game.

I&#39;ve done a near to complete overhaul of my definitions by renaming major integers just to make me feel all warm and fuzzy inside (ex: absX and absY are now parameterJ and parameterK) and I&#39;ve redefined a lot of classes as well.


[b][u]CURRENT PROJECTS:[/u][/b]

[[b]DGDT[/b]] [u][b]B3rnscape[/b][/u]

[b]Base[/b]: Palidino&#39;s 3.2 Base or something, I honestly don&#39;t know what module it is...I was eager and just downloaded some of Palidino&#39;s work from rs-server!

Background: B3rnscape was possibly one of the most famous servers back in the day before fugooscape(or whatever his name was) and Silabsoft&#39;s client (The days when Moparscape 2.0 was still around). I was appointed Lead Java Programmer of B3rnscape before my retirement in early 2005. Before the collapse of B3rnscape in late 2005, early 2006, I re-joined B3rn0ut in his game. The only people who had an understanding for the Java language (even half-ass understanding...  meaning only knowing how to edit shit in a private server source) was B3rn0ut, Cook, and myself. After the fall of B3rnscape B3rn0ut had fled from the scope of the radar. These days all of the admins that were apart of the B3rnscape staff keep in touch with each other, with the exception of Tiffany and that scum The Truth, leader of the downfall of B3rnscape. In October of 2008 I had the idea of re-creating B3rnscape. Luke(MrKalius) and I had tested numerous bases, from some random base packed with nonsense(rejected immediately), to wL base(also rejected, due to me getting bored) until we followed B3rn0ut&#39;s philosophy and upgraded from 317 to 508.


Note:Currently not accepting any new members for our development team, I am looking to get all this crap covered and make it as decent as I can make it.

[b][u]Current Staff[/u][/b]
Steven(Itachi Uchiha) - Lead Programmer/Developer
Luke(MrKalius) - Lead Designer
Adam(Adem70) - Hoster and Data Manager.
Steve(Cook) - Java programmer, Head of Gaming Content, Co-developer
[s]Magicks - Head of Statistics, AI Management[/s]
[s]amm3 - Head of Player Management[/s]

UPDATES ON NEXT POST, CURRENTLY EXCEEDS 20000 CHARACTERS.

List of Skill(name, %done, additional_notes):
(Will add soon)


[u]Newest Pictures[/u]:
[img]http://i43.tinypic.com/zoema.gif[/img]
[img]http://i41.tinypic.com/ixaxiw.jpg[/img]
[img]http://i39.tinypic.com/2mhwmsw.jpg[/img]
[img]http://i43.tinypic.com/2ugihw1.jpg[/img]

[u]Archived Pictures[/u]:
None at this time.

[u]Notes[/u]:
Nuclear Chemical composition outline so far.(work in progress)
[code]                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt; Cupric ore powder
                                                &gt;null
                                &gt; Sulphuric broline
                                                &gt; Sulphur
                                        &gt; Ground sulphur
                                                &gt; Pestle and mortar
                        &gt; ??? mixture
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt; Iron
                                                &gt;null
                                &gt; Iron oxide
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt; Vial of water
                                                &gt;null
                &gt; Cupric sulphate
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt; Cupric ore powder
                                                &gt;null
                                &gt; Sulphuric broline
                                                &gt; Sulphur
                                        &gt; Ground sulphur
                                                &gt; Pestle and mortar
                        &gt; ??? mixture
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt;null
                                                &gt;null
                                &gt; Sodium chloride
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt;null
                                                &gt;null
        &gt; Serum 207
                                                        &gt; Goblin potion
                                                &gt; Mixed chemicals
                                                        &gt; Compost potion
                                        &gt; Strange potion
                                                &gt; Initiate cuisse
                                &gt; Mixture - step 2
                                                &gt; Nitrous oxide
                                        &gt; Mixture - step 1
                                                &gt; Acetic Acid
                        &gt; Relicym&#39;s balm
                                                &gt; Vial of liquid
                                        &gt; Nitroglycerin
                                                &gt; Tin ore powder
                                &gt; Chem compound
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt; Gypsum
                                                &gt;null
                &gt; Relicym&#39;s mix
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt; Ethenea
                                                &gt;null
                                &gt; Bravery potion
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt; Truth serum
                                                &gt;null
                        &gt; Ardrigal mixture
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt; Liquid honey
                                                &gt;null
                                &gt; &#39;voice of doom&#39;
                                                &gt;null
                                        &gt; Snakeweed mix
&lt;chemic.&gt;                                                &gt;null
&gt; Serum 208 &lt;NUCLEAR EVEN THOUGH YOU ARE NOT CAUSING NUCLEAR REACTIONS.....DON&#39;T BRING LOGIC INTO THIS!&gt;
&lt;natural&gt;                                        &gt;null
                                &gt; Fishing mix
                                        &gt;null
                        &gt; Hunting mix
                                        &gt; Strength mix
                                &gt; Ranging mix
                                        &gt; Antidote+ mix
                &gt; Antifire mix
                                        &gt; Sup. def. mix
                                &gt; Sup. restore mix
                                        &gt; Antidote+ mix
                        &gt; Agility mix
                                        &gt;null
                                &gt; Sup. energy mix
                                        &gt;null
        &gt; Zamorak Mix
                                        &gt; Superattack mix
                                &gt; Restore mix
                                        &gt; Antidote+ mix
                        &gt; Energy mix
                                        &gt; Antidote+ mix
                                &gt; Anti-p supermix
                                        &gt; Antipoison mix
                &gt; Magic mix
                                        &gt; Sup. str. mix
                                &gt; Combat mix
                                        &gt; Antidote+ mix
                        &gt; Magic ess. mix
                                        &gt; Attack mix
                                &gt; Prayer mix
                                        &gt;  Antidote+ mix[/code]

[u]Approval[/u]:
[img]http://i43.tinypic.com/b71951.jpg[/img]

More on this project coming soon!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 21:32:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pretty good project, good luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 21:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-279280-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280.rss">B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@9d_n_1_n_e 9d n 1 n e]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/9d_n_1_n_e">@9d_n_1_n_e</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>naise gl</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-279280-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280.rss">B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This looks like a promising project. Good luck. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>Oh, by the way… Don’t use color tags within a code tag; they don’t show up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-279280-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280.rss">B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Itachi_Uchiha Itachi Uchiha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/itachi_uchiha">@Itachi_Uchiha</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-u">Current Updates</span><br>
If you find any of the material listed in here to be yours and you were not given credit, please tell me and I will make the correction(I wrote this up pretty fast and didn’t take time to revise it)</p>
<p>[code]B3rnscape Updates</p>
<p>[Server]<br>
[Version J15RA1]<br>
-Fixed basic chat functions (PM system and login read features.)<br>
-Added Trading base (Pretty much a rip from Blakescape)<br>
-Added minigame base (Simple version of barrows, raising the variables in order, I will set a random int for later.)<br>
-Cleaned up and repaired Magic system (No more disconnect or lag.)<br>
-Upgraded to ~80% Banking (bad habbits from 317 still…)<br>
-Added shopping base ~10% (I forgot who made this but it is the horrid one with the bland, distasteful interface…)<br>
-Added a lot more equipment requirements (Source that I had only contained a few for Attack and Defense.  So I expanded it a lot.)<br>
-Completed banking and added my own noting method. ~95% done, no tabs.<br>
Note: Glitch on noting certain items, creates a null value and replaces the item.</p>
<p>[Version J17TA7]<br>
-Added object training<br>
-Added real-time shopping<br>
-Added realistic shopping interfaces from alwaystuck1’s 99% shopping.<br>
-Fixed NPC nullpointers (For now, until I add something like npc following, then this may get a little sticky…)<br>
-Added token shops from training (Forgot who created the ugly box shops, but that is what is used here.)<br>
-Added new melee base for damage counters<br>
-Added two different NPC spawning bases for summoning. (One works with my pouches and the other is more of a respawn for future minigames set on timers.)<br>
-Added base for following (Could use a little work, right now it will stop to walls defind by my Regions class, but…When the player teleports and returns that NPC retreats out of bounds.)<br>
-Added NPC aggression (Only flaw that I can find is that the NPC does not reset it’s attack when player is out of bounds.)<br>
-Added NPC drops by statistics and base<br>
-Created a cap on object training at 11M XP and increased NPC training<br>
-Added public and private object addition/deletion (Don’t worry, I will not carry horrid habits from the later 317 after -fedexer-(i luvs u) introduced globalObjects.)<br>
-Added two different flood protections(just to be safe)  One by Gravediggah and one by me(Although Gravediggah’s is far better than the one I originally created.)</p>
<p>[Version J23RA3]<br>
-Cleaned up files in base, Player.java went from 60KB to 39KB.<br>
-Packaged a lot of data (SkillMasters.java alone takes up 20KB and it only has about 7 skillmasters in it so far.)<br>
-Added modern teleporting<br>
-Added Rune requirements for ancient spells.<br>
-Added Ghorrak(or whatever it is called) teleport with correct GFX and area, not really something big, I mean any half-wit could do it, I hope to add more soon.  Maybe to some major areas.<br>
-Added food base(So far only Manta, Sharks, Pumpkins, and Easter Eggs.  It works perfectly, all I need is to find the right amount of Milis for my delay.)<br>
-Scrapped zach’s censor and made them load directly from an array in the class.<br>
-Repaired bugs in ObjectOption1 out of area.<br>
-Started packaging more data from my packets package.  ItemOnItem went from 35.1KB to 6.91KB<br>
-Created bone-burying class with member and nonmember capabilities.<br>
-Members now gain 10x more XP in teleporting and dummy training</p>
<p>[Version J24HA22: Theater]<br>
-Added base for singing with commands<br>
Pretty idiotic now that I think about it…I had it set at ::riot1 ::riot2, it would work, but took up a HUGE amount of space in commands., so why do that?<br>
-Deleted my base in commands for singing and moved it to object clicking.<br>
-Made seperate classes for each song<br>
-Created stageArea and stageRoomArea for the books to be used<br>
-Fixed minor glitch by simply making (p2 != p)<br>
-Added stage static int and methods for each side to keep only one person on stage.<br>
-If a person finishes their song they get a reward and int is set to 0 for both songID and the stage int<br>
-Clue Scrolls are single-person ForceChats that can be used anywhere. (No chorus)</p>
<p>Current songs used:<br>
-Colorado Sunrise		- 3OH!3<br>
-Dead!			- My Chemical Romance<br>
-First Date		- Blink 182<br>
-Give It All			- Rise Against<br>
-Gives You Hell		- The All-American Rejects<br>
-I’m coming Home		- Cheeseburger<br>
-Kryptonite		- Three Doors Down<br>
-Minnie The Moocher	- Cab Calloway (Blue’s Brother’s Re-write)<br>
-Riot			- Three Days Grace<br>
-She Was Dead		- SR-71<br>
-This Ain’t a Scene		- Fall Out Boy</p>
<p>[Version J31NA1]<br>
-Created my own Bounty Hunter class, 100% mine…, I threw away momo’s incase you are wondering, his was about 8.37% at best?  Atleast the one that I had.<br>
-Added skull capability;  Need to fix on how to get it shown for all items equiped and in inv.<br>
-Created a method that calculates a player’s entire inv + all equiped from the item.config<br>
-Implemented an int to read from my itemValue method and use that to display skulls in the bounty hunter region.<br>
-Bug: Players who exit the crater still have the skull when they leave.<br>
-Fixed previous bug.<br>
-Added a player finder base (nothing beyond that ATM…)<br>
-Well after a few hours of pretty much testing and retesting I guess this has become pretty decent…Opponent finder now selects an opponent for you that has not been set by a boolean.<br>
-As soon as a new player enters the bounty hunter area a random player in the area will be matched with them, if they do not have an opponent already.<br>
-If you kill someone in bountyhunter you gain a random item based on what your itemValue and the opponents itemValue was [25 arrays]; the lower the skulls the worse the random drop, the higher the skulls the better the random drop.<br>
-Bug: Now players who exit keep their opponent interface.  When another interface is opened, or if they log out, this cancels it, I will probably have to apply another interface to appear…Probably one that shows a message.  ATM my removeInterface method does not work.</p>
<p>[Version J33AA14]<br>
-Started a Range base off of melee.<br>
-Most range projectiles working with minimal flaws.<br>
-XP can not be gained from killing NPCs with a range weapon.<br>
-Started a base to Herblore.<br>
-Nearly completed my Herblore, quest potions are not added.<br>
-Added drinking potions<br>
-BUG FIX: Skillcapes and some other features that require a skill level will now load from XP:if ( p.skillXP[0] &gt;= 13034431 )  [I would rather use this than timers because well…I fell lazy x.x…]</p>
<p>[Version J33NA21]<br>
-DFS is fully functioning with right GFX and Anim.<br>
-Added timers to DFS<br>
-Created a charges value which rises when attacked by dragons.<br>
-Every use the dfsValue lowers by 1<br>
-Stores up to 50 charges<br>
-dfsValue now saves.</p>
<p>[Version J35TA3: Project Coriolis]<br>
-Added weather capabilities<br>
-Weather advisories show for all players when the storm is called.<br>
-Outside areas in major areas will send the player a frame with heavy snow.<br>
-NOTE: Might add the snow global object to entire cities.<br>
-Storms turn on and off by timers(called by a miscRandom for the location, all storms last 5minutes and have a 2 minute break before the next area is selected.)<br>
-Timers can be voided by command and so can the initial method.<br>
-Inside areas are safe from the storm.<br>
SUB_NOTES: After some complications with process, my weather methods would null player interfaces and prevent login.  On this I decided to cut my loses and just make Weather load from commands, this way it is all packed into commands.java, Regions, and Player.<br>
-Project Coriolis has been noted down as the following -<br>
STATUS: Failure. [Wednesday, April 29th, 2009.]<br>
-Weather is still opperational.  It is just manually enabled.<br>
+UPDATE:<br>
After installing Graham’s Eventmanager, I used it to sendMessage every 60seconds my storm method is called and it also calls the next method every 300000 millis.<br>
-Thank you Graham, you made this possible <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
STATUS: Sucessful [Friday, May 1st, 2009]</p>
<p>[Version J37FA11]<br>
-Updated BountyHunter<br>
-Craters load to different height levels, used NoobScape’s entrances as a base (ty), I just didn’t like all the extra bulk O.o…<br>
-Reduced skull values.<br>
-Now BH skulls and opponentFinder reads from the area and not entrance.<br>
-Added day and night<br>
FUTURE_UPDATE: Add this in with player input,  they can set their time and it will darken accordingly.<br>
-Added equipment statistics button interface<br>
-Fixed minor bugs with equipment interface<br>
-Added bone burying,  I had my friend get me all the IDs while I just simple handled them.<br>
-Added someone’s retarded GWD that they said was around 80%, well…I hate you <em>takes cookie back</em><br>
-Repaired doors in GWD so that you use a gfx and a shorter delay instead of teleporting like an idiot.<br>
-Added GWD object sizes so that you do not need to stand in the middle of the object, small bugs are with the Saradomin Alter.<br>
-Members are capable of entering the main boss doors instantly, non-members need a killcount of 10<br>
-Added the actual GWD to the area in my Regions class,  Putting the interface in a command is idiotic and an extremely cheep fix that fails.  I am sorry, but it does.<br>
-From the main room you need the following items:<br>
-Rope to get across to Armadyl area (Might add a method for mithril grappel when I get back to working on range)<br>
-Hammer to get through the door to Bandos area<br>
-Rope to get to Saradomin<br>
-70+ HP (Didn’t require any item on object, just a player class check of level[3] so it was the easiest)<br>
-UNRELATED NOTE: Why do people call the Generals, Commanders, Ect. the actual gods?  They are the minions of the gods…</p>
<p>[Version J39DA7]<br>
-Begain working on Project Coriolis again.<br>
-Eventmanager sends a message every 30 seconds to players when a storm is active.<br>
-Added Thunderstorms to Lumbridge<br>
-Blizzard in Falador causes up to 10 in damage counters.<br>
-Members who chase and stand in the storm gain XP [The more severe the storm(more damage done to you) the greater the XP you get]<br>
-EX: In Falador I have it set so that you gain 1K Farming XP(In my server farming is pathology so…) and 10K hunter XP(Storm Chaser, get it?)<br>
-PROCESS HOLDS NOTHING TO DO WITH PROJECT CORIOLIS!!<br>
-Color coded? :), not that good either but it makes it pretty…<br>
-I voided my randomStorm method and changed activation to commands that only I can access to make it more convenient<br>
-Helps keep order instead of have such hectic randomness…</p>
<p>[Version J40AA1]<br>
-Renamed a ton of methods, just to make it feel nicer <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
-WalkingQueQue is now QuoFacio, absX and absY are now parameterJ and parameterK, ect.<br>
-Started to work on a base for Project Coriolis to run independantly from player enablization.<br>
-Automatic weather is called through the Weather class to the Login class.<br>
-Moved weatherWarnings out of Weather class and into their own class based on location.  IE: Lumbridge, Falador, Desert, ect.</p>
<p>[Version J40TA1]<br>
CLEAN_UP!!!<br>
-Started working on replacing timers in process with Graham’s eventmanager<br>
-Current timers converted:<br>
-Fishing<br>
-Weather<br>
-3 potion timers [One for all potions, another for zammy brew, and another for sara brew.]<br>
I eventually will replace all of the timers, just wait for combattimer…whew…-.-…<br>
-Members do not require runes to teleport.<br>
-Created a bse for smithing(testing rune ATM only now.)</p>
<p>[Version J42NA2]<br>
-Herblore is perfect as to where I want it to be, timers are accurate and all non-mixable and quest pots are drinkable<br>
-Began work on NUCLEAR CHEMISTRY!<br>
-Near completed my diagram for how NC will work.<br>
-Serum 208 can be placed into a capsle for launching a Thermo-nuclear warhead.<br>
-Fixed disconnection glitch with potions.<br>
-Use capsles on object at digsite to bring up a 5 choice text box<br>
-Click Varrock to launch a nuclear missile on Varrock and deal 289 damage to all players in the area.<br>
-Warnings appear for 10min before the bomb drops<br>
-Radiations lingers over Varrock for 12 hours, till the server is reset, or until a command is called to end it.<br>
-Every 2000ms you are hurt by a random poison splat dealing up to 8 damage.</p>
<p>[Version J47AA1: Project Deadscape]<br>
-Created a base for Deadscape minigame<br>
-When players die they turn into the ‘dead’<br>
-dead players are given a different walking, running, and standing emote mask update.<br>
[FIXED]GLITCH: New walking creates running problems<br>
[FIXED]GLITCH: When Deadscape is enabled, right clicking voids out quickly.<br>
-Deads cannot fight other Deads and Humans cannot fight other Humans<br>
-Wilderness is everywhere during Deadscape<br>
-MINIGAME IS NOW SAFE, when it is enabled…Player do not lose their items when killed by natural disasters or other players.<br>
-Dead players gain a random reward from killing humans depending on their opponent’s combat level<br>
[less than 55 gets bad rewards, 56-99 get medium-good rewards, 100+ get great items] (Should stop people from making lots of level 3 accounts for rewards.)<br>
-Minimap goes black during Deadscape, better for strategic gameplay.<br>
-Sextants can be used as a 60 second recon for all humans, (One person calls in recon, the whole team gets it.)<br>
-Humans get a random reward for ever half an hour they survive.<br>
-Teleporting can no longer work during Deadscape gameplay<br>
-Added a 1-way chatline for all players [Deads cannot hear human conversations and humans cannot hear Deads conversations.]<br>
-Used by command, ::hcc and ::dcc<br>
-Recon now sends messages telling you when you have 5 or less seconds, ten seconds till it disappears and when it is launched by someone.<br>
-If someone launches a recon, no one else can use one at that time.<br>
-Added Air-Strike base.<br>
-Started working on AI-Helicopter base.<br>
-Helicopters are based on timed events over an area for 120 seconds.<br>
-Each area is split into 7 regions that are bombarded at by a random counter.<br>
-N, W, E, S, NW, NE, M.<br>
-Every 13 seconds a new area over the region is chosen through the random method in the misc class.<br>
-NOTE: Will need to add an int that resets every 39 seconds to ensure that the same place is not hit around the same time.<br>
-Air-Strikes now work perfectly giving players a 3 second warning before damage is delt every 1000ms for 3 seconds.<br>
-All air-strikes are set-up for:<br>
-Varrock<br>
-Falador<br>
-Lumbridge<br>
-Draynor<br>
-Edgeville and Barbarian Village<br>
SETUP NEW SPECIAL ABILITY BASE!:<br>
-Instead of sextants, you click UAV on a scroll to make the minimap workable for all players.<br>
-All these load from the same scroll<br>
-Air strike and Heli give you a horn that you use to call in your attack.<br>
TABLES:<br>
-Added medical tables at all major cities<br>
-Bandages heal 1-3 health.<br>
-Food can no longer be eaten during Deadscape<br>
-Added Barricades<br>
-Table in Falador<br>
-Barricades can be setup<br>
-Barricades disappear after 20 seconds of being setup<br>
-To make this a team game.  Players can only set-up on barricade per person at a time.[/code]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 20:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-279280-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280.rss">B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Itachi_Uchiha Itachi Uchiha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/itachi_uchiha">@Itachi_Uchiha</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My project had been lost and I discontinued working on this for quite some while.  In fact, I stopped programming any form of documentation with java since the closing of this project.  Since then I have moved onto Python and Delphi…  But I’m hoping to jump right back into this sever.</p>
<p>Special thanks to Adem70 for keeping my backup base files from over a year ago.</p>
<p>It’s based on one of Palidino76’s early releases, so it’s quite outdated.  I have managed to spruce up the code to be stable and reliable with many modifications added.  There might be a gap in my logs, because I started working on code that’s under the hood and wouldn’t effect anything noticeably in game.</p>
<p>I’ve done a near to complete overhaul of my definitions by renaming major integers just to make me feel all warm and fuzzy inside (ex: absX and absY are now parameterJ and parameterK) and I’ve redefined a lot of classes as well.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">CURRENT PROJECTS:</span></span></p>
<p>[<span class="bbcode-b">DGDT</span>] <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">B3rnscape</span></span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Base</span>: Palidino’s 3.2 Base or something, I honestly don’t know what module it is…I was eager and just downloaded some of Palidino’s work from rs-server!</p>
<p>Background: B3rnscape was possibly one of the most famous servers back in the day before fugooscape(or whatever his name was) and Silabsoft’s client (The days when Moparscape 2.0 was still around). I was appointed Lead Java Programmer of B3rnscape before my retirement in early 2005. Before the collapse of B3rnscape in late 2005, early 2006, I re-joined B3rn0ut in his game. The only people who had an understanding for the Java language (even half-ass understanding…  meaning only knowing how to edit shit in a private server source) was B3rn0ut, Cook, and myself. After the fall of B3rnscape B3rn0ut had fled from the scope of the radar. These days all of the admins that were apart of the B3rnscape staff keep in touch with each other, with the exception of Tiffany and that scum The Truth, leader of the downfall of B3rnscape. In October of 2008 I had the idea of re-creating B3rnscape. Luke(MrKalius) and I had tested numerous bases, from some random base packed with nonsense(rejected immediately), to wL base(also rejected, due to me getting bored) until we followed B3rn0ut’s philosophy and upgraded from 317 to 508.</p>
<p>Note:Currently not accepting any new members for our development team, I am looking to get all this crap covered and make it as decent as I can make it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Current Staff</span></span><br>
Steven(Itachi Uchiha) - Lead Programmer/Developer<br>
Luke(MrKalius) - Lead Designer<br>
Adam(Adem70) - Hoster and Data Manager.<br>
Steve(Cook) - Java programmer, Head of Gaming Content, Co-developer<br>
<span class="bbcode-s">Magicks - Head of Statistics, AI Management</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-s">amm3 - Head of Player Management</span></p>
<p>UPDATES ON NEXT POST, CURRENTLY EXCEEDS 20000 CHARACTERS.</p>
<p>List of Skill(name, %done, additional_notes):<br>
(Will add soon)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Newest Pictures</span>:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i43.tinypic.com/zoema.gif" title="zoema.gif" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i43.tinypic.com/zoema.gif" alt width="690" height="483"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">zoema.gif</span><span class="informations">769×539</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i41.tinypic.com/ixaxiw.jpg" title="ixaxiw.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/ixaxiw.jpg" alt width="690" height="480"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">ixaxiw.jpg</span><span class="informations">769×536</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i39.tinypic.com/2mhwmsw.jpg" title="2mhwmsw.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i39.tinypic.com/2mhwmsw.jpg" alt width="690" height="484"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2mhwmsw.jpg</span><span class="informations">771×541</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i43.tinypic.com/2ugihw1.jpg" title="2ugihw1.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i43.tinypic.com/2ugihw1.jpg" alt width="690" height="484"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2ugihw1.jpg</span><span class="informations">771×541</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Archived Pictures</span>:<br>
None at this time.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Notes</span>:<br>
Nuclear Chemical composition outline so far.(work in progress)</p>
<p>[code]                                                &gt;null<br>
&gt; Cupric ore powder<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Sulphuric broline<br>
&gt; Sulphur<br>
&gt; Ground sulphur<br>
&gt; Pestle and mortar<br>
&gt; ??? mixture<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Iron<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Iron oxide<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Vial of water<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Cupric sulphate<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Cupric ore powder<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Sulphuric broline<br>
&gt; Sulphur<br>
&gt; Ground sulphur<br>
&gt; Pestle and mortar<br>
&gt; ??? mixture<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Sodium chloride<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Serum 207<br>
&gt; Goblin potion<br>
&gt; Mixed chemicals<br>
&gt; Compost potion<br>
&gt; Strange potion<br>
&gt; Initiate cuisse<br>
&gt; Mixture - step 2<br>
&gt; Nitrous oxide<br>
&gt; Mixture - step 1<br>
&gt; Acetic Acid<br>
&gt; Relicym’s balm<br>
&gt; Vial of liquid<br>
&gt; Nitroglycerin<br>
&gt; Tin ore powder<br>
&gt; Chem compound<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Gypsum<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Relicym’s mix<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Ethenea<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Bravery potion<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Truth serum<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Ardrigal mixture<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Liquid honey<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; ‘voice of doom’<br>
&gt;null<br>
&gt; Snakeweed mix<br>
&lt;chemic.&gt;                                                &gt;null</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Serum 208 &lt;NUCLEAR EVEN THOUGH YOU ARE NOT CAUSING NUCLEAR REACTIONS…DON’T BRING LOGIC INTO THIS!&gt;<br>
                                        &gt;null<br>
Fishing mix<br>
null<br>
Hunting mix<br>
Strength mix<br>
Ranging mix<br>
Antidote+ mix<br>
Antifire mix<br>
Sup. def. mix<br>
Sup. restore mix<br>
Antidote+ mix<br>
Agility mix<br>
null<br>
Sup. energy mix<br>
null<br>
Zamorak Mix<br>
Superattack mix<br>
Restore mix<br>
Antidote+ mix<br>
Energy mix<br>
Antidote+ mix<br>
Anti-p supermix<br>
Antipoison mix<br>
Magic mix<br>
Sup. str. mix<br>
Combat mix<br>
Antidote+ mix<br>
Magic ess. mix<br>
Attack mix<br>
Prayer mix<br>
Antidote+ mix[/code]</p>
</blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Approval</span>:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i43.tinypic.com/b71951.jpg" title="b71951.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i43.tinypic.com/b71951.jpg" alt width="690" height="206"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">b71951.jpg</span><span class="informations">1064×318</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>More on this project coming soon!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 20:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-279280-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/b3rnscape-project-reopened/279280.rss">B3rnscape - Project[REOPENED]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
