<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538</link>
    <description>This is the best MMORPG Ive ever played.

Heres some info - 

Link to site - [url=http://flyff.gpotato.com/]http://flyff.gpotato.com/[/url]

About this game - In ancient times, five Gods of Lais sought to create a new world with new inhabitants that could live harmoniously among them. They gathered and agreed to create Roika Mainland; their new world. They created water and the earth, animals and plants as well as Humans. At this time, and at all times in Roika Mainland, it is a time of peace.

After years of peace, the God&#39;s decided to leave Roika Mainland and create a new world. With this, in an attempt to maintain the golden age of Roika mainland the Gods of Lais handed all of the secrets of the land as well as the core part of the revolution-genesis gear over to the kind race of Dwarf. The God&#39;s only wish was that the world would remain as beautiful and peaceful as it was in their rule.

Simultaneously, to bring happiness to the race of human, the Gods created Comedian-Clown. The Comedian Clown became enraged about bringing happiness to the race of Human and split its personality into three identities; Imagination Ipuli, Shadow Shield and Chromospheres Bobor. Under the initiation of the evil Shadow Shield, the main body-Imagination Ipuli not only chased away the kind Chromospheres Bobor, but also created numerous Human attacking monsters. These monsters took away the revolution-genesis-gear of the race dwarf and developed a new Mainland; a mainland that was angrier, stronger and prepared to destroy the race of Human.

To save the mainland from chaos, the Chromospheres Bobor inherited the mystical ancient-science and black magic of Human. For the restoration of harmonious simple life, the citizens of Roika Mainland were forced to become warriors who would fight against the evil shadow Shield and uphold the wish of the God&#39;s.

Out numbered and out matched, the race Human prepares themselves for a battle that may prove to be their end!

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img149.imageshack.us/img149/2512/backgroundstorymainga9.gif[/img][/URL]

Vagrant - 



Vagrant is the starting job class you will initially play as when you join the world of FlyFF. It is the starting point of the game, and as a Vagrant you will primarily focus on learning how to play the game.

You will start out with basic equipment, and learn basic fighting skills as you gain experience points through fighting monsters.

You will be able to job change to a more specific and advanced first job class upon reaching level 15. You will be able to fly after you reach level 20, and successfully complete the Flying Quest.

Before then, you do not need to worry about where to distribute your status points as there will be a stat reset after you change your job to the first job class. Generally, you may want to distribute all your points to strength in order to kill monsters more quickly.

The job classes you are able to change into after reaching level 15 are Mercenary, Magician, and Assist. After which you will also learn specific skills selective to the job class you have chosen. Depending on what you prefer, you may want to be up there in the action as a Mercenary, dishing out major damage from the back as a magician, or supporting your friends with healing and buffing spells as an assist.

Icon  	Skill  	Requirement  	Mater Level
	OverCutter 	Chr-Lv 4 	10
	Brendish 	Chr-Lv6 	10
	OverCutter 	Chr-Lv6 	10

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img148.imageshack.us/img148/7642/chabigpicvagantbt7.gif[/img][/URL]

Mercenary - 

You will be able to job change to a Mercenary from the Vagrant class at level 15.

Mercenary is a job that involves close physical combat. The main characteristics of a Mercenary involve physical strength, and a strong body that is able to withstand attacks.

Useful stats for Mercenary are Str.(Strength) And Sta.(Stamina). Strength will increase your attack power, while stamina will increase your HP.

As a Mercenary you will use close range weapons such as swords and axes to attack your enemies. You will also be able to employ the use of a shield in order to reduce damage to yourself when you are attacked.

When you reach level 60, you will be able to change your job class to either Knight or Blade.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Splmash 	Chr-Lv 15 	20
	Keenwheel 	Splmash Lv4, Chr-Lv 18 	20
	Blindside 	Keenwheel Lv6, Chr-Lv 24 	20
	Special Hit 	Blindside Lv8, Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Bloody Strike 	Splmash Lv3, Chr-Lv 20 	20
	Reflex Hit 	Bloody Strike Lv8, Chr-Lv 25 	20
	Guilotine 	Reflex Hit 10, Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Protection 	Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Pan Barrier 	Protection Lv3, Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Sneaker 	Pan Barrier Lv 10, Chr-Lv 20 	20
	Impower weapon 	Protection Lv 5, Chr-Lv 20 	20
	Smite Axe 	Impower weapon Lv4, Chr-Lv 25 	20
	Axe mastery 	Smite Axe Lv9, Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Blazing sword 	Impower weapon Lv4, Chr-Lv 25 	20
	Sword Mastery 	Blazing sword Lv9, Chr-Lv 30 	20

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img156.imageshack.us/img156/7892/chabigpicmercenaryzk9.gif[/img][/URL]



Knight - When you reach level 60 as a Mercenary, you will be able to job change into a Knight.

As a knight you can take on the role of being the tank for the party. You will be at the front taking damage from monsters and dealing damage to monsters.

You will have good defense, enabling you to shield other members from attacks. You will also have the strength to provide consistent damage against monsters.

As a Knight you will wear heavy armor for protection. To fight, you will use swords and axes.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Chagre 	Sword Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Pain Dealer 	Axe Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Guard 	Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Earth Divider 	Chagre Lv4, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Power Stump 	Pain Dealer Lv4, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Rage 	Guard Lv 5,Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Pain Reflection 	Rage Lv 4, Chr-Lv 70 	10
	Power Swing 	Pain Reflection Lv7, Chr-Lv 7 	10

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img293.imageshack.us/img293/6729/chabigpicknightot0.gif[/img][/URL]

Blade - 

When you reach level 60 as a Mercenary, you will be able to job change into a Blade.

As a Blade, you will hit hard and hit fast. A Blade is the equivalent of being an assassin in that you attack quickly and stealthily, aiming for the kill.

You will have lower defense and HP, but can easily make up for it in your quick attacks and higher dodge rate.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Silent Strike 	Sword Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Spring Attack 	Axe Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Armor Penetrate 	Chr-Lv 62 	10
	Blade Dance 	Silent Strike Lv5, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Hawk Attack 	Spring Attack Lv5, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Berserk 	Armor Penetrate Lv4, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Sonic Blade 	Berserk Lv7, Chr-Lv 70 	10
	Cross Strike 	Sonic Blade Lv7, Chr-Lv 75 	10

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img293.imageshack.us/img293/3993/chabigpicbladegb6.gif[/img][/URL]



Assist

You will be able to job change to an Assist from the Vagrant class at level 15.

The Assist class can go at two ways.

You can either lean towards support, where you help out your party members with buffing spells; or you can lean towards hand to hand combat, focusing on becoming a tank type character.

A useful stat for a support oriented Assist is Int. (Intelligence) as it will increase your MP.

Useful stats for a battle oriented Assist are Str.(Strength) And Sta.(Stamina). Strength will increase your attack power, while stamina will increase your HP.

As an Assist you can either use a magic wand to perform buffing spells, or use your fists to fight enemies. You will also wear light armor.

When you reach level 60, you will be able to change your job class to either Billposter or Ringmaster.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Heal 	Chr-Lv15 	20
	Patience 	Heal Lv3, Chr-Lv18 	20
	Resurrection 	Patience Lv4, Chr-Lv20 	20
	Circle Healing 	Resurrection Lv4, Chr-Lv25 	20
	Prevention 	Circle Healing Lv4, Chr-Lv30 	20
	Quick Step 	Heal Lv3, Chr-Lv18 	20
	Haste 	Quick Step Lv3, Chr-Lv25 	20
	Cat&#39;s Reflex 	Haste Lv4, Chr-Lv28 	20
	CannonBall 	Cat&#39;s Reflex Lv4, Chr-Lv35 	20
	MentalSign 	Heal Lv3, Chr-Lv18 	20
	HeapUp 	MentalSign Lv4, Chr-Lv20 	20
	BeefUp 	HeapUp Lv4, Chr-Lv25 	20
	Accuracy 	BeefUp Lv4, Chr-Lv30 	--
	Tamping Hole 	Heal Lv3, Chr-Lv20 	20
	Stonehand 	Tamping Hole Lv4, Chr-Lv25 	20
	Burst Crack 	Stonehand Lv4, Chr-Lv28 	20
	Power Fist 	Burst Crack Lv4, Chr-Lv35 	20

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img96.imageshack.us/img96/8642/chabigpicassistee9.gif[/img][/URL]



Billposter

When you reach level 60 as an Assist, you will be able to job change into a Billposter.

As a Billposter, you will be dealing damage through power boosting magic, you are your own strength.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Belial Smashing 	Power fist Lv5, Chr-Lv60 	10
	Asmodeus 	Chr-Lv60 	10
	Blood Fist 	Belial Smashing Lv2, Chr-Lv65 	10
	Baraqijal Esna 	Asmodeus Lv3, Chr-Lv65 	10
	Piercing Serpent 	Blood Fist Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Bgvur Tialbold 	Baraqijal Esna Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Sonichand 	Piercing Serpent Lv7, Bgvur Tialbold Lv6, Chr-Lv75 	10
	Asalraalaikum 	Sonichand Lv7, Chr-Lv80 	10

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img266.imageshack.us/img266/4223/chabigpicbillpostervz6.gif[/img][/URL]



Ringmaster

When you reach level 60 as an Assist, you will be able to job change into a Ringmaster.

As a Ringmaster, you will be casting healing and buffing spells. Buffing spells will make you an essential part to any party as you will be able to heal your party members, increase their attack speed, and so forth.

However, the skills may be hard to level. This will pay off in the end as you will probably be one of the most sought after classes for a party.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Protect 	Heap up Lv6, Chr-Lv60 	10
	Holycross 	Chr-Lv60 	10
	Gvur Tialla 	Prevention Lv4, Chr-Lv60 	10
	Holyguard 	Protect Lv3, Chr-Lv65 	10
	Spiriture Fortune 	Chr-Lv65 	10
	Heal Rain 	Gvur Tialla Lv3, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Geburah Tiphreth 	Holyguard Lv4, Spiriture Fortune Lv7, Chr-Lv75 	10
	Merkaba Hanzelrusha 	Heal Rain Lv4, Chr-Lv80 	10

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img186.imageshack.us/img186/6642/chabigpicringmasterqr7.gif[/img][/URL]



Magician

You will be able to job change to a Magician from the Vagrant class at level 15.

Magician is a job class that involves dealing magical damage from a distance by casting spells. You will learn spells as skills, and be able to use them to deal massive damage to monsters.

You can deal even more damage by following the elemental chart. [insert link with chart on which element is weak/strong against which]

You will have lower defense, lower HP, and a delay time in casting spells, but you are able to cast massively damaging spells if you do it right.

As a Magician you will use staves and wands to cast magic spells. You will also be wearing light armor.

A useful stat for Magician is Int. (Intelligence), which will increase your magic attack power, and maximum MP.

When you reach level 60, you will be able to change your job class to either Psykeeper or Elementer.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Mental strike 	Chr-Lv 15 	20
	Fire Boomerang 	Mental strile Lv 3, Chr-Lv18 	20
	Hot Air 	Fire Boomerang Lv 25, Chr-Lv25 	20
	Fire strike 	Hot Air Lv7, Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Sword wind 	Mental strike Lv5, Chr-Lv 20 	20
	Strong wind 	Sword wind Lv5, Chr-Lv 25 	20
	Guilotine 	Reflex Hit 10, Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Protection 	Protection Lv3, Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Pan Barrier 	Pan Barrier Lv 10, Chr-Lv 20 	20
	Impower weapon 	Protection Lv 5, Chr-Lv 20 	20
	Smite Axe 	Impower weapon Lv4, Chr-Lv 25 	20
	Axe mastery 	Smite Axe Lv9, Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Blazing sword 	Impower weapon Lv4, Chr-Lv 25 	20
	Sword Mastery 	Blazing sword Lv9, Chr-Lv 30 	20
	Splmash 	Chr-Lv6 	20
	OverCutter 	Chr-Lv6 	20

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img512.imageshack.us/img512/2886/chabigpicmagicianqv7.gif[/img][/URL]



Psykeeper

When you reach level 60 as a Magician, you will be able to job change into a Psykeeper.

As a Psykeeper, you can weaken the enemy by casting debuffing spells. Debuffing spells are weakening spells. Basically, Psykeeper is a support class, and is an asset to any party.

You will be a valuable member of any party due to the fact that your debuffing spells will enable the party to defeat the monster more easily.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Demonolgy 	Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Psychic Bomb 	Mental Strike Lv10, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Crucio Spell 	Mental Strike Lv10, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Satanolgy 	Demonolgy Lv3, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Sprit Bomb 	Psychic Bomb Lv6, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Maximum Crisis 	Crucio Spell Lv7, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Psychic Wall 	Satanolgy Lv4, Sprit Bomb Lv5, Chr-Lv 70 	10
	Psychic Square 	Psychic Wall Lv7, Maximum Crisis Lv5, Chr-Lv 75 	10

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img512.imageshack.us/img512/2024/chabigpicpsykeepermy8.gif[/img][/URL]



Elementer

When you reach level 60 as a Magician, you will be able to job change into an Elementer.

As an Elementer, you will probably be dealing out the most damage out of all the second job classes. However, you will have lower HP, and will most likely not be able to dodge many attacks.

You will be a valuable member of any party due to the sheer amount of damage you can do, taking out chunks of monsters’ HP.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Firebird 	Fire Strike Lv7, Chr-Lv60 	10
	Stone Spear 	Looting Lv3, Chr-Lv60 	10
	Void 	Windcutter Lv7, Chr-Lv60 	10
	Thunder Strike 	Lightening Shock Lv7, Chr-Lv60 	10
	Iceshark 	Spring water Lv7, Chr-Lv60 	10
	Burningfield 	Fire Bird Lv5, Chr-Lv65 	10
	Earthquake 	Stone Spear Lv4, Chr-Lv65 	10
	Windfield 	Void Lv5, Chr-Lv65 	10
	Eletric Shock 	Thunder Strike Lv4, Chr-Lv65 	10
	Poison Cloud 	Iceshark Lv5, Chr-Lv65 	10
	Fire Master 	Fire Strike Lv7, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Earth Master 	Looting Lv3, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Wind Master 	Wind Cutter Lv7, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Lighting Master 	Lightening Shock Lv7, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Water Master 	Spring water Lv7, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Meteo Shower 	Burningfield LV6, Earthquake Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Sandstorm 	Windfield Lv6, Earthquake Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Lightingstorm 	Windfield Lv6, Eletric Shock Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10
	Avalanche 	Poison Cloud Lv7, earthquakeLv7, Chr-Lv75 	10

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img503.imageshack.us/img503/8283/chabigpicelementerle1.gif[/img][/URL]



Acrobat

You will be able to job change to an Acrobat from the Vagrant class at level 15.

The Acrobat class can go at two ways.

Acrobat, who uses mainly long distance attack, is a kind of many who always smile and act gentle. He believe with his speed and accuracy, he can break anybody who want to fight him.

Apparently, he looks very kind and nice person; however, due to the fact that his nature is assassin, he thinks every body can be enemy.

When you reach level 60, you will be able to change your job class to either Jester or Ran

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Pulling 	Chr-Lv15 	20
	Fast Walker 	Pulling Lv4, Chr-Lv18 	20
	Dark Illusion 	Fast Walker Lv5, Chr-Lv30 	20
	Perfect Block 	Dark Illusion Lv8, Chr-Lv45 	20
	Slow Step 	Chr-Lv15 	20
	YoYo Mastery 	Slow Step Lv3, Chr-Lv20 	20
	Cross Line 	YoYo Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv30 	20
	Snitch 	YoYo Mastery 8, Chr-Lv35 	20
	Counter Attack 	Cross Line Lv10, Chr-Lv40 	20
	Deadly Swing 	Snitch Lv3, Chr-Lv50 	20
	Junk Arrow 	Chr-Lv15 	20
	Perfect Block 	Dark Illusion Lv8, Chr-Lv45 	20
	Bow Mastery 	Junk Arrow Lv5, Chr-Lv20 	20
	Silent Shot 	Bow Mastery Lv4, Chr-Lv30 	20
	Aimed Shot 	Bow Mastery Lv5, Chr-Lv35 	20
	Auto Shot 	Silent Shot Lv9, Chr-Lv45 	20
	Arrow Rain 	Aim Shot Lv5 Chr-Lv50 	20

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img111.imageshack.us/img111/2100/chabigpicacrobatxu7.gif[/img][/URL]



Jester

When you reach level 60 as a Acrobat, you will be able to job change into a Jester.

Jester, who has less defense power than attack power, is a derived from acrobat who uses yo-yo as a main weapon. He has a lot of useful skills who make jester more stronger like snatch and hiding.

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Enchant Poison 	Deadly Swing Lv4, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Enchant Blood 	Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Escape 	Perfect Block Lv6, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Critical Swing 	Enchant Poison Lv3, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Back Step 	Enchant Blood Lv3, Chr-Lv 70 	10
	Enchant Absorb 	Escape Lv3, Chr-Lv 70 	10
	Vatal Stab 	Critical Swing Lv4, Backstep Lv7, Chr-Lv 80 	10
	Hit of Penya 	Enchant Absorb Lv4, Chr-Lv 75 	10

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img111.imageshack.us/img111/3279/chabigpicjesterow1.gif[/img][/URL]



Ranger

When you reach level 60 as a Acrobat, you will be able to job change into a Ranger.

Ranger is a derived from acrobat who uses bow as a main weapon

Skills
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level
	Ice Arrow 	Auto Shot Lv4, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Flame Arrow 	Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Poison Arrow 	Arrow Rain Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10
	Fast Shot 	Ice Arrow Lv3, Chr-Lv 65 	10
	Piercing Arrow 	Flame Arrow Lv3, Chr-Lv 70 	10
	Nature 	Poison Arrow Lv4, Chr-Lv 70 	10
	Triple Shot 	Fast Shot Lv4, Piercing Lv7, Chr-Lv 80 	10
	Silent Shot 	Nature Lv4, Chr-Lv 75 	10

[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img399.imageshack.us/img399/7200/chabigpicrangerbq2.gif[/img][/URL]

Thats about it =)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 05:50:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dorkinator dorkinator]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dorkinator">@dorkinator</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lawl my freind who is 13 plays he dosent cheet in my opion its just a memory cliger and there are dozens of much netre games out there, Ex: Defend the Castel, Maple story, Runescape, Newstart, Halo, The sims and so on… It is a crapy game and not only crapy but a big crapy game, don’t call this flaming because it not it <span class="bbcode-b">IS</span> the truth</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 05:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93538-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss">FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxchainxx xxchainxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxchainxx">@xxchainxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im 16 and i play</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2007 08:22:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93538-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss">FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ew WTF HAXXXXXXXXXX?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2007 15:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93538-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss">FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxchainxx xxchainxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxchainxx">@xxchainxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yah they got in english, chinese, japenese, german, French, and phillipines</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2007 15:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93538-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss">FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@billygotshot billygotshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billygotshot">@billygotshot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>my friend pwns at this game and owns everything lol…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2007 08:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93538-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss">FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PandaScape PandaScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pandascape">@PandaScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>they have this in english now?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2007 05:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93538-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss">FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxchainxx xxchainxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxchainxx">@xxchainxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well idk if i can give u links to that but maybe[br][size=1]Posted on: May 12, 2007, 07:36:10 PM[/size][hr]any1 even find this useful/cool???</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2007 05:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93538-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss">FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1337h4x 1337h4x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1337h4x">@1337h4x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That’s cool and all, but now I really really want some hentai.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2007 06:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93538-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss">FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxchainxx xxchainxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxchainxx">@xxchainxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is the best MMORPG Ive ever played.</p>
<p>Heres some info -</p>
<p>Link to site - <a href="http://flyff.gpotato.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://flyff.gpotato.com/</a></p>
<p>About this game - In ancient times, five Gods of Lais sought to create a new world with new inhabitants that could live harmoniously among them. They gathered and agreed to create Roika Mainland; their new world. They created water and the earth, animals and plants as well as Humans. At this time, and at all times in Roika Mainland, it is a time of peace.</p>
<p>After years of peace, the God’s decided to leave Roika Mainland and create a new world. With this, in an attempt to maintain the golden age of Roika mainland the Gods of Lais handed all of the secrets of the land as well as the core part of the revolution-genesis gear over to the kind race of Dwarf. The God’s only wish was that the world would remain as beautiful and peaceful as it was in their rule.</p>
<p>Simultaneously, to bring happiness to the race of human, the Gods created Comedian-Clown. The Comedian Clown became enraged about bringing happiness to the race of Human and split its personality into three identities; Imagination Ipuli, Shadow Shield and Chromospheres Bobor. Under the initiation of the evil Shadow Shield, the main body-Imagination Ipuli not only chased away the kind Chromospheres Bobor, but also created numerous Human attacking monsters. These monsters took away the revolution-genesis-gear of the race dwarf and developed a new Mainland; a mainland that was angrier, stronger and prepared to destroy the race of Human.</p>
<p>To save the mainland from chaos, the Chromospheres Bobor inherited the mystical ancient-science and black magic of Human. For the restoration of harmonious simple life, the citizens of Roika Mainland were forced to become warriors who would fight against the evil shadow Shield and uphold the wish of the God’s.</p>
<p>Out numbered and out matched, the race Human prepares themselves for a battle that may prove to be their end!</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img149.imageshack.us/img149/2512/backgroundstorymainga9.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Vagrant -</p>
<p>Vagrant is the starting job class you will initially play as when you join the world of FlyFF. It is the starting point of the game, and as a Vagrant you will primarily focus on learning how to play the game.</p>
<p>You will start out with basic equipment, and learn basic fighting skills as you gain experience points through fighting monsters.</p>
<p>You will be able to job change to a more specific and advanced first job class upon reaching level 15. You will be able to fly after you reach level 20, and successfully complete the Flying Quest.</p>
<p>Before then, you do not need to worry about where to distribute your status points as there will be a stat reset after you change your job to the first job class. Generally, you may want to distribute all your points to strength in order to kill monsters more quickly.</p>
<p>The job classes you are able to change into after reaching level 15 are Mercenary, Magician, and Assist. After which you will also learn specific skills selective to the job class you have chosen. Depending on what you prefer, you may want to be up there in the action as a Mercenary, dishing out major damage from the back as a magician, or supporting your friends with healing and buffing spells as an assist.</p>
<p>Icon  	Skill  	Requirement  	Mater Level<br>
OverCutter 	Chr-Lv 4 	10<br>
Brendish 	Chr-Lv6 	10<br>
OverCutter 	Chr-Lv6 	10</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img148.imageshack.us/img148/7642/chabigpicvagantbt7.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Mercenary -</p>
<p>You will be able to job change to a Mercenary from the Vagrant class at level 15.</p>
<p>Mercenary is a job that involves close physical combat. The main characteristics of a Mercenary involve physical strength, and a strong body that is able to withstand attacks.</p>
<p>Useful stats for Mercenary are Str.(Strength) And Sta.(Stamina). Strength will increase your attack power, while stamina will increase your HP.</p>
<p>As a Mercenary you will use close range weapons such as swords and axes to attack your enemies. You will also be able to employ the use of a shield in order to reduce damage to yourself when you are attacked.</p>
<p>When you reach level 60, you will be able to change your job class to either Knight or Blade.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Splmash 	Chr-Lv 15 	20<br>
Keenwheel 	Splmash Lv4, Chr-Lv 18 	20<br>
Blindside 	Keenwheel Lv6, Chr-Lv 24 	20<br>
Special Hit 	Blindside Lv8, Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Bloody Strike 	Splmash Lv3, Chr-Lv 20 	20<br>
Reflex Hit 	Bloody Strike Lv8, Chr-Lv 25 	20<br>
Guilotine 	Reflex Hit 10, Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Protection 	Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Pan Barrier 	Protection Lv3, Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Sneaker 	Pan Barrier Lv 10, Chr-Lv 20 	20<br>
Impower weapon 	Protection Lv 5, Chr-Lv 20 	20<br>
Smite Axe 	Impower weapon Lv4, Chr-Lv 25 	20<br>
Axe mastery 	Smite Axe Lv9, Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Blazing sword 	Impower weapon Lv4, Chr-Lv 25 	20<br>
Sword Mastery 	Blazing sword Lv9, Chr-Lv 30 	20</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img156.imageshack.us/img156/7892/chabigpicmercenaryzk9.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Knight - When you reach level 60 as a Mercenary, you will be able to job change into a Knight.</p>
<p>As a knight you can take on the role of being the tank for the party. You will be at the front taking damage from monsters and dealing damage to monsters.</p>
<p>You will have good defense, enabling you to shield other members from attacks. You will also have the strength to provide consistent damage against monsters.</p>
<p>As a Knight you will wear heavy armor for protection. To fight, you will use swords and axes.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Chagre 	Sword Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Pain Dealer 	Axe Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Guard 	Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Earth Divider 	Chagre Lv4, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Power Stump 	Pain Dealer Lv4, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Rage 	Guard Lv 5,Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Pain Reflection 	Rage Lv 4, Chr-Lv 70 	10<br>
Power Swing 	Pain Reflection Lv7, Chr-Lv 7 	10</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img293.imageshack.us/img293/6729/chabigpicknightot0.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Blade -</p>
<p>When you reach level 60 as a Mercenary, you will be able to job change into a Blade.</p>
<p>As a Blade, you will hit hard and hit fast. A Blade is the equivalent of being an assassin in that you attack quickly and stealthily, aiming for the kill.</p>
<p>You will have lower defense and HP, but can easily make up for it in your quick attacks and higher dodge rate.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Silent Strike 	Sword Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Spring Attack 	Axe Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Armor Penetrate 	Chr-Lv 62 	10<br>
Blade Dance 	Silent Strike Lv5, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Hawk Attack 	Spring Attack Lv5, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Berserk 	Armor Penetrate Lv4, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Sonic Blade 	Berserk Lv7, Chr-Lv 70 	10<br>
Cross Strike 	Sonic Blade Lv7, Chr-Lv 75 	10</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img293.imageshack.us/img293/3993/chabigpicbladegb6.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Assist</p>
<p>You will be able to job change to an Assist from the Vagrant class at level 15.</p>
<p>The Assist class can go at two ways.</p>
<p>You can either lean towards support, where you help out your party members with buffing spells; or you can lean towards hand to hand combat, focusing on becoming a tank type character.</p>
<p>A useful stat for a support oriented Assist is Int. (Intelligence) as it will increase your MP.</p>
<p>Useful stats for a battle oriented Assist are Str.(Strength) And Sta.(Stamina). Strength will increase your attack power, while stamina will increase your HP.</p>
<p>As an Assist you can either use a magic wand to perform buffing spells, or use your fists to fight enemies. You will also wear light armor.</p>
<p>When you reach level 60, you will be able to change your job class to either Billposter or Ringmaster.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Heal 	Chr-Lv15 	20<br>
Patience 	Heal Lv3, Chr-Lv18 	20<br>
Resurrection 	Patience Lv4, Chr-Lv20 	20<br>
Circle Healing 	Resurrection Lv4, Chr-Lv25 	20<br>
Prevention 	Circle Healing Lv4, Chr-Lv30 	20<br>
Quick Step 	Heal Lv3, Chr-Lv18 	20<br>
Haste 	Quick Step Lv3, Chr-Lv25 	20<br>
Cat’s Reflex 	Haste Lv4, Chr-Lv28 	20<br>
CannonBall 	Cat’s Reflex Lv4, Chr-Lv35 	20<br>
MentalSign 	Heal Lv3, Chr-Lv18 	20<br>
HeapUp 	MentalSign Lv4, Chr-Lv20 	20<br>
BeefUp 	HeapUp Lv4, Chr-Lv25 	20<br>
Accuracy 	BeefUp Lv4, Chr-Lv30 	–<br>
Tamping Hole 	Heal Lv3, Chr-Lv20 	20<br>
Stonehand 	Tamping Hole Lv4, Chr-Lv25 	20<br>
Burst Crack 	Stonehand Lv4, Chr-Lv28 	20<br>
Power Fist 	Burst Crack Lv4, Chr-Lv35 	20</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img96.imageshack.us/img96/8642/chabigpicassistee9.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Billposter</p>
<p>When you reach level 60 as an Assist, you will be able to job change into a Billposter.</p>
<p>As a Billposter, you will be dealing damage through power boosting magic, you are your own strength.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Belial Smashing 	Power fist Lv5, Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Asmodeus 	Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Blood Fist 	Belial Smashing Lv2, Chr-Lv65 	10<br>
Baraqijal Esna 	Asmodeus Lv3, Chr-Lv65 	10<br>
Piercing Serpent 	Blood Fist Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Bgvur Tialbold 	Baraqijal Esna Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Sonichand 	Piercing Serpent Lv7, Bgvur Tialbold Lv6, Chr-Lv75 	10<br>
Asalraalaikum 	Sonichand Lv7, Chr-Lv80 	10</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img266.imageshack.us/img266/4223/chabigpicbillpostervz6.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Ringmaster</p>
<p>When you reach level 60 as an Assist, you will be able to job change into a Ringmaster.</p>
<p>As a Ringmaster, you will be casting healing and buffing spells. Buffing spells will make you an essential part to any party as you will be able to heal your party members, increase their attack speed, and so forth.</p>
<p>However, the skills may be hard to level. This will pay off in the end as you will probably be one of the most sought after classes for a party.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Protect 	Heap up Lv6, Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Holycross 	Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Gvur Tialla 	Prevention Lv4, Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Holyguard 	Protect Lv3, Chr-Lv65 	10<br>
Spiriture Fortune 	Chr-Lv65 	10<br>
Heal Rain 	Gvur Tialla Lv3, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Geburah Tiphreth 	Holyguard Lv4, Spiriture Fortune Lv7, Chr-Lv75 	10<br>
Merkaba Hanzelrusha 	Heal Rain Lv4, Chr-Lv80 	10</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img186.imageshack.us/img186/6642/chabigpicringmasterqr7.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Magician</p>
<p>You will be able to job change to a Magician from the Vagrant class at level 15.</p>
<p>Magician is a job class that involves dealing magical damage from a distance by casting spells. You will learn spells as skills, and be able to use them to deal massive damage to monsters.</p>
<p>You can deal even more damage by following the elemental chart. [insert link with chart on which element is weak/strong against which]</p>
<p>You will have lower defense, lower HP, and a delay time in casting spells, but you are able to cast massively damaging spells if you do it right.</p>
<p>As a Magician you will use staves and wands to cast magic spells. You will also be wearing light armor.</p>
<p>A useful stat for Magician is Int. (Intelligence), which will increase your magic attack power, and maximum MP.</p>
<p>When you reach level 60, you will be able to change your job class to either Psykeeper or Elementer.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Mental strike 	Chr-Lv 15 	20<br>
Fire Boomerang 	Mental strile Lv 3, Chr-Lv18 	20<br>
Hot Air 	Fire Boomerang Lv 25, Chr-Lv25 	20<br>
Fire strike 	Hot Air Lv7, Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Sword wind 	Mental strike Lv5, Chr-Lv 20 	20<br>
Strong wind 	Sword wind Lv5, Chr-Lv 25 	20<br>
Guilotine 	Reflex Hit 10, Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Protection 	Protection Lv3, Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Pan Barrier 	Pan Barrier Lv 10, Chr-Lv 20 	20<br>
Impower weapon 	Protection Lv 5, Chr-Lv 20 	20<br>
Smite Axe 	Impower weapon Lv4, Chr-Lv 25 	20<br>
Axe mastery 	Smite Axe Lv9, Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Blazing sword 	Impower weapon Lv4, Chr-Lv 25 	20<br>
Sword Mastery 	Blazing sword Lv9, Chr-Lv 30 	20<br>
Splmash 	Chr-Lv6 	20<br>
OverCutter 	Chr-Lv6 	20</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img512.imageshack.us/img512/2886/chabigpicmagicianqv7.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Psykeeper</p>
<p>When you reach level 60 as a Magician, you will be able to job change into a Psykeeper.</p>
<p>As a Psykeeper, you can weaken the enemy by casting debuffing spells. Debuffing spells are weakening spells. Basically, Psykeeper is a support class, and is an asset to any party.</p>
<p>You will be a valuable member of any party due to the fact that your debuffing spells will enable the party to defeat the monster more easily.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Demonolgy 	Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Psychic Bomb 	Mental Strike Lv10, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Crucio Spell 	Mental Strike Lv10, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Satanolgy 	Demonolgy Lv3, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Sprit Bomb 	Psychic Bomb Lv6, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Maximum Crisis 	Crucio Spell Lv7, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Psychic Wall 	Satanolgy Lv4, Sprit Bomb Lv5, Chr-Lv 70 	10<br>
Psychic Square 	Psychic Wall Lv7, Maximum Crisis Lv5, Chr-Lv 75 	10</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img512.imageshack.us/img512/2024/chabigpicpsykeepermy8.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Elementer</p>
<p>When you reach level 60 as a Magician, you will be able to job change into an Elementer.</p>
<p>As an Elementer, you will probably be dealing out the most damage out of all the second job classes. However, you will have lower HP, and will most likely not be able to dodge many attacks.</p>
<p>You will be a valuable member of any party due to the sheer amount of damage you can do, taking out chunks of monsters’ HP.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Firebird 	Fire Strike Lv7, Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Stone Spear 	Looting Lv3, Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Void 	Windcutter Lv7, Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Thunder Strike 	Lightening Shock Lv7, Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Iceshark 	Spring water Lv7, Chr-Lv60 	10<br>
Burningfield 	Fire Bird Lv5, Chr-Lv65 	10<br>
Earthquake 	Stone Spear Lv4, Chr-Lv65 	10<br>
Windfield 	Void Lv5, Chr-Lv65 	10<br>
Eletric Shock 	Thunder Strike Lv4, Chr-Lv65 	10<br>
Poison Cloud 	Iceshark Lv5, Chr-Lv65 	10<br>
Fire Master 	Fire Strike Lv7, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Earth Master 	Looting Lv3, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Wind Master 	Wind Cutter Lv7, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Lighting Master 	Lightening Shock Lv7, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Water Master 	Spring water Lv7, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Meteo Shower 	Burningfield LV6, Earthquake Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Sandstorm 	Windfield Lv6, Earthquake Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Lightingstorm 	Windfield Lv6, Eletric Shock Lv5, Chr-Lv70 	10<br>
Avalanche 	Poison Cloud Lv7, earthquakeLv7, Chr-Lv75 	10</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img503.imageshack.us/img503/8283/chabigpicelementerle1.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Acrobat</p>
<p>You will be able to job change to an Acrobat from the Vagrant class at level 15.</p>
<p>The Acrobat class can go at two ways.</p>
<p>Acrobat, who uses mainly long distance attack, is a kind of many who always smile and act gentle. He believe with his speed and accuracy, he can break anybody who want to fight him.</p>
<p>Apparently, he looks very kind and nice person; however, due to the fact that his nature is assassin, he thinks every body can be enemy.</p>
<p>When you reach level 60, you will be able to change your job class to either Jester or Ran</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Pulling 	Chr-Lv15 	20<br>
Fast Walker 	Pulling Lv4, Chr-Lv18 	20<br>
Dark Illusion 	Fast Walker Lv5, Chr-Lv30 	20<br>
Perfect Block 	Dark Illusion Lv8, Chr-Lv45 	20<br>
Slow Step 	Chr-Lv15 	20<br>
YoYo Mastery 	Slow Step Lv3, Chr-Lv20 	20<br>
Cross Line 	YoYo Mastery Lv3, Chr-Lv30 	20<br>
Snitch 	YoYo Mastery 8, Chr-Lv35 	20<br>
Counter Attack 	Cross Line Lv10, Chr-Lv40 	20<br>
Deadly Swing 	Snitch Lv3, Chr-Lv50 	20<br>
Junk Arrow 	Chr-Lv15 	20<br>
Perfect Block 	Dark Illusion Lv8, Chr-Lv45 	20<br>
Bow Mastery 	Junk Arrow Lv5, Chr-Lv20 	20<br>
Silent Shot 	Bow Mastery Lv4, Chr-Lv30 	20<br>
Aimed Shot 	Bow Mastery Lv5, Chr-Lv35 	20<br>
Auto Shot 	Silent Shot Lv9, Chr-Lv45 	20<br>
Arrow Rain 	Aim Shot Lv5 Chr-Lv50 	20</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img111.imageshack.us/img111/2100/chabigpicacrobatxu7.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Jester</p>
<p>When you reach level 60 as a Acrobat, you will be able to job change into a Jester.</p>
<p>Jester, who has less defense power than attack power, is a derived from acrobat who uses yo-yo as a main weapon. He has a lot of useful skills who make jester more stronger like snatch and hiding.</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Enchant Poison 	Deadly Swing Lv4, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Enchant Blood 	Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Escape 	Perfect Block Lv6, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Critical Swing 	Enchant Poison Lv3, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Back Step 	Enchant Blood Lv3, Chr-Lv 70 	10<br>
Enchant Absorb 	Escape Lv3, Chr-Lv 70 	10<br>
Vatal Stab 	Critical Swing Lv4, Backstep Lv7, Chr-Lv 80 	10<br>
Hit of Penya 	Enchant Absorb Lv4, Chr-Lv 75 	10</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img111.imageshack.us/img111/3279/chabigpicjesterow1.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Ranger</p>
<p>When you reach level 60 as a Acrobat, you will be able to job change into a Ranger.</p>
<p>Ranger is a derived from acrobat who uses bow as a main weapon</p>
<p>Skills<br>
Icon 	Skill 	Requirement 	Mater Level<br>
Ice Arrow 	Auto Shot Lv4, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Flame Arrow 	Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Poison Arrow 	Arrow Rain Lv3, Chr-Lv 60 	10<br>
Fast Shot 	Ice Arrow Lv3, Chr-Lv 65 	10<br>
Piercing Arrow 	Flame Arrow Lv3, Chr-Lv 70 	10<br>
Nature 	Poison Arrow Lv4, Chr-Lv 70 	10<br>
Triple Shot 	Fast Shot Lv4, Piercing Lv7, Chr-Lv 80 	10<br>
Silent Shot 	Nature Lv4, Chr-Lv 75 	10</p>
<p><a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img399.imageshack.us/img399/7200/chabigpicrangerbq2.gif" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Thats about it =)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2007 02:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-93538-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flyff-fly-for-fun/93538.rss">FLYFF (Fly For Fun)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
