<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Problem, Help?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065</link>
    <description>Okay well, I&#39;ve been trying to change maximum players but I don&#39;t really know how. I went into server.java and changed maxconnections but I don&#39;t think it did anything. Then I tried changing that number above returncode = 7 but it just gave me a weird error. Anyone know what to do? Please post here I&#39;ll be checking it often. Does anyone have anything on how to get number of players online changed? I can only get 11 on and it says World Full.  :confused:

Also I have another problem. Sometimes when other people try to log on it says Error connecting to server when the server is up. I know because my friend hosts it and I am usually always in contact with him. Can&#39;t figure out why it says Error, when the server is clearly up.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 08:50:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Problem, Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lorenm lorenm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lorenm">@lorenm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>But I’m pretty sure I can change it because it has absolutely no lag at 11 players and the first day the server was up and on status page I had around 20 players on before it started to lag. Everyone mostly loved it, Idk what happened after that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 08:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136065-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065.rss">Problem, Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problem, Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aff Aff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aff">@Aff</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You can’t really change the max’ players. It depends on how fast your connection is, some sources support the “World is full” thing, and some just start to mass’ lag when the max players are on. So… Yeah.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 08:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136065-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065.rss">Problem, Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Problem, Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lorenm lorenm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lorenm">@lorenm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay well, I’ve been trying to change maximum players but I don’t really know how. I went into server.java and changed maxconnections but I don’t think it did anything. Then I tried changing that number above returncode = 7 but it just gave me a weird error. Anyone know what to do? Please post here I’ll be checking it often. Does anyone have anything on how to get number of players online changed? I can only get 11 on and it says World Full.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>Also I have another problem. Sometimes when other people try to log on it says Error connecting to server when the server is up. I know because my friend hosts it and I am usually always in contact with him. Can’t figure out why it says Error, when the server is clearly up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 08:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-136065-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/problem-help/136065.rss">Problem, Help?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
