<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server offline</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-offline/342854</link>
    <description>Hey guys, Ive been working on my server for quite a while now, and I got it running. My port is open, no-ip, portforwarded and everything. But there is a problem. Whenever I close my client stuff to play, the server is offline and my port cannot be seen by canyouseeme.org i get connectiong refused.
Is there any way to fix this problem? Becuz i wanna get my server running sooner or later. Oh and if you can&#39;t fix this, can anyone tell me how to make the owner never logout? even if he is afk. Cuz that way I will never logout and so will the players.

P.S 

I also wanted to know how people can login without the source folder, I mean when I login without open the &quot;run&quot; thing in my source folder, it doesn&#39;t let me in. So can anybody tell me how others can logon without opening the &quot;run&quot; thing in the source folder? rep+ if help :) come on this thread is dying!!!!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 21:24:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-offline/342854.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server offline</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@usman555 usman555]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/usman555">@usman555</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, Ive been working on my server for quite a while now, and I got it running. My port is open, no-ip, portforwarded and everything. But there is a problem. Whenever I close my client stuff to play, the server is offline and my port cannot be seen by <a href="http://canyouseeme.org" rel="nofollow noopener">canyouseeme.org</a> i get connectiong refused.<br>
Is there any way to fix this problem? Becuz i wanna get my server running sooner or later. Oh and if you can’t fix this, can anyone tell me how to make the owner never logout? even if he is afk. Cuz that way I will never logout and so will the players.</p>
<p>P.S</p>
<p>I also wanted to know how people can login without the source folder, I mean when I login without open the “run” thing in my source folder, it doesn’t let me in. So can anybody tell me how others can logon without opening the “run” thing in the source folder? rep+ if help <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> come on this thread is dying!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-offline/342854/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-offline/342854/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 21:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-342854-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-offline/342854.rss">Server offline</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
