<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Plzz help!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/plzz-help/272597</link>
    <description>Okay. I believe that i have done everything. First I downloaded a server source. Then, I downloaded &quot;No-ip.&quot; I made a host on the &quot;No-ip&quot; website. Next, I logged into my router and tried to port forward. I have a Netgear WGT624v3 Router. I went into the &quot;Port Forwarding/Port Triggering&quot; tab. Then I clicked add service. For the name, I put my server name. I kept it at &quot;TCP/UDP.&quot; For the starting port, I put 43594. For the ending one, I also put 43594. I put in an IP and then I clicked &quot;Apply.&quot; Next, I went into the source and changed The name, my rights, etc. I compiled it and clicked run server. The command prompt came up and it said, &quot;Starting up (My server name) on 0.0.0.0:43594...&quot; But nothing happened after that. Can anyone help me?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 22:47:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/plzz-help/272597.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Plzz help!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@twins twins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/twins">@twins</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>… there are tuts… read them!! good</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/plzz-help/272597/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/plzz-help/272597/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 22:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272597-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/plzz-help/272597.rss">Plzz help!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Plzz help!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bballguy36 Bballguy36]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bballguy36">@Bballguy36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay. I believe that i have done everything. First I downloaded a server source. Then, I downloaded “No-ip.” I made a host on the “No-ip” website. Next, I logged into my router and tried to port forward. I have a Netgear WGT624v3 Router. I went into the “Port Forwarding/Port Triggering” tab. Then I clicked add service. For the name, I put my server name. I kept it at “TCP/UDP.” For the starting port, I put 43594. For the ending one, I also put 43594. I put in an IP and then I clicked “Apply.” Next, I went into the source and changed The name, my rights, etc. I compiled it and clicked run server. The command prompt came up and it said, “Starting up (My server name) on 0.0.0.0:43594…” But nothing happened after that. Can anyone help me?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/plzz-help/272597/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/plzz-help/272597/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 22:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-272597-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/plzz-help/272597.rss">Plzz help!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
