<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cracking Skyward Family Access</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cracking-skyward-family-access/233408</link>
    <description>Skyward Family Access is an online program created by [url=http://skyward.com]Skyward[/url] in hopes of creating a greater link between schools/education, kids, and their families.

Many examples of this online program could be found here (click on any of the million links):
http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;client=firefox-a&amp;channel=s&amp;rls=org.mozilla%3Aen-GB%3Aofficial&amp;hs=XMk&amp;q=Skyward+Family+Access&amp;btnG=Search

My school personally uses it. The thing is, I&#39;ve got a strong hunch the password is generated by the username. At my school, the username is unique for each person (based off of their name) and suffixed with a three-digit number. The name part is eight characters long, which is a characteristic the password has in common. 

The thing is, I want to try and figure out how the password is generated (that&#39;s assuming, of course, IF that&#39;s even true). Skyward MAY provide a default generator for all passwords, and if so, I&#39;d like to crack it. This is most likely false, however, and I know that. But it&#39;s worth a shot. Remember, this is just for fun as I thought of it not too long ago.

So if you&#39;re school uses it, how is your username for the login set up? How long is your password? Do you see any similarities? If you want, can you provide the credentials so I have a database of them to use and compare?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2008 02:25:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cracking-skyward-family-access/233408.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cracking Skyward Family Access</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TeleNubby TeleNubby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/telenubby">@TeleNubby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Skyward Family Access is an online program created by <a href="http://skyward.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Skyward</a> in hopes of creating a greater link between schools/education, kids, and their families.</p>
<p>Many examples of this online program could be found here (click on any of the million links):<br>
<a href="http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;client=firefox-a&amp;channel=s&amp;rls=org.mozilla%3Aen-GB%3Aofficial&amp;hs=XMk&amp;q=Skyward+Family+Access&amp;btnG=Search" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;client=firefox-a&amp;channel=s&amp;rls=org.mozilla%3Aen-GB%3Aofficial&amp;hs=XMk&amp;q=Skyward+Family+Access&amp;btnG=Search</a></p>
<p>My school personally uses it. The thing is, I’ve got a strong hunch the password is generated by the username. At my school, the username is unique for each person (based off of their name) and suffixed with a three-digit number. The name part is eight characters long, which is a characteristic the password has in common.</p>
<p>The thing is, I want to try and figure out how the password is generated (that’s assuming, of course, IF that’s even true). Skyward MAY provide a default generator for all passwords, and if so, I’d like to crack it. This is most likely false, however, and I know that. But it’s worth a shot. Remember, this is just for fun as I thought of it not too long ago.</p>
<p>So if you’re school uses it, how is your username for the login set up? How long is your password? Do you see any similarities? If you want, can you provide the credentials so I have a database of them to use and compare?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cracking-skyward-family-access/233408/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cracking-skyward-family-access/233408/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2008 02:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-233408-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cracking-skyward-family-access/233408.rss">Cracking Skyward Family Access</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
