<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help with something?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-something/470511</link>
    <description>Been looking for a long time and now I&#39;ve found a good looking source and client for starting to develop my own 2006 remake.

I&#39;m using this source and client http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,587965.0.html and feel free to check it out.

He mentions to remove the &quot;anti-leech&quot; you need to do some things which I don&#39;t exactly understand. He says the following &quot;As always, I&#39;ve added an couple of &quot;anti-leeches&quot; and if you&#39;re not capable of fixing them, you should probably consider taking up knitting. All is required of you is to uncomment stuff. One of the anti-leeches is in Constants.java, one if Food.java and one (which stops you compiling) is in UpdateFlags.java&quot;.

I don&#39;t really understand what I have to do for this, if somebody could help me out I would find it very helpful.

Thank-you for the help in advance.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 20:52:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-something/470511.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help with something?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@M0R3TANK1NG M0R3TANK1NG]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m0r3tank1ng">@M0R3TANK1NG</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Been looking for a long time and now I’ve found a good looking source and client for starting to develop my own 2006 remake.</p>
<p>I’m using this source and client <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,587965.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,587965.0.html</a> and feel free to check it out.</p>
<p>He mentions to remove the “anti-leech” you need to do some things which I don’t exactly understand. He says the following “As always, I’ve added an couple of “anti-leeches” and if you’re not capable of fixing them, you should probably consider taking up knitting. All is required of you is to uncomment stuff. One of the anti-leeches is in Constants.java, one if Food.java and one (which stops you compiling) is in UpdateFlags.java”.</p>
<p>I don’t really understand what I have to do for this, if somebody could help me out I would find it very helpful.</p>
<p>Thank-you for the help in advance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-something/470511/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-something/470511/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 20:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470511-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-something/470511.rss">Help with something?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
