<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Adding Interfaces Server Side?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-interfaces-server-side/481133</link>
    <description>Hello, I have made an interface to help me with debugging and logging errors and have packaged it in my cache. I can load the interface correctly in game but I cannot interact with it. I am using a RuneSource base and i believe there is packet checking that works with the cache that is stored server sided. Anyway, I added the &quot;AtActionType&quot; as 1 so I [i]should[/i] be able to click the interface, and when I load the interface I do have the ability to click the button. In ButtonPacketHandler, I have my server&#39;s debug mode on and I have it to print out what has been clicked and all the interfaces send the packet ID but when i click the buttons on my interface nothing happens, and the cases i have added do not work. So I tried to add the interface to the cache server side but still nothing. I am more than sure this is server sided so that&#39;s why I posted this in this section. Thank you :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 19:49:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-interfaces-server-side/481133.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Adding Interfaces Server Side?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ProTayToe ProTayToe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protaytoe">@ProTayToe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I have made an interface to help me with debugging and logging errors and have packaged it in my cache. I can load the interface correctly in game but I cannot interact with it. I am using a RuneSource base and i believe there is packet checking that works with the cache that is stored server sided. Anyway, I added the “AtActionType” as 1 so I <span class="bbcode-i">should</span> be able to click the interface, and when I load the interface I do have the ability to click the button. In ButtonPacketHandler, I have my server’s debug mode on and I have it to print out what has been clicked and all the interfaces send the packet ID but when i click the buttons on my interface nothing happens, and the cases i have added do not work. So I tried to add the interface to the cache server side but still nothing. I am more than sure this is server sided so that’s why I posted this in this section. Thank you <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-interfaces-server-side/481133/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-interfaces-server-side/481133/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 19:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-481133-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-interfaces-server-side/481133.rss">Adding Interfaces Server Side?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
