<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RevoScape / An Idea hoping to Blossom</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revoscape-an-idea-hoping-to-blossom/456362</link>
    <description>[CENTER][IMG]http://i50.tinypic.com/13z6fr7.jpg[/img][/CENTER]

Alright let&#39;s get down to business.
I have been programming delta&#39;s for about 10 months on and off, learning things and applying them. One thing I was always afraid to mount was Project Insanity. I started on Delta, and if you can remember your first time opening up notepad and having a go(now I use notepad++) you realize it is hard to tackle, the lines confuse you, but you look up tuts and start to understand things and get a grasp on what to do.

So I have had a few servers, all delta, none successful. Mostly due to the fact that I was using a Delta, I know Pi&#39;s are still unfavored by a lot of people but still it is a step up from Delta. So as I make this post I have little info on how to work with a Pi except for some things. I know they are both 317 and that they both will use the same lines of code, but the names of the folders and the organization is what puts me off. So I am going to suck it up and just power through this.

I want RevoScape to be server that stays up for a long time and has players who stick around, with a live forum community as well. I am not going to ask for people to help program with me, because more than likely they will do all the big things while I do the small things. So what I need is people who I can add who are experts in Pi&#39;s and 317&#39;s to help guide me and give me advice or help if I need it. Because you can&#39;t google everything.

I know this may seem like I am asking for a group of people to tell me what to do and pretty much me not do any work. But I want people who can teach me not tell me. I just got a cleaned Pi base with a client loading 525.

I will update this topic with screenshots of my progress, and a list of my accomplishments. 

So please if you wish to be a kind person then add me on skype, [B]TikeDesigns[/B]

Thank you and once again I appreciate any good lucks below or words of encouragement because remember, once upon a time you were in the spot I am in :).

I will also have a forums up soon which will also follow my progress or if you want to lend a hand there. 

[B]Hosting Polls on the forums![/B] I Need your votes for decisions! [url=http://www.revoscape.smfnew.com/index.php]Forums Link[/url]

[b]Currently Added[/b]
602 Animations
602 Models
634 Weapons

Thank you.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 03:42:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revoscape-an-idea-hoping-to-blossom/456362.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RevoScape / An Idea hoping to Blossom</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@texiz texiz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/texiz">@texiz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[CENTER]<img src="http://i50.tinypic.com/13z6fr7.jpg" alt width="400" height="90">[/CENTER]</p>
<p>Alright let’s get down to business.<br>
I have been programming delta’s for about 10 months on and off, learning things and applying them. One thing I was always afraid to mount was Project Insanity. I started on Delta, and if you can remember your first time opening up notepad and having a go(now I use notepad++) you realize it is hard to tackle, the lines confuse you, but you look up tuts and start to understand things and get a grasp on what to do.</p>
<p>So I have had a few servers, all delta, none successful. Mostly due to the fact that I was using a Delta, I know Pi’s are still unfavored by a lot of people but still it is a step up from Delta. So as I make this post I have little info on how to work with a Pi except for some things. I know they are both 317 and that they both will use the same lines of code, but the names of the folders and the organization is what puts me off. So I am going to suck it up and just power through this.</p>
<p>I want RevoScape to be server that stays up for a long time and has players who stick around, with a live forum community as well. I am not going to ask for people to help program with me, because more than likely they will do all the big things while I do the small things. So what I need is people who I can add who are experts in Pi’s and 317’s to help guide me and give me advice or help if I need it. Because you can’t google everything.</p>
<p>I know this may seem like I am asking for a group of people to tell me what to do and pretty much me not do any work. But I want people who can teach me not tell me. I just got a cleaned Pi base with a client loading 525.</p>
<p>I will update this topic with screenshots of my progress, and a list of my accomplishments.</p>
<p>So please if you wish to be a kind person then add me on skype, <span class="bbcode-b">TikeDesigns</span></p>
<p>Thank you and once again I appreciate any good lucks below or words of encouragement because remember, once upon a time you were in the spot I am in :).</p>
<p>I will also have a forums up soon which will also follow my progress or if you want to lend a hand there.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Hosting Polls on the forums!</span> I Need your votes for decisions! <a href="http://www.revoscape.smfnew.com/index.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Forums Link</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Currently Added</span><br>
602 Animations<br>
602 Models<br>
634 Weapons</p>
<p>Thank you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revoscape-an-idea-hoping-to-blossom/456362/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revoscape-an-idea-hoping-to-blossom/456362/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 03:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456362-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revoscape-an-idea-hoping-to-blossom/456362.rss">RevoScape / An Idea hoping to Blossom</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
