<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082</link>
    <description>Well, my old version of this is a little out of date and isn&#39;t really configured in a way that would make updating easy. So I re-did it, added some pictures, and tried to make things clearer. Hopefully it worked :D

A WAMP server is what you would use to run php and the like on windows. It stands for Windows Apache MySQL PHP. Windows is the operating system, apache is the actual server, MySQL is the database, and PHP is the language. It can mimic an online server so you can develope your own PHP scripts on your computer wihtout having to go through the hassel of FTPing the files back and forth just to edit them for every little thing. Have fun! 


Phase 1: Installing Apache

Apache is the the actual web server that we will be installing PHP and MySQL in to. It&#39;s free, easy, and simple to set up. Here&#39;s how to set it up:

- Go to apache.org
- Navigate to and download the windows installer for the latest version of apache 2.0.x
[img]http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/1-apacheInstaller.jpg[/img]
- Save this to a folder called MIS in the C directory
- Run the file and set up the server
- Agree to the terms
- Although it doesn&#39;t really matter, set up the domain and such to look like this:
[img]http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/2-InstallApache1.jpg[/img]
- Use the default settings for the rest and finish the installation

Phase 2: Installing php

PHP is the language used in the WAMP server. It could be used as a stand alone language, but it rather useless wihtout HTML. However, it ables the developer to create functionaly websites, for example with logins. It is the most complicated portion to set up.

- Go to php.net
- Navigate to and download the Windows zip package for the latest version of PHP 5.0.x (not the installer)
- Extract all those files to the directory &quot;C:/php/&quot;

Now, we need to add this folder to the PATH system variable:

- Go to control panel
- Double click on System icon
- Open up the advanced tab
- Click the environmental variables button
- Find the Path variable in the System Variables Tab
- Click edit
- Add &quot;;C:\php\&quot; to the end of the string
- Click OK
- Restart your computer for it to take effect

Here&#39;s a little graphic that will hopefully help you see what you need to do:
[img]http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/3-environvar.jpg[/img]

Now we need to configure PHP:

- Go to the C:/php directory
- Rename php.ini-recomended to php.ini and open it
- Search for 
[code]doc_root =[/code]
- Change that to 
[code]doc_root = C:\Program Files\Apache Group\Apache2\htdocs[/code]

I&#39;ll go through a bit more of this configuration at the end. Right now we just want to get it up and make sure it is running correctly. Now we need to make PHP run through Apache:

- Open C:\Program Files\Apache Group\Apache2\conf\Httpd.conf
- Add these lines of code to the end of the file:
[code]LoadModule php5_module &quot;c:/php/php5apache2.dll&quot;
AddType application/x-httpd-php .php
PHPIniDir &quot;C:/php/&quot;[/code]


Phase 3: Installing MySQL

MySQL is one of the most common free databases out there. It works great and isn&#39;t that hard to set up:

- Go to mysql.com
- Navigate to and download the Windows (x86) file for MySQL 5.0.x to the MIS folder
- Extract and install
- Agree to go ahead and configure MySQL
- Do the detailed configuration and press next
- Select developer machine and press next
- Select multifunctional database and press next
- Set the store path to &quot;C:\MySQL InnoDB Datafiles\&quot; and press next
- Select Decision Support and press next
- Make sure both options are selected and press next
- Select Standard Character Set and press next
- Select both options and press next
- Enter your root password and press next
- Select execute and let it configure the database

Now that MySQL is installed, we need to configure php and Apache to be able to use it:

- Open up php.ini again (in the C:/php/ folder)
- Search for
[code];extension=php_mysql.dll[/code]
- Change that to
[code]extension=php_mysql.dll[/code]
- Search for
[code]extension_dir = &quot;./&quot;[/code]
- Change that to
[code]extension_dir = &quot;C:/php/ext/&quot;[/code]
- Copy the following files to the system32 directory (C:\WINDOWS\system32\) 
* C:\php\libmysql.dll 
- Restart the apache server

Now that you have done this, your WAMP server should be up and running. Now we&#39;ll have to test it. All the php files are stored in the C:\Program Files\Apache Group\Apache2\htdocs directory, so it may be easier to make a shortcut to that folder instead of navigating there every time. Go to that directory and delete all the files in it (we won&#39;t need them anymore). Now create a new php file (it doesn&#39;t matter what you name it, but I&#39;ll name mine phptest.php). Put this code in there:

[code]&lt;? phpinfo(); ?&gt;[/code]

This will give all the inormation about your php configuarion from the php.ini file and some installed extensions. Now open a webbrowser and open the file through it (localhost/phptest.php if you used the same name as mine). You should see a page that looks like this:

[img]http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/4-phptest1.jpg[/img]

Now, scroll down and hopefully you should see a section titled &quot;mysql&quot; that looks similar to this:

[img]http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/5-phptest2.jpg[/img]

If you have both of these, then you are ready to go. If not, see if there is an easy fix and if not, uninstall everything, manually delete the folders they were installed to (especially for MySQL), and try again.

Now that everything is installed and ready, we&#39;re going to start making this an easier to use developement server. First of all, we&#39;re going to get a utility that will make the maintainance of the MySQL databases much easier. It is called MySQL Administrator. Basically, go to mysql.com, find it, download it, and install it. When you run it the first time, here is what you should put in the fields (with the dots as the root password that you set when you installed MySQL):

[img]http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/6-mysqladmin.jpg[/img]

Everything is pretty self explanatory after that with the program.

Now we&#39;ll go throught he php.ini file a little bit and see if we can customize it better for developement. First open the file (C:/php/php.ini). There are only a few things you&#39;ll need to worry about and I&#39;ll go through them:

Do a search for &quot;Resource Limits&quot;. That section is where you can set the maximum execution times. It is useful if you are creating files that will take a LONG time to run (ie, brute forcers or password checkers). The default of 30 seconds is plenty of time for the normal file though.

Scrolling down a little bit to &quot;error handling and logging&quot;. This is where we can choose which and if we display runtime errors. With this turned off, PHP will just return a blank page if it hits an error (which is a HUGE pain in the butt if you are trying to debug a long file). Scroll down to where you actually set the level of errors it displays (the first line without a semicolon). I&#39;d suggest leaving it where it is, but if you want, read through the different types of errors it can display and customize it a little. Now we want PHP to print the errors that it hits. Scroll down a few lines until you see &quot;display_errors = Off&quot;. Just change that to &quot;display_errors = On&quot;.

One more thing you may want to set up in this file is the ability to use the mail() function. Do a search for &quot;Module Settings&quot;. Just below it is the options for the mail function. Fill in your information (this is assuming you have an SMTP port to send mail from. If you don&#39;t, don&#39;t worry about this part, but you can&#39;t send mail).

Those few things are all you really need to worry about in this file unless you want some crazy customization (in which case I can&#39;t really help you that much). Just restart the Apache server and you should be ready to go. It is a good idea to check the phpinfo.php file once more after restarting the server to make sure your changes took effect before deleting it.

[i]Notes about this tutorial:

This uses slightly out-of-date versions of PHP and Apache. They both have newer versions, but for the life of me, I couldn&#39;t figure out why they wouldn&#39;t configure together. Apache 2.2.x doesn&#39;t have a &quot;released&quot; version of PHP to go with it yet, but some people have managed to use the php5apache2.2.dll to get it configured. I tried and failed... miserably. Also, with Apache 2.0.x, I couldn&#39;t get PHP 5.1.x to configure properly. Everything was set up correctly, but for some reason, the php.ini file was creating an error, causing PHP to just ignore the PHP code and not process it. If anyone can figure out why eiher things are happening or has suggestions on how to fix them, I&#39;ll gladly try and update this tutorial if it works. There are the exact versions of each product used in this tutorial:

Apache 2.0.59
PHP 5.0.5
MySQL 5.0.24[/i]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2007 08:25:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@samcanbam samcanbam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/samcanbam">@samcanbam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thank you so much! ive been looking for this forever. my dad said to use tomcat, but it sucked. so thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2007 08:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-9082-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082.rss">[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bang_Train Bang Train]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bang_train">@Bang_Train</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If u create a thing such as world switcher and u wanna make it open source u use that for easy reading</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2006 18:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-9082-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082.rss">[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BobDole81 BobDole81]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobdole81">@BobDole81</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That line by sppt basically just allows for syntax colorization of php source files (.phps) in the browser…its just for viewing and personally I don’t see much practical (non-development related) use, but its nice to have on a personal server <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2006 03:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-9082-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082.rss">[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@surfer247 surfer247]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/surfer247">@surfer247</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m pretty sure I read that that enables the color highlighting of the php, but I’m not sure how that actually works. I just downloaded and IDE for web languages and it color-codes everything nicely. How does that one work (or am I totally off on this)?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2006 02:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-9082-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082.rss">[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sppt sppt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sppt">@sppt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>also, i think its quite nice to have these lines in httpd.conf:</p>
<blockquote>AddType application/x-httpd-php-source .phps</blockquote> 
;)
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 21:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-9082-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082.rss">[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bang_Train Bang Train]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bang_train">@Bang_Train</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.wampserver.net" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">www.wampserver.net</a></p>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 19:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-9082-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082.rss">[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@surfer247 surfer247]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/surfer247">@surfer247</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, my old version of this is a little out of date and isn’t really configured in a way that would make updating easy. So I re-did it, added some pictures, and tried to make things clearer. Hopefully it worked <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>A WAMP server is what you would use to run php and the like on windows. It stands for Windows Apache MySQL PHP. Windows is the operating system, apache is the actual server, MySQL is the database, and PHP is the language. It can mimic an online server so you can develope your own PHP scripts on your computer wihtout having to go through the hassel of FTPing the files back and forth just to edit them for every little thing. Have fun!</p>
<p>Phase 1: Installing Apache</p>
<p>Apache is the the actual web server that we will be installing PHP and MySQL in to. It’s free, easy, and simple to set up. Here’s how to set it up:</p>
<ul>
<li>Go to <a href="http://apache.org" rel="nofollow noopener">apache.org</a>
</li>
<li>Navigate to and download the windows installer for the latest version of apache 2.0.x<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/1-apacheInstaller.jpg" title="1-apacheInstaller.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/1-apacheInstaller.jpg" alt width="690" height="286"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">1-apacheInstaller.jpg</span><span class="informations">714×296</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div>
</li>
<li>Save this to a folder called MIS in the C directory</li>
<li>Run the file and set up the server</li>
<li>Agree to the terms</li>
<li>Although it doesn’t really matter, set up the domain and such to look like this:<br>
<img src="http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/2-InstallApache1.jpg" alt width="505" height="388">
</li>
<li>Use the default settings for the rest and finish the installation</li>
</ul>
<p>Phase 2: Installing php</p>
<p>PHP is the language used in the WAMP server. It could be used as a stand alone language, but it rather useless wihtout HTML. However, it ables the developer to create functionaly websites, for example with logins. It is the most complicated portion to set up.</p>
<ul>
<li>Go to <a href="http://php.net" rel="nofollow noopener">php.net</a>
</li>
<li>Navigate to and download the Windows zip package for the latest version of PHP 5.0.x (not the installer)</li>
<li>Extract all those files to the directory “C:/php/”</li>
</ul>
<p>Now, we need to add this folder to the PATH system variable:</p>
<ul>
<li>Go to control panel</li>
<li>Double click on System icon</li>
<li>Open up the advanced tab</li>
<li>Click the environmental variables button</li>
<li>Find the Path variable in the System Variables Tab</li>
<li>Click edit</li>
<li>Add “;C:\php” to the end of the string</li>
<li>Click OK</li>
<li>Restart your computer for it to take effect</li>
</ul>
<p>Here’s a little graphic that will hopefully help you see what you need to do:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/3-environvar.jpg" title="3-environvar.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/3-environvar.jpg" alt width="690" height="495"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">3-environvar.jpg</span><span class="informations">801×575</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Now we need to configure PHP:</p>
<ul>
<li>Go to the C:/php directory</li>
<li>Rename php.ini-recomended to php.ini and open it</li>
<li>Search for</li>
</ul>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">doc_root =</code></pre>
<ul>
<li>Change that to</li>
</ul>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">doc_root = C:\Program Files\Apache Group\Apache2\htdocs</code></pre>
<p>I’ll go through a bit more of this configuration at the end. Right now we just want to get it up and make sure it is running correctly. Now we need to make PHP run through Apache:</p>
<ul>
<li>Open C:\Program Files\Apache Group\Apache2\conf\Httpd.conf</li>
<li>Add these lines of code to the end of the file:</li>
</ul>
<p><code>LoadModule php5_module "c:/php/php5apache2.dll"
AddType application/x-httpd-php .php
PHPIniDir "C:/php/"</code></p>
<p>Phase 3: Installing MySQL</p>
<p>MySQL is one of the most common free databases out there. It works great and isn’t that hard to set up:</p>
<ul>
<li>Go to <a href="http://mysql.com" rel="nofollow noopener">mysql.com</a>
</li>
<li>Navigate to and download the Windows (x86) file for MySQL 5.0.x to the MIS folder</li>
<li>Extract and install</li>
<li>Agree to go ahead and configure MySQL</li>
<li>Do the detailed configuration and press next</li>
<li>Select developer machine and press next</li>
<li>Select multifunctional database and press next</li>
<li>Set the store path to “C:\MySQL InnoDB Datafiles” and press next</li>
<li>Select Decision Support and press next</li>
<li>Make sure both options are selected and press next</li>
<li>Select Standard Character Set and press next</li>
<li>Select both options and press next</li>
<li>Enter your root password and press next</li>
<li>Select execute and let it configure the database</li>
</ul>
<p>Now that MySQL is installed, we need to configure php and Apache to be able to use it:</p>
<ul>
<li>Open up php.ini again (in the C:/php/ folder)</li>
<li>Search for</li>
</ul>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">;extension=php_mysql.dll</code></pre>
<ul>
<li>Change that to</li>
</ul>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">extension=php_mysql.dll</code></pre>
<ul>
<li>Search for</li>
</ul>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">extension_dir = "./"</code></pre>
<ul>
<li>Change that to</li>
</ul>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">extension_dir = "C:/php/ext/"</code></pre>
<ul>
<li>Copy the following files to the system32 directory (C:\WINDOWS\system32)</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>C:\php\libmysql.dll</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Restart the apache server</li>
</ul>
<p>Now that you have done this, your WAMP server should be up and running. Now we’ll have to test it. All the php files are stored in the C:\Program Files\Apache Group\Apache2\htdocs directory, so it may be easier to make a shortcut to that folder instead of navigating there every time. Go to that directory and delete all the files in it (we won’t need them anymore). Now create a new php file (it doesn’t matter what you name it, but I’ll name mine phptest.php). Put this code in there:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;? phpinfo(); ?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This will give all the inormation about your php configuarion from the php.ini file and some installed extensions. Now open a webbrowser and open the file through it (localhost/phptest.php if you used the same name as mine). You should see a page that looks like this:</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/4-phptest1.jpg" title="4-phptest1.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/4-phptest1.jpg" alt width="531" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">4-phptest1.jpg</span><span class="informations">618×581</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Now, scroll down and hopefully you should see a section titled “mysql” that looks similar to this:</p>
<p><img src="http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/5-phptest2.jpg" alt width="625" height="416"></p>
<p>If you have both of these, then you are ready to go. If not, see if there is an easy fix and if not, uninstall everything, manually delete the folders they were installed to (especially for MySQL), and try again.</p>
<p>Now that everything is installed and ready, we’re going to start making this an easier to use developement server. First of all, we’re going to get a utility that will make the maintainance of the MySQL databases much easier. It is called MySQL Administrator. Basically, go to <a href="http://mysql.com" rel="nofollow noopener">mysql.com</a>, find it, download it, and install it. When you run it the first time, here is what you should put in the fields (with the dots as the root password that you set when you installed MySQL):</p>
<p><img src="http://i103.photobucket.com/albums/m138/wamptutorial/6-mysqladmin.jpg" alt width="423" height="329"></p>
<p>Everything is pretty self explanatory after that with the program.</p>
<p>Now we’ll go throught he php.ini file a little bit and see if we can customize it better for developement. First open the file (C:/php/php.ini). There are only a few things you’ll need to worry about and I’ll go through them:</p>
<p>Do a search for “Resource Limits”. That section is where you can set the maximum execution times. It is useful if you are creating files that will take a LONG time to run (ie, brute forcers or password checkers). The default of 30 seconds is plenty of time for the normal file though.</p>
<p>Scrolling down a little bit to “error handling and logging”. This is where we can choose which and if we display runtime errors. With this turned off, PHP will just return a blank page if it hits an error (which is a HUGE pain in the butt if you are trying to debug a long file). Scroll down to where you actually set the level of errors it displays (the first line without a semicolon). I’d suggest leaving it where it is, but if you want, read through the different types of errors it can display and customize it a little. Now we want PHP to print the errors that it hits. Scroll down a few lines until you see “display_errors = Off”. Just change that to “display_errors = On”.</p>
<p>One more thing you may want to set up in this file is the ability to use the mail() function. Do a search for “Module Settings”. Just below it is the options for the mail function. Fill in your information (this is assuming you have an SMTP port to send mail from. If you don’t, don’t worry about this part, but you can’t send mail).</p>
<p>Those few things are all you really need to worry about in this file unless you want some crazy customization (in which case I can’t really help you that much). Just restart the Apache server and you should be ready to go. It is a good idea to check the phpinfo.php file once more after restarting the server to make sure your changes took effect before deleting it.</p>
<p>[i]Notes about this tutorial:</p>
<p>This uses slightly out-of-date versions of PHP and Apache. They both have newer versions, but for the life of me, I couldn’t figure out why they wouldn’t configure together. Apache 2.2.x doesn’t have a “released” version of PHP to go with it yet, but some people have managed to use the php5apache2.2.dll to get it configured. I tried and failed… miserably. Also, with Apache 2.0.x, I couldn’t get PHP 5.1.x to configure properly. Everything was set up correctly, but for some reason, the php.ini file was creating an error, causing PHP to just ignore the PHP code and not process it. If anyone can figure out why eiher things are happening or has suggestions on how to fix them, I’ll gladly try and update this tutorial if it works. There are the exact versions of each product used in this tutorial:</p>
<p>Apache 2.0.59<br>
PHP 5.0.5<br>
MySQL 5.0.24[/i]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 00:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-9082-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-setting-up-a-wamp-server/9082.rss">[php] Setting Up A WAMP Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
