<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Arrows -- #5 -- (Topic got spammed)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arrows-5-topic-got-spammed/141097</link>
    <description>Okay, recently ive been working/testing alot, with my range stuff.. And this one has been a problem ({Which i can&#39;t fix}) for like ages... When i shoot someone with any bow? And there are alot of people around me, the arrow some times tends to go to a different player... Just shoots any random way every time... Is there a way to make the arrow LOCK ON to the target, only hit the target your shooting? By target, i mean enemy... NOT NPC... I couldn&#39;t care a less atm.. I just want player V player fixed for start.

If you do know the answer, could you please post? And please.. Im asking, no posts like &quot;You have to add (EXAMPLE)&quot;

Cause i&#39;ll be like, uhmm, ok? wtf...

P.S -- Helpful posts only please, if your going to be a jerk and post just to get your post count up, like &quot;Oo i need this too&quot;
&quot;Yeah ive been wondering how, if you find out, post success&quot;
&quot;Wrong section&quot;
&quot;HAHAHAAH NOOB&quot;
... Dont post at all...
[size=25pt]DONT SPAM THIS TOPIC! OMG[/size]

Appreciated, thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2007 01:39:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arrows-5-topic-got-spammed/141097.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Arrows -- #5 -- (Topic got spammed)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@X-J-K-X X-J-K-X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x-j-k-x">@X-J-K-X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, recently ive been working/testing alot, with my range stuff… And this one has been a problem ({Which i can’t fix}) for like ages… When i shoot someone with any bow? And there are alot of people around me, the arrow some times tends to go to a different player… Just shoots any random way every time… Is there a way to make the arrow LOCK ON to the target, only hit the target your shooting? By target, i mean enemy… NOT NPC… I couldn’t care a less atm… I just want player V player fixed for start.</p>
<p>If you do know the answer, could you please post? And please… Im asking, no posts like “You have to add (EXAMPLE)”</p>
<p>Cause i’ll be like, uhmm, ok? wtf…</p>
<p>P.S – Helpful posts only please, if your going to be a jerk and post just to get your post count up, like “Oo i need this too”<br>
“Yeah ive been wondering how, if you find out, post success”<br>
“Wrong section”<br>
“HAHAHAAH NOOB”<br>
… Dont post at all…<br>
[size=25pt]DONT SPAM THIS TOPIC! OMG[/size]</p>
<p>Appreciated, thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arrows-5-topic-got-spammed/141097/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arrows-5-topic-got-spammed/141097/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2007 01:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-141097-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/arrows-5-topic-got-spammed/141097.rss">Arrows -- #5 -- (Topic got spammed)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
