<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sigh...X.x Anyone got a solution to this?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-x-x-anyone-got-a-solution-to-this/236487</link>
    <description>Ok people say it&#39;s my source it&#39;s not... I tried another source it doesn&#39;t work... So don&#39;t tell me it&#39;s my server unless you got proof and you can fix it...

Ok this is what&#39;s up.. Whenever I do the ::bank command OR open up a shop manually it will d/c and then log me back in... This needs to be fixed... Also as i&#39;ve seen in freescapepkz when you change you&#39;re character in the ::char command and log out and back in it would of saved you&#39;re character.. As of my server that does not happen.. So if someone could give me a solution to these.

If it&#39;s command issues and It&#39;s coded wrong please post below a little tut with you&#39;re code and how to add it and how many parts etc... Please help me quick with this I can&#39;t release my server possibly source (would be a great one) 

Thanks SO MUCH,

Check my sig</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 19:07:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-x-x-anyone-got-a-solution-to-this/236487.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sigh...X.x Anyone got a solution to this?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cloud7Strife Cloud7Strife]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cloud7strife">@Cloud7Strife</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok people say it’s my source it’s not… I tried another source it doesn’t work… So don’t tell me it’s my server unless you got proof and you can fix it…</p>
<p>Ok this is what’s up… Whenever I do the ::bank command OR open up a shop manually it will d/c and then log me back in… This needs to be fixed… Also as i’ve seen in freescapepkz when you change you’re character in the ::char command and log out and back in it would of saved you’re character… As of my server that does not happen… So if someone could give me a solution to these.</p>
<p>If it’s command issues and It’s coded wrong please post below a little tut with you’re code and how to add it and how many parts etc… Please help me quick with this I can’t release my server possibly source (would be a great one)</p>
<p>Thanks SO MUCH,</p>
<p>Check my sig</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-x-x-anyone-got-a-solution-to-this/236487/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-x-x-anyone-got-a-solution-to-this/236487/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 19:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236487-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sigh-x-x-anyone-got-a-solution-to-this/236487.rss">Sigh...X.x Anyone got a solution to this?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
