<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478</link>
    <description>Hello, I&#39;m Cloudnine. I&#39;m going to explain to you how to get many players for your server.

Before you comment, &quot;They already have this guide n00b!&quot; You need to understand that not everyone&#39;s guide will be the same and that people should learn from more than just one person&#39;s experiences.

1. You should try to avoid hamachi.

2. Use rs-ps and you can pay like $1 for them to redirect people to your webclient. Someone told me if you pay like $10 they&#39;ll add a custom webclient or something like that, not sure if it&#39;s true but worth looking into.

3. Lots and lots of Youtube videos!  My server has 12 videos from me and other videos from my players. YouTube has a lot more people than any toplist combined, it will get you a lot of people.

4. Obviously, toplists. Many many toplists. I have my server on around 7. These are the ones I use:

rsps
http://www.mmorpgtoplist.com/
http://www.ultimateprivateservers.com/
http://www.gtop100.com/
http://www.gamesites100.net/
http://www.xtremetop100.com/

5. You need to make your server look attractive on the top lists.
Ex:
&quot;[YourServersLinkHere!!!]24/7 Webclient Updates &amp; events No lag/rollbacks 525 graphics Good economy &amp; rates Nice staff Active Community&quot;

That&#39;s just an example. I use it for my server on rlocus. Remember, always put your link as the first thing on your servers description. They will see it and automatically think to go to that URL.

6. Make your server look attractive on the YouTube videos. You need to show some combat on every video. Describe your server in depth! Put the link first in description. Describe your server in depth in the video as well. Have a video done with every skill, every mini-game, every boss, all pking zones, fun-pk, webclient mode, special features, home area, and stuff like that. Add some HIT music that A LOT of people like. Just look up a top music list for the previous month of your year. Check out my youtube videos if you want some examples, but don&#39;t you dare advertise on my comments. http://www.youtube.com/belhelmiel

7. Play around on other servers and look for ideas.

8. Do promotions. E.g. 2x rates for the first month of opening! Or something like 2x starter for the first few weeks! Etc.

9. Rs-ps chat room! Best place to advertise. Say something like... &quot;Looking for a good server? Click my house or PC me. :)&quot;

10. Do partnerships with new RSPS toplists. &quot;I&#39;ll advertise you if you advertise me ;) ;)&quot; kind of deal.

11. Do partnerships with other RSPS that suck. Make sure they suck though, that way your players don&#39;t leave your server for their server.

12. Look for servers that may be shutting down soon, or inconsistent up time. Those tend to go down forever and if you talk to the owner and just let him/her know about your server, but stay on their good side, they may say &quot;Server is offline atm try out [YourRSPSHere].&quot; Someone did that for me before when their server went offline, thats how I got 10+ players within the first few days of my server being up and I got $200 in around 4 days. :D

13. When you type in your description on toplists, fit in as much as you can of the best details about your server. Don&#39;t be scared to abbreviate A LITTLE as long as most RSPS players know what those abbreviations mean.

14. Get your players to tell their friends about your server!!!

15. Confront your players on public chat in front of other players and ask them if they would please vote every day. They would feel bad to say no. If they ignore you, wait a little while and say it again. &gt;:D My little trick. Lol.

16. Reward players for voting. E.g. Drop party at ## votes!!!

17. Use vote4cash. I made a custom vote4cash that&#39;s a lot more secure than the old fashioned one and it doesn&#39;t require mysql. It&#39;s very simple. I&#39;m going to release it soon. Idk what to call it though. Please leave ideas in your feedback. :) Thanks!

18. Forum signatures! Link them to your RSPS, or a good YouTube vid about your RSPS. Make sure you follow the rules about signatures though. Lol. Don&#39;t get yourself in trouble, or me. :P

19. Most important of all: Use a good base!!! I recommend using Delta for your first server, but after you get good with Java switch to PI, it&#39;s more up to date with RSPS and it&#39;s more organized, but harder than Delta. Delta has almost everything in 1 file, client.java. Lol. I started with delta and moved to PI.

20. Avoid switching bases too much. I use to do that a lot and I always lost a lot of players. In fact, I made $200 and then switched to a crappy base and then lost all my donators. I went from 10+ to 2+. &gt;:|

21. Make your website look amazing! If you don&#39;t know how to code HTML and CSS, just use Webs.com. Make sure the pages look clean and load fast. The first thing on the homepage should be a video or detailed description of your server, talking about how it&#39;s soo amazing. :P If you do know how to code HTML look for a free online template and edit it, it&#39;s a lot easier than making your own and usually looks a lot better. I code HTML, CSS, PHP, and Java, yet I still prefer online templates over mine because the people who release those templates usually have A LOT more experience than the average coder. I&#39;d give you some examples but I don&#39;t have the templates I like bookmarked on this computer.

22. You don&#39;t have to have a good server to get a lot of players, trust me I use to have a terrible server and I still had A LOT of players. But if you want long term players, make sure you work hard on your server to make it better than all other servers.

23. Avoid rollbacks.

24. Keep a good economy.

25. Keep an active community.

26. Don&#39;t give away free staff spots. Get good staff, make them earn it. I don&#39;t mean let them play for 5 minutes then give it to them, I mean make them earn it. :P

27. Be nice and helpful to your players. Give them tours, that can usually guarantee a long term player if you give an amazing but short tour so they can easily navigate on your server. One of my most active players, now an administrator, fell in love with my server after the tour I gave him.

28. Don&#39;t sell staff spots.

29. Allow donations. Don&#39;t go overboard with it.

30. Make a ::vote and ::donate command. I&#39;m fairly positive that over 100 of my votes last month came from my ::vote command.

31. Get a forums for your server. Webs.com or the people MoparScape forums are through are awesome for forums. Usually you don&#39;t need something as advanced as what MoparScape forums use though. Lol.

32. Get to know your server like your it&#39;s pappy. You need to be able to help your players without thinking twice about their question.

33. Don&#39;t be weak. Never give out items because your players want them. If your players bug you and your busy, don&#39;t just drop everything for them, just tell them you&#39;ll help them in a second. One time, I checked my PM logs and realized my EX co owner was talking to someone about me saying, &quot;He&#39;s always &#39;busy&#39; F**k him!&quot; And denied it to me when I asked. That&#39;s where the ::demote ::mute and ::ban commands come in handy. :) Don&#39;t just ignore that kind of stuff because you&#39;re short on players and really desperately want people to stay. If a player joins and says something like, &quot;This server sucks why should I stay anyways?&quot; Or something like that, just tell them, &quot;This server is a great server and if you&#39;re going to act like that, you should just leave, because I don&#39;t want people like you running around messing up my servers community.&quot; If they leave, consider yourself lucky that you just lost a player. Trust me.

If you need any advice or want to give me some feedback or have an idea for my custom vote4cash&#39;s name, please leave a comment! I really love feedback. It makes me feel special. I&#39;ll give you a cookie. :3

Thanks for reading!! I&#39;m going to have more tutorials soon. Hope you enjoy this one. If you didn&#39;t leave some constructive criticism, just don&#39;t make me have to cry. Well, I probably won&#39;t cry. Hopefully. Maybe. Whatever. Bye. (:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 01:06:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Scape-JAVA, post:10, topic:448478”][quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
2. Use rs-ps and you can pay like $1 for them to redirect people to your webclient. Someone told me if you pay like $10 they’ll add a custom webclient or something like that, not sure if it’s true but worth looking into.[/quote]<br>
No, rs-ps sucks. And why pay 10$ for somebody to jar your client and sign it then upload it to a webhost? This is common sense.</p>
<p>Belhelmiel: You don’t pay them to do that. You pay them to add the embed source, which is worth it if you get a lot of players. I’ve got a surge of 20 players in a few minutes after paying for the $1 ad.</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
11. Do partnerships with other RSPS that suck. Make sure they suck though, that way your players don’t leave your server for their server.[/quote]<br>
If the other server sucks, the affiliation would be inane and frivolous as it would attract virtually no player base to your server.</p>
<p>Belhelmiel: Even if the server sucks, it still may have a bit of players, which will attract you players here and there.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<ol start="15">
<li>Confront your players on public chat in front of other players and ask them if they would please vote every day. They would feel bad to say no. If they ignore you, wait a little while and say it again. &gt;:D My little trick. Lol.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is why you have a voting/reward system, so you don’t need to constantly reiterate yourself on a chatbox.</p>
<p>Yeah but it reminds them to vote, they may not have a voting reward system anyways.</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
16. Reward players for voting. E.g. Drop party at ## votes!!![/quote]</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
This again, brings me back to my other point this is why you have a voting/reward system. A drop party is good, but only as infrequent events like a milestone i.e: The server has been online for a year or we’ve reached 150 players online.[/quote]</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
17. Use vote4cash. I made a custom vote4cash that’s a lot more secure than the old fashioned one and it doesn’t require mysql. [/quote]<br>
An sql database isn’t hard to setup, and it’s a lot less banausic and tedious than editing a player file over and over again. I also took look at your vote4cash system, all it does is write the players ip address to a text document.</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
19. Most important of all: Use a good base!!! I recommend using Delta for your first server, but after you get good with Java switch to PI, it’s more up to date with RSPS and it’s more organized, but harder than Delta. Delta has almost everything in 1 file, client.java. Lol. I started with delta and moved to PI.[/quote]<br>
Delta is a horribly programmed winterLove server, and I don’t recommend using this as it teaches you poor programming conventions and is just generally bad. Quite honestly Delta isn’t that far behind project insanity, as neither of them are ‘great’. They’re both bad when you really take a look at a project insanity server, it’s programming is horrible.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<ol start="21">
<li>Make your website look amazing! If you don’t know how to code HTML and CSS, just use <a href="http://Webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Webs.com</a>.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, <a href="http://webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">webs.com</a> is bad, use a different forum like IPB or myBB and what does knowing HTML or CSS have to do with having a nice forum? Sure it’s useful for a nice homepage, but it’s the forum and how you use it that makes it nice.</p>
<p>Belhelmiel: I wasn’t talking about coding a forums with HTML and CSS I was talking about a homepage :P. And I know webs isn’t the best but it was really simple and popular when I use to use it before I learned HTML CSS and PHP so I recommended it.</p>
<p>Besides those points, all of this tutorial is common sense.[/quote]</p>
<p>I agree with a lot of your statements. But it’s still very helpful for new players, I wish I would’ve known all this when I first started with RSPS. I left replies inside of the quote(Sorry, easier that way. Lol)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 01:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@i_am_infamy i am infamy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_am_infamy">@i_am_infamy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Scape-JAVA, post:10, topic:448478”][quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
2. Use rs-ps and you can pay like $1 for them to redirect people to your webclient. Someone told me if you pay like $10 they’ll add a custom webclient or something like that, not sure if it’s true but worth looking into.[/quote]<br>
No, rs-ps sucks. And why pay 10$ for somebody to jar your client and sign it then upload it to a webhost? This is common sense.</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
11. Do partnerships with other RSPS that suck. Make sure they suck though, that way your players don’t leave your server for their server.[/quote]<br>
If the other server sucks, the affiliation would be inane and frivolous as it would attract virtually no player base to your server.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<ol start="15">
<li>Confront your players on public chat in front of other players and ask them if they would please vote every day. They would feel bad to say no. If they ignore you, wait a little while and say it again. &gt;:D My little trick. Lol.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is why you have a voting/reward system, so you don’t need to constantly reiterate yourself on a chatbox.</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
16. Reward players for voting. E.g. Drop party at ## votes!!![/quote]</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
This again, brings me back to my other point this is why you have a voting/reward system. A drop party is good, but only as infrequent events like a milestone i.e: The server has been online for a year or we’ve reached 150 players online.[/quote]</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
17. Use vote4cash. I made a custom vote4cash that’s a lot more secure than the old fashioned one and it doesn’t require mysql. [/quote]<br>
An sql database isn’t hard to setup, and it’s a lot less banausic and tedious than editing a player file over and over again. I also took look at your vote4cash system, all it does is write the players ip address to a text document.</p>
<p>[quote author=belhelmiel]<br>
19. Most important of all: Use a good base!!! I recommend using Delta for your first server, but after you get good with Java switch to PI, it’s more up to date with RSPS and it’s more organized, but harder than Delta. Delta has almost everything in 1 file, client.java. Lol. I started with delta and moved to PI.[/quote]<br>
Delta is a horribly programmed winterLove server, and I don’t recommend using this as it teaches you poor programming conventions and is just generally bad. Quite honestly Delta isn’t that far behind project insanity, as neither of them are ‘great’. They’re both bad when you really take a look at a project insanity server, it’s programming is horrible.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<ol start="21">
<li>Make your website look amazing! If you don’t know how to code HTML and CSS, just use <a href="http://Webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Webs.com</a>.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, <a href="http://webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">webs.com</a> is bad, use a different forum like IPB or myBB and what does knowing HTML or CSS have to do with having a nice forum? Sure it’s useful for a nice homepage, but it’s the forum and how you use it that makes it nice.</p>
<p>Besides those points, all of this tutorial is common sense.[/quote]</p>
<p>xD</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 00:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scape-JAVA Scape-JAVA]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scape-java">@Scape-JAVA</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/belhelmiel/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> belhelmiel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>2. Use rs-ps and you can pay like $1 for them to redirect people to your webclient. Someone told me if you pay like $10 they’ll add a custom webclient or something like that, not sure if it’s true but worth looking into.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, rs-ps sucks. And why pay 10$ for somebody to jar your client and sign it then upload it to a webhost? This is common sense.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/belhelmiel/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> belhelmiel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>11. Do partnerships with other RSPS that suck. Make sure they suck though, that way your players don’t leave your server for their server.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If the other server sucks, the affiliation would be inane and frivolous as it would attract virtually no player base to your server.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/belhelmiel/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> belhelmiel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>15. Confront your players on public chat in front of other players and ask them if they would please vote every day. They would feel bad to say no. If they ignore you, wait a little while and say it again. &gt;:D My little trick. Lol.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is why you have a voting/reward system, so you don’t need to constantly reiterate yourself on a chatbox.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/belhelmiel/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> belhelmiel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>16. Reward players for voting. E.g. Drop party at ## votes!!!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/belhelmiel/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> belhelmiel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>This again, brings me back to my other point this is why you have a voting/reward system. A drop party is good, but only as infrequent events like a milestone i.e: The server has been online for a year or we’ve reached 150 players online.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/belhelmiel/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> belhelmiel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>17. Use vote4cash. I made a custom vote4cash that’s a lot more secure than the old fashioned one and it doesn’t require mysql.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>An sql database isn’t hard to setup, and it’s a lot less banausic and tedious than editing a player file over and over again. I also took look at your vote4cash system, all it does is write the players ip address to a text document.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/belhelmiel/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> belhelmiel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>19. Most important of all: Use a good base!!! I recommend using Delta for your first server, but after you get good with Java switch to PI, it’s more up to date with RSPS and it’s more organized, but harder than Delta. Delta has almost everything in 1 file, client.java. Lol. I started with delta and moved to PI.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Delta is a horribly programmed winterLove server, and I don’t recommend using this as it teaches you poor programming conventions and is just generally bad. Quite honestly Delta isn’t that far behind project insanity, as neither of them are ‘great’. They’re both bad when you really take a look at a project insanity server, it’s programming is horrible.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/belhelmiel/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> belhelmiel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>21. Make your website look amazing! If you don’t know how to code HTML and CSS, just use <a href="http://Webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Webs.com</a>.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No, <a href="http://webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">webs.com</a> is bad, use a different forum like IPB or myBB and what does knowing HTML or CSS have to do with having a nice forum? Sure it’s useful for a nice homepage, but it’s the forum and how you use it that makes it nice.</p>
<p>Besides those points, all of this tutorial is common sense.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 00:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zach55200 zach55200]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zach55200">@zach55200</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Although these tips are common sense, they may be useful to new people.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>19. Most important of all: Use a good base!!! I recommend using Delta for your first server, but after you get good with Java switch to PI, it's more up to date with RSPS and it's more organized, but harder than Delta. Delta has almost everything in 1 file, client.java. Lol. I started with delta and moved to PI.</blockquote>
<blockquote>21. Make your website look amazing! If you don't know how to code HTML and CSS, just use Webs.com.</blockquote>
no.
<blockquote>31. Get a forums for your server. Webs.com or the people MoparScape forums are through are awesome for forums. Usually you don't need something as advanced as what MoparScape forums use though. Lol.</blockquote>
What? Please elaborate..
<p>A lot of your points are common sense, but thanks for taking your time to write this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 00:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="6" data-topic="448478">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/hash1/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Hash1:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The only thing I highly disagree is the title with all server information in it. It looks unprofessionnal and not clean at all; to avoid.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Um, sorry but, what do you mean? Please quote something I said that has to do with that. Lol. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 00:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hash1 Hash1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hash1">@Hash1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The only thing I highly disagree is the title with all server information in it. It looks unprofessionnal and not clean at all; to avoid.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 00:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="448478">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/codebest/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> CodeBest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Many of these are common sense but its nice to have a list <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> good job.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, I agree but I noticed A LOT of RSPS do not follow those guide lines. So I figured it would be good to release a huge list like mine into the community.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 23:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeBest CodeBest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codebest">@CodeBest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Many of these are common sense but its nice to have a list <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> good job.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 20:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“EatMyWhiteStuff, post:2, topic:448478”]I’m gonna all of these out when I get my server up and running. IF I get it up and running.<br>
On the server I was on, the owner did number 26 all the time… Had around 9 staff and 4 players… (7 of them were admins)<br>
He also switches sources a lot. Ends up switching back the next day.</p>
<p>Thanks for these.[/quote]<br>
Np. Just sharing my past mistakes and experience.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 16:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EatMyWhiteStuff EatMyWhiteStuff]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eatmywhitestuff">@EatMyWhiteStuff</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m gonna all of these out when I get my server up and running. IF I get it up and running.<br>
On the server I was on, the owner did number 26 all the time… Had around 9 staff and 4 players… (7 of them were admins)<br>
He also switches sources a lot. Ends up switching back the next day.</p>
<p>Thanks for these.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 10:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I’m Cloudnine. I’m going to explain to you how to get many players for your server.</p>
<p>Before you comment, “They already have this guide n00b!” You need to understand that not everyone’s guide will be the same and that people should learn from more than just one person’s experiences.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>You should try to avoid hamachi.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Use rs-ps and you can pay like $1 for them to redirect people to your webclient. Someone told me if you pay like $10 they’ll add a custom webclient or something like that, not sure if it’s true but worth looking into.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Lots and lots of Youtube videos!  My server has 12 videos from me and other videos from my players. YouTube has a lot more people than any toplist combined, it will get you a lot of people.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Obviously, toplists. Many many toplists. I have my server on around 7. These are the ones I use:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>rsps<br>
<a href="http://www.mmorpgtoplist.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.mmorpgtoplist.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.ultimateprivateservers.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.ultimateprivateservers.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.gtop100.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.gtop100.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.gamesites100.net/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.gamesites100.net/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.xtremetop100.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.xtremetop100.com/</a></p>
<ol start="5">
<li>You need to make your server look attractive on the top lists.<br>
Ex:<br>
“[YourServersLinkHere!!!]24/7 Webclient Updates &amp; events No lag/rollbacks 525 graphics Good economy &amp; rates Nice staff Active Community”</li>
</ol>
<p>That’s just an example. I use it for my server on rlocus. Remember, always put your link as the first thing on your servers description. They will see it and automatically think to go to that URL.</p>
<ol start="6">
<li>
<p>Make your server look attractive on the YouTube videos. You need to show some combat on every video. Describe your server in depth! Put the link first in description. Describe your server in depth in the video as well. Have a video done with every skill, every mini-game, every boss, all pking zones, fun-pk, webclient mode, special features, home area, and stuff like that. Add some HIT music that A LOT of people like. Just look up a top music list for the previous month of your year. Check out my youtube videos if you want some examples, but don’t you dare advertise on my comments. <a href="http://www.youtube.com/belhelmiel" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/belhelmiel</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Play around on other servers and look for ideas.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do promotions. E.g. 2x rates for the first month of opening! Or something like 2x starter for the first few weeks! Etc.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Rs-ps chat room! Best place to advertise. Say something like… “Looking for a good server? Click my house or PC me. :)”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do partnerships with new RSPS toplists. “I’ll advertise you if you advertise me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> ;)” kind of deal.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Do partnerships with other RSPS that suck. Make sure they suck though, that way your players don’t leave your server for their server.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Look for servers that may be shutting down soon, or inconsistent up time. Those tend to go down forever and if you talk to the owner and just let him/her know about your server, but stay on their good side, they may say “Server is offline atm try out [YourRSPSHere].” Someone did that for me before when their server went offline, thats how I got 10+ players within the first few days of my server being up and I got $200 in around 4 days. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When you type in your description on toplists, fit in as much as you can of the best details about your server. Don’t be scared to abbreviate A LITTLE as long as most RSPS players know what those abbreviations mean.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Get your players to tell their friends about your server!!!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Confront your players on public chat in front of other players and ask them if they would please vote every day. They would feel bad to say no. If they ignore you, wait a little while and say it again. &gt;:D My little trick. Lol.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Reward players for voting. E.g. Drop party at ## votes!!!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Use vote4cash. I made a custom vote4cash that’s a lot more secure than the old fashioned one and it doesn’t require mysql. It’s very simple. I’m going to release it soon. Idk what to call it though. Please leave ideas in your feedback. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Thanks!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Forum signatures! Link them to your RSPS, or a good YouTube vid about your RSPS. Make sure you follow the rules about signatures though. Lol. Don’t get yourself in trouble, or me. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Most important of all: Use a good base!!! I recommend using Delta for your first server, but after you get good with Java switch to PI, it’s more up to date with RSPS and it’s more organized, but harder than Delta. Delta has almost everything in 1 file, client.java. Lol. I started with delta and moved to PI.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Avoid switching bases too much. I use to do that a lot and I always lost a lot of players. In fact, I made $200 and then switched to a crappy base and then lost all my donators. I went from 10+ to 2+. &gt;:|</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make your website look amazing! If you don’t know how to code HTML and CSS, just use <a href="http://Webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Webs.com</a>. Make sure the pages look clean and load fast. The first thing on the homepage should be a video or detailed description of your server, talking about how it’s soo amazing. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> If you do know how to code HTML look for a free online template and edit it, it’s a lot easier than making your own and usually looks a lot better. I code HTML, CSS, PHP, and Java, yet I still prefer online templates over mine because the people who release those templates usually have A LOT more experience than the average coder. I’d give you some examples but I don’t have the templates I like bookmarked on this computer.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You don’t have to have a good server to get a lot of players, trust me I use to have a terrible server and I still had A LOT of players. But if you want long term players, make sure you work hard on your server to make it better than all other servers.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Avoid rollbacks.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Keep a good economy.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Keep an active community.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t give away free staff spots. Get good staff, make them earn it. I don’t mean let them play for 5 minutes then give it to them, I mean make them earn it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Be nice and helpful to your players. Give them tours, that can usually guarantee a long term player if you give an amazing but short tour so they can easily navigate on your server. One of my most active players, now an administrator, fell in love with my server after the tour I gave him.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t sell staff spots.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Allow donations. Don’t go overboard with it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make a ::vote and ::donate command. I’m fairly positive that over 100 of my votes last month came from my ::vote command.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Get a forums for your server. <a href="http://Webs.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Webs.com</a> or the people MoparScape forums are through are awesome for forums. Usually you don’t need something as advanced as what MoparScape forums use though. Lol.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Get to know your server like your it’s pappy. You need to be able to help your players without thinking twice about their question.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t be weak. Never give out items because your players want them. If your players bug you and your busy, don’t just drop everything for them, just tell them you’ll help them in a second. One time, I checked my PM logs and realized my EX co owner was talking to someone about me saying, “He’s always ‘busy’ F**k him!” And denied it to me when I asked. That’s where the ::demote ::mute and ::ban commands come in handy. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Don’t just ignore that kind of stuff because you’re short on players and really desperately want people to stay. If a player joins and says something like, “This server sucks why should I stay anyways?” Or something like that, just tell them, “This server is a great server and if you’re going to act like that, you should just leave, because I don’t want people like you running around messing up my servers community.” If they leave, consider yourself lucky that you just lost a player. Trust me.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>If you need any advice or want to give me some feedback or have an idea for my custom vote4cash’s name, please leave a comment! I really love feedback. It makes me feel special. I’ll give you a cookie. :3</p>
<p>Thanks for reading!! I’m going to have more tutorials soon. Hope you enjoy this one. If you didn’t leave some constructive criticism, just don’t make me have to cry. Well, I probably won’t cry. Hopefully. Maybe. Whatever. Bye. (:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 09:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448478-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/easy-making-your-server-popular-and-getting-players/448478.rss">[EASY] Making your server popular and getting players</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
