<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Project 69</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688</link>
    <description>[i]Hello everyone, before I start praising my server like everyone here does let me tell you a little bit about myself.

My name is Sandy, I have been in the RsPs scene for nearly 4 years now. I have played many servers and have over 3 years of staff experience.
The reason I started my own server is simply because we care. I&#39;ve seen so many owners who think they are above the community, that their voice doesn&#39;t matter, that donators should have unfair perks over players.

I know that many servers here claim to be the best, claim to have the best PK system, the best minigames, the most amazing staff team you have ever seen etc etc.
Well I am not claiming that. I am not claiming to be the best, I am not claiming to be a professional developer who could code a new Runescape combat system in 5 minutes.

I do promise you this though: Our server and its team are there for the community. We update frequently, we do not ignore our players whenever we don&#39;t feel like talking to them.
We don&#39;t ignore people on skype or humiliate them. We show respect to our players FIRST so that we may earn respect from them in return, instead of the other way around.
Our server is small at the moment (5-35 players on at a time) but we plan to grow.

If you&#39;re looking for a server where you can really meet people, where you can be part of a community again and play a server that has more to offer than the standard things every rsps has: You will be right at home with us.[/i]

[b]Now about the server.[/b]
[i]A couple of things we have that you may find appealing:

- 317 PI source 300-400 revision
- Prestiging System
- Melzar&#39;s Maze
- Housing System
- A staff team that&#39;s constantly being moderated by higherup staff members so that we never have corrupt behavior.
- 7 custom areas with monsters that you probably won&#39;t find in other servers, each area has unique drops. (more area&#39;s being added over time)
- A 2 man development team constantly moderating suggestions and problems reported by the community to ensure a fun game at all times.
- Custom items (Different colour party hats, santa hats, H&#39;ween masks, some custom weapons and some custom capes (including 3 kind of wings).
- Craftable items (Using materials gathered from PVM you can make your own strong items) (Example: Making a blurite sword out of drops from the blurite cave).
- A lot of items have been buffed so they can be usefull ingame, they are stronger than the basic D scim/Whip most. (Examples: Shadow sword, Blurite sword, Silverlight, Darklight, Defensive shield and more)
- Open staff positions. We have met wonderfull people over the years, and kept contacts with them to create the best staff team we could come up with. But we do have a couple of open spots. 
(Note: You can&#39;t earn staff positions within a few days, we will have to get to know you, see how you act ingame and moderate your behavior for quite some time before we consider promotions)

We will keep the rest of our content a suprise because we don&#39;t want to spoil everything for you ^.^[/i]


All in all I think you should at least give us a try. If you&#39;re still reading: You know what we have to offer, now I dare you to come by and see the server for yourself.

The server name: Project-69 (Originated from pj69, a big server back in the day. We carry on the name out of respect for the good times we had there.)
Our website: www.project-69.org
Names of the owners: Tristen &amp; Sandy

Feel free to log on and contact us, we&#39;re always open for conversations.

We hope to see you soon!

[spoiler][IMG]http://i41.tinypic.com/25u2jq0.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i39.tinypic.com/2gx3dau.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i41.tinypic.com/esmgjk.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i45.tinypic.com/2qsqm9t.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i44.tinypic.com/npj4o6.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i59.tinypic.com/ru7cx1.jpg[/img][/spoiler]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 16:37:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Project 69</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@project69 project69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project69">@project69</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="2" data-topic="544688">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/devilxsummoner/40/4128_1.png" class="avatar"> DevilXsummoner:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nice server. Won’t be playing because you have nulled vB ._.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Pretty sure our forum is legit seen as we have a Vbulletin account to go with our forums O.o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544688-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688.rss">Project 69</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Project 69</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DevilXsummoner DevilXsummoner]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/devilxsummoner">@DevilXsummoner</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice server. Won’t be playing because you have nulled vB ._.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 16:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544688-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688.rss">Project 69</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Project 69</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@project69 project69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project69">@project69</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[i]Hello everyone, before I start praising my server like everyone here does let me tell you a little bit about myself.</p>
<p>My name is Sandy, I have been in the RsPs scene for nearly 4 years now. I have played many servers and have over 3 years of staff experience.<br>
The reason I started my own server is simply because we care. I’ve seen so many owners who think they are above the community, that their voice doesn’t matter, that donators should have unfair perks over players.</p>
<p>I know that many servers here claim to be the best, claim to have the best PK system, the best minigames, the most amazing staff team you have ever seen etc etc.<br>
Well I am not claiming that. I am not claiming to be the best, I am not claiming to be a professional developer who could code a new Runescape combat system in 5 minutes.</p>
<p>I do promise you this though: Our server and its team are there for the community. We update frequently, we do not ignore our players whenever we don’t feel like talking to them.<br>
We don’t ignore people on skype or humiliate them. We show respect to our players FIRST so that we may earn respect from them in return, instead of the other way around.<br>
Our server is small at the moment (5-35 players on at a time) but we plan to grow.</p>
<p>If you’re looking for a server where you can really meet people, where you can be part of a community again and play a server that has more to offer than the standard things every rsps has: You will be right at home with us.[/i]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Now about the server.</span><br>
[i]A couple of things we have that you may find appealing:</p>
<ul>
<li>317 PI source 300-400 revision</li>
<li>Prestiging System</li>
<li>Melzar’s Maze</li>
<li>Housing System</li>
<li>A staff team that’s constantly being moderated by higherup staff members so that we never have corrupt behavior.</li>
<li>7 custom areas with monsters that you probably won’t find in other servers, each area has unique drops. (more area’s being added over time)</li>
<li>A 2 man development team constantly moderating suggestions and problems reported by the community to ensure a fun game at all times.</li>
<li>Custom items (Different colour party hats, santa hats, H’ween masks, some custom weapons and some custom capes (including 3 kind of wings).</li>
<li>Craftable items (Using materials gathered from PVM you can make your own strong items) (Example: Making a blurite sword out of drops from the blurite cave).</li>
<li>A lot of items have been buffed so they can be usefull ingame, they are stronger than the basic D scim/Whip most. (Examples: Shadow sword, Blurite sword, Silverlight, Darklight, Defensive shield and more)</li>
<li>Open staff positions. We have met wonderfull people over the years, and kept contacts with them to create the best staff team we could come up with. But we do have a couple of open spots.<br>
(Note: You can’t earn staff positions within a few days, we will have to get to know you, see how you act ingame and moderate your behavior for quite some time before we consider promotions)</li>
</ul>
<p>We will keep the rest of our content a suprise because we don’t want to spoil everything for you ^.^[/i]</p>
<p>All in all I think you should at least give us a try. If you’re still reading: You know what we have to offer, now I dare you to come by and see the server for yourself.</p>
<p>The server name: Project-69 (Originated from pj69, a big server back in the day. We carry on the name out of respect for the good times we had there.)<br>
Our website: <a href="http://www.project-69.org" rel="nofollow noopener">www.project-69.org</a><br>
Names of the owners: Tristen &amp; Sandy</p>
<p>Feel free to log on and contact us, we’re always open for conversations.</p>
<p>We hope to see you soon!</p>
<p>[spoiler]<img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/25u2jq0.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i39.tinypic.com/2gx3dau.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/esmgjk.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i45.tinypic.com/2qsqm9t.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i44.tinypic.com/npj4o6.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i59.tinypic.com/ru7cx1.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/spoiler]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 16:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544688-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-69/544688.rss">Project 69</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
