<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Schedule Events [Java/MySQL]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/schedule-events-java-mysql/303337</link>
    <description>Ok, so I am working on a ban system. The names/IPs are stored in a MySQL table `Banned`. Now my problem is I want the removing of names/IPs to be handled outside of the java program. That way If someone get&#39;s banned or muted for 3 days, he server won&#39;t have to cycle every 500 ms to see if the current time is after the ban period. I was thinking of using cron or something like that, but I remember seeing something in a MySQL client about scheduling events. However I can&#39;t find a fully featured MySQL client that&#39;s freeware, or open source. So what would be the best way about doing this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 06:46:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/schedule-events-java-mysql/303337.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Schedule Events [Java/MySQL]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, so I am working on a ban system. The names/IPs are stored in a MySQL table <code>Banned</code>. Now my problem is I want the removing of names/IPs to be handled outside of the java program. That way If someone get’s banned or muted for 3 days, he server won’t have to cycle every 500 ms to see if the current time is after the ban period. I was thinking of using cron or something like that, but I remember seeing something in a MySQL client about scheduling events. However I can’t find a fully featured MySQL client that’s freeware, or open source. So what would be the best way about doing this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/schedule-events-java-mysql/303337/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/schedule-events-java-mysql/303337/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 06:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-303337-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/schedule-events-java-mysql/303337.rss">Schedule Events [Java/MySQL]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
