<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need Help Immediately!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-immediately/379205</link>
    <description>Ok, so I&#39;ve been hosting my server for about 6 months now and its a Allstar server.  It has 1 connection per ip coded into it which allows it to stop nullers if i ban their ip.  I know it works, I&#39;ve done it many times already.  Today was different however, i assume most people who null my server use the AllGoFree Bot thing, but the nuller was much different today.  First, banning the ip worked the first time, then about 10 minutes later it comes back (I assume they switched nullers) and my server couldn&#39;t stop the nulls.  They came extremely fast too, 200 nulls in 15-20 seconds.

I would like to know if anyone knows how that happened and if there&#39;s anyway to protect against it.  Also i&#39;d like to know if they are using a special nuller or something.  Please respond</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 08:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-immediately/379205.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need Help Immediately!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mr_dope mr dope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_dope">@mr_dope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, so I’ve been hosting my server for about 6 months now and its a Allstar server.  It has 1 connection per ip coded into it which allows it to stop nullers if i ban their ip.  I know it works, I’ve done it many times already.  Today was different however, i assume most people who null my server use the AllGoFree Bot thing, but the nuller was much different today.  First, banning the ip worked the first time, then about 10 minutes later it comes back (I assume they switched nullers) and my server couldn’t stop the nulls.  They came extremely fast too, 200 nulls in 15-20 seconds.</p>
<p>I would like to know if anyone knows how that happened and if there’s anyway to protect against it.  Also i’d like to know if they are using a special nuller or something.  Please respond</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-immediately/379205/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-immediately/379205/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 08:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379205-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-immediately/379205.rss">Need Help Immediately!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
