<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fixed Link: Auto-Enrion Variables Quick and easy</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-link-auto-enrion-variables-quick-and-easy/356573</link>
    <description>NOTE: This program HAS been updated. I added the ability to continue adding the folder you selected, even if it wasn&#39;t the right one, and added auto detection which tries to find your JDK folder in the most common locations for each drive in your computer at the time.

Well, I&#39;ve noticed SO many people have trouble on this part. That&#39;s why I made this. You browse for your JDK folder and click Apply! Done!

Screenshot:
[img]http://img842.imageshack.us/img842/2317/xcqgxj.png[/img]



So you don&#39;t fuck up, it checks if you&#39;ve selected the right folder. It does this by checking if the folder starts with &quot;jdk&quot;, and it has some of the files in the bin folder that the JDK comes with.

If you&#39;ve already got your JDK set, it will prompt you to continue. If you do, it&#39;ll just write it to the line.

At the bottom textboxes, you can see what was loaded, and what will be saved. This is good if you don&#39;t trust it.

So, the newest download...
http://www.mediafire.com/?b32fe5w0h9kaqrc

Oh and finally, you need the .NET Framework 2.0 or higher (Meaning atleast Windows 2000 SP4). I developed it using C# .NET 2005/2008.


If you&#39;re totally lost on what to do, follow these instructions.

1. Open the program.
2. Click on the &quot;Search&quot; button.
3. Navigate to your &quot;JDK&quot; folder. It starts at &quot;C:\Program Files\Java&quot;. Basically, go there and click the folder that starts with &quot;jdk&quot;.
4. If you did it right, it won&#39;t give you any warnings.
5. Click the &quot;Apply&quot; button. If done right, it should say &quot;Successfully changed!&quot;

Congratulations!! You did it!!!

Note: You must have permissions to edit your environment variables. For example, if you&#39;re using Windows Vista, you must run under an Administrator account.

All credits go to Lin</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 15:24:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-link-auto-enrion-variables-quick-and-easy/356573.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fixed Link: Auto-Enrion Variables Quick and easy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dy3p8ntrkid dy3p8ntrkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dy3p8ntrkid">@dy3p8ntrkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>NOTE: This program HAS been updated. I added the ability to continue adding the folder you selected, even if it wasn’t the right one, and added auto detection which tries to find your JDK folder in the most common locations for each drive in your computer at the time.</p>
<p>Well, I’ve noticed SO many people have trouble on this part. That’s why I made this. You browse for your JDK folder and click Apply! Done!</p>
<p>Screenshot:<br>
<img src="http://img842.imageshack.us/img842/2317/xcqgxj.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>So you don’t fuck up, it checks if you’ve selected the right folder. It does this by checking if the folder starts with “jdk”, and it has some of the files in the bin folder that the JDK comes with.</p>
<p>If you’ve already got your JDK set, it will prompt you to continue. If you do, it’ll just write it to the line.</p>
<p>At the bottom textboxes, you can see what was loaded, and what will be saved. This is good if you don’t trust it.</p>
<p>So, the newest download…<br>
<a href="http://www.mediafire.com/?b32fe5w0h9kaqrc" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.mediafire.com/?b32fe5w0h9kaqrc</a></p>
<p>Oh and finally, you need the .NET Framework 2.0 or higher (Meaning atleast Windows 2000 SP4). I developed it using C# .NET 2005/2008.</p>
<p>If you’re totally lost on what to do, follow these instructions.</p>
<ol>
<li>Open the program.</li>
<li>Click on the “Search” button.</li>
<li>Navigate to your “JDK” folder. It starts at “C:\Program Files\Java”. Basically, go there and click the folder that starts with “jdk”.</li>
<li>If you did it right, it won’t give you any warnings.</li>
<li>Click the “Apply” button. If done right, it should say “Successfully changed!”</li>
</ol>
<p>Congratulations!! You did it!!!</p>
<p>Note: You must have permissions to edit your environment variables. For example, if you’re using Windows Vista, you must run under an Administrator account.</p>
<p>All credits go to Lin</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-link-auto-enrion-variables-quick-and-easy/356573/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-link-auto-enrion-variables-quick-and-easy/356573/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 15:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-356573-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fixed-link-auto-enrion-variables-quick-and-easy/356573.rss">Fixed Link: Auto-Enrion Variables Quick and easy</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
