<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Requesting Team for 667 server!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-team-for-667-server/548627</link>
    <description>Hello everyone, Let me formally introduce myself. My name is Chris A.K.A Fairs and I&#39;m Canadian, Eh! I have been working on a project and I wanted to make a team to help develop with me. I&#39;ve seen some pretty nasty unorganized servers and some pretty irresponsible staff and quite frankly, getting quite tired of it. So I decided I would make this project and see how it goes.

I&#39;m looking for roughly 2-4 more people, as I have already recruited someone with some coding knowledge (Jared). He is willing to be apart of the TEAM. Unfortunately I haven&#39;t really tried, so here I am. You do not have to expertise in Java coding because your suggestion matters, as long as you&#39;re not &quot;Put that wall there, can I be staff now?&quot; No. We mean legitimately help us throughout development, give us strong ideas and some opinions. 

The server I have created will simply not be a PK Server, There will be some I can imagine, but I was thinking along the lines of an economy server, Well balanced and not &quot;Donate&quot; to win. I am not looking for a one person overpowered dictatorship. HEIL. just kidding, anyways. I will be personally paying for the server out of my own pocket.

Requirements are:
Skype and a mic

Recommended:
Understanding of Java coding
Patience

Skype:
vChris36</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 06:33:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-team-for-667-server/548627.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Requesting Team for 667 server!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fairs Fairs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fairs">@Fairs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello everyone, Let me formally introduce myself. My name is Chris A.K.A Fairs and I’m Canadian, Eh! I have been working on a project and I wanted to make a team to help develop with me. I’ve seen some pretty nasty unorganized servers and some pretty irresponsible staff and quite frankly, getting quite tired of it. So I decided I would make this project and see how it goes.</p>
<p>I’m looking for roughly 2-4 more people, as I have already recruited someone with some coding knowledge (Jared). He is willing to be apart of the TEAM. Unfortunately I haven’t really tried, so here I am. You do not have to expertise in Java coding because your suggestion matters, as long as you’re not “Put that wall there, can I be staff now?” No. We mean legitimately help us throughout development, give us strong ideas and some opinions.</p>
<p>The server I have created will simply not be a PK Server, There will be some I can imagine, but I was thinking along the lines of an economy server, Well balanced and not “Donate” to win. I am not looking for a one person overpowered dictatorship. HEIL. just kidding, anyways. I will be personally paying for the server out of my own pocket.</p>
<p>Requirements are:<br>
Skype and a mic</p>
<p>Recommended:<br>
Understanding of Java coding<br>
Patience</p>
<p>Skype:<br>
vChris36</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-team-for-667-server/548627/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-team-for-667-server/548627/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 06:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-548627-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/requesting-team-for-667-server/548627.rss">Requesting Team for 667 server!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
