<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Good Linux Distro / Overall OS?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050</link>
    <description>Alright guys so I&#39;m kind of hoping for a speedy reply so I can download the OS/whichever Linux Distro I need and go on with my day. I am also aware this has been asked alot but I need an answer for my specific needs. So I feel the need for a new OS in general, whether it&#39;s just something new and different or if you give me a good linux distro, I don&#39;t care. Here are some things I&#39;m going to need:

-A rather user friendly OS, I tried a linux distro once (forgot the name) and honestly I was baffled at how to do ANYTHING.
-I need something very good for gaming and game development, as well as general use, skype etc. I am aware that some Linux platforms aren&#39;t necessarily friendly with daily applications such as skype, etc, so of course I need something that doesnt have many issues with those.

And that&#39;s about it guys, I know it&#39;s very specific, and I realize I couldve just searched for this answer, but I know alot of you guys use different linux distros etc so I wanted a good answer from some of you. Thanks.

EDIT: I just remembered Ubuntu and I believe.. 12.0 or something like that was the version I had previously used. So if anyone thinks thats something good to use, just send me in the direction of a maybe helpful website, or just give me some friendly tips to get used to it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 23:20:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Good Linux Distro / Overall OS?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://distrowatch.com/table.php" rel="nofollow noopener">http://distrowatch.com/table.php</a>?<br>
Here’s a list if you want to look around.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 23:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538050-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050.rss">Good Linux Distro / Overall OS?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good Linux Distro / Overall OS?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Evil1 Evil_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evil1">@Evil1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I hate to break it to you but you pretty much described windows man, you might as well just keep/install windows.  I guess the closest runner up with be Ubuntu, or maybe mint i suppose</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 23:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538050-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050.rss">Good Linux Distro / Overall OS?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Good Linux Distro / Overall OS?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kodiak Kodiak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kodiak">@Kodiak</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright guys so I’m kind of hoping for a speedy reply so I can download the OS/whichever Linux Distro I need and go on with my day. I am also aware this has been asked alot but I need an answer for my specific needs. So I feel the need for a new OS in general, whether it’s just something new and different or if you give me a good linux distro, I don’t care. Here are some things I’m going to need:</p>
<p>-A rather user friendly OS, I tried a linux distro once (forgot the name) and honestly I was baffled at how to do ANYTHING.<br>
-I need something very good for gaming and game development, as well as general use, skype etc. I am aware that some Linux platforms aren’t necessarily friendly with daily applications such as skype, etc, so of course I need something that doesnt have many issues with those.</p>
<p>And that’s about it guys, I know it’s very specific, and I realize I couldve just searched for this answer, but I know alot of you guys use different linux distros etc so I wanted a good answer from some of you. Thanks.</p>
<p>EDIT: I just remembered Ubuntu and I believe… 12.0 or something like that was the version I had previously used. So if anyone thinks thats something good to use, just send me in the direction of a maybe helpful website, or just give me some friendly tips to get used to it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 22:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538050-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/good-linux-distro-overall-os/538050.rss">Good Linux Distro / Overall OS?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
