<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Connection problem</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connection-problem/326981</link>
    <description>Ok to start off i&#39;m sorry if I shouldn&#39;t post this but i read the rules and this is one the only place i can think of asking for help and 2 doesn&#39;t seem to break any so if it is wrong either you can help me or one person can post that it&#39;s wrong and not 20 people.

So over a year ago i hosted a server. I wasn&#39;t the best coder but i did some and i managed to host one. I quit servers and started going off and on hosting them. It&#39;s been a few months and i tried hosting one and not only could no one conenct but if i typed in my own ip or no-ip i couldnt connect to myself.(but i could if i didnt type in anything for ip)
  This could be a problem with just about anything including portforwarding, but the weird thing is i havent really changed anything with my computer so it SHOULD  still work like it did in the fall. 
   Suggestions would be appreciated and I would love you if you used teamview to help but im just trying to get back to hosting thx

ps dont spam or flame if its not allowed in this section only 1 person needs to say so</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 20:29:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connection-problem/326981.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Connection problem</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@veikron veikron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/veikron">@veikron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok to start off i’m sorry if I shouldn’t post this but i read the rules and this is one the only place i can think of asking for help and 2 doesn’t seem to break any so if it is wrong either you can help me or one person can post that it’s wrong and not 20 people.</p>
<p>So over a year ago i hosted a server. I wasn’t the best coder but i did some and i managed to host one. I quit servers and started going off and on hosting them. It’s been a few months and i tried hosting one and not only could no one conenct but if i typed in my own ip or no-ip i couldnt connect to myself.(but i could if i didnt type in anything for ip)<br>
This could be a problem with just about anything including portforwarding, but the weird thing is i havent really changed anything with my computer so it SHOULD  still work like it did in the fall.<br>
Suggestions would be appreciated and I would love you if you used teamview to help but im just trying to get back to hosting thx</p>
<p>ps dont spam or flame if its not allowed in this section only 1 person needs to say so</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connection-problem/326981/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connection-problem/326981/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 20:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326981-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/connection-problem/326981.rss">Connection problem</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
