<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi guys need help if you&#39;d be so kind =D</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-guys-need-help-if-youd-be-so-kind-d/127455</link>
    <description>Ok guy&#39;s heres my first post and im glad to be a part of this forums..

Ummm...Ok see im new to this whole rs private server thing and i&#39;m wondering how can i add specials on my satans isle source if you could help you would be a great help and many thanks. Oh and another problem is when i go into my source and click &quot;shops&quot; i can change whats in a shop like say change a iron plate yo a bronze plate but as soon as i try to add a new one bang when i try run my server it goes fatal error exception in main java thread or something please help. =D

Sorry for poor gramma</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2007 14:34:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-guys-need-help-if-youd-be-so-kind-d/127455.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hi guys need help if you&#39;d be so kind =D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Savagedemon Savagedemon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/savagedemon">@Savagedemon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok guy’s heres my first post and im glad to be a part of this forums…</p>
<p>Ummm…Ok see im new to this whole rs private server thing and i’m wondering how can i add specials on my satans isle source if you could help you would be a great help and many thanks. Oh and another problem is when i go into my source and click “shops” i can change whats in a shop like say change a iron plate yo a bronze plate but as soon as i try to add a new one bang when i try run my server it goes fatal error exception in main java thread or something please help. =D</p>
<p>Sorry for poor gramma</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-guys-need-help-if-youd-be-so-kind-d/127455/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-guys-need-help-if-youd-be-so-kind-d/127455/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2007 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-127455-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-guys-need-help-if-youd-be-so-kind-d/127455.rss">Hi guys need help if you&#39;d be so kind =D</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
