<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Rules</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606</link>
    <description>It seems clear that a major revision of the rules is needed.  I suggest a new format as well, splitting them up into sections.  However, they must follow the KISS principle, Keep It Simple Stupid.

The operative words here being short, simple, clear and concise.

Here are the new rules the staff has came up with so far, mostly it is just a reorganization of the existing rules.

[quote=&quot;Moparisthebest, post:1, topic:223&quot;][center][size=14pt][b]Moparisthebest.com and Moparscape.org Rules[/b][/size][/center]

[size=12pt][u][b]Primary rules[/b][/u]

1. If you don&#39;t have anything nice to say, don&#39;t say anything at all.

2. Use common sense.[/size]

The staff reserves the right to interpret these primary rules any way we see fit, for example while posting child porn is not specifically against the rules, it should be common sense that it is not allowed.

[u][b]Ideals[/b][/u]

Rule 1:
We are not anti-leech. If you respect our community and our ideas, feel free to ask questions and they will be kindly answered if you follow other rules. Answer to questions that others ask if you know the answer or remain silent!

Rule 2:
We don&#39;t talk about things we don&#39;t know. This is an informative, not a misinformative community.

Rule 3:
We respect each other and other communities. We don&#39;t flame each other or other communities. We don&#39;t fight on the forums.

Rule 4:
We don&#39;t care about post count alone. If someone has high post count and most of it is spam, we hate them. If someone has high post count with informative posts, we love them. The higher count, the more we hate/love them.

Rule 5:
We never ask for &quot;rep&quot;.

[u][b]Posts / Topics[/b][/u]

Rule 6:
We don&#39;t make spelling mistakes on purpose. We use &quot;you&quot; not &quot;u&quot;, we use &quot;why&quot; not &quot;y&quot; etc.

Rule 7:
We don&#39;t make posts that contain not useful information. Posts like &quot;cool&quot;, &quot;lol&quot;, &quot;yeah&quot; and &quot;I agree&quot; don&#39;t contain anything useful for others. We are not fans of off topic, unless it contains something smart or funny. Most of things spammers find funny are actually not funny at all.

Rule 8:
We don&#39;t &quot;Bump&quot; or double post whether on purpose or by accident.  Use the edit button instead.  You are however, allowed to post in old topics if it is relevant to your problem.

Rule 9:
Nothing to do with private servers belongs on moparisthebest.com, use [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf]moparisthebest.com/smf[/url] for these things.

Rule 10:
DO [b]NOT[/b] post or upload any copyrighted materials, ie deobs, clients or any other sort (however if you were to link to a file that was uploaded somewhere else or post code in the pasteBin, well, I would have no control over that right? ;) )

[u][b]Buying / Selling[/b][/u]

Rule 11:
We do [b]not[/b] sell anything on this site with the exception of SCAR scripts.  SCAR Scripts must be verified, check the script sales board for more info.

[u][b]Accounts[/b][/u]

Rule 12:
We only have [b]one[/b] Forum account per person for Moparisthebest.com and Moparscape.org.  If you get banned, email an admin, or get a friend to contact an admin.  If you have trouble logging in, click &#39;forgot my password.&#39;

[u][b]Linking / Advertisement[/b][/u]

Rule 13:
We don&#39;t advertise other sites or communities unless we ask and receive permission to from a Gmod or Admin. We don&#39;t post links to sites that are not in safe sites list on Moparisthebest.com main page. 

Rule 14:
We never advertise via the PM system whether the site is approved or not.

Rule 15:
We never have misleading links in our signatures [b]or[/b] posts.  If a link says google.com, we expect it to take us to google.com.

We&#39;re not asking much,

Thank you

Moparisthebest and Moparscape Moderation Team[/quote]

I am opening this up the community to get everyone&#39;s input, please post what you would like to see added or removed, what needs clarified or simplified, etc etc.  After these rules are revised more in the community member section, they may be opened up to the general public for final review before they go into effect.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2007 05:46:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Inside Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WT-Fakawi WT-Fakawi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wt-fakawi">@WT-Fakawi</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I dont generally mix in inside talk, but after reading this thread, I missed out 2 points.</p>
<p>Commercial Issues<br>
A filled up active forum pays the bills and keeps it going. Forums grow, nothing you can do about that. As long as you provide the content, they will come. I am unaware of the state of content here, but if it lacks they will flock.</p>
<p>Target Issues<br>
Runescape is a kids game. Average age is probably 14. There are exceptions (hm) but consequently your average registree will be 14. This puts great pressure on the content of these forums -on any RS-cheating board for that matter- since most 14 year olds havent got a clue what they are talking about (no offence). Especially cheaters.  They lack respect, manner or persistence because they simply dont know how to act in a mature way. Nobody has taught them yet how to. This is something you will need to live with. On the bright side: There are a lot of very talented and well mannered 14 years old that have influenced my view of the future in a very positive way. But the average will be dumb. (once again, no offence)</p>
<p>Whether a forum goes down or not is entirely in the hands of <span class="bbcode-b">active staff </span>for <span class="bbcode-b">control </span>and <span class="bbcode-b">active elite</span> for <span class="bbcode-b">content</span>. Setting out the right directions and appointing the right people is crucial. And dont forget: Kaitnieks had, what, like 8000 members when it went down? And 500 in the old days? It is impossible to compare that to a 143k uncontrolled flow of average mindboggingly mindless communication.</p>
<p>I would suggest further layering the forums. Subgroups (Status) actracts people and stimulates them to comply to group specific rules. I dont know how many moderators or admin this board has, but I we (SRL)  gave out small forumpowers to old and trusted Members. It keeps the joint neat and tidy, and its good for the group.</p>
<p>BTW: GJ on the rules, Mopar.</p>
<p>Fawk!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/44</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2007 05:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sup000 sup000]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sup000">@sup000</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Personally i believe that the will always be these issues. There are many many people her able to contribute, but there is a face on disagreement over the ideology to accept people who ‘do not help themselves’.<br>
I believe the contempt is not being DRIVEN by ‘those who don’t need naming’, but it has now come to a point where it has now become normal to see, everyday, people who are unable to follow the simplest of rules breading pure contempt in those that were once more than happy to give to a successful community.</p>
<p>It in time, without a doubt, will destroy the site to an even further extent.</p>
<p>Unless there is some give back, in respects of the way people want, or more to the point NEED, the site to operate, there will be no future for it. I agree there must always be a balance and new people must always be allowed to join the community, but lets face it, dictatorship didn’t stay around for years because it was 100% unsuccessful. Rules must be strict and you will find the community will benefit from it as a whole. Unless you agree to tighten down on the small things, i personally believe you will lose the last of the able bodied people you have managed to keep here.</p>
<p>In short:<br>
people will not give when they do not receive, fact.<br>
even if new bright minds come, they will still be EXPECTED to be unable, just due to the current situation of the site, and the pure volume of such people, fact.</p>
<p>I always believe the community ruined the likes of Regex etc. They were always able AND willing to contribute, and immaturity only grew from frustration of the situation as a whole. I can understand people getting upset to a degree when nothing changes - that is a life thing, but i do feel the responses are sometimes the only way people listen and/or learn.</p>
<p>Maybe i waffled there, who knows.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 17:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kamu Kamu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kamu">@Kamu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="41" data-topic="154606">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/moparisthebest/40/30_1.png" class="avatar"> Moparisthebest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It seems if anyone has given up it is Kamu.  This thread was made to give you-who-criticize input into how the site is ran, obviously you don’t care so I’ll open it up to the general public shortly to see their input.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Damn straight I have. I, like many others, have given up on you.</p>
<p>The forum is in the fucking shits and your solution is to rewrite the rules?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It seems if anyone has given up it is Kamu.  This thread was made to give you-who-criticize input into how the site is ran, obviously you don’t care so I’ll open it up to the general public shortly to see their input.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kamu, post:39, topic:154606”][quote author=Kmb link=topic=211199.msg1864127#msg1864127 date=1194114098]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Forget it. This place sucks and always will do. You tried to copy a forum that actually worked, but guess what, you aren’t Kaitnieks.</p>
<p>You failed.</p>
<p>Now we just need you to officially admit you have given up. Because it is evident that you have.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That is your opinion. I disagree.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I can tell you where you can ram said opinion too.[/quote]well said</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 20:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kamu Kamu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kamu">@Kamu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kmb, post:38, topic:154606”][quote author=Kamu link=topic=211199.msg1863485#msg1863485 date=1194079061]<br>
Forget it. This place sucks and always will do. You tried to copy a forum that actually worked, but guess what, you aren’t Kaitnieks.</p>
<p>You failed.</p>
<p>Now we just need you to officially admit you have given up. Because it is evident that you have.</p>
<p>[/quote]<br>
That is your opinion. I disagree.[/quote]</p>
<p>I can tell you where you can ram said opinion too.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 20:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kmb Kmb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kmb">@kmb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kamu, post:37, topic:154606”]Forget it. This place sucks and always will do. You tried to copy a forum that actually worked, but guess what, you aren’t Kaitnieks.</p>
<p>You failed.</p>
<p>Now we just need you to officially admit you have given up. Because it is evident that you have.[/quote]<br>
That is your opinion. I disagree.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 18:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kamu Kamu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kamu">@Kamu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Forget it. This place sucks and always will do. You tried to copy a forum that actually worked, but guess what, you aren’t Kaitnieks.</p>
<p>You failed.</p>
<p>Now we just need you to officially admit you have given up. Because it is evident that you have.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 08:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sup000 sup000]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sup000">@sup000</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>moparscape source was sent to me beyond years ago, and, at the time, it was made clear that the reason for it not being made public was fear, as mopar has already said, of copies and non legit modifications would be made from it and haxoryourpcscape would crop up. Tbh, the source sat in my email and was only browsed over due to lack of real interest or time. But as i said there was little objection to sharing it for the right reasons.</p>
<p>i already inputted more than i was actually willing to, so meh. b2l, and nice off topicness</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 00:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Miss Silabsoft, post:34, topic:154606”]im pretty sure mopar gives source upon request.[/quote]I guess he thought I was kidding every time I asked.</p>
<p>And anyone who has anything to say about my avatar; think to yourself.  What do you see?  Safes having sex.  Safe sex?  Oh my!  First off, it doesn’t even look like something to offend someone.  Your mom comes in?  I bet she’d chuckle.  Get the hell over it ruler.  You act like a child when that’s the only thing you can bring up.</p>
<p>Rep negation given to administrators and moderators couldn’t be such a bad thing.  Using this on moparscape would be an amazing tool, I might say ;].</p>
<p>I can’t really comment on the contribution thing, except that ruler doesn’t contribute anything.  I used to, I guess you could say, <span class="bbcode-i">be able</span> to contribute.  That knowledge is kind of outdated, so to speak.  Of course, my newer contributions are to try to keep this forum clean.  I hope to contribute more in the near future.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 18:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im pretty sure mopar gives source upon request.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/34</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 10:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ruler, post:20, topic:154606”][quote author=Lothy link=topic=211199.msg1857716#msg1857716 date=1193814250]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Remove all members who have sexual implications in their avatars.</p>
<p>Give contributors power in return for contributing.</p>
<p>abid by the GPL software license and release moparscape full source.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>How about we ban people that conspire as well? Along with all of the conspiracy nuts.</p>
<p>It’s obvious that you’ve just made it your mission to attack pwnd in a somewhat subtle way, just as you used to bitch about him apparently going out of his way to punish you.<br>
You should get over the whole moparscape thing too - if you want the source code, then decompile it.<br>
[/quote]<br>
People that conspire should not be acceptable for staff positions.</p>
<p>True decompiling is a possiblity however the license does not state decompiling as the method for getting source.[/quote]<br>
Aryan was derived from the runescape client - if any of them believe they have any rights at all, then tell them to seek legal advice. :rolleyes:<br>
Of course, I don’t believe you played any part in Aryan - how about you let them speak for themselves if they choose to do so.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/33</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 09:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:28, topic:154606”]Define the bolded ‘something’ into a tangible context then please.[/quote]frank_ had it right, but I’ll clarify. By “something”, I mean knowledge that isn’t shared by everyone and has some applicable use in the education of the frequenters of the forums, or possibly even within the management of the community. Anyways, because this little inferno is entirely pointless and off-topic, let’s just wrap things up now, mmmk? Also, I intend to do as you ask and make some proper questions for the quiz.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 08:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>would s/something/anything/ assist you perhaps?</p>
<p>you may look apon this community with pride, but you would be kidding yourself if you believed that perception to be true. so something innovative (do you need help with that ‘something’ too?), dont just let this ship sink, grab a bucket</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 08:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“frank_, post:29, topic:154606”]first sentence; abusing negative rep is caused by people being idiots, if this were allowed to truly become a decent community, such members would not obtain a position where they hold such influence</p>
<p>i wasnt capable of intelligent input, but i knew when to shut the fuck up and listen, i had a gauge of what level of question to ask, too. closing registrations i do not agree with, however some sort of test that requires at least some partially in depth research rather than just the results page of google to keep people who wont learn/dont have a clue away</p>
<p>[quote author=Moparisthebest link=topic=211199.msg1857862#msg1857862 date=1193818085]<br>
Define the bolded ‘something’ into a tangible context then please.<br>
[/quote]something that can be valued, perhaps[/quote]</p>
<p>I thought <a href="http://kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">kaitnieks.com</a> was a decent community, yet there was negative reputation abuse there.</p>
<p>Basically you seem to be advocating a more advanced type of quiz than we already have, the framework is there for both multiple choice answers and fill in the blank.  Make another thread suggesting the type of questions that <span class="bbcode-i">should</span> be on the quiz as opposed to what is <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/quiz.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">already there</a>.</p>
<p>Again, the use of the word something, that isn’t very specific at all.</p>
<p>edit: note that the current quiz does keep out quite a few complete morons, the number is at least in the thousands, you should see the posts on the quiz’s ‘technical problems’ board (being the only board people who haven’t taken the quiz can post in)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 08:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>first sentence; abusing negative rep is caused by people being idiots, if this were allowed to truly become a decent community, such members would not obtain a position where they hold such influence</p>
<p>i wasnt capable of intelligent input, but i knew when to shut the fuck up and listen, i had a gauge of what level of question to ask, too. closing registrations i do not agree with, however some sort of test that requires at least some partially in depth research rather than just the results page of google to keep people who wont learn/dont have a clue away</p>
<p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:28, topic:154606”]Define the bolded ‘something’ into a tangible context then please.[/quote]something that can be valued, perhaps</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 08:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Define the bolded ‘something’ into a tangible context then please.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 08:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>moparisthebest, I never said anything about programming knowledge. To suggest that this loose community is mainly programming-oriented is to lie. The average content of this website is comparable to the content of a pubescent girl’s phone conversations: “ohi” “ohi” “omg my ass is bleeding”. I don’t suggest that people know the mechanics of any programming language, but only that they bring <span class="bbcode-b">something</span> to the table beyond the realm of their immature bleeding anuses and Kitsune.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 08:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“frank_, post:25, topic:154606”][quote author=Moparisthebest link=topic=211199.msg1857833#msg1857833 date=1193817094]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>bring back rep negation</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Remember the horrible effect it had at <a href="http://kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">kaitnieks.com</a> and the reason it was removed there? I do.<br>
[/quote]when the average IQ is below the average age which is below teenager, you cannot expect to have maturity without forcing it, which you will not even attempt to do</p>
<p>[quote author=Moparisthebest link=topic=211199.msg1857833#msg1857833 date=1193817094]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Every member of this community should be a contributor, though this is not the case. I personally feel that those who do not make a small contribution should not be allowed to be here; people who join should be muted until they show evidence to an administrator or some set of judges that they are knowledgeable enough to contribute in some form. moparisthebest’s lenience is a death knell to progress of any sort or even just a bit of intelligent conversation. When I attempt to start a small discussion with someone on an interesting subject, I expect that I will not be headed off by a “stfulol” from a global moderator. Yes, yet another not-so-subtle attack on Pwnd.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>blah blah blah i dont want to lose ad money blah blah blah<br>
[/quote]cheating should not be about providing one click tools for kids, it should be an intelligent, mature discussion on how best to beat the system[/quote]</p>
<p>What do you mean by your first sentence?  How am I to enforce maturity on people?  If you have the answer to that I’m sure many parents, schools and institutions will be very interested.</p>
<p>I never said anything about providing one click tools for kids, but you can’t have any fresh influxes of potential talent by closing off registrations to all but the elite that is already in the community.  When you first joined RS cheating in the beginning were you capable of having ‘intelligent, mature discussion on how best to beat the system’? I know I wasn’t.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 08:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:24, topic:154606”][quote author=frank_ link=topic=211199.msg1857150#msg1857150 date=1193799754]<br>
bring back rep negation<br>
[/quote]<br>
Remember the horrible effect it had at <a href="http://kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">kaitnieks.com</a> and the reason it was removed there? I do.[/quote]when the average IQ is below the average age which is below teenager, you cannot expect to have maturity without forcing it, which you will not even attempt to do</p>
<p>[quote=“Moparisthebest, post:24, topic:154606”][quote author=Silver Lining link=topic=211199.msg1857740#msg1857740 date=1193814890]<br>
Every member of this community should be a contributor, though this is not the case. I personally feel that those who do not make a small contribution should not be allowed to be here; people who join should be muted until they show evidence to an administrator or some set of judges that they are knowledgeable enough to contribute in some form. moparisthebest’s lenience is a death knell to progress of any sort or even just a bit of intelligent conversation. When I attempt to start a small discussion with someone on an interesting subject, I expect that I will not be headed off by a “stfulol” from a global moderator. Yes, yet another not-so-subtle attack on Pwnd.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>blah blah blah i dont want to lose ad money blah blah blah[/quote]cheating should not be about providing one click tools for kids, it should be an intelligent, mature discussion on how best to beat the system</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 07:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Many things have been posted here, I’ll try to address them all (even though a few are off-topic)</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="14" data-topic="154606">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 frank_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>bring back rep negation</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Remember the horrible effect it had at <a href="http://kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">kaitnieks.com</a> and the reason it was removed there? I do.</p>
<p>[quote=“ruler, post:16, topic:154606”]Remove all members who have sexual implications in their avatars.</p>
<p>Give contributors power in return for contributing.</p>
<p>abid by the GPL software license and release moparscape full source.[/quote]<br>
This is off-topic, it has nothing to do with the rules and instead seems like an attack, oh well.</p>
<ol>
<li>It’s not like pwnd’s avatar is explicit, instead it is humorous, and clean, far worse ‘implications’ are in so-called children’s movies like shrek.  Just because you have something against pwnd in particular doesn’t mean everyone else should.</li>
<li>As in what? Currently they get status like Community Member and awards for contributing.</li>
<li>No one has ever asked for the source code to moparscape, but in fact I have released parts as people have requested them, for example the music player, and much much better refactorizations than I even use in moparscape, I didn’t modify the aryan portion, so that is readily available as well. Honestly there is only one reason I haven’t publicly released the source to everyone, and that is because in the past when I did this, many new clients sprung up with a new background, a new title and one added feature, namely trojans, keyloggers, or password stealers.</li>
</ol>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="18" data-topic="154606">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Silver Lining:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Every member of this community should be a contributor, though this is not the case. I personally feel that those who do not make a small contribution should not be allowed to be here; people who join should be muted until they show evidence to an administrator or some set of judges that they are knowledgeable enough to contribute in some form. moparisthebest’s lenience is a death knell to progress of any sort or even just a bit of intelligent conversation. When I attempt to start a small discussion with someone on an interesting subject, I expect that I will not be headed off by a “stfulol” from a global moderator. Yes, yet another not-so-subtle attack on Pwnd.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This is an open community that accepts newcomers, not drives them off.  Communities have certainly been created that function as you speak, and they have all died or withered away to nothing (ie reinet, now wartnet)  Since you have so conveniently volunteered yourself to be an example by posting, I will use you as one.  Silver Lining is an example of someone with the elitist attitude that we were discussing earlier.  He posts that basically the community should only allow people to speak if they can contribute (ie, if they have programming experience), yet he, as many people, joined this forum before he could code anything, he picked up help and advice from this forum, became a contributor, and now wants to close it off to future talent? Hypocrite much?  (I started out much the same, not on this forum but on <a href="http://kaitnieks.com" rel="nofollow noopener">kaitnieks.com</a>, I could program basic java and had already written 2 nice SCAR scripts before I joined, but I did learn much from the community afterwards)</p>
<p>[quote=“newbiehacker, post:19, topic:154606”][quote=rules]<br>
If you get banned or have trouble logging in, click ‘forgot my password’, email an admin, or get a friend to contact an admin.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I think this line should be rephrased, as some people might read it and think that you should email an admin if you get banned, which I’m sure would cause unnecessary stress for your admins.[/quote]<br>
It does need reworded to be more clear, thanks.</p>
<p>[quote=“ruler, post:20, topic:154606”]People that conspire should not be acceptable for staff positions.</p>
<p>True decompiling is a possiblity however the license does not state decompiling as the method for getting source.[/quote]<br>
Also I purposefully did not obfuscate it, so that anyone who really wants the full source code can get it. V3 of the GNU/GPL states ‘Our General Public Licenses are designed to make sure that you have the freedom to distribute copies of free software (and charge for them if you wish), that you receive source code or can get it if you want it’  Well, using JAD or JODE you can ‘get it if you want’ (or asking me as well)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 07:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruler ruler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruler">@ruler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“frank_, post:21, topic:154606”]dude, its a piece of shit, it isnt worth decompiling</p>
<p>i dont see why you care about it even, you have never obeyed a license before[/quote]<br>
I obeyed the arga license.  I obeyed the Aryan License for 2 month then i got permission to break it after silbasoft and newbiehacker decided to remove the auth system from a open source bot and release it on this site.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 07:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wonder ruler, did you understand that Lothy was talking about <span class="bbcode-i">you</span>? To target moparisthebest now, do you see how idiotic your advocacy of open-source everything paired with your closed-source software is? Lead by example. Finally, to all “contributors”, stop expecting enormous recognition for your contributions. It is not some heroic deed of yours that you wrote a bot and released a stripped-down version of it for free, nor should you expect a staff position because you’ve given some minimal help. Stop acting as though you are the single candle fighting to stay lit while your peers try to smother your flame.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 07:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>dude, its a piece of shit, it isnt worth decompiling</p>
<p>i dont see why you care about it even, you have never obeyed a license before</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 07:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Rules</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ruler ruler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruler">@ruler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lothy, post:17, topic:154606”][quote author=ruler link=topic=211199.msg1857670#msg1857670 date=1193812513]<br>
Remove all members who have sexual implications in their avatars.</p>
<p>Give contributors power in return for contributing.</p>
<p>abid by the GPL software license and release moparscape full source.<br>
[/quote]<br>
How about we ban people that conspire as well? Along with all of the conspiracy nuts.</p>
<p>It’s obvious that you’ve just made it your mission to attack pwnd in a somewhat subtle way, just as you used to bitch about him apparently going out of his way to punish you.<br>
You should get over the whole moparscape thing too - if you want the source code, then decompile it.[/quote]<br>
People that conspire should not be acceptable for staff positions.</p>
<p>True decompiling is a possiblity however the license does not state decompiling as the method for getting source.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 07:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154606-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-rules/154606.rss">New Rules</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
