<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HELP js5 connect problem when server&#39;s online? HELP</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-js5-connect-problem-when-servers-online-help/325664</link>
    <description>Well, today, I was playing my server and editing it in the files. Also, I went into NPCspawn, I deleted some NPC&#39;s that kinda lagged my server. They were legend guards saying my servers name and I didn&#39;t want so many. So I deleted some from the NPCspawn.java notepad, and i saved, compiled. So then I ran the server, thinking everything&#39;s fine. I opened up my client and it got stuck at connecting to update server. The client prompt thing said error_js5connect thing. But, I turned on the server. So now my client won&#39;t connect to my server. And help? Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 23:40:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-js5-connect-problem-when-servers-online-help/325664.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HELP js5 connect problem when server&#39;s online? HELP</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1337_D 1337 :D]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1337_d">@1337_D</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, today, I was playing my server and editing it in the files. Also, I went into NPCspawn, I deleted some NPC’s that kinda lagged my server. They were legend guards saying my servers name and I didn’t want so many. So I deleted some from the NPCspawn.java notepad, and i saved, compiled. So then I ran the server, thinking everything’s fine. I opened up my client and it got stuck at connecting to update server. The client prompt thing said error_js5connect thing. But, I turned on the server. So now my client won’t connect to my server. And help? Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-js5-connect-problem-when-servers-online-help/325664/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-js5-connect-problem-when-servers-online-help/325664/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 23:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-325664-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-js5-connect-problem-when-servers-online-help/325664.rss">HELP js5 connect problem when server&#39;s online? HELP</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
