<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>FPA Games 1.2.5</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fpa-games-1-2-5/446919</link>
    <description>[IMG]http://i46.tinypic.com/2luxtlu.jpg[/img]

This is FPA Games! The official Minecraft server! It is a 24/7 server! And will be a constinit 24/7 server!

IP:[img]https://minecraftus.avantehosting.net/index.php?r=status/3815.png[/img]
72.29.88.18:25611


Owner: Ima_Davie_Boy
Co-Owner: butteredjames [Me :D]

We have amazing benifits on our server. We have Factions for all players! We have set-up Buycraft to purchase things such as &#39;VIP&#39; and &#39;Platinum&#39; with AMAZING benifits for those.

Plugins we use: World Portal, WorldEdit, AntiBot, BuyCraft, War, Vault, PermissionsEx, ComatTag, Jail, CraftBay, marriage, ObbyDestruct, ZavAutoMessanger, TheReaperThatCares, NoCheat, mcMMO, MobDisguise, Essentials, Citizens, EssentialsProtect, CommandIConomy, EssentialsSpawn, PluginsBaker, iGates, ChestShop, Essentials Chat, and Factions!

CombatTag: Lets say you&#39;re in a fight with someone, this eliminates them from logging in the middle and creates a fake person in his spot, for you to kill. So let&#39;s say, Ima_Davie_Boy attacks me, and I log, it creates a fake character for that time being, Which I don&#39;t know how long the logger is there, will check in due time. And you kill the logged player, and you get all the stuff he was carrying. This will prevent PvP logging. Since we got tired of it.

We plan on adding more plugin&#39;s in the future! So watch out for those! If you have a plugin here that you don&#39;t see, and think we should add, let us know! We would greatly appreciate your suggestions for plugins and such!

 
[IMG]http://i47.tinypic.com/wck2lh.png[/img]

That&#39;s the only picture I feel is needed to be shown, since that it&#39;s mainly in one &#39;location&#39;. But I will post a few &#39;upclose&#39; ones soon. The PvP Arena and Donator room are currently being contructed as you&#39;re reading this! And if you have any questions, comment below, and add your own feedback. :)

No rude commends. -.- We know, our spawn sucks. Woo. Make us a new one if you feel this one isn&#39;t very good at all. That would help you out, and could possibly achieve you a rank. ;)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 00:11:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fpa-games-1-2-5/446919.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>FPA Games 1.2.5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Demon6994 Demon6994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/demon6994">@Demon6994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://i46.tinypic.com/2luxtlu.jpg" alt width="468" height="60"></p>
<p>This is FPA Games! The official Minecraft server! It is a 24/7 server! And will be a constinit 24/7 server!</p>
<p>IP:<img src="https://minecraftus.avantehosting.net/index.php?r=status/3815.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
72.29.88.18:25611</p>
<p>Owner: Ima_Davie_Boy<br>
Co-Owner: butteredjames [Me :D]</p>
<p>We have amazing benifits on our server. We have Factions for all players! We have set-up Buycraft to purchase things such as ‘VIP’ and ‘Platinum’ with AMAZING benifits for those.</p>
<p>Plugins we use: World Portal, WorldEdit, AntiBot, BuyCraft, War, Vault, PermissionsEx, ComatTag, Jail, CraftBay, marriage, ObbyDestruct, ZavAutoMessanger, TheReaperThatCares, NoCheat, mcMMO, MobDisguise, Essentials, Citizens, EssentialsProtect, CommandIConomy, EssentialsSpawn, PluginsBaker, iGates, ChestShop, Essentials Chat, and Factions!</p>
<p>CombatTag: Lets say you’re in a fight with someone, this eliminates them from logging in the middle and creates a fake person in his spot, for you to kill. So let’s say, Ima_Davie_Boy attacks me, and I log, it creates a fake character for that time being, Which I don’t know how long the logger is there, will check in due time. And you kill the logged player, and you get all the stuff he was carrying. This will prevent PvP logging. Since we got tired of it.</p>
<p>We plan on adding more plugin’s in the future! So watch out for those! If you have a plugin here that you don’t see, and think we should add, let us know! We would greatly appreciate your suggestions for plugins and such!</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i47.tinypic.com/wck2lh.png" title="wck2lh.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i47.tinypic.com/wck2lh.png" alt width="690" height="384"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">wck2lh.png</span><span class="informations">854×476</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>That’s the only picture I feel is needed to be shown, since that it’s mainly in one ‘location’. But I will post a few ‘upclose’ ones soon. The PvP Arena and Donator room are currently being contructed as you’re reading this! And if you have any questions, comment below, and add your own feedback. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>No rude commends. -.- We know, our spawn sucks. Woo. Make us a new one if you feel this one isn’t very good at all. That would help you out, and could possibly achieve you a rank. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fpa-games-1-2-5/446919/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fpa-games-1-2-5/446919/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 00:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-446919-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fpa-games-1-2-5/446919.rss">FPA Games 1.2.5</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
