<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Official moparscape?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/official-moparscape/445045</link>
    <description>When I first joined Moparscape I actually thought there would be a &quot;Moparscape&quot; server and was disappointed to find out there wasn&#39;t.

What I suggest is a official Moparscape server for the Moparscape community. Obviously a lot of rules would need to be put in place for this to work how I imagine, I don&#39;t know if this hasn&#39;t already been done due to legal issues but if MITB can host a status page advertising hundreds of private servers surely he could host a server however I don&#39;t know much about legal stuff so I could just be being naive.

The server could work just like the minecraft server we have(moparcraft). I&#39;m willing to listen to all arguments for and against but I for one would love to see this. It&#39;s late so I&#39;ll expand this more if this gets past approval by you mods.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 02:10:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/official-moparscape/445045.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Official moparscape?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It is in the planning phase, but I can’t go beyond that. You’ll learn more as it progresses. Thanks for the suggestion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/official-moparscape/445045/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/official-moparscape/445045/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 02:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445045-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/official-moparscape/445045.rss">Official moparscape?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Official moparscape?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kickingjamie kickingjamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kickingjamie">@kickingjamie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When I first joined Moparscape I actually thought there would be a “Moparscape” server and was disappointed to find out there wasn’t.</p>
<p>What I suggest is a official Moparscape server for the Moparscape community. Obviously a lot of rules would need to be put in place for this to work how I imagine, I don’t know if this hasn’t already been done due to legal issues but if MITB can host a status page advertising hundreds of private servers surely he could host a server however I don’t know much about legal stuff so I could just be being naive.</p>
<p>The server could work just like the minecraft server we have(moparcraft). I’m willing to listen to all arguments for and against but I for one would love to see this. It’s late so I’ll expand this more if this gets past approval by you mods.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/official-moparscape/445045/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/official-moparscape/445045/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445045-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/official-moparscape/445045.rss">Official moparscape?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
