<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forum downtime 10-30-2009</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-downtime-10-30-2009/311566</link>
    <description>If you were wondering what caused the downtime today, like I was when I got home about 30 minutes ago, here is what I found out.

My host &#39;accidentally&#39; null-routed the IP for moparisthebest.com.  I received no email, no phone call, I just got home after a long day of moving and found the IP didn&#39;t work.  To their credit they were quick and helpful getting the IP back online, but it should have never been taken offline in the first place, certainly without notifying me first.

Bottom line is someone over there dropped the ball and I&#39;m mad about it  :mad:  I&#39;ll update this thread when any more details come to light, probably Monday when all the bosses go back to work.  I hate hosting companies sometimes...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2009 04:09:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-downtime-10-30-2009/311566.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Forum downtime 10-30-2009</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you were wondering what caused the downtime today, like I was when I got home about 30 minutes ago, here is what I found out.</p>
<p>My host ‘accidentally’ null-routed the IP for <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a>.  I received no email, no phone call, I just got home after a long day of moving and found the IP didn’t work.  To their credit they were quick and helpful getting the IP back online, but it should have never been taken offline in the first place, certainly without notifying me first.</p>
<p>Bottom line is someone over there dropped the ball and I’m mad about it  :mad:  I’ll update this thread when any more details come to light, probably Monday when all the bosses go back to work.  I hate hosting companies sometimes…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-downtime-10-30-2009/311566/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-downtime-10-30-2009/311566/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2009 04:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-311566-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-downtime-10-30-2009/311566.rss">Forum downtime 10-30-2009</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
