<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878</link>
    <description>How can i make my server so others can play on my server 

thanks if someone can help me out[br][size=1]Posted at: August 24, 2006, 08:11:45 AM[/size][hr]FFs this is gay no one helps each other and then they complain about all the &quot;noobs&quot; maybe there wouldn&#39;t be as many if u actuly helped each other and don&#39;t say uer the search button cause i have tryed everything on this site and have been on this fucking pc for nearly 5 hours now doing nothing but trying to get this server to work for other players so please don&#39;t just click my topic read and go noob then go off saying this forum full of noobs cause it&#39;s your own fault  why do u think we go to school to be taught by another person (teacher) think as yourself as the teacher and me as the pupil your helping me so  i can learn then help others then everyone will know so please tell me how to make it so others may connect to my server because i have tryed everything normal ip,hamahci,no-ip and loads of others so for god&#39;s sake tell me how to let other connect to my server

thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 18:07:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lucas lucas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lucas">@lucas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yea ive tryed that it don’t work</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 18:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10878-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878.rss">Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@X_Mike X_Mike]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x_mike">@X_Mike</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I Agree Man… I Have The Same Problem… U Have Just To Find Ur Ip And Give It To Ur Friends, Then Run Ur Server And U’ll Tell The To Get In…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 17:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10878-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878.rss">Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lucas lucas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lucas">@lucas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>How can i make my server so others can play on my server</p>
<p>thanks if someone can help me out[br][size=1]Posted at: August 24, 2006, 08:11:45 AM[/size][hr]FFs this is gay no one helps each other and then they complain about all the “noobs” maybe there wouldn’t be as many if u actuly helped each other and don’t say uer the search button cause i have tryed everything on this site and have been on this fucking pc for nearly 5 hours now doing nothing but trying to get this server to work for other players so please don’t just click my topic read and go noob then go off saying this forum full of noobs cause it’s your own fault  why do u think we go to school to be taught by another person (teacher) think as yourself as the teacher and me as the pupil your helping me so  i can learn then help others then everyone will know so please tell me how to make it so others may connect to my server because i have tryed everything normal ip,hamahci,no-ip and loads of others so for god’s sake tell me how to let other connect to my server</p>
<p>thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 17:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-10878-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/10878.rss">Help?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
