<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/349214</link>
    <description>Hey guys, i&#39;ve been trying to play mopar for a while, i used to play back in the day but then i stopped. I never had trouble connecting to servers back then, but now its all about downloading the clients, and im sure this question gets asked ooo so much. I&#39;ve used google, and tried to find any help whatsoever but i just can&#39;t. I&#39;m sure its easy to figure out, i downloaded mopar 3.2 and also have the webclient 4.1...i&#39;m just not sure how to get into a server. i know all about the status checker and what not, but when i download the client for the server im trying to get into where do i put it in order to play? i really do appreciate the help, thanks guys.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 21:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/349214.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@j19283746 j19283746]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/j19283746">@j19283746</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wrong section.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/349214/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/349214/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 21:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349214-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/349214.rss">Help?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Instant_Kill Instant Kill]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/instant_kill">@Instant_Kill</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, i’ve been trying to play mopar for a while, i used to play back in the day but then i stopped. I never had trouble connecting to servers back then, but now its all about downloading the clients, and im sure this question gets asked ooo so much. I’ve used google, and tried to find any help whatsoever but i just can’t. I’m sure its easy to figure out, i downloaded mopar 3.2 and also have the webclient 4.1…i’m just not sure how to get into a server. i know all about the status checker and what not, but when i download the client for the server im trying to get into where do i put it in order to play? i really do appreciate the help, thanks guys.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/349214/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/349214/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 16:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349214-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/349214.rss">Help?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
