<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/398266</link>
    <description>[size=14pt]I was just wondering if i could get some help on a small project im working on.
Basically i downloaded a blank source and client . Im working on the client and source. i am a noob coder so i don&#39;t know much about the coding and all. So i had a few questions maybe someone could help ?

1st question - i was wondering how do i change my home location when i log in im in lumbridge and my home teleport is lumbridge how can i set it to spawn in edgeville.

2nd question - i tried to install i shop first i set a ncp id - 520 (shop keeper) at x and y cord 3222 3218 (Lumbridge center) when i attempted to add items to the shop i couldn&#39;t access my server. i then deleted all the code i added to the server.

3rd question - If anyone has a textbox and titlebox for the pillar&#39;s and the burning torches background could you possibly post here or give me a link to get ?

Please and thank you. Im not sure if i need to present this in a format or not. but like i said im a noob coder. Im interested in learning how to do so, maybe in the future you&#39;ll see some of my work. I have some good idea&#39;s for the server but i need to get the basic&#39;s down. my plan is to edit the blank source and client to a basic server. first shop&#39;s . anti leech. anti lagg. anti dupe. ban names that start with admin etc. etc. So i need some help doing so. if anyone could help me i would gladly appreciate it.[/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 23:10:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/398266.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uwpkz Uwpkz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uwpkz">@Uwpkz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=14pt]I was just wondering if i could get some help on a small project im working on.<br>
Basically i downloaded a blank source and client . Im working on the client and source. i am a noob coder so i don’t know much about the coding and all. So i had a few questions maybe someone could help ?</p>
<p>1st question - i was wondering how do i change my home location when i log in im in lumbridge and my home teleport is lumbridge how can i set it to spawn in edgeville.</p>
<p>2nd question - i tried to install i shop first i set a ncp id - 520 (shop keeper) at x and y cord 3222 3218 (Lumbridge center) when i attempted to add items to the shop i couldn’t access my server. i then deleted all the code i added to the server.</p>
<p>3rd question - If anyone has a textbox and titlebox for the pillar’s and the burning torches background could you possibly post here or give me a link to get ?</p>
<p>Please and thank you. Im not sure if i need to present this in a format or not. but like i said im a noob coder. Im interested in learning how to do so, maybe in the future you’ll see some of my work. I have some good idea’s for the server but i need to get the basic’s down. my plan is to edit the blank source and client to a basic server. first shop’s . anti leech. anti lagg. anti dupe. ban names that start with admin etc. etc. So i need some help doing so. if anyone could help me i would gladly appreciate it.[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/398266/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/398266/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 23:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-398266-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help/398266.rss">Help?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
