<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A Helping Had Is Needed No-ip!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-helping-had-is-needed-no-ip/345543</link>
    <description>heya i have been tryed to setup my own server like 1 year ago but my net gear box back then was rubish! So what have i fianaly brought your asking? I GOT A NEW WIRELESS ROUTER :D oh yes i did i still have mi source all ready to go its a 508 i got mi client all good. So what is the problem you may be asking! the problem is i have port forwarded the correct port thats all good. but i cant get this no-ip to work ! i have a smiley face and everything but still only i can connect! dont let me fail at this another time please!!! thanks for your time if you want to email me or add me on msn to give me sum assistance then please do its: g-unit_maz8@hotmail.co.uk

THANKS ( ps. if your sat there thinking why shud i waste mi time with this stranger? Just sit back in ur chair take a deep breath and ask yourself wot would jesus do.....? )

(PSps. come on help me if u laughed at that help me! woop) Thanks for reading hope u laughed :) Have A Nice Day</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 23:36:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-helping-had-is-needed-no-ip/345543.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A Helping Had Is Needed No-ip!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spikemaz Spikemaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spikemaz">@Spikemaz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>heya i have been tryed to setup my own server like 1 year ago but my net gear box back then was rubish! So what have i fianaly brought your asking? I GOT A NEW WIRELESS ROUTER <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> oh yes i did i still have mi source all ready to go its a 508 i got mi client all good. So what is the problem you may be asking! the problem is i have port forwarded the correct port thats all good. but i cant get this no-ip to work ! i have a smiley face and everything but still only i can connect! dont let me fail at this another time please!!! thanks for your time if you want to email me or add me on msn to give me sum assistance then please do its: <a href="mailto:g-unit_maz8@hotmail.co.uk">g-unit_maz8@hotmail.co.uk</a></p>
<p>THANKS ( ps. if your sat there thinking why shud i waste mi time with this stranger? Just sit back in ur chair take a deep breath and ask yourself wot would jesus do…? )</p>
<p>(PSps. come on help me if u laughed at that help me! woop) Thanks for reading hope u laughed <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Have A Nice Day</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-helping-had-is-needed-no-ip/345543/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-helping-had-is-needed-no-ip/345543/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 23:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-345543-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-helping-had-is-needed-no-ip/345543.rss">A Helping Had Is Needed No-ip!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
