<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help getting server up</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-getting-server-up/279474</link>
    <description>Like the title says, I need help getting my server up. I tried port forwarding but my parents changed the username and password on the router and they won&#39;t tell me it. So then i found out about the uTorrent method, which seemed to work like a charm. But when I checked my server status with a status checker, it said my server is down. I made sure my uTorrent is set at port 43594, I ran my server before opening uTorrent, and I opened port 43594 on my computer. Any help would be appreciated, since I just spent the last half year of my life coding my server, and I would be pretty mad if I can&#39;t get it up.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 22:27:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-getting-server-up/279474.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help getting server up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@afataldonkey afataldonkey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/afataldonkey">@afataldonkey</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Like the title says, I need help getting my server up. I tried port forwarding but my parents changed the username and password on the router and they won’t tell me it. So then i found out about the uTorrent method, which seemed to work like a charm. But when I checked my server status with a status checker, it said my server is down. I made sure my uTorrent is set at port 43594, I ran my server before opening uTorrent, and I opened port 43594 on my computer. Any help would be appreciated, since I just spent the last half year of my life coding my server, and I would be pretty mad if I can’t get it up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-getting-server-up/279474/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-getting-server-up/279474/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 22:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-279474-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-getting-server-up/279474.rss">Help getting server up</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
