<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257</link>
    <description>I need some help telling my parents about my true religious beliefs. 
Story time: I was born and raised a Christian, however around the age of 13, I started to question my beliefs and a few weeks later claimed to be an Atheist. I changed my religious beliefs (on facebook) to Atheist, and my family members saw, whom then reported the sudden change to my parents. My parents called me into their room and a baww-fest commenced, and then they started making me go to church with them every Sunday, and made me have weekly talks with their pastor and I had to write down why I was questioning my beliefs. It was honestly hard to explain, so what I wrote down didn&#39;t seem convincing to them. My pastor then went on to preach to me from his bible saying quotes from it and saying how evolution was false, etc. I also had to have daily conferences with my parents about my beliefs (an hour each day), but really all they did was tell me stories about what&#39;s going to happen if I don&#39;t believe in Christianity (they used the good ol&#39; scare tactics). They also, along with multiple other families they&#39;re friends with, bought me a giant bag full of books on why Christianity is the way to go, and why evolution is wrong. One cold day in December, my mom angrily called for me to come into the computer room where she was sitting. She wanted to know where I started to get these ideas that made me question my faith in Christianity, and so off the top of my head, I said science class at school (8th grade at the time), however looking back on it, it really wasn&#39;t the school&#39;s fault, because I questioned my faith on my own time, not because of school. Anyways, she proceeded to write a very angry e-mail to the school saying how they shouldn&#39;t be teaching evolution (even though they hardly even touched on it at all, just said the word once) because it&#39;s causing me to question my faith and all this other stuff. Then a few weeks later my principal had a meeting with me saying that he&#39;s sorry what was in the textbooks caused me to question my faith, and some more awkward talk happened that I can&#39;t remember (he was actually pretty calm about all this like it&#39;s happened before), then I went back to class. Eventually, after a couple weeks of these stressful events and daily conferences with my parents and weekly conferences with my pastor, I just gave in and claimed to magically be a Christian again, and all went back to normal. Although a couple months later, a couple weeks after I got confirmed, I secretly took my place (religiously) as an Agnostic. Over time I looked into other religions and philosophies like Buddhism and Taoism, and as of late, I&#39;ve been really liking the ideas of Taoism and would like to look more into it.
So my question to you is, how can I come out to my VERY Christian parents that I don&#39;t share the same religious beliefs as them, but without getting pressured and scared into believing in their religion like they did last time?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 20:47:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“reyx7, post:18, topic:422257”]Religion was established to answer the unanswerable. Technology has far advanced since those days, and I believe it’s lost purpose.[/quote]I didn’t know you were alive when religion was established =O!</p>
<p>locked on request</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 20:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Religion was established to answer the unanswerable. Technology has far advanced since those days, and I believe it’s lost purpose.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@r0ckstar96 r0ckstar96]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r0ckstar96">@r0ckstar96</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“SilentCJ, post:15, topic:422257”]Religion is stupid, never liked it, a load of rubbish.</p>
<p>Anyway, I’d express your reasoning behind your change and make it sound all intelligent, then basically say it’s my life, I can believe in what I want and your beliefs are not going to influence my own.[/quote]<br>
Me gusta</p>
<p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:16, topic:422257”]Most here probably know I’m Christian and I’d be happy to answer and questions you may have about it if you want to. I completely agree with John, you can believe in science and have a religion without having to chose one over the other.</p>
<p>The main message in the bible (red letters) is to love everyone as He loved us, not that the universe was created in 7 days or Adam and Eve were nude when they met (hubba hubba).</p>
<p>That’s the main issue people see with religion, they can’t accept or don’t believe that the miracles could have happened. And to that I say - does it matter? As long as you love God and love people, you will go to heaven.</p>
<p>Personally I’m with you. I don’t know whether or not I believe the stories of Genesis or not, science can be pretty convincing at times <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> I believe one hundred percent God exists and Jesus walked this earth, and I believe that as long as I love my neighbor as myself and love God, I have nothing to worry about.</p>
<p>Sorry for getting sidetracked into the religion itself… anywho… I suggest you talk to them about it. Tell them about your doubts, questions, or fears. See what they reply? If they tell you to just ‘have faith’ I suggest go to someone else about it. They are still your parents at the moment so you need to be careful…[/quote]<br>
I like the way you think =o Ahh but don’t worry about me, I’ll find myself and what I believe in some day<br>
Thank ya David</p>
<hr>
<p>Hey guys, I’m going to bring this up with my parents sometime although I might have my cousin be there just in case, because she was in the same boat once, although she flat out told her parents how it was gonna be and didn’t do any meetings or conferences.<br>
SO with all that being said, I thank you all for your responses, and will dwell on what has been said here.<br>
Could a mod please lock this thread?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 18:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Most here probably know I’m Christian and I’d be happy to answer and questions you may have about it if you want to. I completely agree with John, you can believe in science and have a religion without having to chose one over the other.</p>
<p>The main message in the bible (red letters) is to love everyone as He loved us, not that the universe was created in 7 days or Adam and Eve were nude when they met (hubba hubba).</p>
<p>That’s the main issue people see with religion, they can’t accept or don’t believe that the miracles could have happened. And to that I say - does it matter? As long as you love God and love people, you will go to heaven.</p>
<p>Personally I’m with you. I don’t know whether or not I believe the stories of Genesis or not, science can be pretty convincing at times <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> I believe one hundred percent God exists and Jesus walked this earth, and I believe that as long as I love my neighbor as myself and love God, I have nothing to worry about.</p>
<p>Sorry for getting sidetracked into the religion itself… anywho… I suggest you talk to them about it. Tell them about your doubts, questions, or fears. See what they reply? If they tell you to just ‘have faith’ I suggest go to someone else about it. They are still your parents at the moment so you need to be careful…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 18:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SilentCJ SilentCJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silentcj">@SilentCJ</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Religion is stupid, never liked it, a load of rubbish.</p>
<p>Anyway, I’d express your reasoning behind your change and make it sound all intelligent, then basically say it’s my life, I can believe in what I want and your beliefs are not going to influence my own.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 18:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@r0ckstar96 r0ckstar96]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r0ckstar96">@r0ckstar96</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="12" data-topic="422257">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 mona lisa:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>it seems you really dont know what you believe in, jumping from one religion or belief to another. Study them all, find which one best suits your beliefs then decide dont just change every other week. also remember that being christian is defined as being Christ-like.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I really don’t know what I believe in honestly, as you can tell <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> At the moment I’m reading into Taoism, but Buddhism has my interests as well. Gah, I’ll get it figured and sorted out eventually. For now, I shall take your advice and just study them all =3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 17:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zuppers zuppers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zuppers">@zuppers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I feel for sorry for you. I have dumb as shit parents too.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mona_lisa mona lisa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mona_lisa">@mona_lisa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>it seems you really dont know what you believe in, jumping from one religion or belief to another. Study them all, find which one best suits your beliefs then decide dont just change every other week. also remember that being christian is defined as being Christ-like.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 17:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@r0ckstar96 r0ckstar96]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r0ckstar96">@r0ckstar96</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="422257">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/travas/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Travas:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They can’t really force you to believe in something.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>They can sure as hell try, though</p>
<p>[quote=“John459, post:3, topic:422257”]“Those who do not believe scripture and science can coexist either do not know know enough scripture, or do not know enough science.”</p>
<p>Remember that.[/quote]<br>
Will do</p>
<p>[quote=“lostmyphat, post:4, topic:422257”][quote author=r0ckstar96 link=topic=524927.msg3821088#msg3821088 date=1321767219]<br>
I need some help telling my parents about my true religious beliefs.<br>
Story time: I was born and raised a Christian, however around the age of 13, I started to question my beliefs and a few weeks later claimed to be an Atheist. I changed my religious beliefs (on facebook) to Atheist, and my family members saw, whom then reported the sudden change to my parents. My parents called me into their room and a baww-fest commenced, and then they started making me go to church with them every Sunday, and made me have weekly talks with their pastor and I had to write down why I was questioning my beliefs. It was honestly hard to explain, so what I wrote down didn’t seem convincing to them. My pastor then went on to preach to me from his bible saying quotes from it and saying how evolution was false, etc. I also had to have daily conferences with my parents about my beliefs (an hour each day), but really all they did was tell me stories about what’s going to happen if I don’t believe in Christianity (they used the good ol’ scare tactics). They also, along with multiple other families they’re friends with, bought me a giant bag full of books on why Christianity is the way to go, and why evolution is wrong. One cold day in December, my mom angrily called for me to come into the computer room where she was sitting. She wanted to know where I started to get these ideas that made me question my faith in Christianity, and so off the top of my head, I said science class at school (8th grade at the time), however looking back on it, it really wasn’t the school’s fault, because I questioned my faith on my own time, not because of school. Anyways, she proceeded to write a very angry e-mail to the school saying how they shouldn’t be teaching evolution (even though they hardly even touched on it at all, just said the word once) because it’s causing me to question my faith and all this other stuff. Then a few weeks later my principal had a meeting with me saying that he’s sorry what was in the textbooks caused me to question my faith, and some more awkward talk happened that I can’t remember (he was actually pretty calm about all this like it’s happened before), then I went back to class. Eventually, after a couple weeks of these stressful events and daily conferences with my parents and weekly conferences with my pastor, I just gave in and claimed to magically be a Christian again, and all went back to normal. Although a couple months later, a couple weeks after I got confirmed, I secretly took my place (religiously) as an Agnostic. Over time I looked into other religions and philosophies like Buddhism and Taoism, and as of late, I’ve been really liking the ideas of Taoism and would like to look more into it.<br>
So my question to you is, how can I come out to my VERY Christian parents that I don’t share the same religious beliefs as them, but without getting pressured and scared into believing in their religion like they did last time?<br>
[/quote]<br>
And what are your reasons for you to question your faith?[/quote]<br>
Well, it’s a bit hard to explain, although it’s mainly because I just started to think something just wasn’t right. Something wasn’t clicking between me and Christianity, and I just couldn’t take it seriously anymore and just thought of it all to be make believe. And on my free time I did read about evolution.</p>
<p>[quote=“vManlyMan, post:5, topic:422257”]Think of how they would respond and be ready to counter it.  That’s what you should do in any situation.</p>
<p>And imo, religion is stupid and the world would be better off without it.  I can’t think of anything good that has come out of religion, only wars.[/quote]<br>
Well, the reason I didn’t want to tell them back when I was 13, was because of that, and I’ve always been really paranoid so I was afraid that they’d sneak into my room at night and kill me because I was unholy, or they’d (physically) torture me into believing again, so yeah… &gt;.&gt;</p>
<p>[quote=“The Outsider, post:6, topic:422257”]Your parents probably won’t accept it so either keep it to yourself and move on when you’re older or put your foot down and rebel.</p>
<p>You know, there is no divine spirit and science is right, and the universe basically “popped” into existence from nothing. Here’s a video you might find interesting that will explain it a lot more:</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Personally, I don’t like religious people that much, because most of them think it’s their duty to convert you. Well how about respect my beliefs as I do yours (tell your parents that).</p>
<p>P.S. Don’t take advice from people off of the internet, lol…[/quote]<br>
I’m gonna have to put my foot down at some point</p>
<p>[quote=“xryz, post:7, topic:422257”][quote author=The Outsider link=topic=524927.msg3821144#msg3821144 date=1321774521]<br>
Your parents probably won’t accept it so either keep it to yourself and move on when you’re older or put your foot down and rebel.</p>
<p>You know, there is no divine spirit and science is right, and the universe basically “popped” into existence from nothing. Here’s a video you might find interesting that will explain it a lot more:</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="WQhd05ZVYWg" data-youtube-title="Curiosity with Stephen Hawking, Did God Create the Universe?" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>Personally, I don’t like religious people that much, because most of them think it’s their duty to convert you. Well how about respect my beliefs as I do yours (tell your parents that).</p>
<p>P.S. Don’t take advice from people off of the internet, lol…<br>
[/quote]<br>
There is as much evidence of the universe “popping” into existence as there is about God. So to claim that is fact is just as bad as any religious person claiming that their God is fact.</p>
<p>yes from my sig u can see i believe in a God(b/c of all the evidence in life that suggested that a God does exist). I have been born as raised a christian, currently I really dont want to claim to be a christian even though most of my beliefs are christian, im pretty open-minded and always trying to grow my knowledge.</p>
<p>OP: tell them why u feel this way. If they say they will disown u and kick u out or something thats not very christian-like(, helping, or loving either) to be honest, and in that case reference the story in the bible about how the son of this rich man(may have been a king idr I’ve never read the bible fully) tells his father he would like to leave and would like his inheritance from his father, and about how when the son comes back years later; the father throws a party that his son comes back(point is a child is always your child no matter what they do or decide and you should love them even when they choose to do something that upsets you). also may I add anyone who claims to be a christian and wanders away most-likely(no saying that the case all the time) has never felt the presence of God or been truly trying to be a christian. gl to anyway.[/quote]<br>
I remember that story =o And yeah I never really tried because I was just born into it all as though that was part of life and I only went to church and believed because they wanted me to</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="422257">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/rscshadow/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> RSCShadow:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote](b/c of all the evidence in life that suggested that a God does exist).[/quote]If that’s all you’re looking for, that’s all you’re going to find. Religion isn’t based on evidence btw.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Indeed, religion is based on faith</p>
<p>[quote=“The Outsider, post:9, topic:422257”][quote author=xryz link=topic=524927.msg3821150#msg3821150 date=1321775861]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote></blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There is as much evidence of the universe “popping” into existence as there is about God. So to claim that is fact is just as bad as any religious person claiming that their God is fact.</p>
<p>yes from my sig u can see i believe in a God(b/c of all the evidence in life that suggested that a God does exist). I have been born as raised a christian, currently I really dont want to claim to be a christian even though most of my beliefs are christian, im pretty open-minded and always trying to grow my knowledge.</p>
<p>OP: tell them why u feel this way. If they say they will disown u and kick u out or something thats not very christian-like(, helping, or loving either) to be honest, and in that case reference the story in the bible about how the son of this rich man(may have been a king idr I’ve never read the bible fully) tells his father he would like to leave and would like his inheritance from his father, and about how when the son comes back years later; the father throws a party that his son comes back(point is a child is always your child no matter what they do or decide and you should love them even when they choose to do something that upsets you). also may I add anyone who claims to be a christian and wanders away most-likely(no saying that the case all the time) has never felt the presence of God or been truly trying to be a christian. gl to anyway.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Note that I said <span class="bbcode-i">more evidence</span> and not <span class="bbcode-i">absolute evidence</span>. Also did you know, in the 1300’s scientists and astrologists were given execution for questioning the existence of God. Then 400 years later it turns out the scientists were right (it was about the Earth going around the Sun and not vice versa).</p>
<p>So yeah, not nice people really considering they’re supposed to be the good guys. Does the religion get changed every time they realise they were wrong? Because Christians no longer kill people, thank God.[/quote]<br>
That’s honestly also what kept me questioning/wandering</p>
<p>[quote=“jme, post:10, topic:422257”]There’s no reason you can’t be a christian who believes in evolution. because frankly, you’d have to be either <span class="bbcode-b">retarded</span> or extremely ignorant to think we haven’t evolved.</p>
<p>I don’t know why religious people don’t eagerly accept science. People are so quick to dismiss the big bang theory, but if they believe in god, then why can’t they believe god created the big bang? Wouldn’t it be exciting, to see some of the inner workings of your god? I say to all christians, science can give you a deeper connection to God.</p>
<p>to the op: this isn’t something the internet can give you advice about. You know your parents better then anyone else. You shouldn’t have to lie to your parents about your beliefs. But walk in their shoes. They made you, they raised you, they loved you. Now they think you are going to hell. You won’t be with them in heaven. They are probably <em>devestated</em><br>
So it’s up to you. Do you hurt them and grow far apart? Or would you rather tell them a fib, that you accept jesus but you’d rather just be a kid right now and do kid things. Explain to them you don’t want those 1 hour meetings with them, you’ve got your full life to figure stuff out.[/quote]<br>
Well, my parents basically reject anything that isn’t in the bible, or that my pastor says is false, so even hearing the word ‘evolution’ would likely cause them to get up and walk off<br>
My parents actually did become devastated telling me that they wanted me to be in heaven with them, not burning and screaming in torture down in hell, and I felt really bad for them so that’s also why I said I believed again. But I don’t want to hurt them and grow far apart, I just want them to respect that this is my life, and I can make my own decisions, and to let me believe in what I want to believe.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There’s no reason you can’t be a christian who believes in evolution. because frankly, you’d have to be either <span class="bbcode-b">retarded</span> or extremely ignorant to think we haven’t evolved.</p>
<p>I don’t know why religious people don’t eagerly accept science. People are so quick to dismiss the big bang theory, but if they believe in god, then why can’t they believe god created the big bang? Wouldn’t it be exciting, to see some of the inner workings of your god? I say to all christians, science can give you a deeper connection to God.</p>
<p>to the op: this isn’t something the internet can give you advice about. You know your parents better then anyone else. You shouldn’t have to lie to your parents about your beliefs. But walk in their shoes. They made you, they raised you, they loved you. Now they think you are going to hell. You won’t be with them in heaven. They are probably <em>devestated</em><br>
So it’s up to you. Do you hurt them and grow far apart? Or would you rather tell them a fib, that you accept jesus but you’d rather just be a kid right now and do kid things. Explain to them you don’t want those 1 hour meetings with them, you’ve got your full life to figure stuff out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 15:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Outsider The Outsider]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_outsider">@The_Outsider</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xryz, post:7, topic:422257”][quote author=The Outsider link=topic=524927.msg3821144#msg3821144 date=1321774521]<br>
[/quote]<br>
There is as much evidence of the universe “popping” into existence as there is about God. So to claim that is fact is just as bad as any religious person claiming that their God is fact.</p>
<p>yes from my sig u can see i believe in a God(b/c of all the evidence in life that suggested that a God does exist). I have been born as raised a christian, currently I really dont want to claim to be a christian even though most of my beliefs are christian, im pretty open-minded and always trying to grow my knowledge.</p>
<p>OP: tell them why u feel this way. If they say they will disown u and kick u out or something thats not very christian-like(, helping, or loving either) to be honest, and in that case reference the story in the bible about how the son of this rich man(may have been a king idr I’ve never read the bible fully) tells his father he would like to leave and would like his inheritance from his father, and about how when the son comes back years later; the father throws a party that his son comes back(point is a child is always your child no matter what they do or decide and you should love them even when they choose to do something that upsets you). also may I add anyone who claims to be a christian and wanders away most-likely(no saying that the case all the time) has never felt the presence of God or been truly trying to be a christian. gl to anyway.[/quote]<br>
If you watch the video (yeah it’s long) there is more evidence of the universe being nothing to something without a cause or a reason, than there is evidence a God. It shows molecules in a cup of coffee disappearing then reappearing, quite literally, then it goes on to describe the laws of the universe quite deeply (gravity, time and space) and how these laws apply to the universe and such.</p>
<p>Lastly it explains that it is quite plausible that the universe can just appear as a singularity where all the matter is insanely small and insanely dense and then “The Big Bang” happens .</p>
<p>Note that I said <span class="bbcode-i">more evidence</span> and not <span class="bbcode-i">absolute evidence</span>. Also did you know, in the 1300’s scientists and astrologists were given execution for questioning the existence of God. Then 400 years later it turns out the scientists were right (it was about the Earth going around the Sun and not vice versa).</p>
<p>So yeah, not nice people really considering they’re supposed to be the good guys. Does the religion get changed every time they realise they were wrong? Because Christians no longer kill people, thank God.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 10:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RSCShadow RSCShadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rscshadow">@RSCShadow</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>(b/c of all the evidence in life that suggested that a God does exist).</blockquote>If that's all you're looking for, that's all you're going to find. Religion isn't based on evidence btw.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 08:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The Outsider, post:6, topic:422257”]Your parents probably won’t accept it so either keep it to yourself and move on when you’re older or put your foot down and rebel.</p>
<p>You know, there is no divine spirit and science is right, and the universe basically “popped” into existence from nothing. Here’s a video you might find interesting that will explain it a lot more:</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="WQhd05ZVYWg" data-youtube-title="Curiosity with Stephen Hawking, Did God Create the Universe?" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>Personally, I don’t like religious people that much, because most of them think it’s their duty to convert you. Well how about respect my beliefs as I do yours (tell your parents that).</p>
<p>P.S. Don’t take advice from people off of the internet, lol…[/quote]<br>
There is as much evidence of the universe “popping” into existence as there is about God. So to claim that is fact is just as bad as any religious person claiming that their God is fact.</p>
<p>yes from my sig u can see i believe in a God(b/c of all the evidence in life that suggested that a God does exist). I have been born as raised a christian, currently I really dont want to claim to be a christian even though most of my beliefs are christian, im pretty open-minded and always trying to grow my knowledge.</p>
<p>OP: tell them why u feel this way. If they say they will disown u and kick u out or something thats not very christian-like(, helping, or loving either) to be honest, and in that case reference the story in the bible about how the son of this rich man(may have been a king idr I’ve never read the bible fully) tells his father he would like to leave and would like his inheritance from his father, and about how when the son comes back years later; the father throws a party that his son comes back(point is a child is always your child no matter what they do or decide and you should love them even when they choose to do something that upsets you). also may I add anyone who claims to be a christian and wanders away most-likely(no saying that the case all the time) has never felt the presence of God or been truly trying to be a christian. gl to anyway.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 07:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Outsider The Outsider]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_outsider">@The_Outsider</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Your parents probably won’t accept it so either keep it to yourself and move on when you’re older or put your foot down and rebel.</p>
<p>You know, there is no divine spirit and science is right, and the universe basically “popped” into existence from nothing. Here’s a video you might find interesting that will explain it a lot more:</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="WQhd05ZVYWg" data-youtube-title="Curiosity with Stephen Hawking, Did God Create the Universe?" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>Personally, I don’t like religious people that much, because most of them think it’s their duty to convert you. Well how about respect my beliefs as I do yours (tell your parents that).</p>
<p>P.S. Don’t take advice from people off of the internet, lol…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 07:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vManlyMan vManlyMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vmanlyman">@vManlyMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Think of how they would respond and be ready to counter it.  That’s what you should do in any situation.</p>
<p>And imo, religion is stupid and the world would be better off without it.  I can’t think of anything good that has come out of religion, only wars.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 06:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lostmyphat lostmyphat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lostmyphat">@lostmyphat</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“r0ckstar96, post:1, topic:422257”]I need some help telling my parents about my true religious beliefs.<br>
Story time: I was born and raised a Christian, however around the age of 13, I started to question my beliefs and a few weeks later claimed to be an Atheist. I changed my religious beliefs (on facebook) to Atheist, and my family members saw, whom then reported the sudden change to my parents. My parents called me into their room and a baww-fest commenced, and then they started making me go to church with them every Sunday, and made me have weekly talks with their pastor and I had to write down why I was questioning my beliefs. It was honestly hard to explain, so what I wrote down didn’t seem convincing to them. My pastor then went on to preach to me from his bible saying quotes from it and saying how evolution was false, etc. I also had to have daily conferences with my parents about my beliefs (an hour each day), but really all they did was tell me stories about what’s going to happen if I don’t believe in Christianity (they used the good ol’ scare tactics). They also, along with multiple other families they’re friends with, bought me a giant bag full of books on why Christianity is the way to go, and why evolution is wrong. One cold day in December, my mom angrily called for me to come into the computer room where she was sitting. She wanted to know where I started to get these ideas that made me question my faith in Christianity, and so off the top of my head, I said science class at school (8th grade at the time), however looking back on it, it really wasn’t the school’s fault, because I questioned my faith on my own time, not because of school. Anyways, she proceeded to write a very angry e-mail to the school saying how they shouldn’t be teaching evolution (even though they hardly even touched on it at all, just said the word once) because it’s causing me to question my faith and all this other stuff. Then a few weeks later my principal had a meeting with me saying that he’s sorry what was in the textbooks caused me to question my faith, and some more awkward talk happened that I can’t remember (he was actually pretty calm about all this like it’s happened before), then I went back to class. Eventually, after a couple weeks of these stressful events and daily conferences with my parents and weekly conferences with my pastor, I just gave in and claimed to magically be a Christian again, and all went back to normal. Although a couple months later, a couple weeks after I got confirmed, I secretly took my place (religiously) as an Agnostic. Over time I looked into other religions and philosophies like Buddhism and Taoism, and as of late, I’ve been really liking the ideas of Taoism and would like to look more into it.<br>
So my question to you is, how can I come out to my VERY Christian parents that I don’t share the same religious beliefs as them, but without getting pressured and scared into believing in their religion like they did last time?[/quote]<br>
And what are your reasons for you to question your faith?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 05:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@John459 John459]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/john459">@John459</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>“Those who do not believe scripture and science can coexist either do not know know enough scripture, or do not know enough science.”</p>
<p>Remember that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 05:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d just come right out and tell them.  They can’t really force you to believe in something.</p>
<p>Religion is stupid tbh.  I’m Christian, but 90% of the time I feel as if I should be atheist because I do not believe all the shit that is in Christianity, or any religion for that matter.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 05:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to come out to parents about beliefs?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@r0ckstar96 r0ckstar96]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r0ckstar96">@r0ckstar96</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I need some help telling my parents about my true religious beliefs.<br>
Story time: I was born and raised a Christian, however around the age of 13, I started to question my beliefs and a few weeks later claimed to be an Atheist. I changed my religious beliefs (on facebook) to Atheist, and my family members saw, whom then reported the sudden change to my parents. My parents called me into their room and a baww-fest commenced, and then they started making me go to church with them every Sunday, and made me have weekly talks with their pastor and I had to write down why I was questioning my beliefs. It was honestly hard to explain, so what I wrote down didn’t seem convincing to them. My pastor then went on to preach to me from his bible saying quotes from it and saying how evolution was false, etc. I also had to have daily conferences with my parents about my beliefs (an hour each day), but really all they did was tell me stories about what’s going to happen if I don’t believe in Christianity (they used the good ol’ scare tactics). They also, along with multiple other families they’re friends with, bought me a giant bag full of books on why Christianity is the way to go, and why evolution is wrong. One cold day in December, my mom angrily called for me to come into the computer room where she was sitting. She wanted to know where I started to get these ideas that made me question my faith in Christianity, and so off the top of my head, I said science class at school (8th grade at the time), however looking back on it, it really wasn’t the school’s fault, because I questioned my faith on my own time, not because of school. Anyways, she proceeded to write a very angry e-mail to the school saying how they shouldn’t be teaching evolution (even though they hardly even touched on it at all, just said the word once) because it’s causing me to question my faith and all this other stuff. Then a few weeks later my principal had a meeting with me saying that he’s sorry what was in the textbooks caused me to question my faith, and some more awkward talk happened that I can’t remember (he was actually pretty calm about all this like it’s happened before), then I went back to class. Eventually, after a couple weeks of these stressful events and daily conferences with my parents and weekly conferences with my pastor, I just gave in and claimed to magically be a Christian again, and all went back to normal. Although a couple months later, a couple weeks after I got confirmed, I secretly took my place (religiously) as an Agnostic. Over time I looked into other religions and philosophies like Buddhism and Taoism, and as of late, I’ve been really liking the ideas of Taoism and would like to look more into it.<br>
So my question to you is, how can I come out to my VERY Christian parents that I don’t share the same religious beliefs as them, but without getting pressured and scared into believing in their religion like they did last time?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 05:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-422257-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-to-come-out-to-parents-about-beliefs/422257.rss">How to come out to parents about beliefs?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
