<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891</link>
    <description>I&#39;m getting ready to write a tutorial on getting started with electronic music production, obviously I&#39;m no professional but I think there&#39;s a lack of tutorials that take people right from the very beginning, so I&#39;m going to write a multi-part &quot;Creating a track from start to finish&quot; type deal. If people would like to see it then I&#39;ll post it on here as I go, if not then I&#39;ll stick the whole thing up on a website somewhere when it&#39;s all done.

I&#39;d quite like a suggestion on the genre of the finished track. Personally I&#39;m into nu skool breaks and drum and bass, however I hardly think they&#39;re the most popular of genres. Anyone got any ideas?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 14:29:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gotta_Catch_Them_All Gotta Catch Them All]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gotta_catch_them_all">@Gotta_Catch_Them_All</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I want that tutorial. Good luck with it. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 14:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-102891-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891.rss">Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_69 Project 69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_69">@Project_69</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, I think it would go in nicely.</p>
<p>I’ve composed and arranged a bunch of songs. Mostly soundtracks or classical though.</p>
<p>A good <span class="bbcode-i">free</span> program would be Anvil Studio for composing, and some sort of sequencer for making beats and so fourth.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 05:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-102891-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891.rss">Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Aight, I’m gonna post the introduction, it dosen’t actually cover anything, but I wanted to give anyone who felt like following along a chance to download the software. (Things work much easier when you can give them a try as you read about them.)</p>
<blockquote>[b]Part 1 – Introduction (and gathering your gear)[/b]
Hey, welcome to my little tutorial on getting started with producing electronic dance music. In this tutorial I'll be taking you through the process of creating your first track, from downloading some software to mixing down. If you've never played with production before then I think this tutorial will be useful to you whatever genre you wish to create, as the techniques vary little between music styles, generally all that changes is structures and “feel”, which you can gather from listening to other peoples tracks (and probably already have an idea of, if you're into the genre a lot).
<p>Before we start, I’d also like to say that I’m not by any means a professional, my formal music education consists of Grade 3 Piano (lol), GCSE Music and AS Level Music Technology in college which I never finished or turned up to much (and no, I don’t have any released tracks, either). The only knowledge I gained from any of this is a bit of musical theory, which although at this stage is not needed (and indeed, many professional producers don’t have an ounce of it - they still make awesome tunes) it comes in helpful occasionally. If you don’t know your major from your minor and a quaver is a cheese flavoured snack to you, maybe check out some of the lessons on <a href="http://www.musictheory.net" rel="nofollow noopener">www.musictheory.net</a>.</p>
<p>So why another tutorial? Well, in my experience, there are two main types of EDM tutorials. There are those aimed at people who already produce (or at the very least, write) music of a more traditional nature and just need help applying this knowledge to dance music. The problem with these tutorials is that they don’t cover the basic questions many newcomers have, which leaves them thinking “what the hell is a sequencer?”. Then you have the other end of the spectrum, the tutorials which are aimed at the listener. These tend to be less technical and much more easily accessible, however the ones I have read either don’t go into enough depth (so you come out of it learning nothing) or expect you to know your genre deeply (“play around with the settings until it sounds like a 303… of course you know what a 303 is!”).<br>
So, without further ado, introducing the easily accessible, non-genre-specific, not-too-technical-but-educational-and-inspiring, FUN tutorial. I hope.</p>
<p>So, is this gear I’m going to ask you to get going to be expensive? Well… sort of. In fact, all I want you to acquire is one piece of software – Propellerhead Software’s excellent Reason 3. This costs about $400 from <a href="http://www.zzsounds.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.zzsounds.com</a> or similar retailers. “What, but that’s expensive!” you cry? Well at least you don’t have to buy entire racks of hardware like producers 10 years ago, and if you can’t afford it I’m sure you can find some other way… I am referring to the demo version, of course. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>A quick note on Reason: If you Google around a bit, you will find many thousands of people telling you that Reason is an inferior application that belongs in the realm of Dance Ejay and is only useful for learning on, takes no skill, etc. etc. These reviews are written either by people who have only used older versions of Reason, or just straight up don’t know what they’re talking about. It’s true that Reason has had sound quality issues in the past, but these were totally cured with Version 3, and myself and many other level-headed people working with audio now agree that it is totally up to par with the likes of Pro Tools and Cubase. As for the argument that using Reason somehow takes less skill than a more traditional program, this is complete and total bull. It is not a drag-and-drop loop “toy” like Ejay (or Music on the playstation, if anyone remembers that). It is a real tool with the same work flow as the ones most of the big names use, and if you can use Reason, you can find your way around a more widely-used application fairly easily. If you don’t believe me, ask Liam Howlett (The Prodigy) and Printz (Black Eyed Peas) – both use Reason fairly heavily, although Howlett uses it more as a notepad for jotting down musical ideas before he programs them on his multi-thousand dollar hardware set-up <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>The main advantage of Reason as far as this tutorial goes is that it comes with everything you need in one application and doesn’t let you add any more. While this may seem like a limitation, it’s actually a godsend. With applications that allow plug-in instruments and effects there is a tendency to download “just one more plug-in” to try and get the sound you want, rather than learning thoroughly how to use the ones you have. Reason can make any sound you wish, if you spend the time learning how it works.</p>
<p>So ends part one of my tutorial, this chapter was a bit of a cop-out really, I just wanted to give people time to get Reason downloaded… shit, I mean bought… and installed so I can hopefully get clips of what people are doing as I go, to remind me of what I forgot to mention. Feedback is good! I’ll be posting the next part over the next few days, which will be covering the basics of what Reason has to offer, and the structure of a track. I know, I’m sorry, you still won’t be bangin’ out any tunes (part 3 is where that starts coming in :P) but I’ll try and fit in some playing with the synthesisers so you can listen to some squelchy noize and keep yourself occupied in the meantime. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
</blockquote>
<p>If anyone is getting Reason, note you won’t need any Refills or patches or samples or anything like that to follow along, I’m going to be guiding y’all through creating all the sounds from scratch - using presets is for pussies <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> Reason 3 is about 1.8gb, if you find one larger than that it will be full of videos or Refills and you should probably look for a smaller one to save your bandwidth. The demo version will do, however bear in mind you can’t export to mp3 with it, so you can’t show off to your friends!</p>
<p>EDIT: Yeah, I knew I forgot something else. A midi controller keyboard is a very very fun and useful thing to have. If you have an old keyboard lying around that can be plugged into the pc and used as a MIDI controller (most of them) now would be the time to dig out the cable for it. If you don’t have one, small 1 or 2 octave keyboard that sit on your desk and plug in via USB can be bought, for about £80 ($150). This won’t be required for the tutorial, but will make things much easier and much more “physical”, in that you can mess around with the sounds on a keyboard rather than clicking everything in and ruining your creative vibes <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> A worthy investment indeed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 02:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-102891-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891.rss">Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kmb Kmb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kmb">@kmb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Post here please! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I have actually thought about getting started with electronic music production, but have no idea where to start (well, I haven’t really started looking at it yet).</p>
<p>About the genre… I vote for trance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 01:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-102891-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891.rss">Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m getting ready to write a tutorial on getting started with electronic music production, obviously I’m no professional but I think there’s a lack of tutorials that take people right from the very beginning, so I’m going to write a multi-part “Creating a track from start to finish” type deal. If people would like to see it then I’ll post it on here as I go, if not then I’ll stick the whole thing up on a website somewhere when it’s all done.</p>
<p>I’d quite like a suggestion on the genre of the finished track. Personally I’m into nu skool breaks and drum and bass, however I hardly think they’re the most popular of genres. Anyone got any ideas?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 00:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-102891-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/would-a-tutorial-on-making-electronic-music-go-down-well/102891.rss">Would a tutorial on making electronic music go down well?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
