<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Q&amp;a</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/q-a/293533</link>
    <description>With the Q&amp;A out there were some of the more interesting questions and answers. (IMO)

Melt The Ice asks;
MMG has mentioned F2P will be updated a lot more frequently, stating that F2P is NOT A DEMO.

A: We are working hard on a new skill, which will be available to free-to-play and members and which shows our continued commitment to the free game. We are also looking to improve some of the free quests as well as early graphics. The free-to-play game is epic - there are tens of thousands of hours of gameplay and we are working on a number of updates at the moment.

- I wonder what the new skill will be. 

Taco 50 asks;
In one of the previous Q&amp;A threads, &quot;noob-free&quot; worlds were mentioned, for players with a certain amount of total experience. These seem to be taking a while, have they been cancelled?

A: Yes, this is still a project we are working on and the project has not been cancelled, we just have a load of other big projects going on at once.

- No Noobs in World 1337

6) Pur35 Ownage asks;
Would there ever be a console version on RuneScape like for xbox360 + PS3, i think that they would be a great success if you could get the controls right, but they would have to speak not type which is much better.

A: Yes, indeed, we are looking at all the consoles at the moment and deciding which one or two are best for our community.

- O god, RuneScape on xbox live!

Snrubnayrpk asks;
I&#39;m a RuneScape video maker (Average, I’m learning still) And I was wondering in the future will there ever be features to help in videos? Special Views, Green rooms, Ect.

A: Absolutely! Andrew and I were actually talking about this the other day. What would be really helpful is to have a list of features you think would help you to make videos, so we can assess which ones are possible.

- Anyone up to makeing another Marah Carey Diss?

20) Roasted Duck7 asks;
Mod MMG, in the RuneScape Classic Q&amp;A session you mentioned making RuneScape Classic servers in which all players would receive the cheat codes, as to stop any cheating in the game. This sounds like an absolutely terrific idea, but so far, all I have seen for it was the Q&amp;A. If you are still considering creating these servers, or if they are already in the works, could you give us a time you expect them to be released?

A: This is currently in development. It has taken a long time, since we had to get all our old code compatible with our latest code libraries and back-office systems. There is still a lot of work to do - probably a few more months - but, rest assured, we are working hard on this. I think it will be very popular when it does finally come out, as we are packing in a bit of a surprise at the same time.

- ::pickup anyone?

Hellroses333 asks;
Now that you have upgraded your bot detection systems, is there any possibility of free trade returning to RuneScape?

I&#39;m tired of using junk to trade occasionally when buying or selling something - it seems completely idiotic to me: you&#39;re basically giving someone a rising item and some junk that won&#39;t sell in the GE, but essentially you&#39;re getting the item for midprice anyways, so the buyer always ends up with profit.

If you will not be planning to return free trade, then is there a possibility that you may try returning free trade for a minimum of one week, just to see how it goes? Obviously it would take months of testing to witness the true number of gold-farmers you would be dealing with again, but hopefully your macro-detection systems would catch them before they did any real damage to the RS economy or your company again.

A: Our ability to detect all botting is not really related to free trade. We are looking at improving the trade system, and we may consider relaxing our trade limits a little more in the future, but this is still under discussion at the moment.

- Just take it out and let us trade again. 

Timmy7072 asks;
I hear rumours of a &quot;Name Changing System&quot; can this be confirmed? If so, how would such a system work?

A: Yes, we are planning to release a new display name system shortly. This will essentially allow you to change your in-game display name to be different from your login name.

- This will most likely bring tons of chaos, I mean hopefully you can remember each name change your friend makes. 

 Robeddarknes asks;
Hi I was wondering when you were planning on releasing the ability for us to look at our character&#39;s statistics such as number of x-monster killed and x-number of hours played and what date our accounts were created, as this has always interested me and I believe I read you were planning to release it.

A: Yes, we currently have a project underway to provide players with a lot more information about their avatar progress and status in game.

- Hay guais I killed 5000 cows!

Bigb4199 asks;
Due to the growing size of your company, more resources have become available to you. To compete with other MMO&#39;s, do you intend to use voice actors to bring NPCs to new life?

A: This is an interesting idea and one we are currently discussing.

- Yay now I can listen to the cows cry as I bot and kill them

2h And Spork asks;
What does Jagex think of private servers that are smaller copies of RuneScape, do you believe that you should fight against such servers or just let them be? I point this out because private servers have been growing in size over the years.

A: We strongly oppose private servers, irrespective of their size, and always look to shut them down. We have also been very successful in taking their ringleaders to court.

- Watch out rsps Jagex is very successful at bringing you down!

Discuss</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2009 17:02:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/q-a/293533.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Q&amp;a</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unlimited1 .Unlimited]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unlimited1">@Unlimited1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>With the Q&amp;A out there were some of the more interesting questions and answers. (IMO)</p>
<p>Melt The Ice asks;<br>
MMG has mentioned F2P will be updated a lot more frequently, stating that F2P is NOT A DEMO.</p>
<p>A: We are working hard on a new skill, which will be available to free-to-play and members and which shows our continued commitment to the free game. We are also looking to improve some of the free quests as well as early graphics. The free-to-play game is epic - there are tens of thousands of hours of gameplay and we are working on a number of updates at the moment.</p>
<ul>
<li>I wonder what the new skill will be.</li>
</ul>
<p>Taco 50 asks;<br>
In one of the previous Q&amp;A threads, “noob-free” worlds were mentioned, for players with a certain amount of total experience. These seem to be taking a while, have they been cancelled?</p>
<p>A: Yes, this is still a project we are working on and the project has not been cancelled, we just have a load of other big projects going on at once.</p>
<ul>
<li>No Noobs in World 1337</li>
</ul>
<ol start="6">
<li>Pur35 Ownage asks;<br>
Would there ever be a console version on RuneScape like for xbox360 + PS3, i think that they would be a great success if you could get the controls right, but they would have to speak not type which is much better.</li>
</ol>
<p>A: Yes, indeed, we are looking at all the consoles at the moment and deciding which one or two are best for our community.</p>
<ul>
<li>O god, RuneScape on xbox live!</li>
</ul>
<p>Snrubnayrpk asks;<br>
I’m a RuneScape video maker (Average, I’m learning still) And I was wondering in the future will there ever be features to help in videos? Special Views, Green rooms, Ect.</p>
<p>A: Absolutely! Andrew and I were actually talking about this the other day. What would be really helpful is to have a list of features you think would help you to make videos, so we can assess which ones are possible.</p>
<ul>
<li>Anyone up to makeing another Marah Carey Diss?</li>
</ul>
<ol start="20">
<li>Roasted Duck7 asks;<br>
Mod MMG, in the RuneScape Classic Q&amp;A session you mentioned making RuneScape Classic servers in which all players would receive the cheat codes, as to stop any cheating in the game. This sounds like an absolutely terrific idea, but so far, all I have seen for it was the Q&amp;A. If you are still considering creating these servers, or if they are already in the works, could you give us a time you expect them to be released?</li>
</ol>
<p>A: This is currently in development. It has taken a long time, since we had to get all our old code compatible with our latest code libraries and back-office systems. There is still a lot of work to do - probably a few more months - but, rest assured, we are working hard on this. I think it will be very popular when it does finally come out, as we are packing in a bit of a surprise at the same time.</p>
<ul>
<li>::pickup anyone?</li>
</ul>
<p>Hellroses333 asks;<br>
Now that you have upgraded your bot detection systems, is there any possibility of free trade returning to RuneScape?</p>
<p>I’m tired of using junk to trade occasionally when buying or selling something - it seems completely idiotic to me: you’re basically giving someone a rising item and some junk that won’t sell in the GE, but essentially you’re getting the item for midprice anyways, so the buyer always ends up with profit.</p>
<p>If you will not be planning to return free trade, then is there a possibility that you may try returning free trade for a minimum of one week, just to see how it goes? Obviously it would take months of testing to witness the true number of gold-farmers you would be dealing with again, but hopefully your macro-detection systems would catch them before they did any real damage to the RS economy or your company again.</p>
<p>A: Our ability to detect all botting is not really related to free trade. We are looking at improving the trade system, and we may consider relaxing our trade limits a little more in the future, but this is still under discussion at the moment.</p>
<ul>
<li>Just take it out and let us trade again.</li>
</ul>
<p>Timmy7072 asks;<br>
I hear rumours of a “Name Changing System” can this be confirmed? If so, how would such a system work?</p>
<p>A: Yes, we are planning to release a new display name system shortly. This will essentially allow you to change your in-game display name to be different from your login name.</p>
<ul>
<li>This will most likely bring tons of chaos, I mean hopefully you can remember each name change your friend makes.</li>
</ul>
<p>Robeddarknes asks;<br>
Hi I was wondering when you were planning on releasing the ability for us to look at our character’s statistics such as number of x-monster killed and x-number of hours played and what date our accounts were created, as this has always interested me and I believe I read you were planning to release it.</p>
<p>A: Yes, we currently have a project underway to provide players with a lot more information about their avatar progress and status in game.</p>
<ul>
<li>Hay guais I killed 5000 cows!</li>
</ul>
<p>Bigb4199 asks;<br>
Due to the growing size of your company, more resources have become available to you. To compete with other MMO’s, do you intend to use voice actors to bring NPCs to new life?</p>
<p>A: This is an interesting idea and one we are currently discussing.</p>
<ul>
<li>Yay now I can listen to the cows cry as I bot and kill them</li>
</ul>
<p>2h And Spork asks;<br>
What does Jagex think of private servers that are smaller copies of RuneScape, do you believe that you should fight against such servers or just let them be? I point this out because private servers have been growing in size over the years.</p>
<p>A: We strongly oppose private servers, irrespective of their size, and always look to shut them down. We have also been very successful in taking their ringleaders to court.</p>
<ul>
<li>Watch out rsps Jagex is very successful at bringing you down!</li>
</ul>
<p>Discuss</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/q-a/293533/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/q-a/293533/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2009 17:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-293533-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/q-a/293533.rss">Q&amp;a</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
