<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Opel Calibra</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581</link>
    <description>In about 6 months I&#39;ll be 18, and I&#39;m allowed to get driving license.

I have a great job, pretty many tools and passion for tuning a car. I started searching for all kind of cheap &quot;sport cars&quot;, mostly coupes. And I won&#39;t need like 200hp engine, im fine with 100-150hp.

Because it&#39;s my first car, I won&#39;t use much money on CAR, but I&#39;ll probably get some nice audio equipment and stuff like that, so I can sell the car without them.
Then I found Opel Calibra, it has just ideal amount of HP (I would like 16V version better ofc :D ), it looks pretty cool (even without any modding!) and the best thing is; it&#39;s not really expensive. In Finland I can get a good one for about 2500 euros.

I will probably spend about 1000 euros for rims, audio, bodykit and stuff like that.

So what are your experiences with Calibra? Pros and cons? Anything I need to know about it? And I must say, I haven&#39;t heard many good things about Opels, pretty much only bad things.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 22:47:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Opel Calibra</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s a great car, my brother planned to buy one. The looks are awesome, but there is one problem. The bottom plate gets rusted quite quick. I had a wet ass when I sat in the back seat, so that will be a problem. We went to a car mechanic (a family member) and he said that a new bottom plate was needed, wich would cost quite a bit. So the deal went off, but if you can do it yourself I’d go for it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 22:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-199581-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581.rss">Opel Calibra</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opel Calibra</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks hot.  Too bad I live in America.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 04:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-199581-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581.rss">Opel Calibra</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Opel Calibra</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mikkomainer Secet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mikkomainer">@mikkomainer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In about 6 months I’ll be 18, and I’m allowed to get driving license.</p>
<p>I have a great job, pretty many tools and passion for tuning a car. I started searching for all kind of cheap “sport cars”, mostly coupes. And I won’t need like 200hp engine, im fine with 100-150hp.</p>
<p>Because it’s my first car, I won’t use much money on CAR, but I’ll probably get some nice audio equipment and stuff like that, so I can sell the car without them.<br>
Then I found Opel Calibra, it has just ideal amount of HP (I would like 16V version better ofc <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> ), it looks pretty cool (even without any modding!) and the best thing is; it’s not really expensive. In Finland I can get a good one for about 2500 euros.</p>
<p>I will probably spend about 1000 euros for rims, audio, bodykit and stuff like that.</p>
<p>So what are your experiences with Calibra? Pros and cons? Anything I need to know about it? And I must say, I haven’t heard many good things about Opels, pretty much only bad things.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 01:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-199581-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/opel-calibra/199581.rss">Opel Calibra</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
