<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I need help logging into moparscape</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-logging-into-moparscape/328897</link>
    <description>When im tryin to log into moparscape i click enter and the server IP is already 127.0.0.1 so i put in my username and pass and it tells me that its already logged in... so i try to use a differant username and it sais the same thing... no matter what i put into the username it doesnt log in... so i put in the Ip address, &quot;newstart.no-ip.info&quot; when i put that in and put my username and pass it logs me in but the sreen is black. all i can only see the chatbox and the stuff 2 the right of it... but then it logs be straight back out again... y does it do this??? what can i put in so i can play moparscape?? plz answer im beggin u ppl 2 help me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 02:36:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-logging-into-moparscape/328897.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I need help logging into moparscape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ZoMb13KiD ZoMb13KiD]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zomb13kid">@ZoMb13KiD</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When im tryin to log into moparscape i click enter and the server IP is already 127.0.0.1 so i put in my username and pass and it tells me that its already logged in… so i try to use a differant username and it sais the same thing… no matter what i put into the username it doesnt log in… so i put in the Ip address, “newstart.no-ip.info” when i put that in and put my username and pass it logs me in but the sreen is black. all i can only see the chatbox and the stuff 2 the right of it… but then it logs be straight back out again… y does it do this??? what can i put in so i can play moparscape?? plz answer im beggin u ppl 2 help me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-logging-into-moparscape/328897/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-logging-into-moparscape/328897/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 02:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-328897-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-need-help-logging-into-moparscape/328897.rss">I need help logging into moparscape</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
