<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Life</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691</link>
    <description>This board is relatively inactive and misused, which is disappointing because I&#39;ve seen some (read: few) pseudo-intellectual discussions take place, and they were atleast thought provoking. Let&#39;s get an [i]actual[/i] intellectual discussion going; not some mundane debate about a black-and-white topic, but at the same time not some esoteric bullshit either. I digress. 

I&#39;ll switch focus to the discussion on hand, life. I&#39;d like to hear everyone&#39;s opinion on life. While this may seem relatively simple, I think it&#39;s a good way to get Moparscape started with intellectual discussion- mostly because it doesn&#39;t require any background knowledge to discuss. I&#39;ll throw around a few example questions which you guys could respond to. Don&#39;t feel like you need to answer these specific questions, if you have something relevant to contribute, by all means, do it. 

[hr]

Why are we alive? 

Are living organisms more important than nonliving objects?

If the entire human population was decimated, would it &#39;matter&#39;, on the grand scale of the universe?

Do living (or even nonliving) objects have any intrinsic value whatsoever? What&#39;s the &#39;point&#39;? 

Every living organism eventually dies. Assuming there is no afterlife, what is the point of living if we are condemned to die? 

[hr]

I&#39;ll fire up the discussion a bit myself, also. In my opinion, life has no intrinsic value or meaning. Life was most likely a mistake, there&#39;s nothing all too special about it. A human life, an animal&#39;s life, or a bug&#39;s life all have the same value-zero. If the entire human population were to disappear, the universe would not notice or care. 
You don&#39;t have to agree with me, in fact I encourage that you disagree and debate this with me, I&#39;d like to get something interesting started on this board. 

I&#39;ll mention, it would be good if you all could [b]not bring religion into this debate[/b]. If you&#39;re religious, that&#39;s great for you, [b]you&#39;ve already found your answer to all of these questions[/b]. Unfortunately, bringing religion into this discussion will not work. This is for a few reasons.

[ul][li]It is impossible to debate religion, there is no way to prove or disprove it.[/li]
[li]The discussion would turn into an atheism vs religion debate, which are [i]not thought provoking in the slightest[/i]. Having a debate between two sides unwilling to change their mind is useless, anyway.[/li]
[li]It turns into mindless bashing of the other person&#39;s point of view, which is extremely boring to read.[/li][/ul]




EDIT: I&#39;d just like to add, I know that the questions are fairly one-sided. If you have better questions of or about life, ask them in the thread and we can have a discussion.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 01:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Sfacciato, post:28, topic:535691”][quote author=The Wanderer link=topic=654496.msg4386925#msg4386925 date=1385943207]<br>
I feel like this is hardly a discussion or a debate. It’s mostly people posting their beliefs, you saying interesting and to read a wikipedia article about a related philosophy. It is hard to debate or discuss a topic as subjective as this especially with intelligent people. As you have said you aren’t going to change your opinion and neither are a lot of people here with something such as life.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Sorry? Would you like to suggest anything that would improve the thread?<br>
As far as wikipedia goes, it’s pretty informative and provides a basic understanding of a topic in just one page whereas a book could take hundreds.[/quote]<br>
I don’t mind stating what my beliefs are or learning about other beliefs, but you slandering this board saying there is no discussion and then by creating a thread where there can be little discussion just seems odd. I cannot suggest how to create a discussion where there is no discussion to be had. I also wasn’t saying wikipedia is bad haha. Wikipedia may be the most credible source out there nowadays.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/29</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 01:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="27" data-topic="535691">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Wanderer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I feel like this is hardly a discussion or a debate. It’s mostly people posting their beliefs, you saying interesting and to read a wikipedia article about a related philosophy. It is hard to debate or discuss a topic as subjective as this especially with intelligent people. As you have said you aren’t going to change your opinion and neither are a lot of people here with something such as life.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Sorry? Would you like to suggest anything that would improve the thread?<br>
As far as wikipedia goes, it’s pretty informative and provides a basic understanding of a topic in just one page whereas a book could take hundreds.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/28</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_wanderer The Wanderer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_wanderer">@the_wanderer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I feel like this is hardly a discussion or a debate. It’s mostly people posting their beliefs, you saying interesting and to read a wikipedia article about a related philosophy. It is hard to debate or discuss a topic as subjective as this especially with intelligent people. As you have said you aren’t going to change your opinion and neither are a lot of people here with something such as life.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/27</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="24" data-topic="535691">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/sinisoul/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> sinisoul:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So many subjective questions. At times its just better to not ask questions and realize the answer is simply that there isn’t an answer or that the answer you are hoping to hear is not the answer to the question.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Not hoping to hear an answer at all, the questions were made to be vague and subjective to spark discussion. I already know how I’d answer the questions, and my answers will likely never change ; ).</p>
<p>[quote=“sinisoul, post:24, topic:535691”]Are living organisms more important than nonliving objects?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Subjective to different situations and who you are asking, and in what context you are asking.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>If the entire human population was decimated, would it ‘matter’, on the grand scale of the universe?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>No. Not at all. Subjective to humans. The universe does not revolve around humanity.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Do living (or even nonliving) objects have any intrinsic value whatsoever? What’s the ‘point’?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Well. ‘They’ are there. You cannot destroy matter and stop from it being where it is minus the force you exert to move it somewhere else. The point being is that you have limited power in the universe, and just get use to it.[/quote]</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Subjective to different situations and who you are asking, and in what context you are asking.<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,654496.msg4384339.html#msg4384339" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,654496.msg4384339.html#msg4384339</a><br>
Read the wikipedia articles I linked Bowser_Jr, they should explain the context well.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>No. Not at all. Subjective to humans. The universe does not revolve around humanity.<br>
Yeah, I agree completely. You might want to read <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cosmicism#Principles_of_cosmicism" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a>, you could find it fairly interesting.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Well. ‘They’ are there. You cannot destroy matter and stop from it being where it is minus the force you exert to move it somewhere else. The point being is that you have limited power in the universe, and just get use to it.<br>
Very metaphysical. You might want to read <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metaphysical_nihilism" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this</a> article, it’s fairly interesting. I’ll quote it a bit:</p>
</blockquote>
<p>[quote=“<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metaphysical_nihilism" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metaphysical_nihilism</a>”]There could have been finitely many things.<br>
For each thing, that thing might not have existed.<br>
The removal of one thing does not necessitate the introduction of another.<br>
Therefore, there could have been no things at all.[/quote]</p>
<p>I omitted the questions which were impossible to disagree with : p.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 16:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NewbieNewty Newty]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/newbienewty">@NewbieNewty</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>entropy can not be reversed</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 08:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So many subjective questions. At times its just better to not ask questions and realize the answer is simply that there isn’t an answer or that the answer you are hoping to hear is not the answer to the question.</p>
<p>Why are we alive?</p>
<p>Why not?</p>
<p>Are living organisms more important than nonliving objects?</p>
<p>Subjective to different situations and who you are asking, and in what context you are asking.</p>
<p>If the entire human population was decimated, would it ‘matter’, on the grand scale of the universe?</p>
<p>No. Not at all. Subjective to humans. The universe does not revolve around humanity.</p>
<p>Do living (or even nonliving) objects have any intrinsic value whatsoever? What’s the ‘point’?</p>
<p>Well. ‘They’ are there. You cannot destroy matter and stop from it being where it is minus the force you exert to move it somewhere else. The point being is that you have limited power in the universe, and just get use to it.</p>
<p>Every living organism eventually dies. Assuming there is no afterlife, what is the point of living if we are condemned to die?</p>
<p>Well you get the chance to live. That’s pretty nice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 05:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“KempiScape, post:22, topic:535691”]All these questions are questions which you can endlessly speculate on and there is no fudgeing point in doing so. The questions you ask are questions you can never get an answer to, there are only our opinions.</p>
<p>“It is impossible to debate religion, there is no way to prove or disprove it.” and then you come up with a topic like this and call it intelligent… just /facepalm[/quote]</p>
<p>Yes, the questions are opinion based, you are very perceptive. I think I mentioned that numerous times (because that is the <span class="bbcode-u">point</span>)… As for endless speculation having no point, it doesn’t need to have a point or a conclusion to be reached.</p>
<p>I’m not calling anything intelligent. I’m not calling my topic intelligent, I’m not calling myself intelligent, and I’m not calling you intelligent. Yes, it is impossible to debate religion, I didn’t feel like the topic becoming an atheism v. religion thread because there are already tons of those in this section.</p>
<p>tell me what exactly the <span class="bbcode-i">point</span> of your post was, seeing as you had nothing to add to the conversation.<br>
"/facepalm"</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 03:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KempiScape KempiScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kempiscape">@KempiScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All these questions are questions which you can endlessly speculate on and there is no fucking point in doing so. The questions you ask are questions you can never get an answer to, there are only our opinions.</p>
<p>“It is impossible to debate religion, there is no way to prove or disprove it.” and then you come up with a topic like this and call it intelligent… just /facepalm</p>
<p>[quote=“Sfacciato, post:21, topic:535691”][quote author=Kidpaparoach link=topic=654496.msg4385449#msg4385449 date=1385306976]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Why are we alive?<br>
Because the Universe is big and in a sense we were accidentally created and since then we have clung to life fearful of death, fearful of not existing. (Not bringing religion into this, when I say God I mean existence, not the guy with a beard that’s up in the clouds) In a sense if I were to call anything God I’d call existence God. In a sense humans are like the cells in the human body (human body = universe, cells = us). We are a part of the Universe, we live and we die and on our own we are essentially valueless <span class="bbcode-u">but when you bundle us all up together you can get an amazing thing</span> (I used the word ‘thing’ because depending on the way the words I could use are interpreted it could be seen as wrong).</p>
<p>Are living organisms more important than nonliving objects?<br>
It depends on who’s answering the question. To other living organisms, living organisms are, but in the grand scale of things we are not.</p>
<p>If the entire human population was decimated, would it ‘matter’, on the grand scale of the universe?<br>
It would not because all that we are still exists in a different form. But again, you need to define what does matter (and other words) in order to answer that question correctly (in relation to what the person defines as correct).</p>
<p>Do living (or even nonliving) objects have any intrinsic value whatsoever? What’s the ‘point’?<br>
None whatsoever.</p>
<p>Every living organism eventually dies. Assuming there is no afterlife, what is the point of living if we are condemned to die?<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">Their is no point but we try to give ourselves reasons to live with the distractions of life. I.e. Let’s say you have a couple of kids; you would want to make sure they are healthy, happy etc. That is a distraction from the emptiness that existence is.<br>
</span></p>
<p>All of those questions answers completely depend on what the answerers (dat wording) perception of ‘x’ are. We’re trying to find answers that their are no answer to or maybe we just aren’t capable of thinking in the ‘correct’ way to understand the answers.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, the questions are opinion based, there is no right way to answer them which is why I thought they’d be good discussion questions.</p>
<p>I agree with some of what you’ve said, thanks for your input :). In my opinion though, even as humans bundled together we are relatively unimportant to the universe.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just wondering out of curiosity but what do you not agree with? I respect your opinions etc, I’m just curious.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I underlined the bits that I didn’t outright agree with, because in my opinion even as a race of humans we’re relatively unimportant to the universe. My views on the subject could best be related to <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cosmicism#Principles_of_cosmicism" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">cosmicism</a>.</p>
<p>I also don’t necessarily agree that people give themselves distractions from the emptiness of existence. On the contrary, I don’t think many people realize how pointless life is, and they truly believe that those distractions actually mean something.</p>
<p>Just minor differences in opinion, because the majority of what you proposed is what I personally believe.[/quote]</p>
<p>We have no way of knowing if we are important to the universe or not. None. I don’t believe if human existence is gone that it will impact the universe in a big way, but STILL there is no way of knowing. We can’t proof that the universe is real, it could be one big illusion, no way of telling.<br>
(gives me a good idea for your next topic, consciousness)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/22</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 00:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kidpaparoach, post:20, topic:535691”][quote author=Sfacciato link=topic=654496.msg4384671#msg4384671 date=1384887354]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Why are we alive?<br>
Because the Universe is big and in a sense we were accidentally created and since then we have clung to life fearful of death, fearful of not existing. (Not bringing religion into this, when I say God I mean existence, not the guy with a beard that’s up in the clouds) In a sense if I were to call anything God I’d call existence God. In a sense humans are like the cells in the human body (human body = universe, cells = us). We are a part of the Universe, we live and we die and on our own we are essentially valueless <span class="bbcode-u">but when you bundle us all up together you can get an amazing thing</span> (I used the word ‘thing’ because depending on the way the words I could use are interpreted it could be seen as wrong).</p>
<p>Are living organisms more important than nonliving objects?<br>
It depends on who’s answering the question. To other living organisms, living organisms are, but in the grand scale of things we are not.</p>
<p>If the entire human population was decimated, would it ‘matter’, on the grand scale of the universe?<br>
It would not because all that we are still exists in a different form. But again, you need to define what does matter (and other words) in order to answer that question correctly (in relation to what the person defines as correct).</p>
<p>Do living (or even nonliving) objects have any intrinsic value whatsoever? What’s the ‘point’?<br>
None whatsoever.</p>
<p>Every living organism eventually dies. Assuming there is no afterlife, what is the point of living if we are condemned to die?<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">Their is no point but we try to give ourselves reasons to live with the distractions of life. I.e. Let’s say you have a couple of kids; you would want to make sure they are healthy, happy etc. That is a distraction from the emptiness that existence is.<br>
</span></p>
<p>All of those questions answers completely depend on what the answerers (dat wording) perception of ‘x’ are. We’re trying to find answers that their are no answer to or maybe we just aren’t capable of thinking in the ‘correct’ way to understand the answers.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, the questions are opinion based, there is no right way to answer them which is why I thought they’d be good discussion questions.</p>
<p>I agree with some of what you’ve said, thanks for your input :). In my opinion though, even as humans bundled together we are relatively unimportant to the universe.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Just wondering out of curiosity but what do you not agree with? I respect your opinions etc, I’m just curious.[/quote]</p>
<p>I underlined the bits that I didn’t outright agree with, because in my opinion even as a race of humans we’re relatively unimportant to the universe. My views on the subject could best be related to <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cosmicism#Principles_of_cosmicism" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">cosmicism</a>.</p>
<p>I also don’t necessarily agree that people give themselves distractions from the emptiness of existence. On the contrary, I don’t think many people realize how pointless life is, and they truly believe that those distractions actually mean something.</p>
<p>Just minor differences in opinion, because the majority of what you proposed is what I personally believe.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 17:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Sfacciato, post:17, topic:535691”][quote author=Kidpaparoach link=topic=654496.msg4384626#msg4384626 date=1384866438]<br>
Why are we alive?<br>
Because the Universe is big and in a sense we were accidentally created and since then we have clung to life fearful of death, fearful of not existing. (Not bringing religion into this, when I say God I mean existence, not the guy with a beard that’s up in the clouds) In a sense if I were to call anything God I’d call existence God. In a sense humans are like the cells in the human body (human body = universe, cells = us). We are a part of the Universe, we live and we die and on our own we are essentially valueless but when you bundle us all up together you can get an amazing thing (I used the word ‘thing’ because depending on the way the words I could use are interpreted it could be seen as wrong).</p>
<p>Are living organisms more important than nonliving objects?<br>
It depends on who’s answering the question. To other living organisms, living organisms are, but in the grand scale of things we are not.</p>
<p>If the entire human population was decimated, would it ‘matter’, on the grand scale of the universe?<br>
It would not because all that we are still exists in a different form. But again, you need to define what does matter (and other words) in order to answer that question correctly (in relation to what the person defines as correct).</p>
<p>Do living (or even nonliving) objects have any intrinsic value whatsoever? What’s the ‘point’?<br>
None whatsoever.</p>
<p>Every living organism eventually dies. Assuming there is no afterlife, what is the point of living if we are condemned to die?<br>
Their is no point but we try to give ourselves reasons to live with the distractions of life. I.e. Let’s say you have a couple of kids; you would want to make sure they are healthy, happy etc. That is a distraction from the emptiness that existence is.</p>
<p>All of those questions answers completely depend on what the answerers (dat wording) perception of ‘x’ are. We’re trying to find answers that their are no answer to or maybe we just aren’t capable of thinking in the ‘correct’ way to understand the answers.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Yes, the questions are opinion based, there is no right way to answer them which is why I thought they’d be good discussion questions.</p>
<p>I agree with some of what you’ve said, thanks for your input :). In my opinion though, even as humans bundled together we are relatively unimportant to the universe.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Animals also have a purpose in life. So the death of humanity would matter for them. Animals would also mourn the death of their owner, so you cannot say that their not affected by the event on an emotional level.</p>
<p>We can objectively decide a object’s value in a society by looking at its usefulness and supply compared to demand. Living objects are more valuable as they give non-living objects value. A pick axe is useful for mining, but worthless without a miner, apart from the value of the materials. But the materials have no value either if there is nobody to process it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Ah, sorry I’ve taken so long to respond.<br>
Okay, in which case replace the decimation of all humans and extend it to all other life forms on our earth. Would anything matter anymore?</p>
<p>Interesting to note though, that a miner without a pickaxe is just as worthless as the lone pickaxe.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Nobody has set purpose, we mold it ourselves and live to fulfill our own created purpose.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A type of existentialism and absurdism, very interesting, thanks for your input.[/quote]<br>
Just wondering out of curiosity but what do you not agree with? I respect your opinions etc, I’m just curious.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 15:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="18" data-topic="535691">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Slave Scyth:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My opinion to your questions is religious. Guess I can’t post. Sadface.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, that’s great for you. Like I said in the OP, you’ve already figured out the answer to the questions. You won’t change your mind by anything anybody could say in this thread, so there’s nothing you can really gain from it. Besides, when religion is brought into a debate it becomes a religion vs atheism shitstorm, which isn’t intellectual in the slightest.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 23:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Slave_Scyth Slave Scyth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slave_scyth">@Slave_Scyth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Sfacciato, post:11, topic:535691”][quote author=Frell link=topic=654496.msg4384340#msg4384340 date=1384731655]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">not bring religion into this debate</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Religion was invented for the sole reason of answering the questions you posted so people would stop wondering about it, because we don’t know the answers.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Just because religion was created to answer those questions doesn’t mean that they can’t be answered otherwise. I’m not asking for an absolute answer, I’m asking for opinions and <span class="bbcode-b">discussion</span>.</p>
<p>I’ll followup by asking you a few questions based on your response.</p>
<p>Why don’t we have the answers? And are you saying that a correct answer does exist? If you aren’t saying that, do you believe that they could exist?[/quote]My opinion to your questions is religious. Guess I can’t post. Sadface.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 20:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kidpaparoach, post:16, topic:535691”]Why are we alive?<br>
Because the Universe is big and in a sense we were accidentally created and since then we have clung to life fearful of death, fearful of not existing. (Not bringing religion into this, when I say God I mean existence, not the guy with a beard that’s up in the clouds) In a sense if I were to call anything God I’d call existence God. In a sense humans are like the cells in the human body (human body = universe, cells = us). We are a part of the Universe, we live and we die and on our own we are essentially valueless but when you bundle us all up together you can get an amazing thing (I used the word ‘thing’ because depending on the way the words I could use are interpreted it could be seen as wrong).</p>
<p>Are living organisms more important than nonliving objects?<br>
It depends on who’s answering the question. To other living organisms, living organisms are, but in the grand scale of things we are not.</p>
<p>If the entire human population was decimated, would it ‘matter’, on the grand scale of the universe?<br>
It would not because all that we are still exists in a different form. But again, you need to define what does matter (and other words) in order to answer that question correctly (in relation to what the person defines as correct).</p>
<p>Do living (or even nonliving) objects have any intrinsic value whatsoever? What’s the ‘point’?<br>
None whatsoever.</p>
<p>Every living organism eventually dies. Assuming there is no afterlife, what is the point of living if we are condemned to die?<br>
Their is no point but we try to give ourselves reasons to live with the distractions of life. I.e. Let’s say you have a couple of kids; you would want to make sure they are healthy, happy etc. That is a distraction from the emptiness that existence is.</p>
<p>All of those questions answers completely depend on what the answerers (dat wording) perception of ‘x’ are. We’re trying to find answers that their are no answer to or maybe we just aren’t capable of thinking in the ‘correct’ way to understand the answers.[/quote]</p>
<p>Yes, the questions are opinion based, there is no right way to answer them which is why I thought they’d be good discussion questions.</p>
<p>I agree with some of what you’ve said, thanks for your input :). In my opinion though, even as humans bundled together we are relatively unimportant to the universe.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:14, topic:535691”]Animals also have a purpose in life. So the death of humanity would matter for them. Animals would also mourn the death of their owner, so you cannot say that their not affected by the event on an emotional level.</p>
<p>We can objectively decide a object’s value in a society by looking at its usefulness and supply compared to demand. Living objects are more valuable as they give non-living objects value. A pick axe is useful for mining, but worthless without a miner, apart from the value of the materials. But the materials have no value either if there is nobody to process it.[/quote]</p>
<p>Ah, sorry I’ve taken so long to respond.<br>
Okay, in which case replace the decimation of all humans and extend it to all other life forms on our earth. Would anything matter anymore?</p>
<p>Interesting to note though, that a miner without a pickaxe is just as worthless as the lone pickaxe.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="15" data-topic="535691">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 -Nothing:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nobody has set purpose, we mold it ourselves and live to fulfill our own created purpose.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A type of existentialism and absurdism, very interesting, thanks for your input.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 18:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My opinions:</p>
<p>Why are we alive?<br>
Because the Universe is big and in a sense we were accidentally created and since then we have clung to life fearful of death, fearful of not existing. (Not bringing religion into this, when I say God I mean existence, not the guy with a beard that’s up in the clouds) In a sense if I were to call anything God I’d call existence God. In a sense humans are like the cells in the human body (human body = universe, cells = us). We are a part of the Universe, we live and we die and on our own we are essentially valueless but when you bundle us all up together you can get an amazing thing (I used the word ‘thing’ because depending on the way the words I could use are interpreted it could be seen as wrong).</p>
<p>Are living organisms more important than nonliving objects?<br>
It depends on who’s answering the question. To other living organisms, living organisms are, but in the grand scale of things we are not.</p>
<p>If the entire human population was decimated, would it ‘matter’, on the grand scale of the universe?<br>
It would not because all that we are still exists in a different form. But again, you need to define what does matter (and other words) in order to answer that question correctly (in relation to what the person defines as correct).</p>
<p>Do living (or even nonliving) objects have any intrinsic value whatsoever? What’s the ‘point’?<br>
None whatsoever.</p>
<p>Every living organism eventually dies. Assuming there is no afterlife, what is the point of living if we are condemned to die?<br>
Their is no point but we try to give ourselves reasons to live with the distractions of life. I.e. Let’s say you have a couple of kids; you would want to make sure they are healthy, happy etc. That is a distraction from the emptiness that existence is.</p>
<p>All of those questions answers completely depend on what the answerers (dat wording) perception of ‘x’ are. We’re trying to find answers that their are no answer to or maybe we just aren’t capable of thinking in the ‘correct’ way to understand the answers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 13:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nothing1 -Nothing]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nothing1">@Nothing1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:10, topic:535691”][quote author=Sfacciato link=topic=654496.msg4383991#msg4383991 date=1384628274]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">not bring religion into this debate</span><br>
[/quote]<br>
Religion was invented for the sole reason of answering the questions you posted so people would stop wondering about it, because we don’t know the answers.[/quote]<br>
Even though everyone knows this fact, they still blindly believe in their religions. They just don’t want to face the fact that life is generally meaningless. Nobody has set purpose, we mold it ourselves and live to fulfill our own created purpose.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 10:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Animals also have a purpose in life. So the death of humanity would matter for them. Animals would also mourn the death of their owner, so you cannot say that their not affected by the event on an emotional level.</p>
<p>We can objectively decide a object’s value in a society by looking at its usefulness and supply compared to demand. Living objects are more valuable as they give non-living objects value. A pick axe is useful for mining, but worthless without a miner, apart from the value of the materials. But the materials have no value either if there is nobody to process it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 01:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:12, topic:535691”]Question number 2:<br>
Yes, living objects are more valuable for society than non-living ones, and this therefore more important for humanity.</p>
<p>Question number 3. Since non-living objects have no concept of purpose. Only thing which happens to living organisms can matter. So yes, it would matter if humanity died tomorrow. It would change the life of all the animals in the world. Those who are dependent of humans would die of, and those threaten by humans would flourish.</p>
<p>Question number 4: Isn’t this the same question as the first one, as Philosophical value deals with importance?</p>
<p>Question number 5: This is a strictly religious question. It cannot be answered in any other way.[/quote]</p>
<p>Alright, now we can get somewhere.</p>
<p>a) But who decides what is valuable? If there’s no objective value, how can something possibly be more valuable than anything else?</p>
<p>b) I completely agree, only that which happens to living organisms can matter, because things ‘mattering’ is a human construct. However, animals have no concept of purpose. Humans are the only mammal to have a high enough level of reasoning to consider such things, do they matter?<br>
I have an interesting question for you. If living objects are only valuable to society, and all that matters is what is important to humanity (refer to a); then how could anything matter if humans and society died?</p>
<p>c) The question was meant to be a bit more metaphysical in nature. The question was if any object really matters at all.</p>
<p>d) I’ll prove that it can be answered in a variety of ways without religion.</p>
<blockquote>Every living organism eventually dies. Assuming there is no afterlife, what is the point of living if we are condemned to die?</blockquote>
<p>[ul][li]To reproduce.[/li]<br>
[li]To love everybody.[/li]<br>
[li]There is no point.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>to name a few<br>
see: <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meaning_of_life" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meaning_of_life</a></p>
<p>Of course, reading a bunch of philosophies isn’t as fun as hearing ones other people have created for themselves; which is why I asked the question.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 01:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Sfacciato, post:9, topic:535691”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=654496.msg4384321#msg4384321 date=1384728022]<br>
If you want to use the common meaning of value, OK. (the material or monetary worth of something)<br>
Yes, both living objects and non-living ones has a monetary value. You can sell a dog or a barrel of oil and get money for it. The universe in itself is quite valuable, put the transport cost make exploiting it not profitable. So we’re more valuable than most of the universe.</p>
<p>Important: "of great significance or value:"<br>
We’ve already established that we’re all quite valuable compared to the universe, so we’re much more important than the universe.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Alright, I guess I was still not straightforward enough for you? I’m assuming you’re trolling, but I don’t care.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Intrinsic value is an ethical and philosophic property. It is the ethical or philosophic value that an object has “in itself” or “for its own sake”, as an intrinsic property. An object with intrinsic value may be regarded as an end or (in Kantian terminology) end-in-itself.[1]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You should also read:<br>
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Intrinsic_value_(ethics)#Absolute_and_relative" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Intrinsic_value_(ethics)#Absolute_and_relative</a><br>
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Value_theory#Ethics_and_axiology" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Value_theory#Ethics_and_axiology</a><br>
because that’s what the questions were about…[/quote]<br>
Finally, you have learn to define the terms you’re talking about. I’m perfectly aware that you didn’t mean monetary value, I’m just playing with your refusal to clarify what you’re talking about.</p>
<p>Question number 2:<br>
Yes, living objects are more valuable for society than non-living ones, and this therefore more important for humanity.</p>
<p>Question number 3. Since non-living objects have no concept of purpose. Only thing which happens to living organisms can matter. So yes, it would matter if humanity died tomorrow. It would change the life of all the animals in the world. Those who are dependent of humans would die of, and those threaten by humans would flourish.</p>
<p>Question number 4: Isn’t this the same question as the first one, as Philosophical value deals with importance?</p>
<p>Question number 5: This is a strictly religious question. It cannot be answered in any other way.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:10, topic:535691”][quote author=Sfacciato link=topic=654496.msg4383991#msg4383991 date=1384628274]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">not bring religion into this debate</span><br>
[/quote]<br>
Religion was invented for the sole reason of answering the questions you posted so people would stop wondering about it, because we don’t know the answers.[/quote]</p>
<p>Just because religion was created to answer those questions doesn’t mean that they can’t be answered otherwise. I’m not asking for an absolute answer, I’m asking for opinions and <span class="bbcode-b">discussion</span>.</p>
<p>I’ll followup by asking you a few questions based on your response.</p>
<p>Why don’t we have the answers? And are you saying that a correct answer does exist? If you aren’t saying that, do you believe that they could exist?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 23:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="1" data-topic="535691">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/sfacciato/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Sfacciato:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">not bring religion into this debate</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Religion was invented for the sole reason of answering the questions you posted so people would stop wondering about it, because we don’t know the answers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 23:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:8, topic:535691”]If you want to use the common meaning of value, OK. (the material or monetary worth of something)<br>
Yes, both living objects and non-living ones has a monetary value. You can sell a dog or a barrel of oil and get money for it. The universe in itself is quite valuable, put the transport cost make exploiting it not profitable. So we’re more valuable than most of the universe.</p>
<p>Important: "of great significance or value:"<br>
We’ve already established that we’re all quite valuable compared to the universe, so we’re much more important than the universe.[/quote]</p>
<p>Alright, I guess I was still not straightforward enough for you? I’m assuming you’re trolling, but I don’t care.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Intrinsic_value_(ethics):</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Intrinsic value is an ethical and philosophic property. It is the ethical or philosophic value that an object has “in itself” or “for its own sake”, as an intrinsic property. An object with intrinsic value may be regarded as an end or (in Kantian terminology) end-in-itself.[1]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You should also read:<br>
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Intrinsic_value_(ethics)#Absolute_and_relative" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Intrinsic_value_(ethics)#Absolute_and_relative</a><br>
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Value_theory#Ethics_and_axiology" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Value_theory#Ethics_and_axiology</a><br>
because that’s what the questions were about…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 23:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Sfacciato, post:7, topic:535691”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=654496.msg4384292#msg4384292 date=1384724068]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Alright, now we’ve got a discussion going. Thanks for your input.</p>
<p>If you have any suggestions as to make the questions better, I’d be happy to hear them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve already done that. Define the words “important” and “value” in the context you’re using them.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I meant something along the lines of providing me with better questions to ask. I shouldn’t have to define words for you, but here you go. <a href="http://lmgtfy.com/?q=define%3Aimportant" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Important</a>, <a href="http://lmgtfy.com/?q=define%3Aintrinsic+value" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">intrinsic value</a>. The questions are simple, and they are rather objective, I don’t know why you had so much trouble answering them. I don’t know how much more straightforward ‘intrinsic value’ could be, either.[/quote]<br>
If you want to use the common meaning of value, OK. (the material or monetary worth of something)<br>
Yes, both living objects and non-living ones has a monetary value. You can sell a dog or a barrel of oil and get money for it. The universe in itself is quite valuable, put the transport cost make exploiting it not profitable. So we’re more valuable than most of the universe.</p>
<p>Important: "of great significance or value:"<br>
We’ve already established that we’re all quite valuable compared to the universe, so we’re much more important than the universe.</p>
<p>Source:<br>
<a href="http://www.oxforddictionaries.com/definition/english/important?q=important" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.oxforddictionaries.com/definition/english/important?q=important</a><br>
<a href="http://www.oxforddictionaries.com/definition/english/value?q=value" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.oxforddictionaries.com/definition/english/value?q=value</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 22:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:6, topic:535691”][quote author=Sfacciato link=topic=654496.msg4384190#msg4384190 date=1384674825]<br>
Alright, now we’ve got a discussion going. Thanks for your input.</p>
<p>If you have any suggestions as to make the questions better, I’d be happy to hear them.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I’ve already done that. Define the words “important” and “value” in the context you’re using them.[/quote]</p>
<p>I meant something along the lines of providing me with better questions to ask. I shouldn’t have to define words for you, but here you go. <a href="http://lmgtfy.com/?q=define%3Aimportant" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Important</a>, <a href="http://lmgtfy.com/?q=define%3Aintrinsic+value" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">intrinsic value</a>. The questions are simple, and they are rather objective, I don’t know why you had so much trouble answering them. I don’t know how much more straightforward ‘intrinsic value’ could be, either.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 22:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Sfacciato, post:5, topic:535691”]Alright, now we’ve got a discussion going. Thanks for your input.</p>
<p>If you have any suggestions as to make the questions better, I’d be happy to hear them.[/quote]<br>
I’ve already done that. Define the words “important” and “value” in the context you’re using them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 21:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sfacciato Sfacciato]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sfacciato">@Sfacciato</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“The Wanderer, post:4, topic:535691”]Why are we alive?<br>
There is no point to being alive. We are just alive and there is nothing else to it. You do not need some point in life you are simply alive and soon you will be dead.</p>
<p>Are living organisms more important than nonliving objects?<br>
As bowser said, define what you would say important is? I think that gasoline is really important as it fuels most of our machines and in nonliving so therefore is extremely important than say a bird. However birds are extremely important in the ecosystems of our world. Therefore, I’d say everything is equally important if you consider importance basically what role it plays in the universe.</p>
<p>If the entire human population was decimated, would it ‘matter’, on the grand scale of the universe?<br>
I don’t think losing 1/10 of the worlds population would matter at all. No matter if you talk about the grand scale of the universe or just the Earth. The Earth will still orbit the Sun and everything will still go on.</p>
<p>Do living (or even nonliving) objects have any intrinsic value whatsoever? What’s the ‘point’?<br>
What point? There is no point and living objects are no different than nonliving objects in the sense that we have some importance to life. We are just atoms that are bonded together that function as a whole.</p>
<p>Every living organism eventually dies. Assuming there is no afterlife, what is the point of living if we are condemned to die?<br>
There is no point of living. Why do you need a point to live?[/quote]</p>
<p>Alright, now we’ve got a discussion going. Thanks for your input.</p>
<p>If you have any suggestions as to make the questions better, I’d be happy to hear them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 07:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535691-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/life/535691.rss">Life</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
