<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Question on using clients</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-using-clients/289418</link>
    <description>I&#39;m having trouble with using clients and things. When I download a client for a specific server, I don&#39;t know how to use it. After downloading, i click the server icon but a window opens saying:

&quot;Windows can not open this file&quot;... &quot;To open this file, Windows need to know what program created it&quot;. 

Am I suppose to click on the icon? Or do I open moparscape and somehow blend the client with the server? I&#39;m terribly confused, and need some help. Oh and I have downloaded moparscape, don&#39;t know if this would help though.

And what is ayran? I thought you just download the moparscape server and play.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 03:31:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-using-clients/289418.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Question on using clients</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@grapejuice grapejuice]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/grapejuice">@grapejuice</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m having trouble with using clients and things. When I download a client for a specific server, I don’t know how to use it. After downloading, i click the server icon but a window opens saying:</p>
<p>“Windows can not open this file”… “To open this file, Windows need to know what program created it”.</p>
<p>Am I suppose to click on the icon? Or do I open moparscape and somehow blend the client with the server? I’m terribly confused, and need some help. Oh and I have downloaded moparscape, don’t know if this would help though.</p>
<p>And what is ayran? I thought you just download the moparscape server and play.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-using-clients/289418/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-using-clients/289418/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 03:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-289418-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-on-using-clients/289418.rss">Question on using clients</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
