<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server is offline (but i can log in)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-is-offline-but-i-can-log-in/190769</link>
    <description>hello... i have follow everystep on this post ( http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,200036.0.html ) and when i compile and then run my server comes online; when i try to log on via moparscape using my ip e-scape.no-ip.info i cannot log in... i tried logging in with &#39;localhost&#39; and i can get in but no one else can. i tried adding my server to the serverlist on this site but it won&#39;t let me because its ofline...
[IMG]http://i98.photobucket.com/albums/l248/bonneau_14/asdas.jpg[/img]
i have no-ip running while i try to do this (it is on the taskbar) and i still can&#39;t get it going... i&#39;m not sure if this is whats supposed to happen when i run the server so i just want to check.
[IMG]http://i98.photobucket.com/albums/l248/bonneau_14/dhdhd.jpg[/img]
i&#39;ll show you guys the router i&#39;m using:
[IMG]http://i98.photobucket.com/albums/l248/bonneau_14/xfhd.jpg[/img]

So? when i try to get the server running all i have to do is run the &#39;runserver.bat&#39; file? becasue that allows me to log on but no one else. and where should i have my source file place?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2008, 03:07:52 PM[/size][hr]*bumb*

I would like to get an answer because i&#39;m anxious to start my server and i do not want to make another thread in order to get my answer...

*sorry for bumping if its against the rules but i believe my reason will allow an exception*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 18:04:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-is-offline-but-i-can-log-in/190769.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server is offline (but i can log in)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vossler Vossler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vossler">@Vossler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hello… i have follow everystep on this post ( <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,200036.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,200036.0.html</a> ) and when i compile and then run my server comes online; when i try to log on via moparscape using my ip e-scape.no-ip.info i cannot log in… i tried logging in with ‘localhost’ and i can get in but no one else can. i tried adding my server to the serverlist on this site but it won’t let me because its ofline…<br>
<img src="http://i98.photobucket.com/albums/l248/bonneau_14/asdas.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
i have no-ip running while i try to do this (it is on the taskbar) and i still can’t get it going… i’m not sure if this is whats supposed to happen when i run the server so i just want to check.<br>
<img src="http://i98.photobucket.com/albums/l248/bonneau_14/dhdhd.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
i’ll show you guys the router i’m using:<br>
<img src="http://i98.photobucket.com/albums/l248/bonneau_14/xfhd.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>So? when i try to get the server running all i have to do is run the ‘runserver.bat’ file? becasue that allows me to log on but no one else. and where should i have my source file place?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 19, 2008, 03:07:52 PM[/size][hr]<em>bumb</em></p>
<p>I would like to get an answer because i’m anxious to start my server and i do not want to make another thread in order to get my answer…</p>
<p><em>sorry for bumping if its against the rules but i believe my reason will allow an exception</em></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-is-offline-but-i-can-log-in/190769/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-is-offline-but-i-can-log-in/190769/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 18:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-190769-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-is-offline-but-i-can-log-in/190769.rss">Server is offline (but i can log in)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
