<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Officer involved in James North shooting (MY AREA)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/officer-involved-in-james-north-shooting-my-area/261884</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;Police have confirmed that an officer was involved in a shooting that closed off a small section of James Street North between Strachan Street and Simcoe Street East after an 18-year-old man was shot late this afternoon.

The Special Investigations Unit, the province’s police watchdog, said they were contacted by Hamilton police this evening after an 18-year-old man was shot.

The SIU says an officer fired at least one shot and the man was struck and taken to Hamilton General Hospital.

The SIU has assigned six investigators and three forensic investigators to probe the circumstances of the incident.

The SIU is a civilian agency that investigates cases of serious injuries and deaths involving the police.

This is the second time in less than a month that Hamilton officers have allegedly been involved in a shooting.

At the scene, several cars crowded the road as police officers attempted to unravel the shooting. On the street, clothing that witnesses say was used to stop the bleeding still lay on James Street. A bullet hole was visible through a passenger’s side window of a car facing south on the curb lane of James.

Sarah, who asked that her last name not be revealed, said she was watching a movie in a nearby row of townhomes when she heard shots ring out.

“All I heard was &#39;bang bang bang,&#39; then I came out and saw a guy laying on the ground next to the van.”

Police have not confirmed if anyone has been arrested.

The other local shooting incident the SIU was called in on occurred shortly after 9 p.m. on Jan. 23 following a holdup at a Tim Hortons at Upper James Street and Stone Church Road. It spurred a chain of events that led to a confrontation on Wycliffe Avenue, in a quiet central Mountain neighbourhood near Inverness Avenue and Upper James.

It&#39;s believed the man fired at police before being shot, but the SIU has not confirmed that.

&quot;The fellow that was injured by the police bullet is ... in hospital under police guard (and) has undergone some surgery,” SIU spokesperson Frank Phillips said yesterday.

The man was shot in the arm. His injuries are not life-threatening.

Hamilton police could not say yesterday which of the two suspects in that case was the injured person because of the SIU investigation.

Phillips said there were &quot;a number of shots fired&quot; during the January incident and two officers have been designated subject officers. Another four have been designated witness officers and there were several independent witnesses, he said.

Two firearms, which will undergo forensic testing, were also recovered at the scene.

Todd Fenty, 26, and Fawad Nouri, 24 — both of no fixed address — were each initially charged with four counts of robbery and one count of wearing a disguise with intent to commit an indictable offence. Police added 36 new charges this week, including some alleging forcible confinement of nine Hortons customers in the store during the robbery.

The SIU is asking anyone who witnessed today&#39;s shooting incident to call 1-800-787-8529.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
sauce: http://thespec.com/News/article/512597

Wow.. I&#39;m stunned. This was literally down the street from my house. At first I heard he was shot in the head, but it says he was shot in the arm.
It happened around 5 and there&#39;s still police there (11:30PM as of this post)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2009 05:52:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/officer-involved-in-james-north-shooting-my-area/261884.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Officer involved in James North shooting (MY AREA)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxKanexX Kane.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxkanexx">@XxKanexX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Take a picture and show.<br>
If that were down the street from me I’d be quite nerved.</p>
<p>Although, anything could happen anywhere.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/officer-involved-in-james-north-shooting-my-area/261884/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/officer-involved-in-james-north-shooting-my-area/261884/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2009 05:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261884-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/officer-involved-in-james-north-shooting-my-area/261884.rss">Officer involved in James North shooting (MY AREA)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Officer involved in James North shooting (MY AREA)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uriko Uriko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uriko">@Uriko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Police have confirmed that an officer was involved in a shooting that closed off a small section of James Street North between Strachan Street and Simcoe Street East after an 18-year-old man was shot late this afternoon.
<p>The Special Investigations Unit, the province’s police watchdog, said they were contacted by Hamilton police this evening after an 18-year-old man was shot.</p>
<p>The SIU says an officer fired at least one shot and the man was struck and taken to Hamilton General Hospital.</p>
<p>The SIU has assigned six investigators and three forensic investigators to probe the circumstances of the incident.</p>
<p>The SIU is a civilian agency that investigates cases of serious injuries and deaths involving the police.</p>
<p>This is the second time in less than a month that Hamilton officers have allegedly been involved in a shooting.</p>
<p>At the scene, several cars crowded the road as police officers attempted to unravel the shooting. On the street, clothing that witnesses say was used to stop the bleeding still lay on James Street. A bullet hole was visible through a passenger’s side window of a car facing south on the curb lane of James.</p>
<p>Sarah, who asked that her last name not be revealed, said she was watching a movie in a nearby row of townhomes when she heard shots ring out.</p>
<p>“All I heard was ‘bang bang bang,’ then I came out and saw a guy laying on the ground next to the van.”</p>
<p>Police have not confirmed if anyone has been arrested.</p>
<p>The other local shooting incident the SIU was called in on occurred shortly after 9 p.m. on Jan. 23 following a holdup at a Tim Hortons at Upper James Street and Stone Church Road. It spurred a chain of events that led to a confrontation on Wycliffe Avenue, in a quiet central Mountain neighbourhood near Inverness Avenue and Upper James.</p>
<p>It’s believed the man fired at police before being shot, but the SIU has not confirmed that.</p>
<p>"The fellow that was injured by the police bullet is … in hospital under police guard (and) has undergone some surgery,” SIU spokesperson Frank Phillips said yesterday.</p>
<p>The man was shot in the arm. His injuries are not life-threatening.</p>
<p>Hamilton police could not say yesterday which of the two suspects in that case was the injured person because of the SIU investigation.</p>
<p>Phillips said there were “a number of shots fired” during the January incident and two officers have been designated subject officers. Another four have been designated witness officers and there were several independent witnesses, he said.</p>
<p>Two firearms, which will undergo forensic testing, were also recovered at the scene.</p>
<p>Todd Fenty, 26, and Fawad Nouri, 24 — both of no fixed address — were each initially charged with four counts of robbery and one count of wearing a disguise with intent to commit an indictable offence. Police added 36 new charges this week, including some alleging forcible confinement of nine Hortons customers in the store during the robbery.</p>
<p>The SIU is asking anyone who witnessed today’s shooting incident to call 1-800-787-8529.</p>
</blockquote><br>
sauce: <a href="http://thespec.com/News/article/512597" rel="nofollow noopener">http://thespec.com/News/article/512597</a>
<p>Wow… I’m stunned. This was literally down the street from my house. At first I heard he was shot in the head, but it says he was shot in the arm.<br>
It happened around 5 and there’s still police there (11:30PM as of this post)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/officer-involved-in-james-north-shooting-my-area/261884/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/officer-involved-in-james-north-shooting-my-area/261884/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2009 04:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-261884-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/officer-involved-in-james-north-shooting-my-area/261884.rss">Officer involved in James North shooting (MY AREA)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
