<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>playerGfx method. #3</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playergfx-method-3/154882</link>
    <description>Still, i haven&#39;t had an answer for this. And i&#39;m not giving up. Over the past few days, i&#39;ve been wondering why this isn&#39;t working. Making new methods to see if i can improve it. And still, nothing.. Looking into the stillGfx method, see if i have anything missing, anything that needs to be changed etc..

As you know, ricscape, or rickscape, is a popular PK source. Based around level 1, varrock wild. It has now developed, to varrock?.. But, it still has the same features. I think it is now called Penguin scape, or something i&#39;m not too sure of. There is also a server, that SWAT made. And i&#39;d like to take his for an example.

The method he used.. ... (playerGfx)
[code]
public void playerGfx(int id, int delay) {
mask100var1 = id;
mask100var2 = delay;
mask100update = true;
updateRequired = true;
}
[/code]

That will make the GFX move with the player, correct?... So i kept on searching, and searching, and searching.. The only think i could find, with playerGfx, inside it, was when it was being called, into a method, like so..
[code]
playerGfx(252, 0);
[/code]

Dds special, gfx 252, delay of gfx? = 0..

Now, that works perfect, i&#39;ve even added it to most spells, and it works 100%.

My problem:

On my source, when i add that method. No errors..

When i call it, same usage:
[code]
playerGfx(252, 0);
[/code]

Into the Dds special method. It doesn&#39;t do the GFX..

It does everything else, emote, hit, special delay, timers, but no Gfx.. It works fine, when i use staticAnimation, or stillGfx.. But not with playerGfx..

I would use staticAnimation, but the special, always faces south when your spec&#39;ing, and it looks rediculous lol.

Does anyone know how to fix this? If so, please post :). Thanks.
[br][size=1]Posted on: October 27, 2007, 03:20:13 PM[/size][hr]Please, c&#39;mon..</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2007 04:53:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playergfx-method-3/154882.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>playerGfx method. #3</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@X-J-K-X X-J-K-X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x-j-k-x">@X-J-K-X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Still, i haven’t had an answer for this. And i’m not giving up. Over the past few days, i’ve been wondering why this isn’t working. Making new methods to see if i can improve it. And still, nothing… Looking into the stillGfx method, see if i have anything missing, anything that needs to be changed etc…</p>
<p>As you know, ricscape, or rickscape, is a popular PK source. Based around level 1, varrock wild. It has now developed, to varrock?.. But, it still has the same features. I think it is now called Penguin scape, or something i’m not too sure of. There is also a server, that SWAT made. And i’d like to take his for an example.</p>
<p>The method he used… … (playerGfx)</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public void playerGfx(int id, int delay) {
mask100var1 = id;
mask100var2 = delay;
mask100update = true;
updateRequired = true;
}</code></pre>
<p>That will make the GFX move with the player, correct?.. So i kept on searching, and searching, and searching… The only think i could find, with playerGfx, inside it, was when it was being called, into a method, like so…</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">playerGfx(252, 0);</code></pre>
<p>Dds special, gfx 252, delay of gfx? = 0…</p>
<p>Now, that works perfect, i’ve even added it to most spells, and it works 100%.</p>
<p>My problem:</p>
<p>On my source, when i add that method. No errors…</p>
<p>When i call it, same usage:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">playerGfx(252, 0);</code></pre>
<p>Into the Dds special method. It doesn’t do the GFX…</p>
<p>It does everything else, emote, hit, special delay, timers, but no Gfx… It works fine, when i use staticAnimation, or stillGfx… But not with playerGfx…</p>
<p>I would use staticAnimation, but the special, always faces south when your spec’ing, and it looks rediculous lol.</p>
<p>Does anyone know how to fix this? If so, please post :). Thanks.<br>
[br][size=1]Posted on: October 27, 2007, 03:20:13 PM[/size][hr]Please, c’mon…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playergfx-method-3/154882/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playergfx-method-3/154882/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2007 04:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154882-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/playergfx-method-3/154882.rss">playerGfx method. #3</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
