<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Brooklyn-Scape 317 [Private Msg me for Reward Details!]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154</link>
    <description>[center][size=18pt]Brooklyn-Scape 317[/size][/center]
[center]Hello, I&#39;m sort of new to hosting private servers yes, But I&#39;m not new to hosting servers in general, I&#39;ve hosted many different types of servers mostly on steam. I&#39;m Looking for a full Development team Including Coder, Web Designer, And Client Manager. I don&#39;t want somebody who is half ass, I am looking for nothing less than great. If You work for me in creating Brooklyn-Scape we expect you to take it serious, I will be Supplying everything, From the Dedicated Server, to the Ip&#39;s To the Domains and to the Website. This is not just a game anymore, This is a job. APPLY NOW[/center]

[center][size=18pt]What I Expect from Brooklyn-Scape 317[/size][/center]
[center]I&#39;m expecting a new and amazing server, Yeah there will always be someone who is better, and in this case a server that is better, But i&#39;d like to have some unique features. I&#39;d be Expecting to see a fully working Site, Forums, Hiscores. I want to see a Great Pking System, And a Even better PvM System, I want people to have to work for they&#39;re items, And When they get them be excited, I want a Economy server, With  Amazing Pking added into it, the best of Both worlds, I want people to skill and I want people to Pk, Just as much as I want PvM. I don&#39;t want it to be Easy to get 99 Everything, I don&#39;t want it to be Easy to get Full Bandos, or Ags. I want Party Hats to be Rare and I don&#39;t want people having EVERYTHING.[/center]

[center][size=18pt]Contact Information![/size][/center]
[center]If Your intrested in what I want to do, Please post a reply here, Or Private message me Threw this, After that We will chat about it,and get further information About your skills, your contact information(Skype, Steam, Email One of the Three must be included), ect. You will Be Treated with respect, and You will Have fun while your at it.[/center]

[size=14pt][b][u]Please Private Message me for information on what you will receive in return for Coding, Web Designing, and managing a Client for me. I Give a Very Good Offer.[/u][/b][/size]

Thanks,
-David (Brooklyn-Scape Founder)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 02:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Brooklyn-Scape 317 [Private Msg me for Reward Details!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zashi2014 Zashi2014]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zashi2014">@Zashi2014</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>iPad typing for the win. And I don’t have one yet, waiting for my pay period to get it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 02:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540154-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154.rss">Brooklyn-Scape 317 [Private Msg me for Reward Details!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Brooklyn-Scape 317 [Private Msg me for Reward Details!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEthanx xEthanx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xethanx">@xEthanx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I may be interested in helping out with web design but I don’t really know anything about your server. Post some pictures or something, your current text is meaningless.</p>
<p>P.S. Your grammar and capitalization is atrocious.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 01:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540154-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154.rss">Brooklyn-Scape 317 [Private Msg me for Reward Details!]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Brooklyn-Scape 317 [Private Msg me for Reward Details!]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zashi2014 Zashi2014]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zashi2014">@Zashi2014</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center][size=18pt]Brooklyn-Scape 317[/size][/center]<br>
[center]Hello, I’m sort of new to hosting private servers yes, But I’m not new to hosting servers in general, I’ve hosted many different types of servers mostly on steam. I’m Looking for a full Development team Including Coder, Web Designer, And Client Manager. I don’t want somebody who is half ass, I am looking for nothing less than great. If You work for me in creating Brooklyn-Scape we expect you to take it serious, I will be Supplying everything, From the Dedicated Server, to the Ip’s To the Domains and to the Website. This is not just a game anymore, This is a job. APPLY NOW[/center]</p>
<p>[center][size=18pt]What I Expect from Brooklyn-Scape 317[/size][/center]<br>
[center]I’m expecting a new and amazing server, Yeah there will always be someone who is better, and in this case a server that is better, But i’d like to have some unique features. I’d be Expecting to see a fully working Site, Forums, Hiscores. I want to see a Great Pking System, And a Even better PvM System, I want people to have to work for they’re items, And When they get them be excited, I want a Economy server, With  Amazing Pking added into it, the best of Both worlds, I want people to skill and I want people to Pk, Just as much as I want PvM. I don’t want it to be Easy to get 99 Everything, I don’t want it to be Easy to get Full Bandos, or Ags. I want Party Hats to be Rare and I don’t want people having EVERYTHING.[/center]</p>
<p>[center][size=18pt]Contact Information![/size][/center]<br>
[center]If Your intrested in what I want to do, Please post a reply here, Or Private message me Threw this, After that We will chat about it,and get further information About your skills, your contact information(Skype, Steam, Email One of the Three must be included), ect. You will Be Treated with respect, and You will Have fun while your at it.[/center]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Please Private Message me for information on what you will receive in return for Coding, Web Designing, and managing a Client for me. I Give a Very Good Offer.</span></span>[/size]</p>
<p>Thanks,<br>
-David (Brooklyn-Scape Founder)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 23:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540154-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-private-msg-me-for-reward-details/540154.rss">Brooklyn-Scape 317 [Private Msg me for Reward Details!]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
