<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Gay Marriage</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039</link>
    <description>Do you agree that people should be allowed to have gay marriage?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 21:36:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nickog15 nickog15]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nickog15">@nickog15</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If it makes them happy…<br>
France -</p>
<blockquote>PARIS (AP) — The French Senate has voted to legalize same-sex marriage in France, putting a landmark bill on track to become law by summer.
<p>The vote in the upper house of parliament — led by President Francois Hollande’s Socialists — comes despite boisterous protests. Opponents — mostly conservatives and fervent Roman Catholics — have sought to defend traditional marriage.</p>
<p>Both houses of parliament will now take up a second reading to consider minor Senate changes to the bill passed in February by the National Assembly, also controlled by a Socialist-led majority.</p>
<p>The bill would allow gay marriage and let same-sex couples adopt children. On the campaign trail last year, Hollande pledged to push through such legislation if elected.</p>
<p>About a dozen mostly European nations already allow gay marriage.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.salon.com/2013/04/12/france_passes_gay_marriage_bill_ap/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.salon.com/2013/04/12/france_passes_gay_marriage_bill_ap/</a></li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/86</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 21:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-86</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:83, topic:515039”]1. Again, do not use the old testament, it is a clusterfu<span class="bbcode-b"></span>ck of rules that are somewhat repealed.<br>
2. Again, the source are not setting the verse into context. But set that to the side, why should St. Paul be an authority on homosexuality?[/quote]</p>
<p>The Old Testament law, put very simply, show God’s mind on <span class="bbcode-s">crime</span> sin. It is his law.<br>
The New Testament is different from the Old Testament in that we are in the Day of Grace.</p>
<p>Check out Romans 1:27. Taking that into context, the Apostle Paul is writing about God’s wrath against all “ungodliness and unrighteousness.”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/85</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 10:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-85</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:83, topic:515039”]1. Again, do not use the old testament, it is a clusterfu<span class="bbcode-b"></span>ck of rules that are somewhat repealed.<br>
2. Again, the source are not setting the verse into context. But set that to the side, why should St. Paul be an authority on homosexuality?[/quote]<br>
Q.Q more about the rules why don’t you, I was proving a point, not preaching or pushing my beliefs onto people.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/84</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 04:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-84</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ol>
<li>Again, do not use the old testament, it is a clusterfu<span class="bbcode-b"></span>ck of rules that are somewhat repealed.</li>
<li>Again, the source are not setting the verse into context. But set that to the side, why should St. Paul be an authority on homosexuality?</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/83</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 03:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-83</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:79, topic:515039”]amy:<br>
Rule number one when speaking about Christian morality:<br>
NEVER quote the old testament.<br>
Rule number two:<br>
Know the source. The bible doesn’t use the phrase “practice homosexuality” in the bible verse you are quoting.[/quote]<br>
Fixed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/82</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 03:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-82</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“JavaTC, post:80, topic:515039”]Here’s an idea<br>
How about we come up with a whole new thing called Homosexual Marriage.  It works just like real marriage, but it’s only for homosexuals, that way all the people the are stuck in the dark ages and think that people shouldn’t be allowed to express their love because they view it as immoral can stop bitching.</p>
<p>I.E There’s no reason it shouldn’t be allowed by law.  Call it civil partnerships since that’s the legal part of it, fine, but don’t outright ban it. [/quote]<br>
Should we have black marriage, and Jew marriage too?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/81</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 02:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-81</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here’s an idea<br>
How about we come up with a whole new thing called Homosexual Marriage.  It works just like real marriage, but it’s only for homosexuals, that way all the people the are stuck in the dark ages and think that people shouldn’t be allowed to express their love because they view it as immoral can stop bitching.</p>
<p>I.E There’s no reason it shouldn’t be allowed by law.  Call it civil partnerships since that’s the legal part of it, fine, but don’t outright ban it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/80</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 02:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-80</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>amy:<br>
Rule number one when speaking about Christian morality:<br>
NEVER quote the old testament.<br>
Rule number two:<br>
Know the source. The bible doesn’t use the phrase “practice homosexuality” in the bible verse you are quoting.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/79</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 02:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-79</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Leviticus 18:22</p>
<p>states you should not have sexual relations with the same sex as you would with the opposite.</p>
<p>1 Corinthians 6:9-10<br>
states whomever does a wrongful deed will not go to heaven, in this it includes homosexuality</p>
<p>God may love everyone, but it is stated that homosexuality in the bible, as are many others, wrongful acts. Therefore religion does not recognise gay sexuality, as it is stated to be a horrible thing.</p>
<p>My family follows a christian religion, my mother only ever went to religious schools, along with the rest of her family. Yet, i do not. Why? Because i like to think for myself and believe things which are proven to me. I was not forced to be religious, nor will i ever.</p>
<p>The bible will not be updated, there are many reasons why and your opinion for them to change it would not put a dint on one of those reasons.</p>
<p>I am not religious, just because i am defending the religious standpoint in this debate does not mean i do not accept gay marriage. I am simply pointing out to you the reasons behind religious beliefs on gay marriage. I would like to see homosexual marriage be brought into effect by law, it would be a glorious day for equal rights. That doesn’t mean religion should not be given fair rights their, they are allowed to believe what they wish and should not be told otherwise. Just as gays should be able to marry, and not be told otherwise.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/78</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 02:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-78</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>marc: The bible was updated in 300 A.D. If anyone was to invent a religion today, we would call them crazy Scientologist and not take them seriously. Religion is a thing of the past and should be kept there.</p>
<p>Also, John 3.16 can be read in different ways.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/77</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 02:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-77</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marc110 marc110]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marc110">@marc110</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:74, topic:515039”][quote author=marc110 link=topic=633289.msg4280733#msg4280733 date=1365528469]<br>
you don’t understand you little bible basher , if your gay then you should be able to get married</p>
<p>straight people don’t understand how hard is it being gay and being told to be straight all the time does not help. Let them get married in  church god is meant to love everyone no matter what so why not let them?<br>
[/quote]<br>
A little bible basher? I am not forcing religious beliefs on you, not can i ever because i am not a religious person. Therefore you statement is incorrect and irrelevant to this entire discussion. Never tell someone they do not understand, when you are the one who is ignorant. It only proves you cannot prove a point and must refer to the other party as uneducated.</p>
<p>As Krackkid said, how can you know how hard it is when you are not gay yourself? Again, do not tell people they do not understand something which you have no experience with. That is hypocritical. Being gay isn’t hard in western society nowadays, it is more accepted then ever and being homosexual does very little to influence your financial and social life. People may make remakes at gays saying ‘you choose your sexuality’, but that does not mean everybody tells gays to be straight. I have multiple homosexual and bisexual friends, neither of which have ever complained about it nor had any other problems.</p>
<p>You cannot say who god does and does not love as an atheist, if god appealed to you then you would be religious which you are not. Therefore do not judge the beliefs of those who have faith, it is your personal opinion and nobody wants you to force it on them. It states that only a man and women shall lay in bed, within the bible. This suggests that gays are not accepted by the bible and therefore religion does not acknowledge gays. It is up to the church in who should marry there, but it is up the government of the country who should decide whether or not gays shall marry.</p>
<p>Niall, you’re right, i should have been more specific. I was implying in the western society and cultural background, mainly between America and Australia. Yes, many countries still have beliefs forced upon them from birth, and ones which influence the law still. This does make it hard for someone to think and feel freely, but you’ll find as these people migrate to another country the generation after them loses their beliefs. This is because the parents no longer force the children to believe in something they do not want, it becomes a personal decision.[/quote]</p>
<p>in the bible</p>
<p>John 3:16</p>
<p>This states that God is love, - and he’d give his own son for even sinners.</p>
<p>While his love is universal, - he also has universal judgement. Which one is invoked on us, - is up to ourselves.</p>
<p>so if god loves everyone why can’t you be gay? gay marriage stands cheers god!!!</p>
<p>being forced religion is still happening all over the world , what would your family say if you didn’t want to follow the religion they wouldn’t like it , if your family are religious then 9/10 you have been forced seen you were born to follow the religion with even knowing it.<br>
Unless of course your family told you it was ok for you not to go to church and follow religion but i doubt very much happens much but that is not the point this is off the topic</p>
<p>The real question is if god loves everyone why is being gay a sin? if god made the world why not just remove gay from the world before making it?</p>
<p>I think the bible needs updating because its 2013 not 500bc</p>
<p>yup i read the bible before you ask</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/76</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 02:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-76</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“arham 4, post:73, topic:515039”][quote author=arham 4 link=topic=633289.msg4279871#msg4279871 date=1365380590]<br>
Bowser and Niall are usually the odd people I see in these 2 sections. They will agree with the opposite of what others agree.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I remain corrected. :P[/quote]<br>
We do not agree on everything. I think marriage should be the legal term. It has been the term since time immemorial, and should therefore still be used, but with an updated definition. I do not think religion is an informed decision either, since most people pick their parents belief.</p>
<p>amy: And I knows gay people who had trouble with their sexuality. Not everyone has the same experience. It isn’t long ago since the sodomy laws in US was repealed.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/75</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 23:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-75</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“marc110, post:69, topic:515039”]you don’t understand you little bible basher , if your gay then you should be able to get married</p>
<p>straight people don’t understand how hard is it being gay and being told to be straight all the time does not help. Let them get married in  church god is meant to love everyone no matter what so why not let them?[/quote]<br>
A little bible basher? I am not forcing religious beliefs on you, not can i ever because i am not a religious person. Therefore you statement is incorrect and irrelevant to this entire discussion. Never tell someone they do not understand, when you are the one who is ignorant. It only proves you cannot prove a point and must refer to the other party as uneducated.</p>
<p>As Krackkid said, how can you know how hard it is when you are not gay yourself? Again, do not tell people they do not understand something which you have no experience with. That is hypocritical. Being gay isn’t hard in western society nowadays, it is more accepted then ever and being homosexual does very little to influence your financial and social life. People may make remakes at gays saying ‘you choose your sexuality’, but that does not mean everybody tells gays to be straight. I have multiple homosexual and bisexual friends, neither of which have ever complained about it nor had any other problems.</p>
<p>You cannot say who god does and does not love as an atheist, if god appealed to you then you would be religious which you are not. Therefore do not judge the beliefs of those who have faith, it is your personal opinion and nobody wants you to force it on them. It states that only a man and women shall lay in bed, within the bible. This suggests that gays are not accepted by the bible and therefore religion does not acknowledge gays. It is up to the church in who should marry there, but it is up the government of the country who should decide whether or not gays shall marry.</p>
<p>Niall, you’re right, i should have been more specific. I was implying in the western society and cultural background, mainly between America and Australia. Yes, many countries still have beliefs forced upon them from birth, and ones which influence the law still. This does make it hard for someone to think and feel freely, but you’ll find as these people migrate to another country the generation after them loses their beliefs. This is because the parents no longer force the children to believe in something they do not want, it becomes a personal decision.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/74</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 23:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-74</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="36" data-topic="515039">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 arham 4:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Bowser and Niall are usually the odd people I see in these 2 sections. They will agree with the opposite of what others agree.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I remain corrected. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/73</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 23:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-73</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I never said marriage was a Christian act, I said the way we did it here in America is. That was kinda the whole point of my post… I was saying it isn’t and shouldn’t be religious… Maybe I don’t know enough about how gays and lesbians marry here in the states that have legalized it, but from the news pictures and things I’ve seen a lot of them look like standard marriages with a priest and such.</p>
<p>Also — there is a big difference between saying a religion HAS to marry a certain way and saying they can’t marry certain people. You brought up multiple wives and children. If we have a legal standard that says a civil union is between <span class="bbcode-i">two</span> people, that’s different than saying the Islamic church isn’t allowed to marry people if it refuses to marry everyone the government says should be able to me married. In other words, any religion should be able to refuse to marry people if it doesn’t want to, but their should always be a governmental option for those that don’t want to get married in any sort of religious way, and that option should be nondiscriminatory.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/72</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 19:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-72</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This post may be rather convoluted, I’m trying to convey several ideas from several standpoints to multiple people and posts in this thread with multiple arguments, and that never ends good.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="8" data-topic="515039">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think that forcing Christians to accept gays into their marriage definition is wrong. It would be like trying to convince Jews to change their bar mitzvah tradition. I say this because of how marriage is done right now – with the Christian bible and ‘in the name of God’.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d rather not do this but I feel it needs to be done Davidi2, marriage is NOT a religious act nor is it a Christian one. The mere fact that you perceive marriage as a Christian ‘owned’ ceremony is more to do with the fact that Christianity is the dominant religion in your country, you know, you weren’t exactly claiming that marriage is an Islamic ceremony or that we should uphold Islamic ideas of marriage now were you? To further my point, marriage is first and foremost a legal term that offers legal rights, Christian churches do not define what legal rights marriage offers nor do they control who gets to marry, those are defined in the legal definition of marriage. The whole idea that we should respect a churches idea of who should be marriage is also bunk, I completely agree with Bowser, if a church wants to obtain <span class="bbcode-b">a licence to grant the legal contract of being married</span> then they should damn well grant the contract of marriage to anyone that legally qualifies, it is NOT the churches decision to decide who can and who cannot get married. <span class="bbcode-b">HOWEVER</span>, if a church wants to refuse the religious ceremony part of a marriage in their church, then that’s their prerogative, however distasteful and discriminatory it may be.</p>
<p>To further expand on why I think allowing churches to decide who cannot get married to be bunk: the analogy of a radical lesbian Feminism church was brought up, how about an Islamic church in America refusing to marry people who aren’t Muslims? What about a church of paedophilia who refused to marry a couple unless a member of the couple was a child? They sure as hell won’t be marrying anyone, but should they be allowed to <span class="bbcode-b">receive a licence to allow them to marry people</span>? They aren’t breaking any rules, on what basis will you refuse issuing the licence?</p>
<p>But I completely agree with you Davidi2 in the sense that marriage should not be de facto standard, civil unions are what they should be called and marriage should merely be an optional additional part of a civil union, marriage in the eyes of god and civil unions in the eyes of the law and all that good stuff.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="44" data-topic="515039">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think if a religion discriminates, you shouldn’t force them to change their religion to force your views on them. It’s setting a double standard if you get angry when religious people try to put their views into government and then you get surprised if they get upset when you try to force your views of what marriage is onto them. Like I pointed out in my previous post, marriage is held out here with their Bible and in the name of THEIR God</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Again I view this whole idea as complete bunk. Which Christian sect are we pandering to? Because many Christian sects recognise same-sex marriages, further more what about other religions? Should we pander to some sects of Islam which state we should allow men to have multiple wives? I know this is a bit of a strawman, but I’m making it to get my point across. If a church is being granted a licence to allow two individuals to enter a legally binding contract, they should not be at liberty to decide who can and cannot enter that contract, regardless if other means are available. The licence is given to allow people to get married, not to allow churches to uphold their bigotry. If a church doesn’t want to marry same-sex couples then they don’t get the licence, it changes nothing for the church, people can still have their religious ceremony there and the church can refuse to allow same-sex couples to have a religious ceremony, the only difference is that the church is no longer at liberty to be discriminatory in their decision to grant a legal god damn right.</p>
<p>But again, I completely agree that marriage shouldn’t be the legal term, but that’s a discussion for another topic.</p>
<p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:46, topic:515039”]I agree with David, except the reason homosexual couples are fighting for religious marriage is because they still follow that religion. They wish to be acknowledged by their religion, rather then have them be forced to marry them.</p>
<p>Creating a different ceremony in order to show that the two have been united just separates equal rights for them, so it wouldn’t solve the problem. As it is, homosexual couples can already have a ceremony where they’re joined as partners (which is recognised by law). That still isn’t enough for them, they want to be treated fairly.[/quote]</p>
<p>The general discussion is about America as can probably be clued from being even the slightest bit aware of American politics. Civil unions in America are NOT equivalent to marriage, as it stands, marriage is de facto standard for legal rights between couples. But I’m glad that you recognise that limiting same-sex couples, by law, into civil unions is at least discriminatory. I won’t bother going into a wall of text to explain why.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="64" data-topic="515039">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/amy_webb/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> amy_webb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People believe in something because they choose to, in today’s society. Not because they are being forced to do so by a previous generation, or because they had been forced many generations ago.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>In today’s society an a ‘liberal’ enough country, that’s an important distinction. If you were born into an oppressive country you WILL believe your parents religion or you’ll be punished, that is not a choice.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="66" data-topic="515039">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/amy_webb/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> amy_webb:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People do choose their religions, it is not forced upon them dispute the influences from relatives or loved ones. Once someone is old enough to think for themselves, they’re old enough to make their own decisions.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Again this is ONLY true if you are in a modern enough country if you will, the fact that you can choose what you want to believe is a relatively new phenomena. If you live in an oppressive country the choice of freedom of expression does not exist, historically people HAVE been killed for choosing a different religion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/71</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 18:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-71</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krackkid Krackkid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krackkid">@krackkid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>marc I don’t think you know what you’re talking about, if you’re not gay how can you tell people that they don’t understand how hard it is to be gay?</p>
<p>It isn’t any harder to be gay than it is to be straight. If gay people would stop being over dramatic over every little god damn fu cking thing. There wouldn’t be such a big god damn mother fu cking deal with the fact I can’t fuck another guy in the ass and get bullied, why must people always tease me just because I want to fu cking fu ck a fu cking gay ass mother fu cking dick sucking ass hole.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/70</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 18:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marc110 marc110]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marc110">@marc110</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:64, topic:515039”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=633289.msg4280599#msg4280599 date=1365504015]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>If people are happy together, why not?<br>
[/quote]Because religion. If marriage gets defined as two people of any sex, it contradicts the Bible and people get pissy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>religion AND the bible was made to control people before we had law and order (police)</p>
<p>to believe in god and all that shit of of them have a low IQ why else would anyone believe it</p>
<p>god is not real wake up and stop following such bullshit</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>People believe in religion because they want to have faith in something greater then life, also because of the family and their values. Who are you to say that anyone with religion has a low IQ? People have their own reasons for religion and they don’t need some ignorant kid telling them their beliefs are ‘bullshit’. Grow up, and respect people’s views rather then being completely rude and degrading.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t respect your religion (Read the Bible and you will know why). You are not a Christian because of your own belief, but because you live in a former British colony. Religion is based on culture and geography. People in 11th century Norway was forced into the new religion (Christianity), and the Norwegian king made it into the state religion. In the 16th century the Danish king forced us into the Lutheran faith and banned Catholic missionaries. People doesn’t believe in something because it is right, but because our ancestors have been forced into it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Do not tell me you do not respect my religion or my beliefs, i do not have any. I am not a religious being nor will i ever be, i do no believe in a greater power. This being said, that does not change my view or my opinion on what is being said. You cannot discourage a religion or a belief because you feel it is wrong or unnecessary. It is wrong and it goes against the freedom of speech and belief, which provides for many things. You want to tell me i believe in god because i am part of a country which was up until recent a colony of great Britain? Then you would be wrong. Australia has very few beliefs of religion, the children of the British who colonised Australia are scarce which proves that you cannot base it on that. Australia is a multicultural country, we are not all white beings descended from the British. No. We are from many parts of the world, i personally am part German. Does this mean i have to believe in whatever religion the Germans choose to follow? No, that is a false statement. Just because your country was forced to believe in a specific religion hundreds of years ago does no give you reason to disrespect religion today. This just suggests because your ancestors were forced and disliked religion, that you dislike it. Do not base your own experiences and thoughts on my own, we are not a like. People believe in something because they choose to, in today’s society. Not because they are being forced to do so by a previous generation, or because they had been forced many generations ago.[/quote]</p>
<p>you don’t understand you little bible basher , if your gay then you should be able to get married</p>
<p>straight people don’t understand how hard is it being gay and being told to be straight all the time does not help. Let them get married in  church god is meant to love everyone no matter what so why not let them?</p>
<p>and not i am not gay</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/69</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 17:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-69</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t see a post below this post, where is the post? Come on, stop hiding things!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/68</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 14:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-68</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I always love to read Niall’s wall of pwnage.</p>
<p>See below this post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/67</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 14:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-67</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="65" data-topic="515039">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Bowser jr:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>People doesn’t choose their religion. Most people pick their parents religion. Most people in Australia are Christians, and that is because they are of mostly European decent.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>People do choose their religions, it is not forced upon them dispute the influences from relatives or loved ones. Once someone is old enough to think for themselves, they’re old enough to make their own decisions. Religion can be believed from the beginning of someones life or they could come across it later in life, because everyone had their own reasons. True, the biggest religion in Australia may be Christianity but that doesn’t mean that compared to all of the other religions it is superior. If you take the percentage of other religions in Australia and then compare it to the percentage, you will find a majority of Australians believe in a different type of religion. This means Australia is not run by a christian faith, or by any faith. There is a freedom to belief here, and no one will ever be forced to believe in something they do not wish to.</p>
<p>Now, if you do not mind, i would suggest taking this thread back on topic rather then furthering it along the train of thought.</p>
<p>The possibility of gay marriage is increasing, it just will not be acknowledged by any religion who does not with it to be. This will lead to many homosexual couples being married be someone who is given authority by the government, or in a court.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/66</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 13:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-66</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>People doesn’t choose their religion, people pick their parents religion. Most people in Australia are Christians, and that is because they are of mostly European decent.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/65</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 13:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-65</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:63, topic:515039”][quote author=amy_webb link=topic=633289.msg4280458#msg4280458 date=1365464305]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>If people are happy together, why not?<br>
[/quote]Because religion. If marriage gets defined as two people of any sex, it contradicts the Bible and people get pissy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>religion AND the bible was made to control people before we had law and order (police)</p>
<p>to believe in god and all that shit of of them have a low IQ why else would anyone believe it</p>
<p>god is not real wake up and stop following such bullshit</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>People believe in religion because they want to have faith in something greater then life, also because of the family and their values. Who are you to say that anyone with religion has a low IQ? People have their own reasons for religion and they don’t need some ignorant kid telling them their beliefs are ‘bullshit’. Grow up, and respect people’s views rather then being completely rude and degrading.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t respect your religion (Read the Bible and you will know why). You are not a Christian because of your own belief, but because you live in a former British colony. Religion is based on culture and geography. People in 11th century Norway was forced into the new religion (Christianity), and the Norwegian king made it into the state religion. In the 16th century the Danish king forced us into the Lutheran faith and banned Catholic missionaries. People doesn’t believe in something because it is right, but because our ancestors have been forced into it.[/quote]<br>
Do not tell me you do not respect my religion or my beliefs, i do not have any. I am not a religious being nor will i ever be, i do no believe in a greater power. This being said, that does not change my view or my opinion on what is being said. You cannot discourage a religion or a belief because you feel it is wrong or unnecessary. It is wrong and it goes against the freedom of speech and belief, which provides for many things. You want to tell me i believe in god because i am part of a country which was up until recent a colony of great Britain? Then you would be wrong. Australia has very few beliefs of religion, the children of the British who colonised Australia are scarce which proves that you cannot base it on that. Australia is a multicultural country, we are not all white beings descended from the British. No. We are from many parts of the world, i personally am part German. Does this mean i have to believe in whatever religion the Germans choose to follow? No, that is a false statement. Just because your country was forced to believe in a specific religion hundreds of years ago does no give you reason to disrespect religion today. This just suggests because your ancestors were forced and disliked religion, that you dislike it. Do not base your own experiences and thoughts on my own, we are not a like. People believe in something because they choose to, in today’s society. Not because they are being forced to do so by a previous generation, or because they had been forced many generations ago.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/64</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 12:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-64</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:58, topic:515039”][quote author=marc110 link=topic=633289.msg4280437#msg4280437 date=1365462748]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>If people are happy together, why not?<br>
[/quote]Because religion. If marriage gets defined as two people of any sex, it contradicts the Bible and people get pissy.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>religion AND the bible was made to control people before we had law and order (police)</p>
<p>to believe in god and all that shit of of them have a low IQ why else would anyone believe it</p>
<p>god is not real wake up and stop following such bullshit</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>People believe in religion because they want to have faith in something greater then life, also because of the family and their values. Who are you to say that anyone with religion has a low IQ? People have their own reasons for religion and they don’t need some ignorant kid telling them their beliefs are ‘bullshit’. Grow up, and respect people’s views rather then being completely rude and degrading.[/quote]<br>
I don’t respect your religion (Read the Bible and you will know why). You are not a Christian because of your own belief, but because you live in a former British colony. Religion is based on culture and geography. People in 11th century Norway was forced into the new religion (Christianity), and the Norwegian king made it into the state religion. In the 16th century the Danish king forced us into the Lutheran faith and banned Catholic missionaries. People doesn’t believe in something because it is right, but because our ancestors have been forced into it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/63</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 10:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-63</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Gay Marriage</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marc110 marc110]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marc110">@marc110</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="61" data-topic="515039">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/shane/40/5941_1.png" class="avatar"> Shane:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Hell no simple as that Gay is wrong go to church…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>you wouldn’t say that if you were gay you dumbass</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039/62</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 01:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-515039-62</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gay-marriage/515039.rss">Gay Marriage</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
