<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311</link>
    <description>These people are a disgrace, they build off their own personal moral beliefs and preach to everyone that it is the word of God. God hates fags they say but I cannot help but point out the fact that they finger one piece script in the Bible and twist it into their liking, that&#39;s it, that is their whole reason for going against gay enablers, with just that reason they push the limits and it goes even further. An interview with 3 main members, Sheryl, Megan and whoever of the church took place where a minster and Christian in the salvation army states that the teaching in the new testament is all about God loving all irregardless of their sexuality. The 3 ladies blatantly call him a liar, that that is not what the word of God really is when it actually doesn&#39;t say anything in the new testament about God hating anyone at all! All this fuss is coming from a lady who said that the 9/11 was fantastic and the Virginia massacre was an act of God, since when was a crazed man with a gun an act of God? Not to mention this is coming from a lady who disowned her own son and believes he is going to hell because he disagreed with her beliefs, she saw that as an act against God. People like this makes me sick. If there is a God then he must be a wise man right? They say age and time makes a man wiser by each day, so how can a God with such age and wisdom judge a human by their sexuality alone? It&#39;s completely idiotic and now she has brain washed her own offspring by teaching her 3-5 year old daughter to hold signs at pickets saying &quot;God hates gays.&quot; Another thing I would like to point out is that a big thing they preach about is that people (by people I mean show hosts) promote homosexuality, from what I see they believe that there are only two sides, gay enablers and then people like them. They don&#39;t seem to realize the middle-man which is where the rest of the world stands with homosexuality, people do not promote any sexuality, they give us the free-will to decide what ever sexuality we want, gay, lesbian, straight or even transvestite even though it is frowned upon. I can go on and on about this but time is my currency and I&#39;m running low at the moment, so please do leave me a comment because I am curious on more point of views.

Surfing the web I came across this video, it really loosened me up after seeing all the bull shit this [i]cult[/i] preached.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OBA6qlHW8po</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 16:52:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“TabbyKiller, post:16, topic:528311”][quote author=eyeownyew link=topic=647061.msg4352039#msg4352039 date=1376821830]<br>
Actually I was raised as a devout Christian for the first fourteen years of my life. I still have well over a thousand bible verses memorized.</p>
<p>You are far too quick to jump to conclusions. I simply said that you are not looking at it from a third person point of view. This is in the intellectual debates forum, not ‘state your already made-up mind’ forum. If you’re going to be ignorant, please leave the thread, and this forum alone.</p>
<p>I stated that you are not looking at it from a third-person point of view as you <span class="bbcode-b">aren’t</span>, not because I disagree with you. A trait that shows intelligence is being able to play the Devil’s Advocate, which requires you can look at any situation from multiple points of view. You are looking at it from one point of view, and yes, <span class="bbcode-b">trolling</span> anyone who asks you to look at it differently.</p>
<p>You’re being ignorant. Take your negative attitude and inferior mind elsewhere if you cannot comprehend debates.<br>
[/quote]<br>
My negative attitude? You cant possibly be saying I have a negative attitude for not supporting them for what they have done and said. Believe me, I can see what point of view they are coming from but in a right mind no one should think about religion in that perspective, twisting morals in such a way to the point where you protest at a soldiers funeral just to make a living from publicity is wrong. I repeat these things because they stand strongly against what they believe. How can you even try to defend them? It doesn’t matter how much bible verses you’ve memorized, it doesn’t make you anymore christian than you think. I also notice you guys pity yourselves for being forced to learn the bible, grow up and move on because complaining about it only gives the effect that you hate it, so aren’t you old enough to decide on your own belief. I myself don’t share the same religion as anyone else because my view on God is my very own and not for anyone to share with, and if you don’t like it then I can say the same about your religion or their religion. This topic is some how derailing from the real point to who can share their own pity for themselves the most. Honestly, you might think I’m the close minded guy around here but you guys are so fixed having to read the bible to be religious it just makes me chuckle. But as you would say, look at it from a third person point of view.[/quote]<br>
That was directed towards Matty, not you… I suppose I should have addressed him</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 16:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“eyeownyew, post:14, topic:528311”]Actually I was raised as a devout Christian for the first fourteen years of my life. I still have well over a thousand bible verses memorized.</p>
<p>You are far too quick to jump to conclusions. I simply said that you are not looking at it from a third person point of view. This is in the intellectual debates forum, not ‘state your already made-up mind’ forum. If you’re going to be ignorant, please leave the thread, and this forum alone.</p>
<p>I stated that you are not looking at it from a third-person point of view as you <span class="bbcode-b">aren’t</span>, not because I disagree with you. A trait that shows intelligence is being able to play the Devil’s Advocate, which requires you can look at any situation from multiple points of view. You are looking at it from one point of view, and yes, <span class="bbcode-b">trolling</span> anyone who asks you to look at it differently.</p>
<p>You’re being ignorant. Take your negative attitude and inferior mind elsewhere if you cannot comprehend debates.[/quote]<br>
My negative attitude? You cant possibly be saying I have a negative attitude for not supporting them for what they have done and said. Believe me, I can see what point of view they are coming from but in a right mind no one should think about religion in that perspective, twisting morals in such a way to the point where you protest at a soldiers funeral just to make a living from publicity is wrong. I repeat these things because they stand strongly against what they believe. How can you even try to defend them? It doesn’t matter how much bible verses you’ve memorized, it doesn’t make you anymore christian than you think. I also notice you guys pity yourselves for being forced to learn the bible, grow up and move on because complaining about it only gives the effect that you hate it, so aren’t you old enough to decide on your own belief. I myself don’t share the same religion as anyone else because my view on God is my very own and not for anyone to share with, and if you don’t like it then I can say the same about your religion or their religion. This topic is some how derailing from the real point to who can share their own pity for themselves the most. Honestly, you might think I’m the close minded guy around here but you guys are so fixed having to read the bible to be religious it just makes me chuckle. But as you would say, look at it from a third person point of view.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xx matty xx, post:11, topic:528311”]You guys are vultures, complete ignorant sheep like the rest of this forum. The funny thing about this forum (and generally society as a whole) is that views that are considered far from those of the masses are ridiculed and mocked, or marked as “trolling” without proper and constructive discussion (Which might I add is a forum rule, ok?). I bet neither have you have read the Bible, just so you know I was forced to read the Bible as a kid because my parents forced me into Catholicism as soon as I could read like most I took it at face value and then re-evaluated my beliefs by reading and studying the Bible a few times, and achieving two A* qualifications in Biblical study.</p>
<p>Let me tell you this: You know <em>nothing</em> about the Bible, you’re another internet warrior who trolls through websites looking for out of context quotes without considering how the Bible functions as an entity. You are an exploiter and mis-seller of the greatest book man has ever had: the Bible.[/quote]<br>
How dare you try and pity yourself for being a Christian? That is exactly what religion is doing to homosexuals as a minority group, they are “ridiculed and mocked… without proper and constructive discussion”. It is pathetic that you attempted to defend yourself in such a way considering religious groups make up a majority of the population. Being forced to read the bible does not show free will, therefore how can you decide truly if you should follow a religion when being forced as a child. Your achievements on reading and studying the bible have no validation on this debate, it does not prove anything.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 11:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Actually I was raised as a devout Christian for the first fourteen years of my life. I still have well over a thousand bible verses memorized.</p>
<p>You are far too quick to jump to conclusions. I simply said that you are not looking at it from a third person point of view. This is in the intellectual debates forum, not ‘state your already made-up mind’ forum. If you’re going to be ignorant, please leave the thread, and this forum alone.</p>
<p>I stated that you are not looking at it from a third-person point of view as you <span class="bbcode-b">aren’t</span>, not because I disagree with you. A trait that shows intelligence is being able to play the Devil’s Advocate, which requires you can look at any situation from multiple points of view. You are looking at it from one point of view, and yes, <span class="bbcode-b">trolling</span> anyone who asks you to look at it differently.</p>
<p>You’re being ignorant. Take your negative attitude and inferior mind elsewhere if you cannot comprehend debates.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 10:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mikeyzzz Mikeyzzz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mikeyzzz">@Mikeyzzz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve seen a lot of photos of people forming walls to prevent these noobs from getting through.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 10:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“xx matty xx, post:11, topic:528311”][quote author=amy_webb link=topic=647061.msg4351858#msg4351858 date=1376787554]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>The westboro baptist church may have some pretty extreme views and get a lot of bad press, but honestly their fundamentals are grounded in reality. Homosexuality IS a sin against God and his children. If you lookup John 3.1 he said ‘Thou shalt only sleep with thy opposite sex, and not with another male’. All these people trying to make them look bad are simply children of the devil… and there’s not really much we can do about that. Furthermore, homosexuality is a lifestyle choice not something you are born with. It is not Gods work, it is their own choice and the work of the devil. If we choose to allow these people to pollute our planet in the name of liberalism then it is us as a community who will pay the price when it comes to our judgement.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe the man in this video used that passage and you’ve quoted it wrong, you should at least quote the correct version when presenting a point. Homosexuality is not a lifestyle choice, and those who say otherwise are ignorant. When would you decided to live with another man to be discriminated against? Why would you choose to be targeted (as a minority group) because you think being homosexual is just a fun way to live? Homosexuality is an attraction to the same sex, you can’t help it because your brain developed in such ways. Over the years, have you seen the people who have been attacked by heterosexual and religious groups? At one point, homosexuals were being taken into camps and forced to watch gay movies while inducing vomiting. Do you still think it is a choice? If it is a choice of the beholder, then why does free will not come into account? You can’t ignore other parts of the bible to specify an issue which you chose, that is bias. We need to accept everyone equally, rather then shun them. If your ‘judgement day’ comes, then so be it. We will all pay the price for accepting our neighbours with open arms, as well as their “lifestyle” choices.<br>
[/quote]<br>
You guys are vultures, complete ignorant sheep like the rest of this forum. The funny thing about this forum (and generally society as a whole) is that views that are considered far from those of the masses are ridiculed and mocked, or marked as “trolling” without proper and constructive discussion (Which might I add is a forum rule, ok?). I bet neither have you have read the Bible, just so you know I was forced to read the Bible as a kid because my parents forced me into Catholicism as soon as I could read like most I took it at face value and then re-evaluated my beliefs by reading and studying the Bible a few times, and achieving two A* qualifications in Biblical study.</p>
<p>Let me tell you this: You know <em>nothing</em> about the Bible, you’re another internet warrior who trolls through websites looking for out of context quotes without considering how the Bible functions as an entity. You are an exploiter and mis-seller of the greatest book man has ever had: the Bible.[/quote]<br>
We frown upon their views because they discriminate others because of their sexuality, how hard can it be to understand that! There is no room for a constructive discussion when it includes someone who says the 9/11 was for the good of man kind, or that the Virginia SCHOOL shooting was an act of God. Students, teachers, innocent people were murdered and they point the finger at the one thing we were taught to love and expect to still love him but with their beliefs. If anything I cannot respect their beliefs but in all honesty I’m sure they can keep that to themselves. Might I also point out that they protested outside of an American soldiers funeral for mere publicity for their church beliefs. They are the vultures, they are the animals feeding on anger. This goes further than just the bible, this goes to the point where they are not actually being religious Christians. “Their goal is to “express their 1st amendment rights” while hopefully angering someone to the point where he takes a swing at one of them.”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 08:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:10, topic:528311”][quote author=xx matty xx link=topic=647061.msg4351605#msg4351605 date=1376754038]<br>
The westboro baptist church may have some pretty extreme views and get a lot of bad press, but honestly their fundamentals are grounded in reality. Homosexuality IS a sin against God and his children. If you lookup John 3.1 he said ‘Thou shalt only sleep with thy opposite sex, and not with another male’. All these people trying to make them look bad are simply children of the devil… and there’s not really much we can do about that. Furthermore, homosexuality is a lifestyle choice not something you are born with. It is not Gods work, it is their own choice and the work of the devil. If we choose to allow these people to pollute our planet in the name of liberalism then it is us as a community who will pay the price when it comes to our judgement.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I believe the man in this video used that passage and you’ve quoted it wrong, you should at least quote the correct version when presenting a point. Homosexuality is not a lifestyle choice, and those who say otherwise are ignorant. When would you decided to live with another man to be discriminated against? Why would you choose to be targeted (as a minority group) because you think being homosexual is just a fun way to live? Homosexuality is an attraction to the same sex, you can’t help it because your brain developed in such ways. Over the years, have you seen the people who have been attacked by heterosexual and religious groups? At one point, homosexuals were being taken into camps and forced to watch gay movies while inducing vomiting. Do you still think it is a choice? If it is a choice of the beholder, then why does free will not come into account? You can’t ignore other parts of the bible to specify an issue which you chose, that is bias. We need to accept everyone equally, rather then shun them. If your ‘judgement day’ comes, then so be it. We will all pay the price for accepting our neighbours with open arms, as well as their “lifestyle” choices.[/quote]<br>
You guys are vultures, complete ignorant sheep like the rest of this forum. The funny thing about this forum (and generally society as a whole) is that views that are considered far from those of the masses are ridiculed and mocked, or marked as “trolling” without proper and constructive discussion (Which might I add is a forum rule, ok?). I bet neither have you have read the Bible, just so you know I was forced to read the Bible as a kid because my parents forced me into Catholicism as soon as I could read like most I took it at face value and then re-evaluated my beliefs by reading and studying the Bible a few times, and achieving two A* qualifications in Biblical study.</p>
<p>Let me tell you this: You know <em>nothing</em> about the Bible, you’re another internet warrior who trolls through websites looking for out of context quotes without considering how the Bible functions as an entity. You are an exploiter and mis-seller of the greatest book man has ever had: the Bible.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 08:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="528311">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 xx matty xx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The westboro baptist church may have some pretty extreme views and get a lot of bad press, but honestly their fundamentals are grounded in reality. Homosexuality IS a sin against God and his children. If you lookup John 3.1 he said ‘Thou shalt only sleep with thy opposite sex, and not with another male’. All these people trying to make them look bad are simply children of the devil… and there’s not really much we can do about that. Furthermore, homosexuality is a lifestyle choice not something you are born with. It is not Gods work, it is their own choice and the work of the devil. If we choose to allow these people to pollute our planet in the name of liberalism then it is us as a community who will pay the price when it comes to our judgement.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe the man in this video used that passage and you’ve quoted it wrong, you should at least quote the correct version when presenting a point. Homosexuality is not a lifestyle choice, and those who say otherwise are ignorant. When would you decided to live with another man to be discriminated against? Why would you choose to be targeted (as a minority group) because you think being homosexual is just a fun way to live? Homosexuality is an attraction to the same sex, you can’t help it because your brain developed in such ways. Over the years, have you seen the people who have been attacked by heterosexual and religious groups? At one point, homosexuals were being taken into camps and forced to watch gay movies while inducing vomiting. Do you still think it is a choice? If it is a choice of the beholder, then why does free will not come into account? You can’t ignore other parts of the bible to specify an issue which you chose, that is bias. We need to accept everyone equally, rather then shun them. If your ‘judgement day’ comes, then so be it. We will all pay the price for accepting our neighbours with open arms, as well as their “lifestyle” choices.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 00:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="528311">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 xx matty xx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The westboro baptist church may have some pretty extreme views and get a lot of bad press, but honestly their fundamentals are grounded in reality. Homosexuality IS a sin against God and his children. If you lookup John 3.1 he said ‘Thou shalt only sleep with thy opposite sex, and not with another male’. All these people trying to make them look bad are simply children of the devil… and there’s not really much we can do about that. Furthermore, homosexuality is a lifestyle choice not something you are born with. It is not Gods work, it is their own choice and the work of the devil. If we choose to allow these people to pollute our planet in the name of liberalism then it is us as a community who will pay the price when it comes to our judgement.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Except you’re entirely basing that statement off of religion. Try looking at it from a third-person point of view, please</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 20:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="7" data-topic="528311">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 xx matty xx:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The westboro baptist church may have some pretty extreme views and get a lot of bad press, but honestly their fundamentals are grounded in reality. Homosexuality IS a sin against God and his children. If you lookup John 3.1 he said ‘Thou shalt only sleep with thy opposite sex, and not with another male’. All these people trying to make them look bad are simply children of the devil… and there’s not really much we can do about that. Furthermore, homosexuality is a lifestyle choice not something you are born with. It is not Gods work, it is their own choice and the work of the devil. If we choose to allow these people to pollute our planet in the name of liberalism then it is us as a community who will pay the price when it comes to our judgement.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>But then again, God is forgiving right? And as I said above, a man with Gods wisdom would not judge someone by their preferred sexuality. To do so he’d have to be a devil himself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 19:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The westboro baptist church may have some pretty extreme views and get a lot of bad press, but honestly their fundamentals are grounded in reality. Homosexuality IS a sin against God and his children. If you lookup John 3.1 he said ‘Thou shalt only sleep with thy opposite sex, and not with another male’. All these people trying to make them look bad are simply children of the devil… and there’s not really much we can do about that. Furthermore, homosexuality is a lifestyle choice not something you are born with. It is not Gods work, it is their own choice and the work of the devil. If we choose to allow these people to pollute our planet in the name of liberalism then it is us as a community who will pay the price when it comes to our judgement.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It is interesting how they choose sections of the bible which they put forward rather then refer to the bible as a whole text. I feel that religion is going in the same direction as selective media, when it comes to various topics. They choose what they want to be heard in order to depict something that otherwise wouldn’t be there had they not selected specific areas.</p>
<p>There isn’t much you can do about people like this, as they have a set mind frame. I think the only other argument against this is free will, as that was never explored. Apparently God gave everyone the right to free will, but disallowing us from areas would not be considered free. To that i say, contradiction. These people should be ignored if not agreed with, that much is simple. To us, they’re cultists but to them, they’ve seen the light and they understand. It is the best we can do by removing ourselves away from such people, if we do not agree.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 15:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If these people could be punished then they would but they cant because freedom of speech. I don’t know if the same rule applies with mitb’s standards but I’m sure he does support homosexuality. As for the topic being in this section, we’ll leave it for the mods to decide.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 04:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think we’d have reason to ban anyone that has an opposing view from the forums simply for incompetence</p>
<p>Really shouldn’t be in intellectual debates though</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 04:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My initial thought was to put it into the general discussion area but then I wondered if anyone here had any input or even a point of view from the opposing side of the church.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 03:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxx123xxx xxx123xxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxx123xxx">@xxx123xxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This sounds like a rant</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Westboro Baptist Church</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>These people are a disgrace, they build off their own personal moral beliefs and preach to everyone that it is the word of God. God hates fags they say but I cannot help but point out the fact that they finger one piece script in the Bible and twist it into their liking, that’s it, that is their whole reason for going against gay enablers, with just that reason they push the limits and it goes even further. An interview with 3 main members, Sheryl, Megan and whoever of the church took place where a minster and Christian in the salvation army states that the teaching in the new testament is all about God loving all irregardless of their sexuality. The 3 ladies blatantly call him a liar, that that is not what the word of God really is when it actually doesn’t say anything in the new testament about God hating anyone at all! All this fuss is coming from a lady who said that the 9/11 was fantastic and the Virginia massacre was an act of God, since when was a crazed man with a gun an act of God? Not to mention this is coming from a lady who disowned her own son and believes he is going to hell because he disagreed with her beliefs, she saw that as an act against God. People like this makes me sick. If there is a God then he must be a wise man right? They say age and time makes a man wiser by each day, so how can a God with such age and wisdom judge a human by their sexuality alone? It’s completely idiotic and now she has brain washed her own offspring by teaching her 3-5 year old daughter to hold signs at pickets saying “God hates gays.” Another thing I would like to point out is that a big thing they preach about is that people (by people I mean show hosts) promote homosexuality, from what I see they believe that there are only two sides, gay enablers and then people like them. They don’t seem to realize the middle-man which is where the rest of the world stands with homosexuality, people do not promote any sexuality, they give us the free-will to decide what ever sexuality we want, gay, lesbian, straight or even transvestite even though it is frowned upon. I can go on and on about this but time is my currency and I’m running low at the moment, so please do leave me a comment because I am curious on more point of views.</p>
<p>Surfing the web I came across this video, it really loosened me up after seeing all the bull shit this <span class="bbcode-i">cult</span> preached.<br>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="OBA6qlHW8po" data-youtube-title="OFFICIAL Video: Russell Brand Interviews Westboro Baptist Church" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-528311-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/westboro-baptist-church/528311.rss">Westboro Baptist Church</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
