<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Howto] Tracking changes to your projects!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/howto-tracking-changes-to-your-projects/413178</link>
    <description>Now, as a forward, I am absolutely [i]terrible[/i] at doing this. :P But as a means to improve both my productivity and yours, I decided to write this up anyway. If you have any additions or changes, please post them. It needs the influence of those whom are more successful at this than me. :)

[b]What is meant by &#39;tracking changes?&#39;[/b]
When you create a project (especially a private one!), it is extremely easy to get into the habit of writing the project, testing it, changing bits of code, testing it again, and repeating the process. You want to make an addition, or remove a bug, so you go in and change the little things in maybe 5-30 minutes, and retest it (or maybe even redeploy it/push it to some repository). The negative in not having some sort of log of what has changed leads to you unable to remember what you did in previous versions (especially if you wish to revert something), other developers on the team being unaware of changes, and the people using your application being unable to know what has changed.

[b]First of all, what does &quot;change&quot; mean?[/b]
Webster defines change as [i]&quot;to make the form, nature, content, future course, etc., of (something) different from what it is or from what it would be if left alone&quot;[/i], which is a rather verbose way of simply saying &quot;altering the state of something.&quot; Basically, if you must modify your application in some way that involves it not being the same as it was  before you made the modifications, it has changed. This is very basic.

In applications, however, we can&#39;t just say &quot;record everything you change.&quot; That is a ridiculous request. Rather, we are going to organize certain changes into categories and specify which ones are import changes, which ones are somewhat important, and which ones are unimportant. Let&#39;s think for a bit which categories of changes could exist. Well most abstractly, we could categories changes as corrective, preventative, additive, or subtractive. This makes sense, right? We either need to fix something we messed up, add code to prevent something that [i]could[/i] mess up, add a new feature, or remove an unneeded feature (the last one we&#39;ll talk about more indepth below, check the deprecation section).

[u]Corrective Changes (problems in the code)[/u]
Basically, if you have a problem in your code, you have a bug. A bug is most simply a logical error when you created the code, leading to unintended or unexpected behavior in your application. A block of code may never be executed, may be executed infinitely, not enough, too much, may not perform the correct operation, may crash the application, and the list goes on. I consider bugs to be mandatory to add to the change log, but be a small factor in the version of the application.

[u]Preventative Changes (avoiding bugs!)[/u]
These are changes you typically make when you are doing one of the other three categories, and when you have unexpected insight into something that could possibly go wrong. I would consider logging this as optional, at best. I personally find them unimportant, but if you are making a rather large change to a very important system in your application, I definitely recommend logging it. If you do wish to change the version according to preventative changes, I would consider it to be the same priority level as a bug, or maybe a level lower.

[u]Additive/Subtractive Changes[/u]

[ul][li]Algorithms/Structural - the lowest level and thus, least important of any change. This could range from simple optimizations to adding more functionality to an algorithm. Definitely not worth logging.[/li]
[li]Features/GUI - this one is typically unimportant for developers, but quite important to users! I would consider feature changes to be one of the higher priorities, and definitely worth logging.[/li]
[li]Build Candidates - if your application is being deployed or changed to/from a major candidate (such as a release candidate, alpha/beta/delta versions, or whatever other scheme you have), I consider it essential to log such candidate changes, and at highest priority.[/li][/ul]


[b]The Math (keeping track of your application&#39;s version)[/b]
Evidently, this comes down to style and preference. Some people prefer not even using version numbers, some people prefer using greek letters (alpha, beta, gamma, delta, etc). Some people even prefer using a complex system of multi-decimal numbers (I believe the windows OS has something like 20 different version categories?) Either way, I will propose a system you can choose to use. Whether you do or not barely affects me, but you should certainly have a system for your application.

First of all, I prefer to have a [b]major[/b] and [b]minor[/b] version. Basically, a major version is the number that would follow the name of the application if you were to market it. &quot;RuneScape 2&quot; &quot;iPad [1]&quot; &quot;iPhone 5&quot; etc. If it is version one or less, don&#39;t bother appending the number. Now, a minor version is the number which notifies developers of the progress the application has undergone. I would personally increment this variable for any feature or systematic change you make. Bugs and preventative changes should not go in this number, because this number is a higher priority, and therefore far more important.

The next part of the version is optional. You can add a second minor variable specifically for tracking very minute changes, such as fixing bugs. I personally would not bother to increment this number, because it would be tracked via a repository anyway (which I&#39;ll explain in another section). But if you aren&#39;t using SVN/CVS/GIT, then you can go ahead and add this if it floats your boat! :)

I would then say a suffix is in order. I prefer using the greek letters of Alpha and Beta for determining the status of the application. After Beta I would consider the application to be a release candidate, meaning it is open to the public for usage. Any major version number under 0 is not a release candidate, and any above 0 is one. I consider Alpha to be the status of the application specifically to developers, meaning only the people involved in making the application can test it. Beta would represent when you profile the application&#39;s use to a a controlled group of testers, whom spend their energies trying to find bugs the developers may have missed, provide feedback on the features, content, visual appearance, performance, etc. Some people here may choose to use additional greek letters, or maybe even hebrew or their own choices, for more stages. Some may choose to use release candidates to represent public versions, meaning an application could have a major version of 2, but have 5 release candidates (such as SMF!) You could choose to use metals/colors such as gold, silver, and platinum to describe the progress of development. Just be creative. :P

Anyway, this is the final format I would use: [i]major[/i] [b].[/b] [i]minor[/i] [i]Alpha/Beta/RC (Release Candidate)[/i] [i]build[/i]

For example, the first version of my application may be 0.15 build 2 ALPHA, which means it is Alpha (though it could be Beta, if it was at that stage in development progress), has a major version of 0, has had 15 changes, and has had 2 different builds deployed. Another may be 2.768 build 259, meaning it is a release candidate, version 2, has 768 minor changes, and has had 259 deployed builds. The list goes on, and on. :)

[hr]

I&#39;ll add more to this later. Feedback is highly encouraged!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 17:12:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/howto-tracking-changes-to-your-projects/413178.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Howto] Tracking changes to your projects!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-i">reserved…</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/howto-tracking-changes-to-your-projects/413178/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/howto-tracking-changes-to-your-projects/413178/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413178-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/howto-tracking-changes-to-your-projects/413178.rss">[Howto] Tracking changes to your projects!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Howto] Tracking changes to your projects!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Now, as a forward, I am absolutely <span class="bbcode-i">terrible</span> at doing this. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> But as a means to improve both my productivity and yours, I decided to write this up anyway. If you have any additions or changes, please post them. It needs the influence of those whom are more successful at this than me. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What is meant by ‘tracking changes?’</span><br>
When you create a project (especially a private one!), it is extremely easy to get into the habit of writing the project, testing it, changing bits of code, testing it again, and repeating the process. You want to make an addition, or remove a bug, so you go in and change the little things in maybe 5-30 minutes, and retest it (or maybe even redeploy it/push it to some repository). The negative in not having some sort of log of what has changed leads to you unable to remember what you did in previous versions (especially if you wish to revert something), other developers on the team being unaware of changes, and the people using your application being unable to know what has changed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">First of all, what does “change” mean?</span><br>
Webster defines change as <span class="bbcode-i">“to make the form, nature, content, future course, etc., of (something) different from what it is or from what it would be if left alone”</span>, which is a rather verbose way of simply saying “altering the state of something.” Basically, if you must modify your application in some way that involves it not being the same as it was  before you made the modifications, it has changed. This is very basic.</p>
<p>In applications, however, we can’t just say “record everything you change.” That is a ridiculous request. Rather, we are going to organize certain changes into categories and specify which ones are import changes, which ones are somewhat important, and which ones are unimportant. Let’s think for a bit which categories of changes could exist. Well most abstractly, we could categories changes as corrective, preventative, additive, or subtractive. This makes sense, right? We either need to fix something we messed up, add code to prevent something that <span class="bbcode-i">could</span> mess up, add a new feature, or remove an unneeded feature (the last one we’ll talk about more indepth below, check the deprecation section).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Corrective Changes (problems in the code)</span><br>
Basically, if you have a problem in your code, you have a bug. A bug is most simply a logical error when you created the code, leading to unintended or unexpected behavior in your application. A block of code may never be executed, may be executed infinitely, not enough, too much, may not perform the correct operation, may crash the application, and the list goes on. I consider bugs to be mandatory to add to the change log, but be a small factor in the version of the application.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Preventative Changes (avoiding bugs!)</span><br>
These are changes you typically make when you are doing one of the other three categories, and when you have unexpected insight into something that could possibly go wrong. I would consider logging this as optional, at best. I personally find them unimportant, but if you are making a rather large change to a very important system in your application, I definitely recommend logging it. If you do wish to change the version according to preventative changes, I would consider it to be the same priority level as a bug, or maybe a level lower.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Additive/Subtractive Changes</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]Algorithms/Structural - the lowest level and thus, least important of any change. This could range from simple optimizations to adding more functionality to an algorithm. Definitely not worth logging.[/li]<br>
[li]Features/GUI - this one is typically unimportant for developers, but quite important to users! I would consider feature changes to be one of the higher priorities, and definitely worth logging.[/li]<br>
[li]Build Candidates - if your application is being deployed or changed to/from a major candidate (such as a release candidate, alpha/beta/delta versions, or whatever other scheme you have), I consider it essential to log such candidate changes, and at highest priority.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Math (keeping track of your application’s version)</span><br>
Evidently, this comes down to style and preference. Some people prefer not even using version numbers, some people prefer using greek letters (alpha, beta, gamma, delta, etc). Some people even prefer using a complex system of multi-decimal numbers (I believe the windows OS has something like 20 different version categories?) Either way, I will propose a system you can choose to use. Whether you do or not barely affects me, but you should certainly have a system for your application.</p>
<p>First of all, I prefer to have a <span class="bbcode-b">major</span> and <span class="bbcode-b">minor</span> version. Basically, a major version is the number that would follow the name of the application if you were to market it. “RuneScape 2” “iPad [1]” “iPhone 5” etc. If it is version one or less, don’t bother appending the number. Now, a minor version is the number which notifies developers of the progress the application has undergone. I would personally increment this variable for any feature or systematic change you make. Bugs and preventative changes should not go in this number, because this number is a higher priority, and therefore far more important.</p>
<p>The next part of the version is optional. You can add a second minor variable specifically for tracking very minute changes, such as fixing bugs. I personally would not bother to increment this number, because it would be tracked via a repository anyway (which I’ll explain in another section). But if you aren’t using SVN/CVS/GIT, then you can go ahead and add this if it floats your boat! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I would then say a suffix is in order. I prefer using the greek letters of Alpha and Beta for determining the status of the application. After Beta I would consider the application to be a release candidate, meaning it is open to the public for usage. Any major version number under 0 is not a release candidate, and any above 0 is one. I consider Alpha to be the status of the application specifically to developers, meaning only the people involved in making the application can test it. Beta would represent when you profile the application’s use to a a controlled group of testers, whom spend their energies trying to find bugs the developers may have missed, provide feedback on the features, content, visual appearance, performance, etc. Some people here may choose to use additional greek letters, or maybe even hebrew or their own choices, for more stages. Some may choose to use release candidates to represent public versions, meaning an application could have a major version of 2, but have 5 release candidates (such as SMF!) You could choose to use metals/colors such as gold, silver, and platinum to describe the progress of development. Just be creative. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Anyway, this is the final format I would use: <span class="bbcode-i">major</span> <span class="bbcode-b">.</span> <span class="bbcode-i">minor</span> <span class="bbcode-i">Alpha/Beta/RC (Release Candidate)</span> <span class="bbcode-i">build</span></p>
<p>For example, the first version of my application may be 0.15 build 2 ALPHA, which means it is Alpha (though it could be Beta, if it was at that stage in development progress), has a major version of 0, has had 15 changes, and has had 2 different builds deployed. Another may be 2.768 build 259, meaning it is a release candidate, version 2, has 768 minor changes, and has had 259 deployed builds. The list goes on, and on. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>I’ll add more to this later. Feedback is highly encouraged!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/howto-tracking-changes-to-your-projects/413178/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/howto-tracking-changes-to-your-projects/413178/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 17:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-413178-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/howto-tracking-changes-to-your-projects/413178.rss">[Howto] Tracking changes to your projects!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
