<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319</link>
    <description>Hello there moparscape.

I know I&#39;ve posted quite a few PHP tutorials over the past day since this board has been brought in, but I just want to keep it busy and for people to get to use PHP more. I consider myself pretty good with PHP, however I do sometimes leave loopholes and such and even leave it open to SQL Injection, so if you ever see me posting it with these problems don&#39;t hesitate to tell me. My code is sometimes scruffy and scrappy, but it does get the job done.

Without further ado, here is my PHP crash course. 

With me posting this, I assume you have PHP set up and you have it ready to start creating scripts, I will not run through this, there are countless guides everywhere. Even look on our mother site [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board=39.00]moparisthebest, web design section.[/url]

[b]Part 1, initiating php.[/b]
The first thing you want to learn to do when learning PHP is how to initiate PHP. This tells your browser that it is relaying PHP, not HTML. You do this by using the following tags;
[code]
&lt;?php //starts  php
//your code in here
?&gt;//ends php[/code]

You will probably see me posting them like this though;
[code]
&lt;? //starts php
//your code in here
?&gt;//ends php[/code]

This does the very same job, but it&#39;s shorter and I think it looks tidier, but that&#39;s just me. You can use either and they&#39;ll work exactly the same. Just whenever you&#39;re programming php, you must use these tags and include all of the PHP coding between these tags.

[b]Part 2, echoing data.[/b]
So, the second part of learning PHP is how to actually display writing on a page. You do this by using the echo() function. This can also be done using the print() function, however I remember reading somewhere that echo() was faster than print() so I always use echo(). Lets get to our first script!
[code]
&lt;?
echo &quot;Hello there moparscape!&quot;;
?&gt;
[/code]

If you put this inside a .php file and relay it through a server then you&#39;ll find your page will now just display the words &quot;Hello there moparscape&quot;.

What this code is is that you have your opening &lt;? ?&gt; tags, you then have your echo() function, your message between the quotation marks, and then finally, one of the most important parts of PHP, the semicolon at the end of the line. 
[b]ALWAYS PUT A SEMI COLON AT THE END OF THE LINE UNLESS INSTRUCTED NOT TO.[/b]

Echoing a variable, or several.
[code]
&lt;?
$testString = &quot;Hello MoparScape!&quot;;
echo $testString;
?&gt;
[/code]

Notice here how you do not use any kind of quotation marks around the variable when echoing.

[code]
&lt;?
$testString = &quot;Hello &quot;;
$testString2 = &quot;MoparScape!&quot;;
echo $testString.$testString2;
?&gt;
[/code]

This here is what you would do if you wanted to echo two variables beside each other in a piece of code, you join them by a period &quot;.&quot; this is used as a joining factor throughout PHP, but more on that later.

Be careful when echoing quotation marks, for example, through HTML tags.
[code]
&lt;?
echo &quot;&lt;font color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;I love mopar!&lt;/font&gt;&quot;;  
?&gt;
[/code]

The above code won&#39;t work because of the multiple quotation marks in the echo statement.

[code]
echo &quot;&lt;font color=\&quot;red\&quot;&gt;I love mopar!&lt;/font&gt;&quot;;  

echo &quot;&lt;font color=&#39;red&#39;&gt;I love mopar!&lt;/font&gt;&quot;;  
[/code]

The above two codes will however, work. The first because of the backward slashes showing they&#39;re not the end to the echo statement. The second because we used apostrophe&#39;s instead of quotation marks.

Echoing variables and text strings:
[code]&lt;?
$my_string = &quot;Hello Ruby.  My name is: &quot;;
echo &quot;$my_string Cammy &lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
echo &quot;Hi, I&#39;m Ruby.  Who are you?&lt;br /&gt;&quot;; 
echo &quot;$my_string Cammy&quot;;
?&gt;[/code]

Test this code out, it&#39;s rather fun to play around with these as they can be slightly confusing at first.

Okay, that&#39;s our first section done on Echoing. We also covered some variables inside that there, however it shouldn&#39;t be too confusing as we move onto Variables right now.

[b]Part 3, Variables.[/b]

A variable is a means of storing a value, such as text string &quot;Hello World!&quot; or the integer value 4. A variable can then be reused throughout your code, instead of having to type out the actual value over and over again. In PHP you define a variable with the following form:
$variableName = Value;
If you forget that dollar sign at the beginning, it will not work. This is a common mistake for new PHP programmers!
Note: Also, variable names are case-sensitive, so use the exact same capitalization when using a variable. The variables $aNumber and $Anumber are different variables in PHP&#39;s eyes.

Okay, so now you know the basics, lets use some more variables!

We&#39;ll start off with this code;
[code]
&lt;?
$text = &quot;Hello MoparScape!&quot;;
$aNumber = 4;
$anotherNumber = 8;
?&gt;
[/code]
Here we have stored 3 variables, one text string and two numerical values. Note how the text must be wrapped in quotation marks, but the numerical values don&#39;t.
PHP also doesn&#39;t need the variables to be declared before being initialized.

Naming Conventions.

PHP variables must start with a letter or underscore &quot;_&quot;.
PHP variables may only be comprised of alpha-numeric characters and underscores. a-z, A-Z, 0-9, or _ .
Variables with more than one word should be distinguished with capitalization. $testVariable

You have already used variables  in the echoing part, but we&#39;ll do a small exercise here.

[code]
&lt;?
$myVar = &quot;Rubys tutorial &quot;;
$secondVar = &quot;is &quot;;
$thirdVar = 1337;

//echo all three together

echo $myVar.$secondVar.$thirdVar;
?&gt;
[/code]

Remember that? Mess around with it and get used to variables, these are [b]essential[/b] in any programming language.

You can also do mathematics inside variables and using variables. To times a number, use the asterisk - &quot;*&quot;, to subtract, use &quot;-&quot;, to add use &quot;+&quot; and to divide use &quot;/&quot;.

Use these for a while too, just get used to them.

[b]Part 4, Functions[/b]
A function is just a name we give to a block of code that can be executed whenever we need it. This might not seem like that big of an idea, but believe me, when you understand and use functions you will be able to save a ton of time and write code that is much more readable! Functions are generally thought too hard for beginners to use, but if you stick with them and persevere then you&#39;ll be 100% fine and it&#39;ll bring you on a lot through programming.

So, lets create our first function!

[code]
&lt;?
function whatIsMoparscape() {
echo &quot;The best community ever!&quot;;
}
?&gt;
[/code]

This may seem just a question and answer, but you can do a lot with functions. For example;

[code]
&lt;?
function whatIsMoparscape() {
echo &quot;The best community ever!&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
}
echo &quot;Welcome to MoparScape!&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
whatIsMoparscape();
echo &quot;We love to see new users coming in!&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
echo &quot;enjoy your stay, and remember we are...&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
whatIsMoparscape();
?&gt;
[/code]
So this is more or less what you can use a function for, but the list is endless, there is hundreds of reasons to use functions.

You may realise that the above function is more or less an oversized variable.  Here&#39;s a much better use for functions;
[code]
&lt;?
function myFunction($firstName, $lastName){
    echo &quot;Hello there &quot;. $firstName .&quot; &quot;. $lastName .&quot;!&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
}
myFunction(&quot;Mod&quot;, &quot;Cammy&quot;);
myFunction(&quot;Mod&quot;, &quot;Nick&quot;);
myFunction(&quot;Mod&quot;, &quot;Omer&quot;);
myFunction(&quot;Mod&quot;, &quot;Tyler&quot;);
myFunction(&quot;Mod&quot;, &quot;Justin&quot;);
myFunction(&quot;Mod&quot;, &quot;Whackatre&quot;);
?&gt;
[/code]

This is a more useful function, just adapt it to your needs.

Here&#39;s a few protips for when you&#39;re using php functions;
- Always start your function with the keyword function
- Remember that your function&#39;s code must be between the &quot;{&quot; and the &quot;}&quot;
- When you are using your function, be sure you spell the function name correctly
- Don&#39;t give up!

Our last and final function is for php functions returning values.
[code]
&lt;?
function mySum($numX, $numY){
    $total = $numX * $numY;
    return $total; 
}
$myNumber = 0;
echo &quot;Before the function, myNumber = &quot;. $myNumber .&quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
$myNumber = mySum(3, 4);
echo &quot;After the function, myNumber = &quot; . $myNumber .&quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
?&gt;
[/code]

What this function does is holds a value of 0 before the function, after executing the function it then gains the value of the two numbers you had. You can also add in more variables such as $numZ and what not.

Okay, so that wraps up functions, if you don&#39;t get it, don&#39;t worry. Keep at it!

[b]Part 5, switch statements.[/b]
The way the Switch statement works is it takes a single variable as input and then checks it against all the different cases you set up for that switch statement. Instead of having to check that variable one at a time, as it goes through a bunch of If Statements, the Switch statement only has to check one time.

Here&#39;s an example of a switch statement;
[code]
&lt;?
$revision = &quot;317&quot;;
echo &quot;Your current revision is: &lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
switch ($revision){
	case &quot;317&quot;:
		echo &quot;317, the best there ever was!&quot;;
		break;
	case &quot;474&quot;:
		echo &quot;474, alright, but starting to get worse.&quot;;
		break;	
	case &quot;508&quot;:
		echo &quot;508, the peak of runescape, before it got horrible.&quot;;
		break;	
	case &quot;525&quot;:
		echo &quot;525, the begin of the demise of runescape&quot;;
		break;
	case &quot;525+&quot;:
		echo &quot;Over 525, ew.&quot;;
		break;	
}
?&gt;
[/code]

After doing this, you can then put the default value in. If you look at my other tutorial on switch statements for pages in this board, you&#39;ll realise I use the default value there. This is more or less what shows if the variable is empty.

You&#39;d use it like this;
[code]
&lt;?
$revision = &quot;317&quot;;
echo &quot;Your current revision is: &lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
switch ($revision){
	case &quot;317&quot;:
		echo &quot;317, the best there ever was!&quot;;
		break;
	case &quot;474&quot;:
		echo &quot;474, alright, but starting to get worse.&quot;;
		break;	
	case &quot;508&quot;:
		echo &quot;508, the peak of runescape, before it got horrible.&quot;;
		break;	
	case &quot;525&quot;:
		echo &quot;525, the begin of the demise of runescape&quot;;
		break;
	case &quot;525+&quot;:
		echo &quot;Over 525, ew.&quot;;
		break;	
              default:
                echo &quot;Would you like to find out what revision your server is?&quot;;
                break;
}
?&gt;
[/code]

That&#39;s more or less switch statements, they&#39;re a lot easier than people think and can be used for a lot of things.

[b]Part 6, if/ifelse statements[/b]
The if statement is necessary for most programming, thus it is important in PHP. Imagine that on January 1st you want to print out &quot;Happy New Year!&quot; at the top of your personal web page. With the use of PHP if statements you could have this process automated, months in advance, occuring every year on January 1st.

[code]
&lt;?
$yourName = &quot;Ruby&quot;;

if ( $yourName == &quot;Ruby&quot; ) {
	echo &quot;Your name is Ruby!&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
} else {
       echo &quot;Your name is not Ruby!&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
}
echo &quot;Welcome to MoparScape!&quot;;

?&gt;
[/code]

This is just a general if else statement, if you wish to create an if statement, remove the else. Although, it works a tonne better with else in there, it&#39;s more professional in my opinion.

There isn&#39;t really much to cover on this topic, you can add in as many else&#39;s as you need with certain parameters on them.

[b]Part 7, Cookies in PHP[/b]
This is where I cover cookies and how you can use them, this type of cookie is a small text document that sits on your hard-drive and is accessed by the website that created them. These are used all the time, you probably have hundreds stored.
[code]
&lt;?
  $visits = $_COOKIE[&#39;moparscape&#39;] + 1
    setcookie(&quot;moparscape&quot;, $visits, time()+3600*24*365, &quot;/&quot;, &quot;www.moparisthebest.com&quot;, 0);
    if($visits &gt; 1) {      
     echo &quot;You have visited moparscape &lt;? $visits ?&gt; times.&quot;;      
  } else {
      echo &quot;Welcome to moparscape, may you have many more pleasant visits.&quot;;
         }
?&gt;
[/code]

This right here is almost the exact cookie I use on Xythax. What this does is that it stores the cookie on your hard drive with the setcookie() function and everytime I revisit a url with the name xythax.org in it, it adds 1 to the $visits variable and then you display it to someone who has more than 1 visit.

This code uses everything from the setcookie() function, an if/else statement, mathematics in php and variables. This just shows you that a script this small uses all of that.

Anyway MoparScape, I&#39;ve just spent the past like 2 and a half hours writing this guide for you, I hope you enjoy it and use it.

Kind Regards,
Ruby.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 11:43:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What are you even doing with your life you mess of a person.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 11:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the supportive comments guys.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 20:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uncalled Uncalled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uncalled">@Uncalled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>pretty good, keep it up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 20:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks mate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pink_Phat Pink Phat]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pink_phat">@Pink_Phat</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>a very detailed guide Ruby, good job.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 12:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Justin, I believe it’s easier to tell people to just put a semi-colon at the end of the line. I know it’s not right, but it’s easier to understand for beginners I think, however, I’ll change it.</p>
<p>And I’m not wrong on how variables must start with a letter or an underscore, that’s 100% accurate.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/nothing">@Nothing</a>- PHP coding conventions state that it’s okay to do either, but I think that myVariable looks better than my_variable. But you can do either.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 12:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I see both, but more of the latter.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 03:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nothing1 -Nothing]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nothing1">@Nothing1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Usually at all PHP pages I see conventions as ‘variable_name’ and not ‘variableName’.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 03:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>ALWAYS PUT A SEMI COLON AT THE END OF THE LINE UNLESS INSTRUCTED NOT TO.</blockquote>
<p>Wrong! You should be more clear when explaining this; a semi colon is only used at the end of a statement. You should explain the difference between statements and blocks/conditional statements.</p>
<blockquote>PHP variables must start with a letter or underscore "_".</blockquote>
<p>Wrong again! In <span class="bbcode-b">most</span> PHP standard coding conventions, variable names follow Java’s camelCase.</p>
<p>By the way, you should format your code.</p>
<p>Aside from that, good job.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks, Nick.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 20:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxxtilllyxxx xxxtilllyxxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxxtilllyxxx">@xxxtilllyxxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice tutorial bro, this will help people who are new.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello there moparscape.</p>
<p>I know I’ve posted quite a few PHP tutorials over the past day since this board has been brought in, but I just want to keep it busy and for people to get to use PHP more. I consider myself pretty good with PHP, however I do sometimes leave loopholes and such and even leave it open to SQL Injection, so if you ever see me posting it with these problems don’t hesitate to tell me. My code is sometimes scruffy and scrappy, but it does get the job done.</p>
<p>Without further ado, here is my PHP crash course.</p>
<p>With me posting this, I assume you have PHP set up and you have it ready to start creating scripts, I will not run through this, there are countless guides everywhere. Even look on our mother site <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board=39.00" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest, web design section.</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 1, initiating php.</span><br>
The first thing you want to learn to do when learning PHP is how to initiate PHP. This tells your browser that it is relaying PHP, not HTML. You do this by using the following tags;</p>
<p>[code]</p>
&lt;?php //starts  php
//your code in here
?&gt;//ends php[/code]
<p>You will probably see me posting them like this though;</p>
<p>[code]</p>
&lt;? //starts php
//your code in here
?&gt;//ends php[/code]
<p>This does the very same job, but it’s shorter and I think it looks tidier, but that’s just me. You can use either and they’ll work exactly the same. Just whenever you’re programming php, you must use these tags and include all of the PHP coding between these tags.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 2, echoing data.</span><br>
So, the second part of learning PHP is how to actually display writing on a page. You do this by using the echo() function. This can also be done using the print() function, however I remember reading somewhere that echo() was faster than print() so I always use echo(). Lets get to our first script!</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
echo "Hello there moparscape!";
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>If you put this inside a .php file and relay it through a server then you’ll find your page will now just display the words “Hello there moparscape”.</p>
<p>What this code is is that you have your opening &lt;? ?&gt; tags, you then have your echo() function, your message between the quotation marks, and then finally, one of the most important parts of PHP, the semicolon at the end of the line.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">ALWAYS PUT A SEMI COLON AT THE END OF THE LINE UNLESS INSTRUCTED NOT TO.</span></p>
<p>Echoing a variable, or several.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
$testString = "Hello MoparScape!";
echo $testString;
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>Notice here how you do not use any kind of quotation marks around the variable when echoing.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
$testString = "Hello ";
$testString2 = "MoparScape!";
echo $testString.$testString2;
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This here is what you would do if you wanted to echo two variables beside each other in a piece of code, you join them by a period “.” this is used as a joining factor throughout PHP, but more on that later.</p>
<p>Be careful when echoing quotation marks, for example, through HTML tags.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
echo "&lt;font color="red"&gt;I love mopar!&lt;/font&gt;";  
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>The above code won’t work because of the multiple quotation marks in the echo statement.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">echo "&lt;font color=\"red\"&gt;I love mopar!&lt;/font&gt;";  

echo "&lt;font color='red'&gt;I love mopar!&lt;/font&gt;";  </code></pre>
<p>The above two codes will however, work. The first because of the backward slashes showing they’re not the end to the echo statement. The second because we used apostrophe’s instead of quotation marks.</p>
<p>Echoing variables and text strings:</p>
<p><code>&lt;?
$my_string = "Hello Ruby.  My name is: ";
echo "$my_string Cammy &lt;br /&gt;";
echo "Hi, I'm Ruby.  Who are you?&lt;br /&gt;"; 
echo "$my_string Cammy";
?&gt;</code></p>
<p>Test this code out, it’s rather fun to play around with these as they can be slightly confusing at first.</p>
<p>Okay, that’s our first section done on Echoing. We also covered some variables inside that there, however it shouldn’t be too confusing as we move onto Variables right now.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 3, Variables.</span></p>
<p>A variable is a means of storing a value, such as text string “Hello World!” or the integer value 4. A variable can then be reused throughout your code, instead of having to type out the actual value over and over again. In PHP you define a variable with the following form:<br>
$variableName = Value;<br>
If you forget that dollar sign at the beginning, it will not work. This is a common mistake for new PHP programmers!<br>
Note: Also, variable names are case-sensitive, so use the exact same capitalization when using a variable. The variables $aNumber and $Anumber are different variables in PHP’s eyes.</p>
<p>Okay, so now you know the basics, lets use some more variables!</p>
<p>We’ll start off with this code;</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
$text = "Hello MoparScape!";
$aNumber = 4;
$anotherNumber = 8;
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>Here we have stored 3 variables, one text string and two numerical values. Note how the text must be wrapped in quotation marks, but the numerical values don’t.<br>
PHP also doesn’t need the variables to be declared before being initialized.</p>
<p>Naming Conventions.</p>
<p>PHP variables must start with a letter or underscore “_”.<br>
PHP variables may only be comprised of alpha-numeric characters and underscores. a-z, A-Z, 0-9, or _ .<br>
Variables with more than one word should be distinguished with capitalization. $testVariable</p>
<p>You have already used variables  in the echoing part, but we’ll do a small exercise here.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
$myVar = "Rubys tutorial ";
$secondVar = "is ";
$thirdVar = 1337;

//echo all three together

echo $myVar.$secondVar.$thirdVar;
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>Remember that? Mess around with it and get used to variables, these are <span class="bbcode-b">essential</span> in any programming language.</p>
<p>You can also do mathematics inside variables and using variables. To times a number, use the asterisk - “*”, to subtract, use “-”, to add use “+” and to divide use “/”.</p>
<p>Use these for a while too, just get used to them.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 4, Functions</span><br>
A function is just a name we give to a block of code that can be executed whenever we need it. This might not seem like that big of an idea, but believe me, when you understand and use functions you will be able to save a ton of time and write code that is much more readable! Functions are generally thought too hard for beginners to use, but if you stick with them and persevere then you’ll be 100% fine and it’ll bring you on a lot through programming.</p>
<p>So, lets create our first function!</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
function whatIsMoparscape() {
echo "The best community ever!";
}
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This may seem just a question and answer, but you can do a lot with functions. For example;</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
function whatIsMoparscape() {
echo "The best community ever!&lt;br /&gt;";
}
echo "Welcome to MoparScape!&lt;br /&gt;";
whatIsMoparscape();
echo "We love to see new users coming in!&lt;br /&gt;";
echo "enjoy your stay, and remember we are...&lt;br /&gt;";
whatIsMoparscape();
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>So this is more or less what you can use a function for, but the list is endless, there is hundreds of reasons to use functions.</p>
<p>You may realise that the above function is more or less an oversized variable.  Here’s a much better use for functions;</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
function myFunction($firstName, $lastName){
    echo "Hello there ". $firstName ." ". $lastName ."!&lt;br /&gt;";
}
myFunction("Mod", "Cammy");
myFunction("Mod", "Nick");
myFunction("Mod", "Omer");
myFunction("Mod", "Tyler");
myFunction("Mod", "Justin");
myFunction("Mod", "Whackatre");
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This is a more useful function, just adapt it to your needs.</p>
<p>Here’s a few protips for when you’re using php functions;</p>
<ul>
<li>Always start your function with the keyword function</li>
<li>Remember that your function’s code must be between the “{” and the “}”</li>
<li>When you are using your function, be sure you spell the function name correctly</li>
<li>Don’t give up!</li>
</ul>
<p>Our last and final function is for php functions returning values.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
function mySum($numX, $numY){
    $total = $numX * $numY;
    return $total; 
}
$myNumber = 0;
echo "Before the function, myNumber = ". $myNumber ."&lt;br /&gt;";
$myNumber = mySum(3, 4);
echo "After the function, myNumber = " . $myNumber ."&lt;br /&gt;";
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>What this function does is holds a value of 0 before the function, after executing the function it then gains the value of the two numbers you had. You can also add in more variables such as $numZ and what not.</p>
<p>Okay, so that wraps up functions, if you don’t get it, don’t worry. Keep at it!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 5, switch statements.</span><br>
The way the Switch statement works is it takes a single variable as input and then checks it against all the different cases you set up for that switch statement. Instead of having to check that variable one at a time, as it goes through a bunch of If Statements, the Switch statement only has to check one time.</p>
<p>Here’s an example of a switch statement;</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
$revision = "317";
echo "Your current revision is: &lt;br /&gt;";
switch ($revision){
	case "317":
		echo "317, the best there ever was!";
		break;
	case "474":
		echo "474, alright, but starting to get worse.";
		break;	
	case "508":
		echo "508, the peak of runescape, before it got horrible.";
		break;	
	case "525":
		echo "525, the begin of the demise of runescape";
		break;
	case "525+":
		echo "Over 525, ew.";
		break;	
}
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>After doing this, you can then put the default value in. If you look at my other tutorial on switch statements for pages in this board, you’ll realise I use the default value there. This is more or less what shows if the variable is empty.</p>
<p>You’d use it like this;</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
$revision = "317";
echo "Your current revision is: &lt;br /&gt;";
switch ($revision){
	case "317":
		echo "317, the best there ever was!";
		break;
	case "474":
		echo "474, alright, but starting to get worse.";
		break;	
	case "508":
		echo "508, the peak of runescape, before it got horrible.";
		break;	
	case "525":
		echo "525, the begin of the demise of runescape";
		break;
	case "525+":
		echo "Over 525, ew.";
		break;	
              default:
                echo "Would you like to find out what revision your server is?";
                break;
}
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>That’s more or less switch statements, they’re a lot easier than people think and can be used for a lot of things.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 6, if/ifelse statements</span><br>
The if statement is necessary for most programming, thus it is important in PHP. Imagine that on January 1st you want to print out “Happy New Year!” at the top of your personal web page. With the use of PHP if statements you could have this process automated, months in advance, occuring every year on January 1st.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
$yourName = "Ruby";

if ( $yourName == "Ruby" ) {
	echo "Your name is Ruby!&lt;br /&gt;";
} else {
       echo "Your name is not Ruby!&lt;br /&gt;";
}
echo "Welcome to MoparScape!";

?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This is just a general if else statement, if you wish to create an if statement, remove the else. Although, it works a tonne better with else in there, it’s more professional in my opinion.</p>
<p>There isn’t really much to cover on this topic, you can add in as many else’s as you need with certain parameters on them.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Part 7, Cookies in PHP</span><br>
This is where I cover cookies and how you can use them, this type of cookie is a small text document that sits on your hard-drive and is accessed by the website that created them. These are used all the time, you probably have hundreds stored.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?
  $visits = $_COOKIE['moparscape'] + 1
    setcookie("moparscape", $visits, time()+3600*24*365, "/", "www.moparisthebest.com", 0);
    if($visits &gt; 1) {      
     echo "You have visited moparscape &lt;? $visits ?&gt; times.";      
  } else {
      echo "Welcome to moparscape, may you have many more pleasant visits.";
         }
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>This right here is almost the exact cookie I use on Xythax. What this does is that it stores the cookie on your hard drive with the setcookie() function and everytime I revisit a url with the name <a href="http://xythax.org" rel="nofollow noopener">xythax.org</a> in it, it adds 1 to the $visits variable and then you display it to someone who has more than 1 visit.</p>
<p>This code uses everything from the setcookie() function, an if/else statement, mathematics in php and variables. This just shows you that a script this small uses all of that.</p>
<p>Anyway MoparScape, I’ve just spent the past like 2 and a half hours writing this guide for you, I hope you enjoy it and use it.</p>
<p>Kind Regards,<br>
Ruby.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 18:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-450319-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/php-php-echo-variables-functions-switch-if-ifelse-and-cookies-php/450319.rss">[PHP] PHP Echo, Variables, Functions, Switch, If/Ifelse and Cookies [PHP]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
