<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320</link>
    <description>Moderators you may lock this if you please but i think i speak as a group or as the majority that i am getting sick and tired of all the bullshit that goes on in the models forums. 

@ Flamers- I don&#39;t understand why people are set on acting like such children that they feel the need to go into other peoples threads that they spent time making and talk a lot of shit. These are probably the most annoying people in the community and these people would be better off leaving.

@ Criticism- This also pertains to flaming but if you go into someones thread that they spent time on making people need to begin spending time and putting thought into their posts. I believe that it is perfectly fine if someone comments on your model and all they say is ,&quot;I like it&quot;... as long as it&#39;s positive and i do not think this should be considered spamming. However, if you are going to say that someones model does not look good or for some of you children, look likes shit, then why don&#39;t the tell the modeler what he/she can do to improve the model instead of just telling them it looks bad.

@ Gravedigging- Gravedigging as most are calling it is becoming very common recently however it is not all gravedigging... It is a gravedig if you go into a old topic and say some half-brained comment or something stupid just so it bumps back to the first page of threads. However, it is not a gravedig if the person finds an old topic but has a question about it, alot of flamers nowadays have been calling these questions gravedigs but they are wrong.

@ Newcomers- There seems to be alot of newcomers into the modeling community lately and they have been stirring up some problems. It seems that some people have been joining this community with the main intention of causing problems / flaming other people. This is beginning to get EXTREMELY annoying and i think that the moderators need to begin to take more serious actions against these people. However, there are also a select few newcomers that are actually here for modeling and want to learn it but whenever they post asking a question or posting their [First Model] they are getting flamed like crazy which in some situations might begin driving potential good modelers away from the modeling community. Also i would have to agree with most people that when someone comes in and asks questions that are answered in a tutorial it may get annoying but instead of flaming them and calling them a noob how about you help them out and send them a link to the tutorial.

@ Recolors- We may see alot of these and it may start to become annoying but guess what? its not against the rules, so all you people who complain about people recoloring models... its not getting you anywhere to sit there and flame the person AS LONG AS THE ORIGINAL MODELER WAS PROPERLY CREDITED. Although we would like to see more quality models and not just a 2 second recolor out of these people there is nothing that we can do to stop it so just live with it.

@ Models- It seems like there is not many QUALITY modelers in these forums anymore. There may be like 4-5, and we rarely see work out of SilentCJ, ACF, and Dylan anymore (although we would like to see more  ;)) So that leaves the normal modelers to step up their game and actually make some good models. I understand if your model doesnt look good and if its one of your first and you spent a fair amount of time on it, but if you have been modeling for a while and just keep posting 10 minute shitty models then just gtfo cause your doing more bad to this community rather than good. What i&#39;m trying to get at is that we need more people to spend lots of time on their models and WE NEED SOME GOOD MODELS!

@ Request- Sure it is ok to request a model based off of a picture. However DO NOT request a recolor as this can be done in 2 seconds by yourself and if just beginning to flood this section. Also DO NOT request an item id because most of the helpful id&#39;s are posted in the helpful id&#39;s thread... go there if you are requesting an item id. Also there is no problem with requesting an item as long as you are not going to scold the modeler for their attempt at your request, at least they tried. Last but not least, do not request high poly count models because these are useless to us as we can not use most of them in game. 

Before you know it this section is either gonna be deserted or filled with children... or if we could all get along like civilized people we could go back to like it used to be with minimal flaming and having the people more focused on modeling rather than arguing with someone if their post is a gravedig or not.

I believe that i have covered everything but if there is anything that needs to be added let me know.
I know that the flamers are gonna come the second i post this but idc all of this bullshit that has been happening recently is starting to get on everyones nerves and needs to be put to an end.

 ;D[u][b][size=16pt]All Supporters Post Below[/size][/b][/u] ;D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 05:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@owned654321241 owned654321241]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owned654321241">@owned654321241</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh gotcha haha. thats an easy word =P</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 05:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jjones10 jjones10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jjones10">@jjones10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“owned654321241, post:8, topic:284320”]Lol what does aforementioned mean?<br>
I feel stupid. :P[/quote]<br>
What was stated i the above list of guidlines.</p>
<p>aforementioned. BEFORE MENTIONED. Thats how i remember it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 23:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@owned654321241 owned654321241]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owned654321241">@owned654321241</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol what does aforementioned mean?<br>
I feel stupid. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 22:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Assassins_Creed_Fan Assassins Creed Fan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/assassins_creed_fan">@Assassins_Creed_Fan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="6" data-topic="284320">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/jjones10/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> jjones10:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>All the people who dont do the aforementioned dont have any common sense. So it helps <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 22:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jjones10 jjones10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jjones10">@jjones10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All the people who dont do the aforementioned dont have any common sense. So it helps <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 22:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@owned654321241 owned654321241]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owned654321241">@owned654321241</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s not common sense considering that there had been a high increase in this shit lately. I was tired of listening to it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 21:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this is just common sense, if people need to read this shit then they shouldnt be here</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 21:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@owned654321241 owned654321241]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owned654321241">@owned654321241</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Haha thanks frell for not locking it still =P</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 21:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cleaned for proper discussion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 18:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@owned654321241 owned654321241]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/owned654321241">@owned654321241</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Moderators you may lock this if you please but i think i speak as a group or as the majority that i am getting sick and tired of all the bullshit that goes on in the models forums.</p>
<p>@ Flamers- I don’t understand why people are set on acting like such children that they feel the need to go into other peoples threads that they spent time making and talk a lot of shit. These are probably the most annoying people in the community and these people would be better off leaving.</p>
<p>@ Criticism- This also pertains to flaming but if you go into someones thread that they spent time on making people need to begin spending time and putting thought into their posts. I believe that it is perfectly fine if someone comments on your model and all they say is ,“I like it”… as long as it’s positive and i do not think this should be considered spamming. However, if you are going to say that someones model does not look good or for some of you children, look likes shit, then why don’t the tell the modeler what he/she can do to improve the model instead of just telling them it looks bad.</p>
<p>@ Gravedigging- Gravedigging as most are calling it is becoming very common recently however it is not all gravedigging… It is a gravedig if you go into a old topic and say some half-brained comment or something stupid just so it bumps back to the first page of threads. However, it is not a gravedig if the person finds an old topic but has a question about it, alot of flamers nowadays have been calling these questions gravedigs but they are wrong.</p>
<p>@ Newcomers- There seems to be alot of newcomers into the modeling community lately and they have been stirring up some problems. It seems that some people have been joining this community with the main intention of causing problems / flaming other people. This is beginning to get EXTREMELY annoying and i think that the moderators need to begin to take more serious actions against these people. However, there are also a select few newcomers that are actually here for modeling and want to learn it but whenever they post asking a question or posting their [First Model] they are getting flamed like crazy which in some situations might begin driving potential good modelers away from the modeling community. Also i would have to agree with most people that when someone comes in and asks questions that are answered in a tutorial it may get annoying but instead of flaming them and calling them a noob how about you help them out and send them a link to the tutorial.</p>
<p>@ Recolors- We may see alot of these and it may start to become annoying but guess what? its not against the rules, so all you people who complain about people recoloring models… its not getting you anywhere to sit there and flame the person AS LONG AS THE ORIGINAL MODELER WAS PROPERLY CREDITED. Although we would like to see more quality models and not just a 2 second recolor out of these people there is nothing that we can do to stop it so just live with it.</p>
<p>@ Models- It seems like there is not many QUALITY modelers in these forums anymore. There may be like 4-5, and we rarely see work out of SilentCJ, ACF, and Dylan anymore (although we would like to see more  ;)) So that leaves the normal modelers to step up their game and actually make some good models. I understand if your model doesnt look good and if its one of your first and you spent a fair amount of time on it, but if you have been modeling for a while and just keep posting 10 minute shitty models then just gtfo cause your doing more bad to this community rather than good. What i’m trying to get at is that we need more people to spend lots of time on their models and WE NEED SOME GOOD MODELS!</p>
<p>@ Request- Sure it is ok to request a model based off of a picture. However DO NOT request a recolor as this can be done in 2 seconds by yourself and if just beginning to flood this section. Also DO NOT request an item id because most of the helpful id’s are posted in the helpful id’s thread… go there if you are requesting an item id. Also there is no problem with requesting an item as long as you are not going to scold the modeler for their attempt at your request, at least they tried. Last but not least, do not request high poly count models because these are useless to us as we can not use most of them in game.</p>
<p>Before you know it this section is either gonna be deserted or filled with children… or if we could all get along like civilized people we could go back to like it used to be with minimal flaming and having the people more focused on modeling rather than arguing with someone if their post is a gravedig or not.</p>
<p>I believe that i have covered everything but if there is anything that needs to be added let me know.<br>
I know that the flamers are gonna come the second i post this but idc all of this bullshit that has been happening recently is starting to get on everyones nerves and needs to be put to an end.</p>
<p>;D<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">[size=16pt]All Supporters Post Below[/size]</span></span> ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 08:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284320-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/current-problems-in-models-section/284320.rss">~~~Current Problems in Models Section~~~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
