<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubuntu 10.10 Sound messed up</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ubuntu-10-10-sound-messed-up/384789</link>
    <description>I use Ubuntu 10.10 and recently I&#39;ve begun to have problems with gmail chat. After a few minutes of video chatting the sound changes to a screeching white noise, but the other person can still hear me. In a few minutes it reverts at a lowered volume and then it goes back to static after another few. I didn&#39;t have these problems before, and the only other sound problems I have noticed are with minecraft sound lagging/stopping sometimes. I didn&#39;t use to have this problem and I first noticed it today. I did do a firefox update though...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 00:30:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ubuntu-10-10-sound-messed-up/384789.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ubuntu 10.10 Sound messed up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I use Ubuntu 10.10 and recently I’ve begun to have problems with gmail chat. After a few minutes of video chatting the sound changes to a screeching white noise, but the other person can still hear me. In a few minutes it reverts at a lowered volume and then it goes back to static after another few. I didn’t have these problems before, and the only other sound problems I have noticed are with minecraft sound lagging/stopping sometimes. I didn’t use to have this problem and I first noticed it today. I did do a firefox update though…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ubuntu-10-10-sound-messed-up/384789/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ubuntu-10-10-sound-messed-up/384789/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 00:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384789-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ubuntu-10-10-sound-messed-up/384789.rss">Ubuntu 10.10 Sound messed up</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
