<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I created a new skill and</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-created-a-new-skill-and/49064</link>
    <description>Hey. I made a new skill called &quot;Barfusing&quot;. I used Mod Taharok&#39;s guide, but only used it for the searching (Since I had a different source) and I got my skill on everywhere I was supposed to in my client.java, and I got it to show at the top of the screen. I also got the barfusing combo done (Since I used to have it as crafting XP, it fused and gave the new bar and crafting xp), and now when I use it (Since I set the skill to [22], cause that&#39;s what it is), it freezes. Can someone tell me why? Is it because it&#39;s not on the character list???[br][size=1]Posted on: January 18, 2007, 04:36:59 PM[/size][hr]Okay. Its with al my players in my character folder... But if someone uses a bar with another bar and has the right level (1 with bronze), it freezes. It doesn&#39;t freeze with the wrong level, though :(.[br][size=1]Posted on: January 18, 2007, 04:42:37 PM[/size][hr]Oh yeah, it only freezes when I level up. I figured that much out.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 05:22:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-created-a-new-skill-and/49064.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I created a new skill and</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey. I made a new skill called “Barfusing”. I used Mod Taharok’s guide, but only used it for the searching (Since I had a different source) and I got my skill on everywhere I was supposed to in my client.java, and I got it to show at the top of the screen. I also got the barfusing combo done (Since I used to have it as crafting XP, it fused and gave the new bar and crafting xp), and now when I use it (Since I set the skill to [22], cause that’s what it is), it freezes. Can someone tell me why? Is it because it’s not on the character list???[br][size=1]Posted on: January 18, 2007, 04:36:59 PM[/size][hr]Okay. Its with al my players in my character folder… But if someone uses a bar with another bar and has the right level (1 with bronze), it freezes. It doesn’t freeze with the wrong level, though :(.[br][size=1]Posted on: January 18, 2007, 04:42:37 PM[/size][hr]Oh yeah, it only freezes when I level up. I figured that much out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-created-a-new-skill-and/49064/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-created-a-new-skill-and/49064/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 05:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-49064-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/i-created-a-new-skill-and/49064.rss">I created a new skill and</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
