<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913</link>
    <description>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lL1iyG2_hOQ


Okay so humanity is facing three major problems.
1. We have relied on hydrocarbons (oil and gas) for our energy. There may not be any in the future (Resource depletion)
2. Hydrocarbons have altered the composition of the Earth&#39;s atmosphere lead to enormous consequences (climate change)
3. Those hydrocarbons remaining are increasingly controlled by people whose interests may not be aligned with our own (energy security)

http://www.decc.gov.uk/en/content/cms/what_we_do/lc_uk/2050/2050.aspx
http://my2050.decc.gov.uk/

The UK is one of the countries committed to reducing its carbon dioxide emissions by 80% from 1990 levels. To do this we&#39;ll have to make some very significant changes to our lifestyle (or you use politician-speak, we&#39;re faced with very difficult choices.)

The government has made a website with many knobs and sliders representing these choices and invites you to twiddle and tune them to create your own policy (or pathway). There are also many sample pathways 

I&#39;m in the second year of my university physics course in which one of modules is Environmental Physics which discusses these topics. The lecturer showed us this website and encouraged us to play with it. Although having said that, you need only a rudimentary knowledge of physics to use this and almost everything is explained in clear terms.

Hopefully many people will play with this to realise the scale of the problem we&#39;re facing and maybe they&#39;ll stop claiming silly things like it being at all plausible to reduce emissions without using nuclear power.


&lt;blockquote&gt;The 2050 Web tool is a user-friendly model that lets you create your own UK emissions reduction pathway, and see the impact using real UK data. Within the tool you can see example pathways that show different ways of reaching the 2050 target, while keeping the lights on.

The tool presents you with three charts, describing the demand for energy, the supply of energy and the greenhouse gas emissions for the UK. Below the charts are a list of sectors. For each sector of the economy, four trajectories have been developed, ranging from little or no effort to reduce emissions (level 1) to extremely ambitious changes that push towards the physical or technical limits of what can be achieved (level 4). These are indicated by four numbered boxes.

If you click on a number, then that trajectory is selected and the charts recalculate - this calculation may take up to 30 seconds. If you move your mouse over the levels, a box will appear describing what that choice represents. You can find out more about each sector and what the changes would mean in practice by clicking the question mark icons next to each sector - these will display a short summary introducing the sector and explaining the levels and choices available.

Where there are letters (A, B, C, D) instead of numbers this shows that trajectories within this sector represent different scenarios, rather than levels of effort. For example, we could derive energy from a biomass (a lump of wood) in different ways – we could leave it as a solid fuel, or turn it into a liquid or a gas. 

[b]Create your Pathway[/b]
* Demand
On the demand side, you can make choices about the amount of energy the UK uses. For example, you can choose how far to insulate our houses, how much more efficient to make our lighting and appliances, or choose how we travel and in what kind of vehicles.
       
* Supply
On the supply side you can choose how the UK produces its energy. For example, you can choose to build up to 40,000 offshore wind turbines or up to 50 3GW nuclear power stations, you can allocate up to 20% of the UK’s land to growing bio crops and you can reduce our use of landfill sites. (note: if your pathway doesn&#39;t supply enough energy, the shortfall is made up by fossil fuels)

[b]Outputs from your Pathway[/b]
* Emissions
The emissions chart on the right-hand side of the screen shows the emissions from your pathway to 2050 and allows you to check whether it meets the 2050 target by cutting UK emissions by at least 80% from 1990 levels.
       
* Energy Security
Part of choosing a pathway is evaluating how well it could cope with real-life weather events and demand patterns. To test this, the 2050 Web tool simulates a cold, windless week. This means significant increases in the amount of energy demanded for heating, whilst reducing the energy supplied by some renewables, including wind turbines and solar panels. The 2050 Web tool will show how much back-up generation your pathway requires, and you can choose what level of effort put into storing energy, shifting demand and using interconnection to help meet the challenge.

[b]Implications of your Pathway[/b]
You can explore some of the wider implications of your pathway by using the Web tool’s tabs. For example, you can see the implications of your pathway for the size of the electricity sector. You can visually track how energy flows through the system in your pathways. You can see the amount of UK land required by different energy supply technologies in your pathways. And you can read a short summary of your pathway on the story tab.
Things to think about in constructing a pathway

While this analysis helps us look ahead, there are some limitations to the approach:

* The model does not account for all possible feedbacks between trajectory levels in different sectors.
* It does not prevent implausible combinations of action, such as:
      - Very high levels of both solar PV and solar thermal at the same time — in practice these technologies may be competing for the same roof space;
      - A thriving manufacturing industry and high levels of additional construction at the same time as a reducing demand for freight transport;
      - Generating electricity through non-thermal processes, whilst at the same time rolling out use of district heating.
* No assumptions are made about what the rest of the world does. It does not consider the role that international emissions credits might play.
* Like the UK&#39;s emission target, it does not take account of the emissions from:
      - growing biofuels abroad,
      - electricity generated in other countries.
      - the overseas manufacture of products which the UK imports.
* Any new, unabated generation is provided by gas-fired power stations.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 21:14:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@z z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/z">@z</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>(Slightly off-topic?) During Richard Heinberg’s lecture “Life After Growth: Building Community Resilience in a World of Declining Energy”, he evaluated something like two dozen energy sources, but he found that there was no credible scenario in which the alternative energy source could make up for fossil fuels once declines begin.</p>
<p>In order to replace fossil fuels, we would need to evaluate these eight points on the energy source in mind.</p>
<p>[ul][li]energy return on investment[/li]<br>
[li]size of resource[/li]<br>
[li]infrastructure requirement[/li]<br>
[li]convenience of use[/li]<br>
[li]environmental impact[/li]<br>
[li]renewability[/li]<br>
[li]scalability[/li]<br>
[li]location of resource[/li][/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 21:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mopman, post:14, topic:393913”][quote author=R.I.P RSC link=topic=491098.msg3591569#msg3591569 date=1304683560]<br>
I’d like to say that I’m proud to be Dutch. We signed an agreement which stated that 20% of our energy would be green by 2020.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>So did we. I think it’s EU wide rite?[/quote]</p>
<p>Yes it is. I love it when politicians make plans and then just forget about them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 14:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="9" data-topic="393913">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 R.I.P RSC:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’d like to say that I’m proud to be Dutch. We signed an agreement which stated that 20% of our energy would be green by 2020.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>So did we. I think it’s EU wide rite?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 01:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yakman yakman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yakman">@yakman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sanga look at the example pathways. Like I said, its hard.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="393913">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/unhandled/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Unhandled:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>yakman you probably know more about this than me, why aren’t we using more <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Breeder_reactor" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">breeder reactors</a> to safely dispose of the depleted uranium? (one of the main arguments against nuclear fission)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Some people thought Uranium breeder reactors could be used to make nuclear weapons. Nobody has managed it but I suppose not many people work on nuclear weapons these days.</p>
<p>Thorium breeder reactors are really good but more research is needed since the technology is quite young. All we need is the political will to work on it some more.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.argee.net/DefenseWatch/Nuclear%20Waste%20and%20Breeder%20Reactors.htm" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.argee.net/DefenseWatch/Nuclear%20Waste%20and%20Breeder%20Reactors.htm</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 14:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>also this simulation thing is retarded i set evgerything to max and demand to low and it didnt reach 20%? am i missing something</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 13:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:5, topic:393913”]we make a big vacuum to suck all the CO2 out of the air, shoot it back out over the middle east and make them sick</p>
<p>???</p>
<p>make oil even less profitable</p>
<p>???</p>
<p>profit[/quote]<br>
If you make them sick, the oil will be more profitable since the production will go down.</p>
<p>???</p>
<p>Huge profit. (For the remaining oil-producers)</p>
<p>So lets do it (Only bad thing is that non-oil technologies will be more attractive)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 12:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="393913">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_1.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So if the destruction of our race is inevitable, just… who cares when it happens? Bring it on tomorrow?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>i havent slept with enough women yet</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 12:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d like to say that I’m proud to be Dutch. We signed an agreement which stated that 20% of our energy would be green by 2020. But in the mean time, we’re building 3 (initially 4, but one is postponed) new coal plants! Hurrah for the Netherlands!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="6" data-topic="393913">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I say we drill a giant hole from the USA to under the middle east, and siphon the oil over here</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="RKQ3LXHKB34" data-youtube-title="i drink your milkshake" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque&amp;start=36"></div>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 06:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="393913">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/unhandled/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Unhandled:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>getting rid of poorly informed hysterics speading FUD about nuclear power would probably be a good place to start.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This this this this this this this this this this this this…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 06:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I say we drill a giant hole from the USA to under the middle east, and siphon the oil over here</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 04:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>we make a big vacuum to suck all the CO2 out of the air, shoot it back out over the middle east and make them sick</p>
<p>???</p>
<p>make oil even less profitable</p>
<p>???</p>
<p>profit</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 02:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>getting rid of poorly informed hysterics speading FUD about nuclear power would probably be a good place to start.</p>
<p>yakman you probably know more about this than me, why aren’t we using more <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Breeder_reactor" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">breeder reactors</a> to safely dispose of the depleted uranium? (one of the main arguments against nuclear fission)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 02:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So if the destruction of our race is inevitable, just… who cares when it happens? Bring it on tomorrow?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 02:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SETO SETO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/seto">@SETO</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>in reality, although small steps do make big differences, but no one sees the bigger picture.<br>
bottom line: we won’t nor can kill planet earth but we will kil everything on it. it just a phase of evolution.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 01:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yakman yakman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yakman">@yakman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="lL1iyG2_hOQ" data-youtube-title="The 2050 Energy Pathways Calculator" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>Okay so humanity is facing three major problems.</p>
<ol>
<li>We have relied on hydrocarbons (oil and gas) for our energy. There may not be any in the future (Resource depletion)</li>
<li>Hydrocarbons have altered the composition of the Earth’s atmosphere lead to enormous consequences (climate change)</li>
<li>Those hydrocarbons remaining are increasingly controlled by people whose interests may not be aligned with our own (energy security)</li>
</ol>
<p><a href="http://www.decc.gov.uk/en/content/cms/what_we_do/lc_uk/2050/2050.aspx" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.decc.gov.uk/en/content/cms/what_we_do/lc_uk/2050/2050.aspx</a><br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/static/favicon-8d811b8c3badbc0b0e2f6e25d3660a96cc0cca7993e6f32e98785f205fc40907.ico" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://www.gov.uk/guidance/2050-pathways-analysis" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">GOV.UK</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:690/362;"><img src="https://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/static/opengraph-image-a1f7d89ffd0782738b1aeb0da37842d8bd0addbd724b8e58c3edbc7287cc11de.png" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://www.gov.uk/guidance/2050-pathways-analysis" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">2050 Pathways</a></h3>

<p>Exploring how the UK can meet the 2050 emission reduction target using the web-based 2050 Calculator.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>The UK is one of the countries committed to reducing its carbon dioxide emissions by 80% from 1990 levels. To do this we’ll have to make some very significant changes to our lifestyle (or you use politician-speak, we’re faced with very difficult choices.)</p>
<p>The government has made a website with many knobs and sliders representing these choices and invites you to twiddle and tune them to create your own policy (or pathway). There are also many sample pathways</p>
<p>I’m in the second year of my university physics course in which one of modules is Environmental Physics which discusses these topics. The lecturer showed us this website and encouraged us to play with it. Although having said that, you need only a rudimentary knowledge of physics to use this and almost everything is explained in clear terms.</p>
<p>Hopefully many people will play with this to realise the scale of the problem we’re facing and maybe they’ll stop claiming silly things like it being at all plausible to reduce emissions without using nuclear power.</p>
<blockquote>The 2050 Web tool is a user-friendly model that lets you create your own UK emissions reduction pathway, and see the impact using real UK data. Within the tool you can see example pathways that show different ways of reaching the 2050 target, while keeping the lights on.
<p>The tool presents you with three charts, describing the demand for energy, the supply of energy and the greenhouse gas emissions for the UK. Below the charts are a list of sectors. For each sector of the economy, four trajectories have been developed, ranging from little or no effort to reduce emissions (level 1) to extremely ambitious changes that push towards the physical or technical limits of what can be achieved (level 4). These are indicated by four numbered boxes.</p>
<p>If you click on a number, then that trajectory is selected and the charts recalculate - this calculation may take up to 30 seconds. If you move your mouse over the levels, a box will appear describing what that choice represents. You can find out more about each sector and what the changes would mean in practice by clicking the question mark icons next to each sector - these will display a short summary introducing the sector and explaining the levels and choices available.</p>
<p>Where there are letters (A, B, C, D) instead of numbers this shows that trajectories within this sector represent different scenarios, rather than levels of effort. For example, we could derive energy from a biomass (a lump of wood) in different ways – we could leave it as a solid fuel, or turn it into a liquid or a gas.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Create your Pathway</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Demand<br>
On the demand side, you can make choices about the amount of energy the UK uses. For example, you can choose how far to insulate our houses, how much more efficient to make our lighting and appliances, or choose how we travel and in what kind of vehicles.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Supply<br>
On the supply side you can choose how the UK produces its energy. For example, you can choose to build up to 40,000 offshore wind turbines or up to 50 3GW nuclear power stations, you can allocate up to 20% of the UK’s land to growing bio crops and you can reduce our use of landfill sites. (note: if your pathway doesn’t supply enough energy, the shortfall is made up by fossil fuels)</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Outputs from your Pathway</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Emissions<br>
The emissions chart on the right-hand side of the screen shows the emissions from your pathway to 2050 and allows you to check whether it meets the 2050 target by cutting UK emissions by at least 80% from 1990 levels.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Energy Security<br>
Part of choosing a pathway is evaluating how well it could cope with real-life weather events and demand patterns. To test this, the 2050 Web tool simulates a cold, windless week. This means significant increases in the amount of energy demanded for heating, whilst reducing the energy supplied by some renewables, including wind turbines and solar panels. The 2050 Web tool will show how much back-up generation your pathway requires, and you can choose what level of effort put into storing energy, shifting demand and using interconnection to help meet the challenge.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Implications of your Pathway</span><br>
You can explore some of the wider implications of your pathway by using the Web tool’s tabs. For example, you can see the implications of your pathway for the size of the electricity sector. You can visually track how energy flows through the system in your pathways. You can see the amount of UK land required by different energy supply technologies in your pathways. And you can read a short summary of your pathway on the story tab.<br>
Things to think about in constructing a pathway</p>
<p>While this analysis helps us look ahead, there are some limitations to the approach:</p>
<ul>
<li>The model does not account for all possible feedbacks between trajectory levels in different sectors.</li>
<li>It does not prevent implausible combinations of action, such as:<br>
- Very high levels of both solar PV and solar thermal at the same time — in practice these technologies may be competing for the same roof space;<br>
- A thriving manufacturing industry and high levels of additional construction at the same time as a reducing demand for freight transport;<br>
- Generating electricity through non-thermal processes, whilst at the same time rolling out use of district heating.</li>
<li>No assumptions are made about what the rest of the world does. It does not consider the role that international emissions credits might play.</li>
<li>Like the UK’s emission target, it does not take account of the emissions from:<br>
- growing biofuels abroad,<br>
- electricity generated in other countries.<br>
- the overseas manufacture of products which the UK imports.</li>
<li>Any new, unabated generation is provided by gas-fired power stations.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>

          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-393913-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/design-your-own-pathway-to-carbon-reduction/393913.rss">Design your own pathway to carbon reduction</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
