<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Del tha Funkee Homosapien</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/del-tha-funkee-homosapien/190162</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;Del tha Funkee Homosapien is an [b]alternative hip hop artist[/b]. Del was born Teren Delvon Jones on August 12, 1972 in Oakland, California. He currently lives in Richmond, California.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;Cousin of renowned rapper Ice Cube, Del began his career writing lyrics for Cube&#39;s backing band, Da Lench Mob. In 1991, with the help of Ice Cube, Del released at 19 years old his first solo album, I Wish My Brother George Was Here. The album was a commercial success, largely due to the popularity of the hit single, &quot;Mistadobalina&quot;. Ultimately Del, who was not pleased with the limited musical range of the album, took matters into his own hands, and severed his production-artist relationship with Ice Cube for his next album, No Need for Alarm.

No Need for Alarm also saw the introduction of the famous Oakland clique Hieroglyphics, whose original members included the widely acclaimed Souls of Michief, Casual, Domino, and Pep Love. No Need for Alarm was a bold move on Del&#39;s part as it allowed him to develop, display, and solidify his unique style as an MC, and also helped to expose both the regional Oakland sound of hip hop, as well as the freestyle based, &quot;golden era-97&quot; style of hip hop being expanded at the time. Rather than the use of multiple funk samples, including those of Pfunk, No Need for Alarm features a bold, classic hip hop sound, often referred to as an updated Oakland version of Boom Bap, which is a certain archetypal hip hop sound, and because Del and his crew represents Oakland. The sound of this album was largely due to the production work of Domino, a producer for the Hieroglyphics crew. The album No Need for Alarm is still considered one of the greatest albums ever to come out of Del, Hieroglyphics, or Oakland, and is highly regarded as one of the all time classic albums of hip hop. The instrumental pressings of this record is considered the &quot;holy grail&quot; of hiphop instrumental albums, due to the quality of production on the album and also due to its extremely limited pressing.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;Also known as: 	


[ul][*]Del
[*]Deltron Zero
[*]Deltron Z
[*]Dr. Bombay
[*]Del Diablo Diabolique
[*]Sir Diesel
[*]Sir DZL[/ul]&lt;/blockquote&gt;

[url=http://youtube.com/watch?v=9wa9vZDOY-Y]Del tha Funkee Homosapien (Turbulence)[/url]
[url=http://youtube.com/watch?v=9foyE-hPOaQ]Del tha Funkee Homosapien (Madness)[/url]
[url=http://youtube.com/watch?v=tRYP4xCpaWI]Del tha Funkee Homosapien (Virus)[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 07:14:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/del-tha-funkee-homosapien/190162.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Del tha Funkee Homosapien</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Crack_Miners Crack Miners]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/crack_miners">@Crack_Miners</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Del tha Funkee Homosapien is an [b]alternative hip hop artist[/b]. Del was born Teren Delvon Jones on August 12, 1972 in Oakland, California. He currently lives in Richmond, California.</blockquote>
<blockquote>Cousin of renowned rapper Ice Cube, Del began his career writing lyrics for Cube's backing band, Da Lench Mob. In 1991, with the help of Ice Cube, Del released at 19 years old his first solo album, I Wish My Brother George Was Here. The album was a commercial success, largely due to the popularity of the hit single, "Mistadobalina". Ultimately Del, who was not pleased with the limited musical range of the album, took matters into his own hands, and severed his production-artist relationship with Ice Cube for his next album, No Need for Alarm.
<p>No Need for Alarm also saw the introduction of the famous Oakland clique Hieroglyphics, whose original members included the widely acclaimed Souls of Michief, Casual, Domino, and Pep Love. No Need for Alarm was a bold move on Del’s part as it allowed him to develop, display, and solidify his unique style as an MC, and also helped to expose both the regional Oakland sound of hip hop, as well as the freestyle based, “golden era-97” style of hip hop being expanded at the time. Rather than the use of multiple funk samples, including those of Pfunk, No Need for Alarm features a bold, classic hip hop sound, often referred to as an updated Oakland version of Boom Bap, which is a certain archetypal hip hop sound, and because Del and his crew represents Oakland. The sound of this album was largely due to the production work of Domino, a producer for the Hieroglyphics crew. The album No Need for Alarm is still considered one of the greatest albums ever to come out of Del, Hieroglyphics, or Oakland, and is highly regarded as one of the all time classic albums of hip hop. The instrumental pressings of this record is considered the “holy grail” of hiphop instrumental albums, due to the quality of production on the album and also due to its extremely limited pressing.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>Also known as: 	
<p>[ul][<em>]Del<br>
[</em>]Deltron Zero<br>
[<em>]Deltron Z<br>
[</em>]Dr. Bombay<br>
[<em>]Del Diablo Diabolique<br>
[</em>]Sir Diesel<br>
[*]Sir DZL[/ul]</p>
</blockquote>
<p><a href="http://youtube.com/watch?v=9wa9vZDOY-Y" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Del tha Funkee Homosapien (Turbulence)</a><br>
<a href="http://youtube.com/watch?v=9foyE-hPOaQ" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Del tha Funkee Homosapien (Madness)</a><br>
<a href="http://youtube.com/watch?v=tRYP4xCpaWI" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Del tha Funkee Homosapien (Virus)</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/del-tha-funkee-homosapien/190162/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/del-tha-funkee-homosapien/190162/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 07:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-190162-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/del-tha-funkee-homosapien/190162.rss">Del tha Funkee Homosapien</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
