<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Eating in Satan&#39;s Isle</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eating-in-satans-isle/111090</link>
    <description>I am having a problem with my new server. I used to have a fr33sc4p3 server and by popular demand I switched to Satan&#39;s Isle. People liked the way I kept up with my server and they thought I would do good with a Satan&#39;s Isle. Everything was working OK when the food stopped working. Everyone with their hitpoints at 135 had it shot up to 136. So then, they couldn&#39;t eat. Stats that were 135 worked fine on fr33sc4p3, and never went up. I need some help, maybe keeping the stats at 135. They are set at 135 and they won&#39;t go back down.

Thanks.

Seth</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2007 07:26:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eating-in-satans-isle/111090.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Eating in Satan&#39;s Isle</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xone xone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xone">@xone</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am having a problem with my new server. I used to have a fr33sc4p3 server and by popular demand I switched to Satan’s Isle. People liked the way I kept up with my server and they thought I would do good with a Satan’s Isle. Everything was working OK when the food stopped working. Everyone with their hitpoints at 135 had it shot up to 136. So then, they couldn’t eat. Stats that were 135 worked fine on fr33sc4p3, and never went up. I need some help, maybe keeping the stats at 135. They are set at 135 and they won’t go back down.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
<p>Seth</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eating-in-satans-isle/111090/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eating-in-satans-isle/111090/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2007 07:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-111090-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eating-in-satans-isle/111090.rss">Eating in Satan&#39;s Isle</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
