<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Moparland Server Rules and General Information!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparland-server-rules-and-general-information/553638</link>
    <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/azkb3FR.jpg[/img]

Moparland is Speljohan_&#39;s Wurm Unlimited server hosted in a datacentre in Sweden, currently administrated by myself. Why is Speljohan_ not an administrator you ask? Well, he is, but he is dedicating all of his free time to working on a modding framework so he can deliver top quality mods and content to Moparland! 

Moparland is primarily a PvE server with potential to add large PvP zones as we use a 4096 sized custom generated map. Future goals for the server include custom mods and content that will be decided by the community. Moparland strives to be a community driven server, and as a result the GM&#39;s policy on administration is non-interference for the most part unless where necessary.

[hr]

[b]General Information[/b]

Moparland has a player limit of 100 (which may be adjusted as we go along), with a map size of 4096. Skillgain and Action timers are currently set to 5x and 4x respectively, which may be reduced in the future if it&#39;s deemed too quick progression. Mob cap is set to 35k, with 25% being aggressive, again, this may be adjusted as we go along depending on the dedicated server performance and how well our server copes. The goal of the server is to allow players who don&#39;t have much free time, or work full time, to still be able to make meaningful progress. Settlements are currently free (please read the rules below for more information), and at some point we will start adding patches of Mycelium if players choose to pray to Libila. 

[b]Rules[/b]

As stated, the goal of the server is to be as community driven as possible, and as a result any possible rules we would have would be too lax to clearly define, matters that require a GM will be dealt with using a best discretion policy where available so we stress that you also use your best discretion. 

While we don&#39;t want to impose rules on griefing or the like, we ask that players not go out of their way to harass other players. 

Settlements are currently free, while we don&#39;t want to impose size limits on players, we ask that you consider the needs of yourself along with the needs of others. Settlements that are obnoxiously large or have an unnecessary perimeter size that is causing problems for other players will be dealt with by a GM, which may include forcibly resizing your settlement. We ask that you use settlements along with settlement policies to prevent issues that may arise such as theft or griefing. 

We would ask that players try to be polite and civil when interacting with other players both in game and through the chat. 

[hr]

PSAs: The map and players were reset 20~ hours after launch, as a result of a poor map and incorrectly configured skillgain. We shouldn&#39;t need to do this again. Clay and Sand can now be found at water level (only).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 23:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparland-server-rules-and-general-information/553638.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Moparland Server Rules and General Information!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://i.imgur.com/azkb3FR.jpg" title="azkb3FR.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/azkb3FR.jpg" alt width="690" height="388"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">azkb3FR.jpg</span><span class="informations">1024×576</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Moparland is Speljohan_'s Wurm Unlimited server hosted in a datacentre in Sweden, currently administrated by myself. Why is Speljohan_ not an administrator you ask? Well, he is, but he is dedicating all of his free time to working on a modding framework so he can deliver top quality mods and content to Moparland!</p>
<p>Moparland is primarily a PvE server with potential to add large PvP zones as we use a 4096 sized custom generated map. Future goals for the server include custom mods and content that will be decided by the community. Moparland strives to be a community driven server, and as a result the GM’s policy on administration is non-interference for the most part unless where necessary.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">General Information</span></p>
<p>Moparland has a player limit of 100 (which may be adjusted as we go along), with a map size of 4096. Skillgain and Action timers are currently set to 5x and 4x respectively, which may be reduced in the future if it’s deemed too quick progression. Mob cap is set to 35k, with 25% being aggressive, again, this may be adjusted as we go along depending on the dedicated server performance and how well our server copes. The goal of the server is to allow players who don’t have much free time, or work full time, to still be able to make meaningful progress. Settlements are currently free (please read the rules below for more information), and at some point we will start adding patches of Mycelium if players choose to pray to Libila.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rules</span></p>
<p>As stated, the goal of the server is to be as community driven as possible, and as a result any possible rules we would have would be too lax to clearly define, matters that require a GM will be dealt with using a best discretion policy where available so we stress that you also use your best discretion.</p>
<p>While we don’t want to impose rules on griefing or the like, we ask that players not go out of their way to harass other players.</p>
<p>Settlements are currently free, while we don’t want to impose size limits on players, we ask that you consider the needs of yourself along with the needs of others. Settlements that are obnoxiously large or have an unnecessary perimeter size that is causing problems for other players will be dealt with by a GM, which may include forcibly resizing your settlement. We ask that you use settlements along with settlement policies to prevent issues that may arise such as theft or griefing.</p>
<p>We would ask that players try to be polite and civil when interacting with other players both in game and through the chat.</p>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>PSAs: The map and players were reset 20~ hours after launch, as a result of a poor map and incorrectly configured skillgain. We shouldn’t need to do this again. Clay and Sand can now be found at water level (only).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparland-server-rules-and-general-information/553638/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparland-server-rules-and-general-information/553638/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 23:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553638-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparland-server-rules-and-general-information/553638.rss">Moparland Server Rules and General Information!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
