<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking to join a Team/Project</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-to-join-a-team-project/544724</link>
    <description>Hi, I am looking to join a Development Team/Project. 

A little about myself - I&#39;ll be turning 21 in 23 days, I play Runescape off and on, I like to go for walks, I love being part of a team, and also I like to help out.

What kind of team am I looking for? - An honest, active team. Something with a goal in mind, rather it be Economy based, PvP based, etc.

What Can I offer? Well I&#39;m not the best coder by far, but I do have experience in real life and on RSPS&#39;s as a Community Manager.


I&#39;m basically looking for a part of a team that thinks it will go far and to help out with things daily and stuff.



If you&#39;re looking for help, add me on Skype at - Garrett3650</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 18:07:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-to-join-a-team-project/544724.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking to join a Team/Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mister_Master Mister Master]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mister_master">@Mister_Master</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi, I am looking to join a Development Team/Project.</p>
<p>A little about myself - I’ll be turning 21 in 23 days, I play Runescape off and on, I like to go for walks, I love being part of a team, and also I like to help out.</p>
<p>What kind of team am I looking for? - An honest, active team. Something with a goal in mind, rather it be Economy based, PvP based, etc.</p>
<p>What Can I offer? Well I’m not the best coder by far, but I do have experience in real life and on RSPS’s as a Community Manager.</p>
<p>I’m basically looking for a part of a team that thinks it will go far and to help out with things daily and stuff.</p>
<p>If you’re looking for help, add me on Skype at - Garrett3650</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-to-join-a-team-project/544724/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-to-join-a-team-project/544724/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 18:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-544724-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-to-join-a-team-project/544724.rss">Looking to join a Team/Project</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
