<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help with a lot of things! (Potion and emote/animation related!)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-lot-of-things-potion-and-emote-animation-related/400043</link>
    <description>Okay, first off I would like to say that I have tried to resolve these by myself and have done many web searches. A huge problem why I can&#39;t resolve this issue myself is because I am definitely a beginner and don&#39;t have a huge amount of knowledge in Java though I understand the main and basic concepts of it. My problems are rooted in the animations and potions. When I do startAnimation(XXXX); or setAnimation(XXXX); to add the burying bones animation when you bury them nothing happens. You do get the exp for burying them and there is a message that shows up that says &quot;You have buried &quot;+name+&quot; bones.&quot; but that&#39;s all. I may just not know the correct way to call and animation but I would like some kind of feed back on this. Another issue is that this source does not have a &quot;Potions.java&quot; and a lot of threads and web search results had answers revolving around that. There is some scrappy code for potions, food, and bones, but none of that even works (they are in client.java). Potions just say &quot;Nothing interesting happened.&quot; Food is okay. Some of it works but I have no clue where it calls the animations since the code inside of &quot;Client.java&quot; just has the healing stats. I have looked all over the server source and can&#39;t find a thing to help. Is this a client sided issue? (If it is then I am really stupid because I just thought of that while I was typing this :P).
Help is very much appreciated. Thank you, 97Scape.
-&gt; (Sorry, forgot to add that I am using NullPkz Source!) &lt;-</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 02:07:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-lot-of-things-potion-and-emote-animation-related/400043.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help with a lot of things! (Potion and emote/animation related!)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@97Scape 97Scape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/97scape">@97Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, first off I would like to say that I have tried to resolve these by myself and have done many web searches. A huge problem why I can’t resolve this issue myself is because I am definitely a beginner and don’t have a huge amount of knowledge in Java though I understand the main and basic concepts of it. My problems are rooted in the animations and potions. When I do startAnimation(XXXX); or setAnimation(XXXX); to add the burying bones animation when you bury them nothing happens. You do get the exp for burying them and there is a message that shows up that says “You have buried “+name+” bones.” but that’s all. I may just not know the correct way to call and animation but I would like some kind of feed back on this. Another issue is that this source does not have a “Potions.java” and a lot of threads and web search results had answers revolving around that. There is some scrappy code for potions, food, and bones, but none of that even works (they are in client.java). Potions just say “Nothing interesting happened.” Food is okay. Some of it works but I have no clue where it calls the animations since the code inside of “Client.java” just has the healing stats. I have looked all over the server source and can’t find a thing to help. Is this a client sided issue? (If it is then I am really stupid because I just thought of that while I was typing this :P).<br>
Help is very much appreciated. Thank you, 97Scape.<br>
-&gt; (Sorry, forgot to add that I am using NullPkz Source!) &lt;-</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-lot-of-things-potion-and-emote-animation-related/400043/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-lot-of-things-potion-and-emote-animation-related/400043/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 02:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-400043-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-lot-of-things-potion-and-emote-animation-related/400043.rss">Need help with a lot of things! (Potion and emote/animation related!)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
