<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Client cut off?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-cut-off/314513</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve edited my client many times, and i know how to change the size and various other things...it&#39;s just that for some reason when i run my client on my server it cuts off things on the left, like parts of names when people talk, and things in the top left corner like names of objects and npcs when you mouseover them. And i&#39;ve seen on other servers when you log in with their clients those things aren&#39;t cut off, and the hits,coords,prayer,etc information is further to the right then mine...I&#39;ve been trying to fix this but i can&#39;t find how. Anyone have any idea what to do? I&#39;m using default client size btw.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2009 23:04:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-cut-off/314513.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Client cut off?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spyke8x Spyke8x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spyke8x">@Spyke8x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve edited my client many times, and i know how to change the size and various other things…it’s just that for some reason when i run my client on my server it cuts off things on the left, like parts of names when people talk, and things in the top left corner like names of objects and npcs when you mouseover them. And i’ve seen on other servers when you log in with their clients those things aren’t cut off, and the hits,coords,prayer,etc information is further to the right then mine…I’ve been trying to fix this but i can’t find how. Anyone have any idea what to do? I’m using default client size btw.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-cut-off/314513/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-cut-off/314513/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2009 23:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-314513-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-cut-off/314513.rss">Client cut off?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
