<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466</link>
    <description>I thought this may be a cool idea to try out, with six years of professional web design on hand, I thought I would attempt to do this myself, considering the fact that I&#39;ve played Runescape quite a bit to re-create it in my browser. Before any confusion, this is NOT a private server, this is a clone / re-create of runescape that is in your browser. Most of us know the game, &quot;Mafia Wars&quot; that was primarily popular on Facebook about a year or two ago, right? That is a browser based MMORPG, some people also call these types of games, &quot;Text Based&quot; games. Before reading further please note the two things. To start, this is not coded in Java, i&#39;m using Html, CSS, Php, MySQL (Main coding languages for web development) and possible some javascript, which is somewhat java coding but different in many ways. And also, note that this isn&#39;t a private server, and this is going to take a while to complete. After its done and I open it in beta mode to about 50 users, i&#39;ll then get all of the bugs out that I can find, and then make the website easy to install for the average Joe, and hopefully release some tutorials on how to edit it. Once again, this is Text / Browser based, no java coding is used for this. 

Now, Moving on.. This thought randomly popped up a couple days ago and I thought it would be pretty cool to try out and see how it works out. I&#39;ve already started coding a few things, please keep in mind that i&#39;m doing everything from scratch, the log-in box looks exactly like runescape except it&#39;s in your browser, like this text that you&#39;re reading, you can click and drag your mouse over it and highlight the text. There will obviously be things that are different, it&#39;s physically impossible to re-create Runescape 2 without using any Java coding, i&#39;ll just throw that out there. The things you do in Runescape, you&#39;ll be able to do on here, in a mafia wars type theme, lets go through an example, front to back, lets say you want to train your woodcutting level..

You&#39;d click the spellbook on the right side of your screen, the minimap and inventory area acts like a minimap, and will follow you to every web page that you go to. Then click the teleport for skilling, you&#39;ll be presented with a short loading screen, and a teleporting &quot;.gif&quot; short animation will show, then you&#39;ll go the the webpage called &#39;skilling.php&#39;. From there, you&#39;ll see a screen with options for different skills, you&#39;d find the tree and click it which will redirect you to the &#39;woodcutting.php&#39; file of the website. On the woodcutting.php file you now need to do some type of work or something to actually get the logs, the logs are then put into your inventory, say the logs have an item id of 600, the .php file will store the log in your MySQL table for the user, under &quot;character_inventory_1&quot; and it will put 600 in the Item_ID column and 1 in the Amount column. Then this will connect with the inventory.php file and tell it to display all of the information in the character_inventory_1 slot and character_inventory_2 slot in the 2nd slot of the inventory, I want to have it set up so that getting a full inventory of logs will give you X Amount of xp per log, and it takes about 4 seconds per log. 

Explaining what i&#39;m working on is somewhat hard to do, you&#39;d have to see it to actually know what i&#39;m talking about, i&#39;ll post a test one in a couple days so that people can create accounts, log-in and possibly some other things. I&#39;ve been working on it for about three hours already, I have almost an exact clone of the log-in screen, the text is somewhat noticeably different, and i have a redirect after log-in page, you&#39;ll log in, and then be presented with a loading screen (what is the runescape loading screen when logging in, and it actually works), I have all of the mouse-overs working aswell, so when you hover your mouse over the log-in button, it will glow like it would in runescape. It&#39;s already set up in full screen and can easily support full screen, however, you can drag your web browser to make it different sizes and play at whatever size you&#39;d like. 

This isn&#39;t going to be all graphic fancy and such, considering the fact that at first i&#39;m recreating it, and making it playable before I worry about HD pictures, and also the fact that this isn&#39;t coded in java and everything is text/browser based. If you don&#39;t know what a browser based game is, you&#39;re really not going to get much of a concept of what i&#39;m talking about, and chances are you wont until I release a test to the community and have people register and log-in. As for now, I have two pictures, what you see in the pictures has taken me about four hours in total, and 35-45 lines of html code, 150 lines of CSS code, and about 250 lines of php code (for the log-in system), and 12 images have been used so far. This first image is the main screen you get when you first go to the website, this log-in screen is almost exact to the runescape log-in screen, yet the amazing thing is, I haven&#39;t used any java while doing so.

(The image is fairly large)
[IMG]http://i41.tinypic.com/2aka64j.png[/img]

Now, this second page is after you log-in and you&#39;re sent to this page, which displays a loading screen, after three seconds, you get redirected to the new page, where you can train skills and do other tasks in the game, pretty much everything that you can do in Runescape, here&#39;s the loading screen. 

(Once again ; Image is fairly large)
[IMG]http://i43.tinypic.com/351tqmx.png[/img]

After you logged in all that it says for now is, &quot;You have sucessfully logged in, &#39;USERNAME_HERE&#39; &quot; Just so that i know the script actually is working and everything is working now. Now I need to work on the page you&#39;re presented after you&#39;ve logged in, which will be a two column website base, with the sidebar in the right column (where the minimap, health, inventory, and other things are), and the game in the left column, where you&#39;ll be able to train the skills, do the quests, and where your bank will show up and what not. 

Today i&#39;m going to be focusing mainly on that third page after you&#39;ve logged in, primarily the side bar because that&#39;s probably one of the hardest thing to recreate, because there are about 200 active objects and links all in the sidebar, for different tabs, viewing skills, and using all of the teleports and the mage book, re-creating the teleport system will probably be one of the hardest things. You&#39;ll be re-directed to a page when you click a teleport and it will change the info in the MySQL database to say, &quot;Character_Location&quot; 1-50, if you teleport to varrock it may put Character_Location as 2, then the browser reads it and it will re-direct you to the correct page. 

I hope some of you will understand exactly what i&#39;m re-creating after i&#39;ve described it a bit, and hopefully you guys support me so that i can continue in my development, i&#39;m also currently looking for a Graphics Person that can help me along the way with some graphics, let me know if interested. I&#39;ll be updating soon with more posts and probably a test in a few days, so people can log-in and what not. Here two logs, the first one is what i&#39;ve already done, and the second one is some of what I hope to accomplish soon (list is as for now, the basic stuff)

(Completed so far) 
[code]
- Create a Log-in screen that is almost identical to Runescape.
- Make the Log-in script actually work.
- Create a three second loading screen after logging in.
- Re-direct to the new page saying, &quot; You&#39;ve Successfully logged in, USERNAME &quot;.
- Get most of the things mapped out for future work. 
- Clean stuff up with the code and scripts, to make it run faster.
- Set up Databases and prepare them for data. 
- Create a register script and register screen (30% done)
[/code]

(Still needs work, plan to complete soon)
[code]
- Sets all skills to one except hp when registering a new character.
- Create your own character after logging in for the first time.
- Have a quick tutorial after you log-in for the first time.
- Create the screen after you&#39;ve logged in, with the sidebar section.
- Code the sidebar, and make it run smoothly and match teleports accordingly.
- Create teleporting system for various places, and make sure it works.
- Re-Create Lumbridge, as the starting home area.
- Create a system for killing npcs, and make npcs take X amount of health.
- Add the first skills, probably Attack, Strength, Defence, and Health/Constitution.
- Create a minimap with arrows that you click to navigate
[/code]

Let me know what you think of my progress so far, and if you think i should continue with my work, keep in mind that I probably wont release this to the public to play for a couple months, considering the fact that i&#39;m only 14 and I have school and sports to worry about aswell. I&#39;ll be working on this with all if not, most of my free time. I also need a graphics designer, so if anyone is good with graphics let me know, i&#39;m also going to post some of my previous website related released that i&#39;ve done on Moparscape, to give you a better view that i&#39;m not joking around with this project, and I plan to get it done soon. 

[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,529925.msg3868525.html#msg3868525]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,529925.msg3868525.html#msg3868525[/url] (Social Network Project)
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537548.msg3930637.html#msg3930637]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537548.msg3930637.html#msg3930637[/url] (Blue Mystic Highscores Theme)
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537715.msg3933058.html#msg3933058]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537715.msg3933058.html#msg3933058[/url] (Orange Abstract Highscores Theme)
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,536919.msg3926149.html#msg3926149]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,536919.msg3926149.html#msg3926149[/url] (Tutorial for setting up forums/website)
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537738.msg3932511.html#msg3932511]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537738.msg3932511.html#msg3932511[/url] (Cracked Customizable Runescape Website)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 00:19:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Advocatus, post:24, topic:438466”]Imho this is idiotic and will fail. Reasons include lack of willing players, and also the illegality of the content which would prevent it from being used on high traffic sites.</p>
<p>Go ahead and prove me wrong though. Goodluck with this.[/quote]</p>
<p>I’m primarily doing it for fun, and may release it even when i’m done. I’m doing this because it has never been done before, and it would be cool to see something new.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 00:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Advocatus Advocatus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/advocatus">@Advocatus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Imho this is idiotic and will fail. Reasons include lack of willing players, and also the illegality of the content which would prevent it from being used on high traffic sites.</p>
<p>Go ahead and prove me wrong though. Goodluck with this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“luminance, post:12, topic:438466”][quote author=zyle1992 link=topic=541184.msg3968341#msg3968341 date=1333932736]<br>
Prepare for legal trouble.<br>
[/quote]This and are you going for the older version of runescape, or the current DEOB?[/quote]</p>
<p>This is my new account, seeing as my old one had been unrightfully banned by a moderator because I didn’t want to be web developer for his server (alrighty then)… I’m continuing with work and progress on this project though, and I’m going for it based somewhat off 2006  RS/317 Graphics. I’ll show a few pictures of the starting screen when it’s finished. Thanks for the Support everyone!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/23</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chillwitm888 chillwitm888]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chillwitm888">@chillwitm888</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have an urge to beta or try this out<br>
because I loved mafia wars</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 22:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“runescape sucks, post:18, topic:438466”][quote author=Kidpaparoach link=topic=541184.msg3969414#msg3969414 date=1334016917]<br>
Sounds amazing but unneeded.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Is any project really needed?[/quote]<br>
lol, not even worth the effort of explaining to you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 21:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Daginith Daginith]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/daginith">@Daginith</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In theory is sounds amazing, if you do it right.<br>
Good luck pulling this off.</p>
<p>Also,</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="14" data-topic="438466">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/zyle1992/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> zyle1992:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Text based or not, you can still get into legal trouble. Especially for using their COPYRIGHTED images.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>8/10 people on this site could get into legal trouble for the same thing. But no one ever thinks twice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 05:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kronixz kronikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kronixz">@kronixz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 03:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="17" data-topic="438466">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kidpaparoach/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Kidpaparoach:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sounds amazing but unneeded.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Is any project really needed?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 03:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds amazing but unneeded.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I understood it as which version OP is creating (317 graphics, 508, ***, etc)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 00:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chillwitm888 chillwitm888]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chillwitm888">@chillwitm888</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="14" data-topic="438466">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/zyle1992/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> zyle1992:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Text based or not, you can still get into legal trouble. Especially for using their COPYRIGHTED images.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No I mean he IS asking what deob this is.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 21:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Text based or not, you can still get into legal trouble. Especially for using their COPYRIGHTED images.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 21:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chillwitm888 chillwitm888]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chillwitm888">@chillwitm888</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“luminance, post:12, topic:438466”][quote author=zyle1992 link=topic=541184.msg3968341#msg3968341 date=1333932736]<br>
Prepare for legal trouble.<br>
[/quote]This and are you going for the older version of runescape, or the current DEOB?[/quote]<br>
ITS TEXT based</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 21:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@luminance luminance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/luminance">@luminance</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“zyle1992, post:11, topic:438466”]Prepare for legal trouble.[/quote]This and are you going for the older version of runescape, or the current DEOB?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 02:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Prepare for legal trouble.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“EclipseRuins, post:9, topic:438466”]I’d like to thank everyone for their input and encouragement with this project, i’m also glad to announce that i’ve gone a step further, after logging in and everything, i’ve almost got a working inventory system, along with the sidebar section of runescape, after getting this to work, i’m going to work and make sure that users get starting items, after setting the inventory up to align everything to a 4x7 table, creating a working 28-slot inventory system, and give users initial starter items.</p>
<p>Then next, i’ll work on adding all items, or atleast the majorly important ones, about 700-800 items will be added soon and each given their own item id, and working functions.</p>
<p>I’ll let you guys know when i get something else majorly done, thanks everyone - EclipseRuins[/quote]<br>
This is very nice, but I have a question. Couldn’t people just press View Page Source and get your work?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EclipseRuins EclipseRuins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eclipseruins">@EclipseRuins</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d like to thank everyone for their input and encouragement with this project, i’m also glad to announce that i’ve gone a step further, after logging in and everything, i’ve almost got a working inventory system, along with the sidebar section of runescape, after getting this to work, i’m going to work and make sure that users get starting items, after setting the inventory up to align everything to a 4x7 table, creating a working 28-slot inventory system, and give users initial starter items.</p>
<p>Then next, i’ll work on adding all items, or atleast the majorly important ones, about 700-800 items will be added soon and each given their own item id, and working functions.</p>
<p>I’ll let you guys know when i get something else majorly done, thanks everyone - EclipseRuins</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 23:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Support fully, If i could code Html, CSS, Php, MySQL, or javascript I would try to offer my best help.</p>
<p>But supporting is all I can do <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 04:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fakee Fakee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fakee">@Fakee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great Job hope to play this sometime in the future!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 03:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck with this project, if you put this amount of effort into the description of the project, then you must be putting a lot of effort into creating this unique game.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 03:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Somebody did some stuff with php a while back… I thought it was a kewl project. I suggest you look for it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 00:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scarecrows Scarecrows]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scarecrows">@Scarecrows</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Interesting. I like unique ideas. I can’t wait to see how this works out. Either really bad or really good. Hopefully the latter.</p>
<p>Impressive.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 23:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EclipseRuins EclipseRuins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eclipseruins">@EclipseRuins</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ix Soulcist xI, post:2, topic:438466”]This has to be the longest development I’ve read in some time. I can see that at least SOME if not a lot of effort was put into this. I’ll be checking this over from time-to-time.</p>
<p>Good luck with the development![/quote]</p>
<p>Yeah, only took 20 or so minutes to write up though, thanks for the support.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 14:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This has to be the longest development I’ve read in some time. I can see that at least SOME if not a lot of effort was put into this. I’ll be checking this over from time-to-time.</p>
<p>Good luck with the development!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 14:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EclipseRuins EclipseRuins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eclipseruins">@EclipseRuins</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I thought this may be a cool idea to try out, with six years of professional web design on hand, I thought I would attempt to do this myself, considering the fact that I’ve played Runescape quite a bit to re-create it in my browser. Before any confusion, this is NOT a private server, this is a clone / re-create of runescape that is in your browser. Most of us know the game, “Mafia Wars” that was primarily popular on Facebook about a year or two ago, right? That is a browser based MMORPG, some people also call these types of games, “Text Based” games. Before reading further please note the two things. To start, this is not coded in Java, i’m using Html, CSS, Php, MySQL (Main coding languages for web development) and possible some javascript, which is somewhat java coding but different in many ways. And also, note that this isn’t a private server, and this is going to take a while to complete. After its done and I open it in beta mode to about 50 users, i’ll then get all of the bugs out that I can find, and then make the website easy to install for the average Joe, and hopefully release some tutorials on how to edit it. Once again, this is Text / Browser based, no java coding is used for this.</p>
<p>Now, Moving on… This thought randomly popped up a couple days ago and I thought it would be pretty cool to try out and see how it works out. I’ve already started coding a few things, please keep in mind that i’m doing everything from scratch, the log-in box looks exactly like runescape except it’s in your browser, like this text that you’re reading, you can click and drag your mouse over it and highlight the text. There will obviously be things that are different, it’s physically impossible to re-create Runescape 2 without using any Java coding, i’ll just throw that out there. The things you do in Runescape, you’ll be able to do on here, in a mafia wars type theme, lets go through an example, front to back, lets say you want to train your woodcutting level…</p>
<p>You’d click the spellbook on the right side of your screen, the minimap and inventory area acts like a minimap, and will follow you to every web page that you go to. Then click the teleport for skilling, you’ll be presented with a short loading screen, and a teleporting “.gif” short animation will show, then you’ll go the the webpage called ‘skilling.php’. From there, you’ll see a screen with options for different skills, you’d find the tree and click it which will redirect you to the ‘woodcutting.php’ file of the website. On the woodcutting.php file you now need to do some type of work or something to actually get the logs, the logs are then put into your inventory, say the logs have an item id of 600, the .php file will store the log in your MySQL table for the user, under “character_inventory_1” and it will put 600 in the Item_ID column and 1 in the Amount column. Then this will connect with the inventory.php file and tell it to display all of the information in the character_inventory_1 slot and character_inventory_2 slot in the 2nd slot of the inventory, I want to have it set up so that getting a full inventory of logs will give you X Amount of xp per log, and it takes about 4 seconds per log.</p>
<p>Explaining what i’m working on is somewhat hard to do, you’d have to see it to actually know what i’m talking about, i’ll post a test one in a couple days so that people can create accounts, log-in and possibly some other things. I’ve been working on it for about three hours already, I have almost an exact clone of the log-in screen, the text is somewhat noticeably different, and i have a redirect after log-in page, you’ll log in, and then be presented with a loading screen (what is the runescape loading screen when logging in, and it actually works), I have all of the mouse-overs working aswell, so when you hover your mouse over the log-in button, it will glow like it would in runescape. It’s already set up in full screen and can easily support full screen, however, you can drag your web browser to make it different sizes and play at whatever size you’d like.</p>
<p>This isn’t going to be all graphic fancy and such, considering the fact that at first i’m recreating it, and making it playable before I worry about HD pictures, and also the fact that this isn’t coded in java and everything is text/browser based. If you don’t know what a browser based game is, you’re really not going to get much of a concept of what i’m talking about, and chances are you wont until I release a test to the community and have people register and log-in. As for now, I have two pictures, what you see in the pictures has taken me about four hours in total, and 35-45 lines of html code, 150 lines of CSS code, and about 250 lines of php code (for the log-in system), and 12 images have been used so far. This first image is the main screen you get when you first go to the website, this log-in screen is almost exact to the runescape log-in screen, yet the amazing thing is, I haven’t used any java while doing so.</p>
<p>(The image is fairly large)<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i41.tinypic.com/2aka64j.png" title="2aka64j.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/2aka64j.png" alt width="690" height="367"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2aka64j.png</span><span class="informations">1368×729</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Now, this second page is after you log-in and you’re sent to this page, which displays a loading screen, after three seconds, you get redirected to the new page, where you can train skills and do other tasks in the game, pretty much everything that you can do in Runescape, here’s the loading screen.</p>
<p>(Once again ; Image is fairly large)<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i43.tinypic.com/351tqmx.png" title="351tqmx.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i43.tinypic.com/351tqmx.png" alt width="690" height="381"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">351tqmx.png</span><span class="informations">1355×750</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>After you logged in all that it says for now is, "You have sucessfully logged in, ‘USERNAME_HERE’ " Just so that i know the script actually is working and everything is working now. Now I need to work on the page you’re presented after you’ve logged in, which will be a two column website base, with the sidebar in the right column (where the minimap, health, inventory, and other things are), and the game in the left column, where you’ll be able to train the skills, do the quests, and where your bank will show up and what not.</p>
<p>Today i’m going to be focusing mainly on that third page after you’ve logged in, primarily the side bar because that’s probably one of the hardest thing to recreate, because there are about 200 active objects and links all in the sidebar, for different tabs, viewing skills, and using all of the teleports and the mage book, re-creating the teleport system will probably be one of the hardest things. You’ll be re-directed to a page when you click a teleport and it will change the info in the MySQL database to say, “Character_Location” 1-50, if you teleport to varrock it may put Character_Location as 2, then the browser reads it and it will re-direct you to the correct page.</p>
<p>I hope some of you will understand exactly what i’m re-creating after i’ve described it a bit, and hopefully you guys support me so that i can continue in my development, i’m also currently looking for a Graphics Person that can help me along the way with some graphics, let me know if interested. I’ll be updating soon with more posts and probably a test in a few days, so people can log-in and what not. Here two logs, the first one is what i’ve already done, and the second one is some of what I hope to accomplish soon (list is as for now, the basic stuff)</p>
<p>(Completed so far)</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">- Create a Log-in screen that is almost identical to Runescape.
- Make the Log-in script actually work.
- Create a three second loading screen after logging in.
- Re-direct to the new page saying, " You've Successfully logged in, USERNAME ".
- Get most of the things mapped out for future work. 
- Clean stuff up with the code and scripts, to make it run faster.
- Set up Databases and prepare them for data. 
- Create a register script and register screen (30% done)</code></pre>
<p>(Still needs work, plan to complete soon)</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">- Sets all skills to one except hp when registering a new character.
- Create your own character after logging in for the first time.
- Have a quick tutorial after you log-in for the first time.
- Create the screen after you've logged in, with the sidebar section.
- Code the sidebar, and make it run smoothly and match teleports accordingly.
- Create teleporting system for various places, and make sure it works.
- Re-Create Lumbridge, as the starting home area.
- Create a system for killing npcs, and make npcs take X amount of health.
- Add the first skills, probably Attack, Strength, Defence, and Health/Constitution.
- Create a minimap with arrows that you click to navigate</code></pre>
<p>Let me know what you think of my progress so far, and if you think i should continue with my work, keep in mind that I probably wont release this to the public to play for a couple months, considering the fact that i’m only 14 and I have school and sports to worry about aswell. I’ll be working on this with all if not, most of my free time. I also need a graphics designer, so if anyone is good with graphics let me know, i’m also going to post some of my previous website related released that i’ve done on Moparscape, to give you a better view that i’m not joking around with this project, and I plan to get it done soon.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,529925.msg3868525.html#msg3868525" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,529925.msg3868525.html#msg3868525</a> (Social Network Project)<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537548.msg3930637.html#msg3930637" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537548.msg3930637.html#msg3930637</a> (Blue Mystic Highscores Theme)<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537715.msg3933058.html#msg3933058" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537715.msg3933058.html#msg3933058</a> (Orange Abstract Highscores Theme)<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,536919.msg3926149.html#msg3926149" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,536919.msg3926149.html#msg3926149</a> (Tutorial for setting up forums/website)<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537738.msg3932511.html#msg3932511" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,537738.msg3932511.html#msg3932511</a> (Cracked Customizable Runescape Website)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 13:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-438466-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/re-creating-runescape-2-browser-text-based/438466.rss">Re-Creating Runescape 2 [Browser/Text Based]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
