<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server activating. help me!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-activating-help-me/247969</link>
    <description>please someone help me when i double-click runserver a window pops up and very quickly closes that even when i hold the enter button i still cant read it
but by luck and my 1000th shot i got a pic
[IMG]http://i33.tinypic.com/2hhpsg0.jpg[/img]
plz help me i&#39;ve done EVERYTHING
latest java
enviremental variables
im using a router and i succesfully completed portforwarding
NOW IDK WHAT TO DO PLEASE HELP[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 01, 2008, 05:33:43 pm[/size][hr] 
BTW i&#39;ve realized that this error pops up everytime i set my &quot;variables&quot; i go to java.com, verify my installation, and it says
&quot;congratulations, you have the latest java installed to your computer&quot; but when i go THROUGH my compiler there&#39;s &quot;press r to run your server&quot; when i type r in the black box, it says &quot;you do not have JDK v.6.0 or JDK v.5.0 installed to your computer, please go to mod taharok&#39;s tutorial on the moparscape tutorial section for step-by-step instructions, link to java.&quot;
&quot;press any key to continue...&quot;
But when i driectly double-click &quot;runserver&quot; OR &quot;copy of runserver&quot; it just opens a box and VERY QUICKLY closes it.
and i&#39;ve also realized that everytime i Recover my pc, install java,i&#39;m able to play any private servers on my computer.
So its the variables i GUESS, i have JDK version 6 update 10, someone please give me a right enviremental variables. 


Thanks,
Sencerely,
Zubei</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 05:51:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-activating-help-me/247969.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server activating. help me!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zubei Zubei]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zubei">@Zubei</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>please someone help me when i double-click runserver a window pops up and very quickly closes that even when i hold the enter button i still cant read it<br>
but by luck and my 1000th shot i got a pic<br>
<img src="http://i33.tinypic.com/2hhpsg0.jpg" alt width="140" height="120"><br>
plz help me i’ve done EVERYTHING<br>
latest java<br>
enviremental variables<br>
im using a router and i succesfully completed portforwarding<br>
NOW IDK WHAT TO DO PLEASE HELP[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 01, 2008, 05:33:43 pm[/size][hr]<br>
BTW i’ve realized that this error pops up everytime i set my “variables” i go to <a href="http://java.com" rel="nofollow noopener">java.com</a>, verify my installation, and it says<br>
“congratulations, you have the latest java installed to your computer” but when i go THROUGH my compiler there’s “press r to run your server” when i type r in the black box, it says “you do not have JDK v.6.0 or JDK v.5.0 installed to your computer, please go to mod taharok’s tutorial on the moparscape tutorial section for step-by-step instructions, link to java.”<br>
“press any key to continue…”<br>
But when i driectly double-click “runserver” OR “copy of runserver” it just opens a box and VERY QUICKLY closes it.<br>
and i’ve also realized that everytime i Recover my pc, install java,i’m able to play any private servers on my computer.<br>
So its the variables i GUESS, i have JDK version 6 update 10, someone please give me a right enviremental variables.</p>
<p>Thanks,<br>
Sencerely,<br>
Zubei</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-activating-help-me/247969/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-activating-help-me/247969/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 05:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-247969-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-activating-help-me/247969.rss">Server activating. help me!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
