<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744</link>
    <description>This is just a compilation of ideas that I had thought of while reading through the development threads. These ideas are completely public, and are given for everyone to use. Just give me credits if you do use these. ;)

I will continue to update this thread with ideas sent to me and ideas that I happen to just think up of.

[center]---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------[/center]
[center][u]Minigames[/u][/center]

1. [u]Backyard Frenzy[/u]
&lt;blockquote&gt;[u][b]Location: Castle Wars[/b][/u]

[b][u]The Objective:[/u][/b] 
[ul][li]The zombies have invaded your neighboring armory! You have to stop them before they take over your last resource stop, and time is running out! You have 10 minutes to kill as many zombies as you can.[/li][/ul]


[b][u]The Resources:[/u][/b] 
[ul]You are provided with resources to help you overcome the zombie invasion. You must use these to your advantage, and only time will tell who will prevail.
[list][li][u]Healing Kits[/u] - These kits will heal just about any illness and injury you can imagine. Things such as poison, cuts, scratches, and even broken limbs are no match against the abilities of these. Using the castle wars bandages as the model, these kits heal poison, give a 5% hunger boost, and heal 10/99 hp.[/li]
[li][u]Explosive Potions[/u] - These remarkable weapons blow up just about anything that manages to put foot on them. When dropped, you have 5 seconds to *[i]run[/i]* before these self-destruct, inflicting 20/99 damage on anything within a 7x7 range. These use the castle wars explosive potion as the model.[/li]
[li][u]Pickaxes[/u] - These are useful when trying to dig through the underground tunnels. Because of the reckless nature of zombies, there have been many collapsed passageways under your armories and supply castle. These miraculous items have a 75% chance of breaking through each individual collapsed passage, and a 25% of breaking due to not digging through. One can only hold 3 pickaxes at one time.[/li]
[li][u] Barricades[/u] - Zombies are stupid. So stupid, in fact, that a simple wooden barricade is enough to temporarily stand in their way of getting any further. When placed, zombies are able to attack them, and set them on fire. Only 10 barricades can be placed at one time.[/li]
[li][u] Rocks/Catapult[/u] - Ever wondered what it would be like to crush a zombie with some 50 pound rocks? Well, now you can! The catapult can be upgraded to three different tiers, with each tier being able to hold heavier rocks with a wider range of damage.
[list][li]Tier 1:[/li][/list] - The first catapult tier can hold 25-pound stones. These stones inflict 10 damage to all enemies within a 5x5 range. [b]COST = 5 ZOMBIE KILLS[/b]
[list][li]Tier 2:[/li][/list] - The second catapult tier can hold 50-pound stones. These stones inflict 25 damage to all enemies within a 8x8 range. [b]COST = 10 ZOMBIE KILLS[/b] 
[list][li]Tier 3:[/li][/list] - The third, and strongest, catapult tier, can hold 100-pound boulders. These boulders inflict 50-75 damage to all enemies within a 10x10 range. [b]COST = 25 ZOMBIE KILLS[/b]
[/list]

[b][u]The Rewards:[/u][/b]
Should you manage to prevail over most, if not all, of the invading zombies, there are spoils to be rewarded.
[list]
[li][u]Prize One:[/u] - [b]PRICE = 20 INDIVIDUAL ZOMBIE KILLS[/b] [list type=decimal]
[li]10,000 gold coins to be spent however the victorious pleases[/li]
[li]The [i]Amateur Zombie Slaughterer[/i] cloak. This cloak provides the wearer a 5% slower hunger rate.[/li]
[/list][/li]
[li][u]Price Two:[/u] - [b]PRICE = 50 INDIVIDUAL ZOMBIE KILLS[/b] [list type=decimal]
[li]50,000 gold coins to be spent however the victorious pleases[/li]
[li]The [i]Boots of the Apocalypse[/i], which provide the wearer with a 10% slower hunger rate, and gives a 7% defense boost to the wearer.[/li]
[/list][/li]
[li][u]Price Three:[/u] - [b]PRICE = 100 INDIVIDUAL ZOMBIE KILLS[/b] 
This tier can only be given to the greatest of the apocalypse adventurers. To achieve this is to achieve true mastery in the art of zombie hunting.[list type=decimal]
[li]100,000 gold coins to be spent however the victorious pleases[/li]
[li]The [i]Amateur Zombie Slaughterer cloak, Boots of the Apocalypse, &amp; The Zombie Skin Outfit.[/i] The zombie skin outfit can be put to great use, as it gives the wearer the ability to overcome the aggressiveness of all zombies, and seem to fit in amongst them.[/li]
[/list][/list]&lt;/blockquote&gt;

[i]More Minigames to Come.[/i]
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
[center][u]Skills[/u][/center]
1. [u]Disintegration[/u]&lt;blockquote&gt;This ancient skill was rediscovered just recently, and can only be learnt by the most willing of adventurers. In order to begin this skill, one must speak with the Disintegration Grand Master, found only in his cave hidden in the wilderness, and meet all of the following requirements.

[b]Uses:[/b]
[list]
[li]Has that tree or fence ever gotten in your way? This skill exists because, sometimes, there isn&#39;t a short passage around it, and you don&#39;t have the patience to weave your way around the woods.[/li]
[/list]
[b]Requirements:[/b]
Due to this skill being quite useful in more ways than one, the adventure must have achieved more than average.
[list]
[li][u]Skills:[/u]
[list]
[li]At least level 99 in four skills, and 99 magic.[/li]
[/list][/li]
[li][u]Quests:[/u]
[list]
[li]At least 7 quests must be completed in order to begin practicing this skill.[/li]
[/list][/li]
[/list]
[b]Abilities and Required Levels:[/b]
[list][li][u]Level 1-15[/u][/li][/list] - The adventurer is able to [i]attempt[/i] to disintegrate through the common door and fence. Each disintegrated door gives the player 20 experience, while each disintegrated fence yields the player with 30 experience. There is only a 30% success rate for each time the skill is used.
[list][li][u]Level 15-30[/u][/li][/list] - The adventurer now has a 75% success rate of disintegrating the above objects. In addition, the player now has the option of disintegrating through walls and trees. Each disintegrated wall yields the user 120 experience, while each disintegrated tree gives 200 experience. There is only a 30% success rate for each time the skill is used.
[list][li][u]Level 30-45[/u][/li][/list] - The adventurer now has a 75% success rate of disintegrating the above objects. In addition, the player now has the option of disintegrating a 1x1 range path through water. Each 1x1 path created yields the player with 500 experience. There is only a 30% success rate for each time the skill is used.
[list][li][u]Level 45-80[/u][/li][/list] - The adventure now has a 80% chance of disintegrating trees, fences, walls, and doors. There is a 30% chance of carving 1x1 paths through water. Now, 5,000 experience is granted for every object successfully disintegrated. There are no new advances in the skill.
[list][li][u]Level 80-95[/u][/li][/list] - The adventurer now has a 90% chance of disintegrating through trees, fences, walls, and doors. There is a 50% chance of carving 1x1 paths through water. In addition, there is a chance of receiving random amount of gold coins from each object disintegrated. Now, 10,000 experience is granted for each object disintegrated.
[list][li][u]Level 99[/u][/li][/list] - True mastery of the skill is achieved. There is now a 95% chance of disintegrating through any object listed, and a 50% chance of receiving random amounts of gold coins from the skill. The skillcape can be retrieved through talking to the Disintegration Grand Master.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

[i]More Skills/Abilities to Come.[/i]
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
[center][u]Quests[/u][/center]
1. [u]Comeuppance of the King[/u] (could use a name suggestion)
&lt;blockquote&gt;[u]Storyline:[/u]
The dragons are invading the wilderness, and are quickly making their way into edgeville! It is now up to you, adventurer, to stop them from wrecking havoc all across Geilinor. Should you choose to embark on this quest, there are great rewards if you complete it.

[u]Difficulty: [/u]Epic

[u]Requirements:[/u]
[list]
[li][i]Recommended:[/i] [list]
[li]50+ defense[/li]
[li]30+ strength[/li]
[li]Good armour (preferably rune+)[/li]
[li]Anti-fire shield/Dragonfire shield[/li]
[/list]
[/list]
[li]Skills[/li]
[list]
[li]50+ Summoning[/li]
[li]75+ Thieving[/li]
[li]A combat level of at least 80[/li]
[/list][/ul]

[u]The Walkthrough:[/u]

[ol][li]To start the quest, talk to the warrior that is guarding the wilderness ditch. He will ask if you would like to assist him in fending off the recent invasion of dragons. Say yes, and he will tell you to report deeper into the wilderness to get your task.[/li]
[li]Near level 20 wilderness, you will see a cutscene in which a warrior defeats a dragon. When the cutscene ends, walk up to him, and say that the warrior guard sent you to him. He will tell you that your next task is to attempt to make negotiations with the King Black Dragon, who is the one responsible for the recent invasions.[/li]
[li]You must dwell even deeper into the wilderness now, where you will find the King Black Dragon&#39;s lair, which is being heavily guarded by the King Dragon&#39;s minions. You must be able to slay all three guards, who are level 60+. Upon killing the final dragon, a key will be dropped that will allow you to gain entrance to the King Black Dragon&#39;s lair.[/li]
[li]You will now enter the King Black Dragon&#39;s lair. Another cutscene occurs where you are spotted walking into the lair, and the King Black Dragon will ask in a very rude manner what you are doing infiltrating his lair. You will say that you have been sent by the Warriors of Edgeville to demand an answer as to why the dragons have been attacking the humans.[/li]
[li]The King Black Dragon will say that it is because the humans have stolen the egg of the King Black Dragon. You now ask that if you bring back the egg, will the King Black Dragon stop the attacks upon the humans? He will say yes.[/li]
[li]The King Black Dragon will send you back to the humans to retrieve his egg. Upon talking to the guard, you will discover that the egg was stolen by the humans, and was being hidden in the Varrock castle. The only way to get the egg is to talk the Varrock King into giving you the egg.[/li]
[li]You now must go to the King of Varrock and talk him into giving you the egg. He will not agree to give you the egg, as he sees it as a trophy to his royalty. He will, though, tell you that the egg in on the top floor of the castle, hidden in a chest.[/li]
[li]Venture to the top of the castle, and use your thieving skill to unlock the chest. When you open the chest, 2 guards will see you, and you must kill them in order to get the egg. The guards are both level 20.[/li]
[li]After killing the guards, take the egg and go back to edgeville.[/li]
[li]Now, travel back to the warrior guards and tell them you have the egg. Upon hearing this, the warrior will give you a quick teleport to the King Black Dragon&#39;s lair.[/li]
[li]When you give the King Black Dragon his egg, he will now say that he will kill you as vengeance for causing him so much trouble. Prepare for a boss fight![/li]
[li]Slay the King Black Dragon, and a cutscene will now occur in which the egg hatches, and a baby black dragon appears. Having seen you first, it will consider you its parent, and now be your familiar.[/li][/ol]


[u]The Rewards:[/u]

[ul][li]The black dragon familiar[/li]
[li]The [i]Dragon Kinship[/i] ring, which makes all dragons no longer aggressive to you[/li]
[li]100,000 gold coins[/li]
[li]An experience lamp granting 5,000 thieving experience[/li][/ul]&lt;/blockquote&gt;

[i]More Quests to Come.[/i]
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

I will add to this list as more ideas are presented to me and more have been thought up of. These ideas are open for everyone to use, just give me credits for the concepts if you use them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 16:47:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Teem_Rocket Teem_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teem_rocket">@Teem_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Digging this out of the grave just to say that this user is not/was not me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@strucker Strucker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/strucker">@strucker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You shouldn’t be given credit because you got that ideas from dev. threads however thanks. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> i will use the barricade one, i already had that in my mind.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 03:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Flame_, post:13, topic:479744”][quote author=sk8rdude461 link=topic=597979.msg4208828#msg4208828 date=1359270801]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Well, summoning is the same concept. There is a quest behind it, and afterwards you learn the skill. If you have an idea to make it less complicated, let me know.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Explain how I got 50 summoning without doing the quest…<br>
[/quote]<br>
Hax[/quote]<br>
Actually, I just used the SoF xp lamps to around 30, and just used charms from there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@luna-scape luna-scape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/luna-scape">@luna-scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Fridder, post:15, topic:479744”][quote author=luna-scape link=topic=597979.msg4209043#msg4209043 date=1359303826]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>this guy is exactly like team_rocket lol… hmmmmmmm</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[/quote]</p>
<p>Luna-scape to the rescue! Thank you for clearing things up for us.</p>
<p>Don’t bother replying, I already know what you’re going to say:</p>
<p>[quote author=luna-scape link=topic=598229.msg4209042#msg4209042 date=1359303642]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>lol</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[/quote][/quote]<br>
Lolled Bout that</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 20:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“luna-scape, post:14, topic:479744”][quote author=Clawz fury link=topic=597979.msg4207893#msg4207893 date=1359171671]<br>
this guy is exactly like team_rocket lol… hmmmmmmm<br>
[/quote][/quote]</p>
<p>Luna-scape to the rescue! Thank you for clearing things up for us.</p>
<p>Don’t bother replying, I already know what you’re going to say:</p>
<p>[quote=“luna-scape, post:14, topic:479993”][quote author=Ashley link=topic=598229.msg4208414#msg4208414 date=1359238477]<br>
lol<br>
[/quote][/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 16:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@luna-scape luna-scape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/luna-scape">@luna-scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="479744">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Clawz fury:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this guy is exactly like team_rocket lol… hmmmmmmm</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 16:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <ul>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="10" data-topic="479744">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Flame_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Well, summoning is the same concept. There is a quest behind it, and afterwards you learn the skill. If you have an idea to make it less complicated, let me know.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Explain how I got 50 summoning without doing the quest…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 07:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kodiak Kodiak]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kodiak">@Kodiak</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>why did you put your name in the title</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 04:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, summoning is the same concept. There is a quest behind it, and afterwards you learn the skill. If you have an idea to make it less complicated, let me know.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 16:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Int_Bauk Int Bauk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/int_bauk">@Int_Bauk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you don’t need a storyline and all this nuisance for a skill…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 16:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Could name it Draconic Invasion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 15:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll think up of a storyline for it, then.<br>
EDIT: Naw, I’d rather have a submitted one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 12:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Int_Bauk Int Bauk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/int_bauk">@Int_Bauk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>all gay, this isn’t some WoW private server matey.</p>
<p>Disintegration skill sounds more like a quest because you need requirements (skills and quests) to use it or w/e</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 11:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="479744">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/asshole_rule/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> asshole_rule:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>team rocket is a faggot</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>l0l</p>
<p><span class="mention">@thread</span>: actually some nice ideas up here</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 05:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>team rocket is a faggot</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="479744">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Clawz fury:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>this guy is exactly like team_rocket lol… hmmmmmmm</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You are the 2[sup]nd[/sup] person to have said that to me. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="1983" data-topic="338845">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kodiak/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-are-you-listening-to/338845/1983">What are you listening to..?</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just curious, you joined on the 6th and want TR for server helper badge? A little suspicious.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 03:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this guy is exactly like team_rocket lol… hmmmmmmm</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 03:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is just a compilation of ideas that I had thought of while reading through the development threads. These ideas are completely public, and are given for everyone to use. Just give me credits if you do use these. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I will continue to update this thread with ideas sent to me and ideas that I happen to just think up of.</p>
<p>[center]---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------[/center]<br>
[center]<span class="bbcode-u">Minigames</span>[/center]</p>
<ol>
<li><span class="bbcode-u">Backyard Frenzy</span></li>
</ol>
<blockquote>[u][b]Location: Castle Wars[/b][/u]
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">The Objective:</span></span><br>
[ul][li]The zombies have invaded your neighboring armory! You have to stop them before they take over your last resource stop, and time is running out! You have 10 minutes to kill as many zombies as you can.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">The Resources:</span></span><br>
[ul]You are provided with resources to help you overcome the zombie invasion. You must use these to your advantage, and only time will tell who will prevail.<br>
[list][li]<span class="bbcode-u">Healing Kits</span> - These kits will heal just about any illness and injury you can imagine. Things such as poison, cuts, scratches, and even broken limbs are no match against the abilities of these. Using the castle wars bandages as the model, these kits heal poison, give a 5% hunger boost, and heal 10/99 hp.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">Explosive Potions</span> - These remarkable weapons blow up just about anything that manages to put foot on them. When dropped, you have 5 seconds to <em><span class="bbcode-i">run</span></em> before these self-destruct, inflicting 20/99 damage on anything within a 7x7 range. These use the castle wars explosive potion as the model.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">Pickaxes</span> - These are useful when trying to dig through the underground tunnels. Because of the reckless nature of zombies, there have been many collapsed passageways under your armories and supply castle. These miraculous items have a 75% chance of breaking through each individual collapsed passage, and a 25% of breaking due to not digging through. One can only hold 3 pickaxes at one time.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u"> Barricades</span> - Zombies are stupid. So stupid, in fact, that a simple wooden barricade is enough to temporarily stand in their way of getting any further. When placed, zombies are able to attack them, and set them on fire. Only 10 barricades can be placed at one time.[/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u"> Rocks/Catapult</span> - Ever wondered what it would be like to crush a zombie with some 50 pound rocks? Well, now you can! The catapult can be upgraded to three different tiers, with each tier being able to hold heavier rocks with a wider range of damage.<br>
[list][li]Tier 1:[/li][/list] - The first catapult tier can hold 25-pound stones. These stones inflict 10 damage to all enemies within a 5x5 range. <span class="bbcode-b">COST = 5 ZOMBIE KILLS</span><br>
[list][li]Tier 2:[/li][/list] - The second catapult tier can hold 50-pound stones. These stones inflict 25 damage to all enemies within a 8x8 range. <span class="bbcode-b">COST = 10 ZOMBIE KILLS</span><br>
[list][li]Tier 3:[/li][/list] - The third, and strongest, catapult tier, can hold 100-pound boulders. These boulders inflict 50-75 damage to all enemies within a 10x10 range. <span class="bbcode-b">COST = 25 ZOMBIE KILLS</span><br>
[/list]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">The Rewards:</span></span><br>
Should you manage to prevail over most, if not all, of the invading zombies, there are spoils to be rewarded.<br>
[list]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">Prize One:</span> - <span class="bbcode-b">PRICE = 20 INDIVIDUAL ZOMBIE KILLS</span> [list type=decimal]<br>
[li]10,000 gold coins to be spent however the victorious pleases[/li]<br>
[li]The <span class="bbcode-i">Amateur Zombie Slaughterer</span> cloak. This cloak provides the wearer a 5% slower hunger rate.[/li]<br>
[/list][/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">Price Two:</span> - <span class="bbcode-b">PRICE = 50 INDIVIDUAL ZOMBIE KILLS</span> [list type=decimal]<br>
[li]50,000 gold coins to be spent however the victorious pleases[/li]<br>
[li]The <span class="bbcode-i">Boots of the Apocalypse</span>, which provide the wearer with a 10% slower hunger rate, and gives a 7% defense boost to the wearer.[/li]<br>
[/list][/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">Price Three:</span> - <span class="bbcode-b">PRICE = 100 INDIVIDUAL ZOMBIE KILLS</span><br>
This tier can only be given to the greatest of the apocalypse adventurers. To achieve this is to achieve true mastery in the art of zombie hunting.[list type=decimal]<br>
[li]100,000 gold coins to be spent however the victorious pleases[/li]<br>
[li]The <span class="bbcode-i">Amateur Zombie Slaughterer cloak, Boots of the Apocalypse, &amp; The Zombie Skin Outfit.</span> The zombie skin outfit can be put to great use, as it gives the wearer the ability to overcome the aggressiveness of all zombies, and seem to fit in amongst them.[/li]<br>
[/list][/list]</p>
</blockquote>
<h2><span class="bbcode-i">More Minigames to Come.</span></h2>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u">Skills</span>[/center]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-u">Disintegration</span><blockquote>This ancient skill was rediscovered just recently, and can only be learnt by the most willing of adventurers. In order to begin this skill, one must speak with the Disintegration Grand Master, found only in his cave hidden in the wilderness, and meet all of the following requirements.</blockquote>
</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Uses:</span><br>
[list]<br>
[li]Has that tree or fence ever gotten in your way? This skill exists because, sometimes, there isn’t a short passage around it, and you don’t have the patience to weave your way around the woods.[/li]<br>
[/list]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Requirements:</span><br>
Due to this skill being quite useful in more ways than one, the adventure must have achieved more than average.<br>
[list]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">Skills:</span><br>
[list]<br>
[li]At least level 99 in four skills, and 99 magic.[/li]<br>
[/list][/li]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-u">Quests:</span><br>
[list]<br>
[li]At least 7 quests must be completed in order to begin practicing this skill.[/li]<br>
[/list][/li]<br>
[/list]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Abilities and Required Levels:</span><br>
[list][li]<span class="bbcode-u">Level 1-15</span>[/li][/list] - The adventurer is able to <span class="bbcode-i">attempt</span> to disintegrate through the common door and fence. Each disintegrated door gives the player 20 experience, while each disintegrated fence yields the player with 30 experience. There is only a 30% success rate for each time the skill is used.<br>
[list][li]<span class="bbcode-u">Level 15-30</span>[/li][/list] - The adventurer now has a 75% success rate of disintegrating the above objects. In addition, the player now has the option of disintegrating through walls and trees. Each disintegrated wall yields the user 120 experience, while each disintegrated tree gives 200 experience. There is only a 30% success rate for each time the skill is used.<br>
[list][li]<span class="bbcode-u">Level 30-45</span>[/li][/list] - The adventurer now has a 75% success rate of disintegrating the above objects. In addition, the player now has the option of disintegrating a 1x1 range path through water. Each 1x1 path created yields the player with 500 experience. There is only a 30% success rate for each time the skill is used.<br>
[list][li]<span class="bbcode-u">Level 45-80</span>[/li][/list] - The adventure now has a 80% chance of disintegrating trees, fences, walls, and doors. There is a 30% chance of carving 1x1 paths through water. Now, 5,000 experience is granted for every object successfully disintegrated. There are no new advances in the skill.<br>
[list][li]<span class="bbcode-u">Level 80-95</span>[/li][/list] - The adventurer now has a 90% chance of disintegrating through trees, fences, walls, and doors. There is a 50% chance of carving 1x1 paths through water. In addition, there is a chance of receiving random amount of gold coins from each object disintegrated. Now, 10,000 experience is granted for each object disintegrated.<br>
[list][li]<span class="bbcode-u">Level 99</span>[/li][/list] - True mastery of the skill is achieved. There is now a 95% chance of disintegrating through any object listed, and a 50% chance of receiving random amounts of gold coins from the skill. The skillcape can be retrieved through talking to the Disintegration Grand Master.</p>
<h2><span class="bbcode-i">More Skills/Abilities to Come.</span></h2>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u">Quests</span>[/center]</p>
<ol>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-u">Comeuppance of the King</span> (could use a name suggestion)</li>
</ol>
<blockquote>[u]Storyline:[/u]
The dragons are invading the wilderness, and are quickly making their way into edgeville! It is now up to you, adventurer, to stop them from wrecking havoc all across Geilinor. Should you choose to embark on this quest, there are great rewards if you complete it.
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Difficulty: </span>Epic</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">Requirements:</span><br>
[list]<br>
[li]<span class="bbcode-i">Recommended:</span> [list]<br>
[li]50+ defense[/li]<br>
[li]30+ strength[/li]<br>
[li]Good armour (preferably rune+)[/li]<br>
[li]Anti-fire shield/Dragonfire shield[/li]<br>
[/list]<br>
[/list]<br>
[li]Skills[/li]<br>
[list]<br>
[li]50+ Summoning[/li]<br>
[li]75+ Thieving[/li]<br>
[li]A combat level of at least 80[/li]<br>
[/list][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">The Walkthrough:</span></p>
<p>[ol][li]To start the quest, talk to the warrior that is guarding the wilderness ditch. He will ask if you would like to assist him in fending off the recent invasion of dragons. Say yes, and he will tell you to report deeper into the wilderness to get your task.[/li]<br>
[li]Near level 20 wilderness, you will see a cutscene in which a warrior defeats a dragon. When the cutscene ends, walk up to him, and say that the warrior guard sent you to him. He will tell you that your next task is to attempt to make negotiations with the King Black Dragon, who is the one responsible for the recent invasions.[/li]<br>
[li]You must dwell even deeper into the wilderness now, where you will find the King Black Dragon’s lair, which is being heavily guarded by the King Dragon’s minions. You must be able to slay all three guards, who are level 60+. Upon killing the final dragon, a key will be dropped that will allow you to gain entrance to the King Black Dragon’s lair.[/li]<br>
[li]You will now enter the King Black Dragon’s lair. Another cutscene occurs where you are spotted walking into the lair, and the King Black Dragon will ask in a very rude manner what you are doing infiltrating his lair. You will say that you have been sent by the Warriors of Edgeville to demand an answer as to why the dragons have been attacking the humans.[/li]<br>
[li]The King Black Dragon will say that it is because the humans have stolen the egg of the King Black Dragon. You now ask that if you bring back the egg, will the King Black Dragon stop the attacks upon the humans? He will say yes.[/li]<br>
[li]The King Black Dragon will send you back to the humans to retrieve his egg. Upon talking to the guard, you will discover that the egg was stolen by the humans, and was being hidden in the Varrock castle. The only way to get the egg is to talk the Varrock King into giving you the egg.[/li]<br>
[li]You now must go to the King of Varrock and talk him into giving you the egg. He will not agree to give you the egg, as he sees it as a trophy to his royalty. He will, though, tell you that the egg in on the top floor of the castle, hidden in a chest.[/li]<br>
[li]Venture to the top of the castle, and use your thieving skill to unlock the chest. When you open the chest, 2 guards will see you, and you must kill them in order to get the egg. The guards are both level 20.[/li]<br>
[li]After killing the guards, take the egg and go back to edgeville.[/li]<br>
[li]Now, travel back to the warrior guards and tell them you have the egg. Upon hearing this, the warrior will give you a quick teleport to the King Black Dragon’s lair.[/li]<br>
[li]When you give the King Black Dragon his egg, he will now say that he will kill you as vengeance for causing him so much trouble. Prepare for a boss fight![/li]<br>
[li]Slay the King Black Dragon, and a cutscene will now occur in which the egg hatches, and a baby black dragon appears. Having seen you first, it will consider you its parent, and now be your familiar.[/li][/ol]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">The Rewards:</span></p>
<p>[ul][li]The black dragon familiar[/li]<br>
[li]The <span class="bbcode-i">Dragon Kinship</span> ring, which makes all dragons no longer aggressive to you[/li]<br>
[li]100,000 gold coins[/li]<br>
[li]An experience lamp granting 5,000 thieving experience[/li][/ul]</p>
</blockquote>
<h2><span class="bbcode-i">More Quests to Come.</span></h2>
<p>I will add to this list as more ideas are presented to me and more have been thought up of. These ideas are open for everyone to use, just give me credits for the concepts if you use them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 03:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-479744-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/flame--creative-server-concepts/479744.rss">[Flame_] Creative Server Concepts</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
