<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server Advertisement Approval</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200</link>
    <description>It&#39;s been two months, an application I had made for a chance to even bid for my server hasn&#39;t be reviewed. I&#39;ve lost another month of possible advertisement. I&#39;ve contacted staff but to no avail, they don&#39;t respond. It&#39;s apparent they don&#39;t respond to server applicant needs, and I get that, but if you are going to go down that road, than the least you can do is review the applications in the sections that require assistance every couple days. Or, since moparscape barely meets 10 sponsors a month anymore, you could have an automatic bidding system that allows members that have met certain requirements to bid automatically than have this old style of review and pass. Im sick and tired of being overlooked by the staff, I want to see something done. Everyone says this community is different than Rune-Server, and Runelocus but i&#39;m beginning to see no difference.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 06:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server Advertisement Approval</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All is well now I assume? If you have any problems that require help from an admin then message me and I will forward it to Tom. For future reference it would be nice if you could message any sort of moderator and if they cannot resolve the problem I’d assume they will forward the message right to an admin.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 06:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535200-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200.rss">Server Advertisement Approval</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server Advertisement Approval</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Veldahar Veldahar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/veldahar">@Veldahar</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you for the informative reply but to be quite frank with you, I quickly noticed after creating the thread that I was approved. To be quite honest, I guess I was wrong about the functionality of this community. Truly impressed by the response time and cooperation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 05:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535200-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200.rss">Server Advertisement Approval</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server Advertisement Approval</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m pretty sure that MITB is the ONLY person that can approve servers and accept the money that comes through so that it can be approved, not too sure - the best thing to do is to PM him, if he doesn’t answer then perhaps PM another administrator and have that one send it over to MITB. I doubt you’re being ignored unless you simply don’t meet the guidelines and they aren’t accepting it until you do, or they simply think you don’t deserve it through some sort-of measures, that’s all I can think of.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535200-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200.rss">Server Advertisement Approval</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server Advertisement Approval</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Veldahar Veldahar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/veldahar">@Veldahar</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s been two months, an application I had made for a chance to even bid for my server hasn’t be reviewed. I’ve lost another month of possible advertisement. I’ve contacted staff but to no avail, they don’t respond. It’s apparent they don’t respond to server applicant needs, and I get that, but if you are going to go down that road, than the least you can do is review the applications in the sections that require assistance every couple days. Or, since moparscape barely meets 10 sponsors a month anymore, you could have an automatic bidding system that allows members that have met certain requirements to bid automatically than have this old style of review and pass. Im sick and tired of being overlooked by the staff, I want to see something done. Everyone says this community is different than Rune-Server, and Runelocus but i’m beginning to see no difference.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 05:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535200-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-advertisement-approval/535200.rss">Server Advertisement Approval</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
