<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Some unique ideas</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230</link>
    <description>Well as I don&#39;t program anymore I am going to post some of my ideas in here and if anybody wishes to use them/make them/whatever feel free to!

[b]-Terrain effects. Let&#39;s say for example you are mining in alkirahd mine. Because it&#39;s hot, sand around you , etc  then you can&#39;t mine as fast and your backpack is heavier. perhaps you can&#39;t add as many items into your inventory.[/b]

Now... keep in mind I am very skiller oriented so you won&#39;t see any combat stuff on here most likely now I will go into more specific skills.

[b]-Agility:[/b] Instead of making it  where you can  run for a longer period of time make it so it  co-resides with terrain effects. You aren&#39;t affected as bad  when your in the desert carrying stuff, it also makes it so while in combat your able to evade special attacks a little better.

[b]-Mining:[/b] Well instead of using a pickaxe, consider it like explosives! You have a rock that has ore in it. You make an explosive potion (could use a few herbs or leaves from different quests! ) and like you &quot;pour&quot; the potion over the rock. Use a tinderbox on the now wet rock. You then have to move within a certain timer delay period. If you don&#39;t you can be hurt in the process. ( 9/10th of life maybe? ) , you can  use  the explosive potion   gfx  from castle wars or the chinchompa gfx easily for the explosive. Maybe even make the screen shake! You will see 2-7 ore appear around the rock randomly. 

[b]-Construction:[/b] Well something I always hated about construction is that you  can&#39;t build anything actually USEFUL. This has been done before but the higher your construction level, the better skilling items can be placed inside your house. (maybe a skiller room? )  If you can buy a bloody dragon to go into a dungeon then you can buy skiller supplies just the way I see it. 

[b]-Hunter:[/b] I would call this &quot;rare animal hunting&quot; It involves replacing kebbits and the  uh   pitfall trap things (sabres? ) whatever they are called. Anywho, the main idea here is that the varrock musuem is in need of some rare bone artifacts to go on their new section of rare animals. You would do the skill by first tracking just like on runescape. You would then need some archaeological items in your backpack( like a brush ) and inspect the tracks. After you have done enough tracking you will understand the last place the animal was seen. You can then use a scent disguiser  to hide your scent and also to attempt to intoxicate the  rare animal. You must then  &quot;sneak and  catch&quot; so  to s speak to  end it. For the sabre type monsters I would suggest requiring several ropes to catch.  I would personally make this like a mini-quest that could only be done maybe once a day with a limit of 3-5 rare animal finds! To make it more challenging a person can return the rare animal / bone to the museum and they will claim for most of the time that this isn&#39;t the rare animal they were expecting and that this is a modern version of it and not an original.

[b]-Herblore:[/b] I found this one to be somewhat hard to make. Mine is actually creating an entire new collection of &quot;poisons&quot; for the game. There are:

-paralyzing
-fatal
-pain
-unconscious

you can decide on colors etc. You can easily recolor a  potion vial etc so yeah... anywho, the main idea is to make it so you  use herbs with the  different herbs found at the as a last resort quest. (600 plus items I know for sure has these I am not sure of exact revision! ) I had started this my own self and it was fun to start designing but I never completed it.

[b]-Runecrafting/Crafting combination: [/b]I got this idea from a Harry Potter fanfiction actually haha. What it does is, let&#39;s say you create a battlestaff/etc. You can  add runes to the object, or any other object for that matter. To change how the object works. In this case  for example if you used a nature rune with a fire staff it may make it so it has properties to help with natural skills such as farming growth.

[b]-Firemaking: [/b]Arson is always fun xD! I know it&#39;s possible to change walls to be fire instead so I thought it was a cool idea. You could set a timer so over time the  house will be &quot;rebuilt&quot; 
Note: just to keep a somewhat sense of reality, shops, banks, that type of stuff cannot be burned down. Other buildings can be though and I think players would like it even more if you made it so it can only be done every so often and make it so if you do much of it you become &quot;hot&quot; and you have to stop for a while (2-4 days ) unless you want a high chance of being jailed. (mods cant unjail)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 01:04:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Some unique ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“runescape sucks, post:6, topic:454230”]I’d like to incorporate lockpicking from TES games into my server(probably Oblivion out of all of them, Only played 3 though.)[/quote]sounds interesting actually would love to see something like this</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 01:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454230-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230.rss">Some unique ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some unique ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runescape_sucks runescape sucks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runescape_sucks">@runescape_sucks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d like to incorporate lockpicking from TES games into my server(probably Oblivion out of all of them, Only played 3 though.)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454230-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230.rss">Some unique ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some unique ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“arham 4, post:2, topic:454230”]I never thought someone had a more imaginative mind than me. GREAT ideas :).[/quote]&lt;3</p>
<p>[quote=“imsuperman05, post:3, topic:454230”]i like the mining and firemaking one lol.</p>
<p>the construction is stupid…  if u want to build something useful then go smith… no point in combing two skills</p>
<p>the terrain effects are interesting too</p>
<p>but basically what ur thinking of is somewhat have the game more realistic, really.[/quote]I was grabbing at straws lol. You know how I am customscape  xD</p>
<p>[quote=“Jaxus, post:4, topic:454230”]They are certainly great imaginative ideas, but it would not only take time to implement them, but also take players a long time to get used to it. It would pretty much be a new game from a certain perspective. Great ideas though.[/quote]that’s what people like though as well</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 21:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454230-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230.rss">Some unique ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some unique ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jaxus Jaxus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jaxus">@Jaxus</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>They are certainly great imaginative ideas, but it would not only take time to implement them, but also take players a long time to get used to it. It would pretty much be a new game from a certain perspective. Great ideas though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 04:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454230-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230.rss">Some unique ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some unique ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i like the mining and firemaking one lol.</p>
<p>the construction is stupid…  if u want to build something useful then go smith… no point in combing two skills</p>
<p>the terrain effects are interesting too</p>
<p>but basically what ur thinking of is somewhat have the game more realistic, really.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 01:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454230-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230.rss">Some unique ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some unique ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I never thought someone had a more imaginative mind than me. GREAT ideas :).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 16:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454230-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230.rss">Some unique ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some unique ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well as I don’t program anymore I am going to post some of my ideas in here and if anybody wishes to use them/make them/whatever feel free to!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Terrain effects. Let’s say for example you are mining in alkirahd mine. Because it’s hot, sand around you , etc  then you can’t mine as fast and your backpack is heavier. perhaps you can’t add as many items into your inventory.</span></p>
<p>Now… keep in mind I am very skiller oriented so you won’t see any combat stuff on here most likely now I will go into more specific skills.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Agility:</span> Instead of making it  where you can  run for a longer period of time make it so it  co-resides with terrain effects. You aren’t affected as bad  when your in the desert carrying stuff, it also makes it so while in combat your able to evade special attacks a little better.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Mining:</span> Well instead of using a pickaxe, consider it like explosives! You have a rock that has ore in it. You make an explosive potion (could use a few herbs or leaves from different quests! ) and like you “pour” the potion over the rock. Use a tinderbox on the now wet rock. You then have to move within a certain timer delay period. If you don’t you can be hurt in the process. ( 9/10th of life maybe? ) , you can  use  the explosive potion   gfx  from castle wars or the chinchompa gfx easily for the explosive. Maybe even make the screen shake! You will see 2-7 ore appear around the rock randomly.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Construction:</span> Well something I always hated about construction is that you  can’t build anything actually USEFUL. This has been done before but the higher your construction level, the better skilling items can be placed inside your house. (maybe a skiller room? )  If you can buy a bloody dragon to go into a dungeon then you can buy skiller supplies just the way I see it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Hunter:</span> I would call this “rare animal hunting” It involves replacing kebbits and the  uh   pitfall trap things (sabres? ) whatever they are called. Anywho, the main idea here is that the varrock musuem is in need of some rare bone artifacts to go on their new section of rare animals. You would do the skill by first tracking just like on runescape. You would then need some archaeological items in your backpack( like a brush ) and inspect the tracks. After you have done enough tracking you will understand the last place the animal was seen. You can then use a scent disguiser  to hide your scent and also to attempt to intoxicate the  rare animal. You must then  “sneak and  catch” so  to s speak to  end it. For the sabre type monsters I would suggest requiring several ropes to catch.  I would personally make this like a mini-quest that could only be done maybe once a day with a limit of 3-5 rare animal finds! To make it more challenging a person can return the rare animal / bone to the museum and they will claim for most of the time that this isn’t the rare animal they were expecting and that this is a modern version of it and not an original.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Herblore:</span> I found this one to be somewhat hard to make. Mine is actually creating an entire new collection of “poisons” for the game. There are:</p>
<p>-paralyzing<br>
-fatal<br>
-pain<br>
-unconscious</p>
<p>you can decide on colors etc. You can easily recolor a  potion vial etc so yeah… anywho, the main idea is to make it so you  use herbs with the  different herbs found at the as a last resort quest. (600 plus items I know for sure has these I am not sure of exact revision! ) I had started this my own self and it was fun to start designing but I never completed it.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Runecrafting/Crafting combination: </span>I got this idea from a Harry Potter fanfiction actually haha. What it does is, let’s say you create a battlestaff/etc. You can  add runes to the object, or any other object for that matter. To change how the object works. In this case  for example if you used a nature rune with a fire staff it may make it so it has properties to help with natural skills such as farming growth.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-Firemaking: </span>Arson is always fun xD! I know it’s possible to change walls to be fire instead so I thought it was a cool idea. You could set a timer so over time the  house will be “rebuilt”<br>
Note: just to keep a somewhat sense of reality, shops, banks, that type of stuff cannot be burned down. Other buildings can be though and I think players would like it even more if you made it so it can only be done every so often and make it so if you do much of it you become “hot” and you have to stop for a while (2-4 days ) unless you want a high chance of being jailed. (mods cant unjail)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 13:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454230-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-unique-ideas/454230.rss">Some unique ideas</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
