<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ulitmate rs guides</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001</link>
    <description>chapter 1:how to start a bakery!
chapter 2:how to make a melle pure
chapter 3:Ultimate Guide To PK For Warriors (50+ Combat, (40+ DEF)  
chapter 4:ultimate pk guide for mages
chapter 5:castle wars guide
chapter 6:money making guides(with the s)

                                         chapter 1:how to start a bakery

Start Your Own Bakery
1. First choose a spot (Near a oven or windmill-source)
Popular Available Places Are-
-Falador General Store, Top floor
-Bear Room in the Varrock Sewers, Zombie Section
-Falador Bar, Top Floor
-Falador jewelry shop outdoor spots.
-Back spot in Varrock Ruins
-Top floor in Varrock shops

2. Gather your supplies/tools
For a small business-
Bread
Pies
Cakes

For a big business-
Bread
Pies
Meat Pies
Apple Pies
Cakes
Chocolate Cakes
Pizzas
Meat Pizzas
Anchovery Pizzas

3. Hire Employees
Get employees…
3 for a small business
8 for a big business
You do all the cooking, half of your employees advertise your shop, the other half gathers your needs such as grain, chocolate…etc. Choose 1 employee to be your assistant, assistants usually help sell half the goods. Pay your employees 12k per hour or 2k per 10 minutes. 

4. Advertising
Your ads should contain name, place, date…etc
Example:
-Ayeung’s Bakery- Open 3 hours a day, selling pies, pizza and more! Head to Falador General Store, top floor. 50% off!
Include effects-
Glow 1,2,3:
Flash 1,2,3:
Red:
Cyan:
White: 
Don’t include effects-
Scroll:
Slide:
Wave:
Shake:

5. Uniform
The Shopkeeper/boss wears-
Brown Apron
Any coloured gloves
Chef hat

Employees wear-
Chef Hat
White apron

6. Out of world advertising
Advertising on blogs and forums help, read 4) again to advertise.

7. Business Managing
As your stocks grow. Add new products such as fresh, or “PK ready” which are breads that are NOT noted.

                                       chapter 2:how to make a melle pure

1. id recommend you train at the chickens place till you get to about 20 str

2. you&#39;ll have about 3k feathers then, sell them, get some moolah, and keep in bank

3. train ur atk to 10 at monks, then str to 30. at 10 atk, id train with steel scimmy because black scimmys are a bit too costly

4. train to 20 atk at cows, while getting cowhides, make runs from cow pen to the bank in lumby castle

5. get about 5k cowhides, which is about 500k-550k, and this will take you to about 52 str.

6. train to 40 atk and get rune scimmy and 2h, then train at barb village to 60 str

7. id leave atk at 40 for now, and train at lvl 22 minotaurs to get iron arrows. you can sell these arrows or train with them. i would start pking at lvl 74 str, thats when you hit 22s with 2h and pot

                                                   chapter 3:Ultimate Guide To PK For Warriors (50+ Combat, (40+ DEF)  

Wear-
Black Platemail
Rune Full Helm
Rune Platemail
Rune Platelegs
Black Kite

Weild-
Rune/Adamant Scimitar
Rune/Adamant Battleaxe
Rune/Adamant Longsword

Bring-
Backup Runes (Combat)
Teleporting Runes
Lobsters
Swordfish

Why?-
Black Kite and platebody offer good defence and camoflague you at the same time, scimitar and longswords deal with a good amount of damage and are still fast, the battleaxe is slow but deals with a high number of damage shocking the opponent, backup runes are for when your getting owned or if the opponent is running away. Tele runes are for teleporting in emergency situations, lobsters and swordfish offer a good amount of HP healed and aren&#39;t that expensive, especially swordfish (compared to the lobsters)

                                   chapter 4:ultimate pk guide for mages

Wear-
Shade Robes
Black Wizard Hat
Elemental Staff(s) (Air,water,earth or fire)/Magic Staff (If possible)
No Boots
No Gloves
Black Cape
No Ring
Amulet Of Power/Defence/Magic

Runes-
Teleporting Runes
Spell Casting Runes
Freezing Runes

Food-
Tunas
Lobsters
Swordfish
Salmon

Prayer-
Related To Magic prayers
Healing Prayers

Explainations-
Dark clothers because of camoflague,
tele runes because of emergancy teleports, freezing runes for extra good pk, tunas, lobsters, swordfish and salmons are quite cheap and heal alot. Amulets for extra bonuses.

                                              chapter 5:castle wars guide

 every one has a role to play in castle wars this guide will help you choose that role be you lvl 15 or lvl 126 this guide can help

lvl&#39;s 3-40 - you guys should maintain the castle eg. keep the doors closed repair things you will not help much fighting so running from fights is advised you have no idea how much keeping the castle maintained helps to attain victory so get repairing most importint keep the underground passidge ways clear. you could also grab some medkits and heal your allies (right click on medkits click use then right click on intended player then click on use on) or use the catapult (guide to how at the bottem of page)

lvl&#39;s 41-69 - you guys could ever do some of the above or try your luck taking the flag but the best role for you guys is to destroy enemy barricades so the higher lvl people get a clear passage to the flag.

lvls-70-95 - ok you guys are the main flag stealers the work force of the team have in your ivent medkits, pickaxe, tinderbox have your defence prayers on and go for that flag if you get it you should go to the bottom of the castle and go underground as people are hardly ever there if people are chasin you drop the rocks as you go as they will have to go around (and if they are under it kill them) wich gives you a clear road to your flag the tinder box is for any barricades you might come across. 

lvl&#39;s 95+ - you guys should defend the flag i hear you all screaming yeah right! but here is how it goes person gets your flag you kill person you have flag and if our lvl 100 and somthing they will have a hard time geting the flag back now wont they. ofcourse if you hate that idea then just do what the lvl 70-95 people do but defending the flag is the best option for you

for all lvl&#39;s - WORK AS A TEAM it is a team game and you will fail if you try to do this buy yourslef and if you fail chances are everyone else fails 

pure mages or rangers - stay on your castle walls and just attack all enemy players that come past if your mage/ranging lvl is very high they will ever die before they get in or have below half hp

using the catapult - grab a invent of racks from dowstairs and go to the catapult now look at your cumpass if you see a enemy move the cross over that spot that u see on the compass and fire MAKE SURE NONE OF YOUR PLAYERS ARE NEARBUY OR THEY WILL BE HIT TO works best on large groups of enemies

No Cost Method

Flax is the buzz word here. Note that this is member only. First, go to Camelot. Directly below Cammy, there is a flax field. Stock up, and head to the bank. Repeat until you have at least 1K. Then post on the forums that you are selling flax. Do not make it into bowstrings! This eliminates your crafting buyers. Flax generally sells for 50-100 gp each. Sell on the forums. The profit odds for this are 0:50-100 (0 being it costs you nothing and 50-100 being the unit price). Profit odds will be used a lot in this guide. These profit odds are good, but time consuming for little cash (only 50K-100K for 1K flax).


Low/High Cost Method

The second method is to buy water runes. This works for both free players and members. To do this, you need around 40K-100K. Go to a lowly populated free world. Next, go to the Port Sarim rune shop. Talk to Betty, and, if there are 5,000 waters in stock, buy 1K. If not, switch worlds and try again. You buy 1K waters at around 6 each, on average. After buying 1K, switch worlds and repeat. At an average of 6 each, you can buy anywhere from 6.5K-16.5K waters. Sell these waters on the forums for 20-30 each. You will make around 130K-495K. Now that you have the low cost money-making methods down, let’s see higher cost strategies.


Low Risk, High Reward

These methods are effective, no doubt about it. The method that I usually use will be talked about in this section, as well as other effective ways to make money.


Reselling for a Profit

Most people look at this title, and assume that I mean any item. However, this tactic only applies to SOME items. Here are different ways to use this tactic to the most effective degree.


Dragon Chainbody

This item is for true high rollers, as the regular price is between 15M-20M! The way to do this is to buy for around 15M, and sell for 20M. This way can be quite easy. I am not going to go into detail on other items, but here are some items that are easy to make a profit on:




RuneScape is Like the Stock Market?

Yes friends, it is! At first glance, you might think I am crazy for stating this. However, when you think about it, that’s exactly what RuneScape is. If you are familiar with the stock market, you know that you invest in a stock you think is going to go up. Now, replace the word “stock” with the word “item”, and you get “You invest in an item you think is going to go up”. For example, a few months ago, the value of claws skyrocketed. At this time, the claws were overpriced, and were twice as much as the price now. There has been no way to detect tomorrow’s popular item, until now! I have devised a system to detect hot items, using basic business principles.


Supply vs. Demand

This principle is used most commonly with holiday drops. As time passes, and the amount of these items decreases, price goes up. This has happened with all tradable holiday drops, and is the reason that Jagex stopped giving out tradable holiday drops.


New Items

RuneScape has come out with many new items. Usually, these items start out really inflated in price, and then the price plummets as the item becomes more common. Examples of this include claws, Infinity Robes, planks, and Dragon 2h. So, the rule of thumb here is that if a new item comes out, wait a few months before buying it.


New!!! My Market Predictions!

Here are my predictions, as of 2/07:

• As more people begin to play RuneScape, more money is created. Thus, prices will start to increase.
• More people will sign up for memberships, most of them noobs.
• New member quests will be coming out soon.
• Your RS friends will be at higher levels.
• As RuneScape becomes more member-dominated, free players will have less and less RS rights.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 04:29:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ulitmate rs guides</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blade_arrow0 blade arrow0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blade_arrow0">@blade_arrow0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>so how much more guides tell me k</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 04:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72001-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001.rss">Ulitmate rs guides</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ulitmate rs guides</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice try, Could be a little better though   :rolleyes: Maybe add a bit more detail, or more guides.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2007 18:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72001-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001.rss">Ulitmate rs guides</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ulitmate rs guides</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blade_arrow0 blade arrow0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blade_arrow0">@blade_arrow0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>srry i used internet explore to do this</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72001-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001.rss">Ulitmate rs guides</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ulitmate rs guides</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eifel_65 Eifel 65]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eifel_65">@Eifel_65</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wish there was spellcheck…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 06:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72001-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001.rss">Ulitmate rs guides</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ulitmate rs guides</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blade_arrow0 blade arrow0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blade_arrow0">@blade_arrow0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ill do that on my next coming guide[br][size=1]Posted on: March 28, 2007, 05:22:22 PM[/size][hr]guide updated</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 05:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72001-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001.rss">Ulitmate rs guides</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ulitmate rs guides</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aftermath_961 Aftermath]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aftermath_961">@Aftermath_961</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, you’re trying. Try using spellcheck before you post, though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72001-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001.rss">Ulitmate rs guides</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ulitmate rs guides</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blade_arrow0 blade arrow0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blade_arrow0">@blade_arrow0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>chapter 1:how to start a bakery!<br>
chapter 2:how to make a melle pure<br>
chapter 3:Ultimate Guide To PK For Warriors (50+ Combat, (40+ DEF)<br>
chapter 4:ultimate pk guide for mages<br>
chapter 5:castle wars guide<br>
chapter 6:money making guides(with the s)</p>
<pre><code>                                     chapter 1:how to start a bakery
</code></pre>
<p>Start Your Own Bakery</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>First choose a spot (Near a oven or windmill-source)<br>
Popular Available Places Are-<br>
-Falador General Store, Top floor<br>
-Bear Room in the Varrock Sewers, Zombie Section<br>
-Falador Bar, Top Floor<br>
-Falador jewelry shop outdoor spots.<br>
-Back spot in Varrock Ruins<br>
-Top floor in Varrock shops</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Gather your supplies/tools<br>
For a small business-<br>
Bread<br>
Pies<br>
Cakes</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>For a big business-<br>
Bread<br>
Pies<br>
Meat Pies<br>
Apple Pies<br>
Cakes<br>
Chocolate Cakes<br>
Pizzas<br>
Meat Pizzas<br>
Anchovery Pizzas</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<p>Hire Employees<br>
Get employees…<br>
3 for a small business<br>
8 for a big business<br>
You do all the cooking, half of your employees advertise your shop, the other half gathers your needs such as grain, chocolate…etc. Choose 1 employee to be your assistant, assistants usually help sell half the goods. Pay your employees 12k per hour or 2k per 10 minutes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Advertising<br>
Your ads should contain name, place, date…etc<br>
Example:<br>
-Ayeung’s Bakery- Open 3 hours a day, selling pies, pizza and more! Head to Falador General Store, top floor. 50% off!<br>
Include effects-<br>
Glow 1,2,3:<br>
Flash 1,2,3:<br>
Red:<br>
Cyan:<br>
White:<br>
Don’t include effects-<br>
Scroll:<br>
Slide:<br>
Wave:<br>
Shake:</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Uniform<br>
The Shopkeeper/boss wears-<br>
Brown Apron<br>
Any coloured gloves<br>
Chef hat</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Employees wear-<br>
Chef Hat<br>
White apron</p>
<ol start="6">
<li>
<p>Out of world advertising<br>
Advertising on blogs and forums help, read 4) again to advertise.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Business Managing<br>
As your stocks grow. Add new products such as fresh, or “PK ready” which are breads that are NOT noted.</p>
<pre><code>                                chapter 2:how to make a melle pure
</code></pre>
</li>
<li>
<p>id recommend you train at the chickens place till you get to about 20 str</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>you’ll have about 3k feathers then, sell them, get some moolah, and keep in bank</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>train ur atk to 10 at monks, then str to 30. at 10 atk, id train with steel scimmy because black scimmys are a bit too costly</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>train to 20 atk at cows, while getting cowhides, make runs from cow pen to the bank in lumby castle</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>get about 5k cowhides, which is about 500k-550k, and this will take you to about 52 str.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>train to 40 atk and get rune scimmy and 2h, then train at barb village to 60 str</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>id leave atk at 40 for now, and train at lvl 22 minotaurs to get iron arrows. you can sell these arrows or train with them. i would start pking at lvl 74 str, thats when you hit 22s with 2h and pot</p>
<pre><code>                                            chapter 3:Ultimate Guide To PK For Warriors (50+ Combat, (40+ DEF)  
</code></pre>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Wear-<br>
Black Platemail<br>
Rune Full Helm<br>
Rune Platemail<br>
Rune Platelegs<br>
Black Kite</p>
<p>Weild-<br>
Rune/Adamant Scimitar<br>
Rune/Adamant Battleaxe<br>
Rune/Adamant Longsword</p>
<p>Bring-<br>
Backup Runes (Combat)<br>
Teleporting Runes<br>
Lobsters<br>
Swordfish</p>
<p>Why?-<br>
Black Kite and platebody offer good defence and camoflague you at the same time, scimitar and longswords deal with a good amount of damage and are still fast, the battleaxe is slow but deals with a high number of damage shocking the opponent, backup runes are for when your getting owned or if the opponent is running away. Tele runes are for teleporting in emergency situations, lobsters and swordfish offer a good amount of HP healed and aren’t that expensive, especially swordfish (compared to the lobsters)</p>
<pre><code>                               chapter 4:ultimate pk guide for mages
</code></pre>
<p>Wear-<br>
Shade Robes<br>
Black Wizard Hat<br>
Elemental Staff(s) (Air,water,earth or fire)/Magic Staff (If possible)<br>
No Boots<br>
No Gloves<br>
Black Cape<br>
No Ring<br>
Amulet Of Power/Defence/Magic</p>
<p>Runes-<br>
Teleporting Runes<br>
Spell Casting Runes<br>
Freezing Runes</p>
<p>Food-<br>
Tunas<br>
Lobsters<br>
Swordfish<br>
Salmon</p>
<p>Prayer-<br>
Related To Magic prayers<br>
Healing Prayers</p>
<p>Explainations-<br>
Dark clothers because of camoflague,<br>
tele runes because of emergancy teleports, freezing runes for extra good pk, tunas, lobsters, swordfish and salmons are quite cheap and heal alot. Amulets for extra bonuses.</p>
<pre><code>                                          chapter 5:castle wars guide
</code></pre>
<p>every one has a role to play in castle wars this guide will help you choose that role be you lvl 15 or lvl 126 this guide can help</p>
<p>lvl’s 3-40 - you guys should maintain the castle eg. keep the doors closed repair things you will not help much fighting so running from fights is advised you have no idea how much keeping the castle maintained helps to attain victory so get repairing most importint keep the underground passidge ways clear. you could also grab some medkits and heal your allies (right click on medkits click use then right click on intended player then click on use on) or use the catapult (guide to how at the bottem of page)</p>
<p>lvl’s 41-69 - you guys could ever do some of the above or try your luck taking the flag but the best role for you guys is to destroy enemy barricades so the higher lvl people get a clear passage to the flag.</p>
<p>lvls-70-95 - ok you guys are the main flag stealers the work force of the team have in your ivent medkits, pickaxe, tinderbox have your defence prayers on and go for that flag if you get it you should go to the bottom of the castle and go underground as people are hardly ever there if people are chasin you drop the rocks as you go as they will have to go around (and if they are under it kill them) wich gives you a clear road to your flag the tinder box is for any barricades you might come across.</p>
<p>lvl’s 95+ - you guys should defend the flag i hear you all screaming yeah right! but here is how it goes person gets your flag you kill person you have flag and if our lvl 100 and somthing they will have a hard time geting the flag back now wont they. ofcourse if you hate that idea then just do what the lvl 70-95 people do but defending the flag is the best option for you</p>
<p>for all lvl’s - WORK AS A TEAM it is a team game and you will fail if you try to do this buy yourslef and if you fail chances are everyone else fails</p>
<p>pure mages or rangers - stay on your castle walls and just attack all enemy players that come past if your mage/ranging lvl is very high they will ever die before they get in or have below half hp</p>
<p>using the catapult - grab a invent of racks from dowstairs and go to the catapult now look at your cumpass if you see a enemy move the cross over that spot that u see on the compass and fire MAKE SURE NONE OF YOUR PLAYERS ARE NEARBUY OR THEY WILL BE HIT TO works best on large groups of enemies</p>
<p>No Cost Method</p>
<p>Flax is the buzz word here. Note that this is member only. First, go to Camelot. Directly below Cammy, there is a flax field. Stock up, and head to the bank. Repeat until you have at least 1K. Then post on the forums that you are selling flax. Do not make it into bowstrings! This eliminates your crafting buyers. Flax generally sells for 50-100 gp each. Sell on the forums. The profit odds for this are 0:50-100 (0 being it costs you nothing and 50-100 being the unit price). Profit odds will be used a lot in this guide. These profit odds are good, but time consuming for little cash (only 50K-100K for 1K flax).</p>
<p>Low/High Cost Method</p>
<p>The second method is to buy water runes. This works for both free players and members. To do this, you need around 40K-100K. Go to a lowly populated free world. Next, go to the Port Sarim rune shop. Talk to Betty, and, if there are 5,000 waters in stock, buy 1K. If not, switch worlds and try again. You buy 1K waters at around 6 each, on average. After buying 1K, switch worlds and repeat. At an average of 6 each, you can buy anywhere from 6.5K-16.5K waters. Sell these waters on the forums for 20-30 each. You will make around 130K-495K. Now that you have the low cost money-making methods down, let’s see higher cost strategies.</p>
<p>Low Risk, High Reward</p>
<p>These methods are effective, no doubt about it. The method that I usually use will be talked about in this section, as well as other effective ways to make money.</p>
<p>Reselling for a Profit</p>
<p>Most people look at this title, and assume that I mean any item. However, this tactic only applies to SOME items. Here are different ways to use this tactic to the most effective degree.</p>
<p>Dragon Chainbody</p>
<p>This item is for true high rollers, as the regular price is between 15M-20M! The way to do this is to buy for around 15M, and sell for 20M. This way can be quite easy. I am not going to go into detail on other items, but here are some items that are easy to make a profit on:</p>
<p>RuneScape is Like the Stock Market?</p>
<p>Yes friends, it is! At first glance, you might think I am crazy for stating this. However, when you think about it, that’s exactly what RuneScape is. If you are familiar with the stock market, you know that you invest in a stock you think is going to go up. Now, replace the word “stock” with the word “item”, and you get “You invest in an item you think is going to go up”. For example, a few months ago, the value of claws skyrocketed. At this time, the claws were overpriced, and were twice as much as the price now. There has been no way to detect tomorrow’s popular item, until now! I have devised a system to detect hot items, using basic business principles.</p>
<p>Supply vs. Demand</p>
<p>This principle is used most commonly with holiday drops. As time passes, and the amount of these items decreases, price goes up. This has happened with all tradable holiday drops, and is the reason that Jagex stopped giving out tradable holiday drops.</p>
<p>New Items</p>
<p>RuneScape has come out with many new items. Usually, these items start out really inflated in price, and then the price plummets as the item becomes more common. Examples of this include claws, Infinity Robes, planks, and Dragon 2h. So, the rule of thumb here is that if a new item comes out, wait a few months before buying it.</p>
<p>New!!! My Market Predictions!</p>
<p>Here are my predictions, as of 2/07:</p>
<p>• As more people begin to play RuneScape, more money is created. Thus, prices will start to increase.<br>
• More people will sign up for memberships, most of them noobs.<br>
• New member quests will be coming out soon.<br>
• Your RS friends will be at higher levels.<br>
• As RuneScape becomes more member-dominated, free players will have less and less RS rights.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 02:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72001-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ulitmate-rs-guides/72001.rss">Ulitmate rs guides</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
