<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Using Rotten Potato to Kill &amp; Ban Players?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/using-rotten-potato-to-kill-ban-players/551026</link>
    <description>Hey guys,

I was recently watching a stream on OSRS where Mod Ronan was using the rotten potato on a bot to kill them and ban them.

Is there a way to do this on an RSPS? Is it server-sided?

Basically, I want to be able to click &#39;use&#39; on the rotten potato and then click on a player. After using the potato on a player I want it to kill them on the spot and then ban them about 2 seconds later/at the same time if that is not possible.

All help is appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 20:25:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/using-rotten-potato-to-kill-ban-players/551026.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Using Rotten Potato to Kill &amp; Ban Players?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll give you a quick “rundown” on how to do this. Do not expect it to be super in depth.</p>
<p><a href="https://rswiki.moparisthebest.com/index.php?title=317:Item_on_player" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Item on Player packet</a></p>
<p>Use the above packet to get the id of the player you use the rotten potato on.</p>
<p>Save the playerId of that player to the current session, which means you need to declare a variable in Player.java to hold it. I personally would make the value be equal to -1 when it’s not being used. As -1 is not a valid playerId.</p>
<p>If you don’t have a custom interface for it:<br>
Create the options in the dialoguehandler. Set a custom dialogueActionId or equivalent.</p>
<p>In ClickingButtons, you need to find the button IDs for each of the actions, if a custom interface, you probably need to add the cases.<br>
Add an if statement to check the dialogueActionId from above, and also check if the playerId from the Item on Player packet isn’t -1.</p>
<p>The next part, there are a multitude of ways to handle this. I am giving you <span class="bbcode-u">ONE</span> of those ways. Understand that.</p>
<p>Create a method in PlayerAssistant. Make it require an integer for it’s only parameter.</p>
<p>First, make a Player object in the method. Set it to the player based on the ID you got from earlier.<br>
Optional but safer: Above the player object add a check the playerId is not less than 0, because if it is you will get an array out of bounds exception.<br>
Second, check if the player object is null, if it is null I’d return a message to the player stating so, and then stop the method there (using a return or equal).<br>
Third, make a switch statement based on the integer that is a parameter of the method. Each case of the statement will be a different punishment.<br>
For instance, case 0 would be kick, case 1 would be mute, case 2 would be ban, etc.<br>
Within each case add the proper code for each punishment/etc. I will not go in depth on this as it varies widely.</p>
<p>Now back in the clicking buttons, make use of that new method, and change the parameter for each button based on what punishment it is.</p>
<p>*NOTE: Strings can also be used in switch statements, so you could always replace the integer value in the method with a String, but they care case sensitive when you use them in switch statements.<br>
**NOTE: There is probably a better way to handle this.<br>
***NOTE: If the lingo used here is confusing, or something doesn’t make sense. It may be because you don’t understand some terms used in programming and the language of Java, if that’s the case you may want to look up some tutorials <a href="https://docs.oracle.com/javase/tutorial/reallybigindex.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a></p>
<p>Do not hesitate to ask questions, but remember that <a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://google.com</a> exists and it may/may not be easier to ask it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/using-rotten-potato-to-kill-ban-players/551026/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/using-rotten-potato-to-kill-ban-players/551026/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 20:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551026-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/using-rotten-potato-to-kill-ban-players/551026.rss">Using Rotten Potato to Kill &amp; Ban Players?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Using Rotten Potato to Kill &amp; Ban Players?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mrpopyman mrpopyman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrpopyman">@mrpopyman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,</p>
<p>I was recently watching a stream on OSRS where Mod Ronan was using the rotten potato on a bot to kill them and ban them.</p>
<p>Is there a way to do this on an RSPS? Is it server-sided?</p>
<p>Basically, I want to be able to click ‘use’ on the rotten potato and then click on a player. After using the potato on a player I want it to kill them on the spot and then ban them about 2 seconds later/at the same time if that is not possible.</p>
<p>All help is appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/using-rotten-potato-to-kill-ban-players/551026/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/using-rotten-potato-to-kill-ban-players/551026/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 06:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551026-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/using-rotten-potato-to-kill-ban-players/551026.rss">Using Rotten Potato to Kill &amp; Ban Players?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
