<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796</link>
    <description>[b][size=12pt]I do not encourage you all to buy/sell/trade accounts, but if you do, read this guide.[/size][/b]


[b]30% of credits for the details of this guide go to the Crew at sythe, for the MM forums, 30% to mastercheif and 40% to Me (for the MM guide a rsaddict.com)[/b]


[b]Just so you know you have a 99% chance of getting scammed.[/b]


&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote:
Jagex can&#39;t even see the site. All they get is a 404 error, SO THEY DON&#39;T KNOW THE SITE IS STILL EVEN RUNNING! YOU CAN POST YOUR ACCOUNT NAME, AND YOU CAN POST ALL ITS STATS WITHOUT BEING BANNED.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Also, if you think jagex would use a proxy, I laugh at you. They were blocked for a reason, and they aren&#39;t the kind to try to get there nose into things.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Here&#39;s a list of when it&#39;s stupid to buy an account...&lt;/blockquote&gt;

1. It&#39;s been banned before- Jagex watches accounts like that. Really dumb move to buy an account that&#39;s had a ban.

2. WHEN IT HAS MEMBERS ON IT!- It can be scammed back VERY easily. Common sense guys, they have everything and could be lying to you when they give account info in the trade.

3. When recovs are set- Dur...

4. When the guy has comments saying he&#39;s a scammer.- Make sure you always check comments.

If anyone has anything to add, go ahead. I laugh when people ask me to MM for trades with characters with members on them... C&#39;mon... Common sense.

Quote:
-Scammers tend to be seasoned in their job, having been through this site multiple times.
-The way to know you are dealing with one, is by them referencing to being trustworthy, especially if they mention it numerous times. This is a sign of the scammer being nervous. They tend to be paranoid with asserting that they are infact not scammers, so they tell you they aren&#39;t.
-Lots of scammers tend to offer too much for characters, and want to do the deal fast, either saying they have to leave, or something of the sort. Do not be fooled by this. Take your time.
-Scammers come in all types of levels, its all based on their self-control. Almost everyone has their limit, so deal with your money wisely.
-Don&#39;t be fooled by imposters, be sure you always check the MM guid at sythe.
-Don&#39;t ever get too comfortable with someone to let them wear your expensive items etc...like I mentioned earlier, people have their limits, and they could merely befriending you to scam.
-Don&#39;t trust anyone just because a friend says so, trust people based on your experiences, not based on theirs.
-Don&#39;t assume someone is trustworthy based on how long he/she has been at the site or how high their post count is.
-Always try to use the official middle men, you are most likely not going to get scammed with them. They are official for a reason.
-People who advertise middle manning in their signatures tend to be people who want to gain status fast, and therefore scam in the future when a good opportunity arises.
-Try to not spend too much at one time, people are less likely to risk getting banned for a small amount of money.
-Scammers do what they do for a reason, they should not be forgiven.

Quote:
Originally Posted by Alpaca
OK recently I have seen heaps of complains of people that have used the Sticky of how to unset your recovery questions. I have been selling accounst for years and have unset over 100 Recovery questions, Ive done them recently and with no problem.

Its basicaly the same as the old way but now it seems that Fagsex is looking for more information to proof that you are infact the original owner and that you have all the accounts information!

I will go through this step by step

Step 1
Go to www.RuneScape.com
Scroll down to Account Recovery &amp; CLick on Recover A Lost Password



Step 2
Type in your username and the email you used to make the account a member, if you do not have it just use your current msn email. Next select Someone else knows my recovery questions!


Step 3
* Type in ALL of your Recovery Answers
* Type in your Earliset Agreement number and Transcaion ID (If you paid with a Credit Card for membership!
*Type in your Earliest Pin Number (If you paid by pbp)
*Type in Your first password, On the bottom field any password that youve had, and on the last field your current password
*Type in your zip code that u entered when you made the account a member with Credit Card OR The zip code of the phone that was used to make it a member through pbp!
*Type in When You last Logged In
*Enter A New password




***Most Important part***
This is the last box where you get to put in your last information to proove to them!


This is one of many excuses! You can pm me and ask me for more!

Step 4
*Click Submit and copy the Tracker ID on to a notepad file ( The letters must be in Capital Letters)
Save this Notepad File as you will need it later on!


Step 5
*Paste the Tracker ID&#39;s into the next box and click activate!


^^ If you get this message you have entered the Tracker ID Correctly and Now all you have to do is wait!

Step 6
Once you have activated the Tracker ID, Go back to the main menu and Click on Track a Recovery Request In the Account recovery Section!

Enter the Tracker ID that you had in your NotePad File And Click Continue!


**Results** You can get 1 of 3 results once you enter your Tracker ID
Pending: Jagex Staff is working on your request. You will need to wait and try Step 6 Again!
Accepted: Jagex has accepted your request and your recovery questions have been unset!
Declined: Jagex Has Declined your request and your recovery questions have not been unset!

If your Request has been Declined or your account has been locked, Pm me for Help on how to get your account back Or get more info to Unset your recovery questions.

- Alpaca

================================================== ===================

The Guide to Using the Black Market

Hi there, and welcome to my guide for black market! If there is something missing, please let me know!

1st of all you HAVE to read the rules before starting unless you want to get banned.
2nd[/u]
When selling accounts in the black market you will be needing to post a picture of both stats (not highscore stats!) and the &quot;welcome box&quot; where it says if u got recoveries etc.

I use www.imageshack.us &amp; www.photobucket.com to host my pictures.


3rd
If you do have recoveries, but do not know how to unset them as people rarely do buy accounts with recs on. Click here!
http://www.sythe.org/about6330.html


4th

When doing larger trades, then I would recomend you to use officials MMs
(MM stands for MiddleMan) which do the trades safer.


5th
Offering your mm services, or account training services should be in user services:

http://rsaddict.com

If you got scammed or found a scammer, do not post here. You will have to post in &quot;report to moderator&quot; or PM a modeator like, The Un-Named, jme_009 etc. (you will need proof)
www.moparisthebest.com/smf


6th
Always make the person you are trading with pm you on moparscape forum so you know your trading with the correct person and not an imposter.
&lt;If having the same username as hotmail accounts makes it easier to remember you, though this aint needed.&gt;


7th
Ready for doing trades now? GREAT! But before giving your cash away (or account for that sake) remember to look inside of these 3 links for imposterts(mail), scammers mail adress and scamming rs accounts

~Ikick~


===============================================

WAYS TO CHECK FOR POSSIBLE SCAMMERS: BY IKICK

SCAMS MAY CONTAIN
* Odd looking pictures (depending on file format always remember other then bmp. the file could loose alot of format, not always a scam just pointing it out. Also you could be viewing a private server.
* Extremely High Stats (eg. 99hp along with other 99 melee stats with low lvl&#39;d skill totals) - not always scam&#39;s but be very aware.
* Obvious Edits to the Picture.
* Low post count (not always the case)
* Seem desperate to sell quick, meaning there hungry for money fast.
* Keen grammer, by this i mean seems very formal and seems to be a CON.
* Not providing ingame PROOF.
* Not showing things in reason that can lead to them not being proved a scammer.
* Idiots claiming to be girls (Obviously if they speak or talk like a Guy there Obviously a girl to influence you on a trade, BE AWARE YOUNG GUYS LOL).
* Weird MSN names - eg. ikick@sythe.com, ikick_codex@hotmail.com (not my email&#39;s just a point).
* Not wanting to use MM&#39;s this is usaully an obvious reason.
* lots of spelling mistakes.
* Ask them to use a Offical MM of your choice if they disagree its a SCAM.
* Also watch out for MM&#39;s they decide that you have never heard nothing about.

:::WAYS TO PROVE ITS NOT A SCAM:::
* Ask what MM they want to use (if a non rsaddict.com MM (offical) it is most likely to be a scam)
* Ask them to meet you ingame.
* Ask on MSN or However you decide to Contact them, what there RSN is.
* Ask how long they have played - not always helpful but could lead to having them lie, this is Obvious in some cases.
* Tell them your MM (offical) if they dont agree, obviously a scam.
* Ask them if there willing to have there Account logged on ingame, via MM or OFFICALS (ONLY).
* Ask them there reason for selling?, if it sounds bullshit its obviously a bull shit trade.

:::WAYS TO RESOLVE A SCAM:::
* Always Check Offical MM list. (found at rsaddict.com)
* Ask them to meet you ingame
* Ask for more pics Via MSN or contact of your choice. ( if they are member of moparisthebest.com, Pm them here.)
* Always Ask for Runecape name when asking about the Account (if they disagree might be a scam) - btw dont ask on there thread ask in PRIV ONLY.
* Ask who there choice of MM is, if they pick a no namer not from Offical list ignore them and ask to USE OFFICAL.
* Always check to see there recovs are unset before buying. (DO SO VIA THERE RUNESCAPE NAME ON OFFICAL JAGEX SITE, TRY RECOVER THERE ACCOUNT VIA - I HAVE FORGOTTEN MY PASSWORD -) - Most of the time it will say Recov Q 1,2,3,4,5 if they are unset.
* Always ask the MM if they think its about fishy, Only when there in convo.
* ALWAYS CHECK SCAMMERS MSN LIST ANYTHING YOU CAN THINK OF.

===============================================

IDENTIFYING FALSE MIDDLEMEN: mastercheif

Time and time again, people are being scammed by MMs who claim that they are official. If you have had any doubts about whether that MM really was who he/she claimed to be, this is the right guide for you.

Step 1: Check the Official MM list here, to see if this person really is official
This topic contains the names of every Official MM on Sythe.org.
If the person is not there, he/she is NOT an official MM

Step 2: Check, double check, and triple check the MM&#39;s Email Address
If the MM is a fake, the Email Address will be slightly different to the one stated on the Official MM list. Using MSN Messenger would be better than AIM because it&#39;s harder to &quot;fake&quot; and Email. Check, double check and tripple check the Email until your eyes start to hurt.
Don&#39;t even pay attention to the screen name because it mean nothing.

Step 3: Get the MM to PM you on moparisthebest.com/smf
Even after the checking, you must get the MM to PM or Private Message you.
This is one of the easiest ways to find out if the so-called MM is legit. Ask the MM to Private Message you in the forums telling you that he/she is really who he/she claims.
Don&#39;t accept excuses such as:
1. Sythe.org isn&#39;t working for me right now
2. I&#39;m laggin too much, I&#39;ll do it later
Demand a PM and I suggest you back out of the trade if they are unable to comply.

Step 4: Ready to trade
Once you have received the PM and are conviced that the person is who they claim, go ahead with the trade BUT pay attention of who you trade your items to in RuneScape. Pause and check even the first trade screen just to be sure.

IMPORTANT: Even some official MMs may be unknown scammers so PLEASE be cautious with whoever you are dealing with. It is recommended not to do trades of over 5mil at a time.

MSN Messenger Tips
MSN Messenger is by far best thing to use in all kinds of trades. However, there might still be some fake MMs with similar Email addresses to the official ones offering to MM.

There is one simple way to avoid this.

In the list of official MMs, add everyone on that list to your MSN Messenger contacts in a SPECIFIC group. Name this group well and clearly:



Now you will clearly be able to see if the MMs Email address if correct or not. Do not fall for the &quot;I changed my Email Address trick.&quot;
Now you know that if that person is legit, he will appear as Online in your Mods and Official MMs group.

Remember, if you are ever in any doubt whatsoever, completely back out of the trade. You might lose a customer, but that&#39;s better than losing your hard earned goods.

i really do hope it helped.
Regards,
ikick</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 12:32:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ikick221 ikick221]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ikick221">@ikick221</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ty</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 12:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83796-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796.rss">Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xbox_Modder Xbox Modder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xbox_modder">@Xbox_Modder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank you…</p>
<p>I was confused lol</p>
<p>Nice anyway…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 12:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83796-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796.rss">Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ikick221 ikick221]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ikick221">@ikick221</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i though i better move it here.<br>
I will delete if from there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 12:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83796-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796.rss">Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xbox_Modder Xbox Modder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xbox_modder">@Xbox_Modder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Did you double post this or something I’m so confused…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 12:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83796-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796.rss">Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ikick221 ikick221]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ikick221">@ikick221</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i am talking about any sale… Thanks xbox Modder</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 12:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83796-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796.rss">Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fedexer -fedexer-]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fedexer">@fedexer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Emmm whats the point ina  thread like this when the only thing that is ment to be sold on here is scar scripts which is at <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.moparisthebest.com</a> ?</p>
<p>this will probably be locked</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 12:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83796-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796.rss">Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xbox_Modder Xbox Modder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xbox_modder">@Xbox_Modder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Very, very nice dude…</p>
<p>I will definetly use this if I sell one of my account or anything RS Related…</p>
<p>Thanks for the information!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 12:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83796-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796.rss">Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ikick221 ikick221]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ikick221">@ikick221</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=12pt]I do not encourage you all to buy/sell/trade accounts, but if you do, read this guide.[/size]</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">30% of credits for the details of this guide go to the Crew at sythe, for the MM forums, 30% to mastercheif and 40% to Me (for the MM guide a <a href="http://rsaddict.com" rel="nofollow noopener">rsaddict.com</a>)</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Just so you know you have a 99% chance of getting scammed.</span></p>
<blockquote>Quote:
Jagex can't even see the site. All they get is a 404 error, SO THEY DON'T KNOW THE SITE IS STILL EVEN RUNNING! YOU CAN POST YOUR ACCOUNT NAME, AND YOU CAN POST ALL ITS STATS WITHOUT BEING BANNED.</blockquote>
<p>Also, if you think jagex would use a proxy, I laugh at you. They were blocked for a reason, and they aren’t the kind to try to get there nose into things.</p>
<blockquote>Here's a list of when it's stupid to buy an account...</blockquote>
<ol>
<li>
<p>It’s been banned before- Jagex watches accounts like that. Really dumb move to buy an account that’s had a ban.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>WHEN IT HAS MEMBERS ON IT!- It can be scammed back VERY easily. Common sense guys, they have everything and could be lying to you when they give account info in the trade.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When recovs are set- Dur…</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When the guy has comments saying he’s a scammer.- Make sure you always check comments.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>If anyone has anything to add, go ahead. I laugh when people ask me to MM for trades with characters with members on them… C’mon… Common sense.</p>
<p>Quote:<br>
-Scammers tend to be seasoned in their job, having been through this site multiple times.<br>
-The way to know you are dealing with one, is by them referencing to being trustworthy, especially if they mention it numerous times. This is a sign of the scammer being nervous. They tend to be paranoid with asserting that they are infact not scammers, so they tell you they aren’t.<br>
-Lots of scammers tend to offer too much for characters, and want to do the deal fast, either saying they have to leave, or something of the sort. Do not be fooled by this. Take your time.<br>
-Scammers come in all types of levels, its all based on their self-control. Almost everyone has their limit, so deal with your money wisely.<br>
-Don’t be fooled by imposters, be sure you always check the MM guid at sythe.<br>
-Don’t ever get too comfortable with someone to let them wear your expensive items etc…like I mentioned earlier, people have their limits, and they could merely befriending you to scam.<br>
-Don’t trust anyone just because a friend says so, trust people based on your experiences, not based on theirs.<br>
-Don’t assume someone is trustworthy based on how long he/she has been at the site or how high their post count is.<br>
-Always try to use the official middle men, you are most likely not going to get scammed with them. They are official for a reason.<br>
-People who advertise middle manning in their signatures tend to be people who want to gain status fast, and therefore scam in the future when a good opportunity arises.<br>
-Try to not spend too much at one time, people are less likely to risk getting banned for a small amount of money.<br>
-Scammers do what they do for a reason, they should not be forgiven.</p>
<p>Quote:<br>
Originally Posted by Alpaca<br>
OK recently I have seen heaps of complains of people that have used the Sticky of how to unset your recovery questions. I have been selling accounst for years and have unset over 100 Recovery questions, Ive done them recently and with no problem.</p>
<p>Its basicaly the same as the old way but now it seems that Fagsex is looking for more information to proof that you are infact the original owner and that you have all the accounts information!</p>
<p>I will go through this step by step</p>
<p>Step 1<br>
Go to <a href="http://www.RuneScape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.RuneScape.com</a><br>
Scroll down to Account Recovery &amp; CLick on Recover A Lost Password</p>
<p>Step 2<br>
Type in your username and the email you used to make the account a member, if you do not have it just use your current msn email. Next select Someone else knows my recovery questions!</p>
<p>Step 3</p>
<ul>
<li>Type in ALL of your Recovery Answers</li>
<li>Type in your Earliset Agreement number and Transcaion ID (If you paid with a Credit Card for membership!<br>
*Type in your Earliest Pin Number (If you paid by pbp)<br>
*Type in Your first password, On the bottom field any password that youve had, and on the last field your current password<br>
*Type in your zip code that u entered when you made the account a member with Credit Card OR The zip code of the phone that was used to make it a member through pbp!<br>
*Type in When You last Logged In<br>
*Enter A New password</li>
</ul>
<p><em><strong>Most Important part</strong></em><br>
This is the last box where you get to put in your last information to proove to them!</p>
<p>This is one of many excuses! You can pm me and ask me for more!</p>
<p>Step 4<br>
*Click Submit and copy the Tracker ID on to a notepad file ( The letters must be in Capital Letters)<br>
Save this Notepad File as you will need it later on!</p>
<p>Step 5<br>
*Paste the Tracker ID’s into the next box and click activate!</p>
<p>^^ If you get this message you have entered the Tracker ID Correctly and Now all you have to do is wait!</p>
<p>Step 6<br>
Once you have activated the Tracker ID, Go back to the main menu and Click on Track a Recovery Request In the Account recovery Section!</p>
<p>Enter the Tracker ID that you had in your NotePad File And Click Continue!</p>
<p><strong>Results</strong> You can get 1 of 3 results once you enter your Tracker ID<br>
Pending: Jagex Staff is working on your request. You will need to wait and try Step 6 Again!<br>
Accepted: Jagex has accepted your request and your recovery questions have been unset!<br>
Declined: Jagex Has Declined your request and your recovery questions have not been unset!</p>
<p>If your Request has been Declined or your account has been locked, Pm me for Help on how to get your account back Or get more info to Unset your recovery questions.</p>
<ul>
<li>Alpaca</li>
</ul>
<p>================================================== ===================</p>
<p>The Guide to Using the Black Market</p>
<p>Hi there, and welcome to my guide for black market! If there is something missing, please let me know!</p>
<p>1st of all you HAVE to read the rules before starting unless you want to get banned.<br>
2nd[/u]<br>
When selling accounts in the black market you will be needing to post a picture of both stats (not highscore stats!) and the “welcome box” where it says if u got recoveries etc.</p>
<p>I use <a href="http://www.imageshack.us" rel="nofollow noopener">www.imageshack.us</a> &amp; <a href="http://www.photobucket.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.photobucket.com</a> to host my pictures.</p>
<p>3rd<br>
If you do have recoveries, but do not know how to unset them as people rarely do buy accounts with recs on. Click here!<br>
<a href="http://www.sythe.org/about6330.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.sythe.org/about6330.html</a></p>
<p>4th</p>
<p>When doing larger trades, then I would recomend you to use officials MMs<br>
(MM stands for MiddleMan) which do the trades safer.</p>
<p>5th<br>
Offering your mm services, or account training services should be in user services:</p>
<p><a href="http://rsaddict.com" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rsaddict.com</a></p>
<p>If you got scammed or found a scammer, do not post here. You will have to post in “report to moderator” or PM a modeator like, The Un-Named, jme_009 etc. (you will need proof)<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>6th<br>
Always make the person you are trading with pm you on moparscape forum so you know your trading with the correct person and not an imposter.<br>
&lt;If having the same username as hotmail accounts makes it easier to remember you, though this aint needed.&gt;</p>
<p>7th<br>
Ready for doing trades now? GREAT! But before giving your cash away (or account for that sake) remember to look inside of these 3 links for imposterts(mail), scammers mail adress and scamming rs accounts</p>
<p>~Ikick~</p>
<p>===============================================</p>
<p>WAYS TO CHECK FOR POSSIBLE SCAMMERS: BY IKICK</p>
<p>SCAMS MAY CONTAIN</p>
<ul>
<li>Odd looking pictures (depending on file format always remember other then bmp. the file could loose alot of format, not always a scam just pointing it out. Also you could be viewing a private server.</li>
<li>Extremely High Stats (eg. 99hp along with other 99 melee stats with low lvl’d skill totals) - not always scam’s but be very aware.</li>
<li>Obvious Edits to the Picture.</li>
<li>Low post count (not always the case)</li>
<li>Seem desperate to sell quick, meaning there hungry for money fast.</li>
<li>Keen grammer, by this i mean seems very formal and seems to be a CON.</li>
<li>Not providing ingame PROOF.</li>
<li>Not showing things in reason that can lead to them not being proved a scammer.</li>
<li>Idiots claiming to be girls (Obviously if they speak or talk like a Guy there Obviously a girl to influence you on a trade, BE AWARE YOUNG GUYS LOL).</li>
<li>Weird MSN names - eg. <a href="mailto:ikick@sythe.com">ikick@sythe.com</a>, <a href="mailto:ikick_codex@hotmail.com">ikick_codex@hotmail.com</a> (not my email’s just a point).</li>
<li>Not wanting to use MM’s this is usaully an obvious reason.</li>
<li>lots of spelling mistakes.</li>
<li>Ask them to use a Offical MM of your choice if they disagree its a SCAM.</li>
<li>Also watch out for MM’s they decide that you have never heard nothing about.</li>
</ul>
<p>:::WAYS TO PROVE ITS NOT A SCAM:::</p>
<ul>
<li>Ask what MM they want to use (if a non <a href="http://rsaddict.com" rel="nofollow noopener">rsaddict.com</a> MM (offical) it is most likely to be a scam)</li>
<li>Ask them to meet you ingame.</li>
<li>Ask on MSN or However you decide to Contact them, what there RSN is.</li>
<li>Ask how long they have played - not always helpful but could lead to having them lie, this is Obvious in some cases.</li>
<li>Tell them your MM (offical) if they dont agree, obviously a scam.</li>
<li>Ask them if there willing to have there Account logged on ingame, via MM or OFFICALS (ONLY).</li>
<li>Ask them there reason for selling?, if it sounds bullshit its obviously a bull shit trade.</li>
</ul>
<p>:::WAYS TO RESOLVE A SCAM:::</p>
<ul>
<li>Always Check Offical MM list. (found at <a href="http://rsaddict.com" rel="nofollow noopener">rsaddict.com</a>)</li>
<li>Ask them to meet you ingame</li>
<li>Ask for more pics Via MSN or contact of your choice. ( if they are member of <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a>, Pm them here.)</li>
<li>Always Ask for Runecape name when asking about the Account (if they disagree might be a scam) - btw dont ask on there thread ask in PRIV ONLY.</li>
<li>Ask who there choice of MM is, if they pick a no namer not from Offical list ignore them and ask to USE OFFICAL.</li>
<li>Always check to see there recovs are unset before buying. (DO SO VIA THERE RUNESCAPE NAME ON OFFICAL JAGEX SITE, TRY RECOVER THERE ACCOUNT VIA - I HAVE FORGOTTEN MY PASSWORD -) - Most of the time it will say Recov Q 1,2,3,4,5 if they are unset.</li>
<li>Always ask the MM if they think its about fishy, Only when there in convo.</li>
<li>ALWAYS CHECK SCAMMERS MSN LIST ANYTHING YOU CAN THINK OF.</li>
</ul>
<p>===============================================</p>
<p>IDENTIFYING FALSE MIDDLEMEN: mastercheif</p>
<p>Time and time again, people are being scammed by MMs who claim that they are official. If you have had any doubts about whether that MM really was who he/she claimed to be, this is the right guide for you.</p>
<p>Step 1: Check the Official MM list here, to see if this person really is official<br>
This topic contains the names of every Official MM on <a href="http://Sythe.org" rel="nofollow noopener">Sythe.org</a>.<br>
If the person is not there, he/she is NOT an official MM</p>
<p>Step 2: Check, double check, and triple check the MM’s Email Address<br>
If the MM is a fake, the Email Address will be slightly different to the one stated on the Official MM list. Using MSN Messenger would be better than AIM because it’s harder to “fake” and Email. Check, double check and tripple check the Email until your eyes start to hurt.<br>
Don’t even pay attention to the screen name because it mean nothing.</p>
<p>Step 3: Get the MM to PM you on <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com/smf</a><br>
Even after the checking, you must get the MM to PM or Private Message you.<br>
This is one of the easiest ways to find out if the so-called MM is legit. Ask the MM to Private Message you in the forums telling you that he/she is really who he/she claims.<br>
Don’t accept excuses such as:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<a href="http://Sythe.org" rel="nofollow noopener">Sythe.org</a> isn’t working for me right now</li>
<li>I’m laggin too much, I’ll do it later<br>
Demand a PM and I suggest you back out of the trade if they are unable to comply.</li>
</ol>
<p>Step 4: Ready to trade<br>
Once you have received the PM and are conviced that the person is who they claim, go ahead with the trade BUT pay attention of who you trade your items to in RuneScape. Pause and check even the first trade screen just to be sure.</p>
<p>IMPORTANT: Even some official MMs may be unknown scammers so PLEASE be cautious with whoever you are dealing with. It is recommended not to do trades of over 5mil at a time.</p>
<p>MSN Messenger Tips<br>
MSN Messenger is by far best thing to use in all kinds of trades. However, there might still be some fake MMs with similar Email addresses to the official ones offering to MM.</p>
<p>There is one simple way to avoid this.</p>
<p>In the list of official MMs, add everyone on that list to your MSN Messenger contacts in a SPECIFIC group. Name this group well and clearly:</p>
<p>Now you will clearly be able to see if the MMs Email address if correct or not. Do not fall for the “I changed my Email Address trick.”<br>
Now you know that if that person is legit, he will appear as Online in your Mods and Official MMs group.</p>
<p>Remember, if you are ever in any doubt whatsoever, completely back out of the trade. You might lose a customer, but that’s better than losing your hard earned goods.</p>
<p>i really do hope it helped.<br>
Regards,<br>
ikick</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 11:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-83796-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/complete-mms-and-black-market-guide-a-must-read/83796.rss">Complete MM&#39;s and Black market Guide- A MUST READ!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
