<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Port forward help need admin/mod or someone who knows what there doing</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forward-help-need-admin-mod-or-someone-who-knows-what-there-doing/154701</link>
    <description>ok i have Belkin router  F5D6231-4

but the last step is confusing this is what it says 

Put a checkmark in the Enable checkbox. Enter the name of the program into the Description box. It doesn&#39;t really matter what you put into this box, but something that will remind you why these ports are being forwarded would be a good idea. If you are forwarding a single port, enter that port number into both of the Inbound port and both of the Private port boxes. If you are forwarding a range of ports, enter the lowest number of that range into the left hand Inbound port and Private port boxes. Then enter the highest number of that range into the right hand Inbound port and Private port boxes. Use the Type drop down box to select the protocol type of the ports you are forwarding. Enter the ip address to forward these ports to into the Private IP address box. If you are forwarding ports so you can run a program on your computer, you should enter your computer&#39;s ip address into that box. 
And that is it! You are done! 




uhhh im confused when it says type ur ip adress,it only allows 3 keys to type. and where do i enter the static ip adress....  
[br][size=1]Posted on: October 27, 2007, 09:51:14 AM[/size][hr]btw sorry god of ikilili for wrong section</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2007 20:51:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forward-help-need-admin-mod-or-someone-who-knows-what-there-doing/154701.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Port forward help need admin/mod or someone who knows what there doing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@M_0_N_3_Y M 0 N 3 Y]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m_0_n_3_y">@M_0_N_3_Y</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok i have Belkin router  F5D6231-4</p>
<p>but the last step is confusing this is what it says</p>
<p>Put a checkmark in the Enable checkbox. Enter the name of the program into the Description box. It doesn’t really matter what you put into this box, but something that will remind you why these ports are being forwarded would be a good idea. If you are forwarding a single port, enter that port number into both of the Inbound port and both of the Private port boxes. If you are forwarding a range of ports, enter the lowest number of that range into the left hand Inbound port and Private port boxes. Then enter the highest number of that range into the right hand Inbound port and Private port boxes. Use the Type drop down box to select the protocol type of the ports you are forwarding. Enter the ip address to forward these ports to into the Private IP address box. If you are forwarding ports so you can run a program on your computer, you should enter your computer’s ip address into that box.<br>
And that is it! You are done!</p>
<p>uhhh im confused when it says type ur ip adress,it only allows 3 keys to type. and where do i enter the static ip adress…<br>
[br][size=1]Posted on: October 27, 2007, 09:51:14 AM[/size][hr]btw sorry god of ikilili for wrong section</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forward-help-need-admin-mod-or-someone-who-knows-what-there-doing/154701/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forward-help-need-admin-mod-or-someone-who-knows-what-there-doing/154701/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2007 20:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-154701-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/port-forward-help-need-admin-mod-or-someone-who-knows-what-there-doing/154701.rss">Port forward help need admin/mod or someone who knows what there doing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
