<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] REP++ You must restart the client to login if you insert wrong password</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-rep-you-must-restart-the-client-to-login-if-you-insert-wrong-password/506735</link>
    <description>Base: I use [PI] Insanity-X. 

Yeah I know it&#39;s pretty crap base but I&#39;ve improved it a lot and I have a bigg problem with my webclient at the moment.

Problem: When a user attempts to login and inputs the wrong password, the user must restart the client before they can try to login again.

Example:
If you type in your password wrong the first time you attempt to login, then you type it right the second time you attempt to login, it just says &quot;Error connecting to server.&quot; You then must restart the client and make sure you type it in correctly the first time.

This may be kind of helpful for security purposes, but if a new player goes to make an account thats already taken, they&#39;ll have to restart the client in order to try again, which just results in most of the new players quitting.

So if you have had the similiar problem, please explain how you fixed it. Or if you believe you know how to fix it, please tell me.

If you need to view my files, just tell me which ones and I&#39;ll give u the codes.

Thanks! I&#39;ll repp+ :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 16:44:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-rep-you-must-restart-the-client-to-login-if-you-insert-wrong-password/506735.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] REP++ You must restart the client to login if you insert wrong password</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@belhelmiel belhelmiel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/belhelmiel">@belhelmiel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Base: I use [PI] Insanity-X.</p>
<p>Yeah I know it’s pretty crap base but I’ve improved it a lot and I have a bigg problem with my webclient at the moment.</p>
<p>Problem: When a user attempts to login and inputs the wrong password, the user must restart the client before they can try to login again.</p>
<p>Example:<br>
If you type in your password wrong the first time you attempt to login, then you type it right the second time you attempt to login, it just says “Error connecting to server.” You then must restart the client and make sure you type it in correctly the first time.</p>
<p>This may be kind of helpful for security purposes, but if a new player goes to make an account thats already taken, they’ll have to restart the client in order to try again, which just results in most of the new players quitting.</p>
<p>So if you have had the similiar problem, please explain how you fixed it. Or if you believe you know how to fix it, please tell me.</p>
<p>If you need to view my files, just tell me which ones and I’ll give u the codes.</p>
<p>Thanks! I’ll repp+ <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-rep-you-must-restart-the-client-to-login-if-you-insert-wrong-password/506735/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-rep-you-must-restart-the-client-to-login-if-you-insert-wrong-password/506735/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 16:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506735-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-rep-you-must-restart-the-client-to-login-if-you-insert-wrong-password/506735.rss">[PI] REP++ You must restart the client to login if you insert wrong password</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
