<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ruby&#39;s PHP Tutorial Series - Lesson 1</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915</link>
    <description>Hey guys, so I thought it was about time I started creating the tutorials for this, as found in my index post, this is lesson 1 of my 11 lessons on PHP.

I&#39;ll recap what this lesson is going to cover;
An introduction to PHP.
Creating your first PHP page.
Variables and their uses.


So without further ado, here&#39;s the first step of the tutorial!
[hr]

[b]PHP 101 - An introduction to PHP.[/b]
PHP is the abbreviation for [i]Hypertext Pre-Processor[/i]. You may be thinking &quot;but that&#39;s then HPP?&quot; Yes, HPP was re-arranged to PHP for a whole manner of reasons that don&#39;t matter. PHP is probably the most widely used scripting language on the internet today. With PHP, you can do things like create username and password login pages, check details from a form, create forums, picture galleries, surveys, and a whole lot more. If you&#39;ve come across a web page that ends in PHP, then this page usually has some programming code to liven up the plain, old HTML.

PHP is what&#39;s known as a server-sided language. This is because PHP doesn&#39;t get executed on your computer, it gets executed on the computer that requested the page. They&#39;re then displayed in the browser.

Okay, so that&#39;s more or less the introduction to PHP, it isn&#39;t required that you know all of that information, that&#39;s just for people who don&#39;t know what it&#39;s for. So, moving swiftly on;

[b]Your first PHP page.[/b]
Okay, so here&#39;s how you would go about creating your first page in PHP.

First of all, unlike HTML, PHP doesn&#39;t show up by just simply clicking the file. With PHP, you either need web space, or a server. If you don&#39;t have web space, I suggest you download [url=http://www.wampserver.com/en/download.php]this.[/url]

Okay, so hopefully now you have downloaded and installed wampserver. This basically creates a server on your PC, so you can now test your scripts.

So, if the download and installation worked correctly, you&#39;ll now have a new icon in your tray, next to the clock. You can control your server from here, stop it, start it, whatever.
You  now want to click on [b]localhost[/b] and a page should appear. Click the link under Tools called phpinfo().

If a page appears showing you all your information associated with PHP, congratulations, you&#39;ve done it all correctly!

Some tips;
When saving your PHP files, save them to the WWW directory.
When launching your PHP files, type in the address bar of your browser &quot;http://localhost/SCRIPTNAME.php&quot; your server knows where the www folder is and it doesn&#39;t need to be told where the &quot;wamp&quot; folder is. Obviously, replace SCRIPTNAME with your file name.

If you have any problems, redo the previous steps. If that doesn&#39;t work visit the [url=http://www.wampserver.com/phorum/]wampserver forums[/url].

So now, on to actually writing a script!

What you want to do is create a new file named [b]test.php[/b] and place it in your WWW directory of wamp. We&#39;re going to create a file that displays the text &quot;Hello there, moparians!&quot;

First step - open up test.php in your preferred text editor.

Second step - making it display the text.

So, whenever you&#39;re trying to display PHP code, you need to tell the browser you&#39;re using PHP coding at this point. You do this by the use of the &lt;?php parameter. So put that at the top of your file. Now, move on to a different line and type the word [b]echo[/b] followed by &quot;Hello there, Moparians!&quot;; you then want to go to a new line again and tell your browser that you no longer want to use PHP coding, you do that by typing [b]?&gt;[/b] so now your whole code will look like this:
[code]
&lt;?php
echo &quot;Hello there, Moparians!&quot;;
?&gt;
[/code]

Save the file, then open it in your browser by typing &quot;http://localhost/test.php&quot; this should now bring up a page that says - Hello there, Moparians!

If it doesn&#39;t, you&#39;ve not completed all of the steps, go back and read over it.
Otherwise, congratulations, you&#39;ve just created your first PHP script!
[hr]

So now on to the next part of the tutorial;

In this section of the tutorial, we&#39;re going to work on [b]Variables[/b]. For those of you who don&#39;t know what a variable is, a variable is more or less a storage point. You put code into these to use and manipulate throughout your code, these can store both numbers and text.

Here&#39;s how you&#39;d go about storing a number in a PHP Variable;
In PHP, variables are defined by a dollar sign &quot;$&quot; so i&#39;ll show you what the variable code should look like and then I&#39;ll talk you through it.
[code]
&lt;?php

$moparscape = 10;

echo &quot;$moparscape&quot;;

?&gt;
[/code]

So, what the above code is doing.

at $moparscape, it&#39;s defining the variable moparscape. So that anywhere in your code that you type $moparscape, the code is going to see it as the value on the right of your equals sign.

Also, I should&#39;ve said this earlier, but I&#39;m saying it now, end your php coding lines with a semicolon &quot;[b];[/b]&quot; unless instructed otherwise, or you know it&#39;s wrong.

Back to explaining the code;
Then after the variable of moparscape has been assigned the value of 10, we want to test our variable. So, remember the echo function we tried out before this? We use that again. We echo the variable $moparscape, this being assigned the value of 10 means the browser reads it as 10, understand?

Congratulations, you&#39;ve just created your first variable! 

Obviously, this isn&#39;t the only variable in PHP, this is only for assigning numbers to. I&#39;ll now show you how to assign text to a variable.

So, what you want to do is most of the above, but the difference here is that instead of just doing &gt;
[code]
$moparscape = the best community ever!;
[/code]

We&#39;re going to wrap the text we want to be assigned to the $moparscape variable in speech marks - &quot; &quot;.
So it&#39;d look like;
[code]
$moparscape = &quot;the best community ever!&quot;;
[/code]

So now, your whole code will look like;
[code]
&lt;?php

$moparscape = &quot;The best community ever!&quot;;

echo &quot;$moparscape&quot;;

?&gt;
[/code]

So there you go, you can now assign both text and numbers to variables in PHP, congratulations!

Until tomorrow, I suggest you mess around with your variables and practise them by doing stuff like this;
[code]
&lt;?php
$community = &quot;Moparscape!&quot;;
$rate = &quot;10 out of 10&quot;;

echo &quot;What&#39;s the best community ever? $community&quot;;
echo &quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
echo &quot;What would you rate $community?&quot;;
echo &quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;
echo &quot;I&#39;d rate it $rate!&quot;;

?&gt;
[/code]

So now, you can screw around with variables until tomorrow, when I release my second lesson which is slightly more advanced with statements, take a look at my index found [urlhttp://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,548780.0.html]here[/url] for more information on my lessons.

Now, that&#39;s all I&#39;m going to speak about today, hang in there until tomorrow!

Ruby.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 17:51:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ruby&#39;s PHP Tutorial Series - Lesson 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I abandoned these tutorials, sorry.</p>
<p>I had too much going on in my life at the time, however, if you check back in this board now and again you’ll see a new PHP tutorial from me at least twice a week.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 17:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445915-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915.rss">Ruby&#39;s PHP Tutorial Series - Lesson 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ruby&#39;s PHP Tutorial Series - Lesson 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dunder_Mifflin1 Dunder  Mifflin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dunder_mifflin1">@Dunder_Mifflin1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Better way to open it is use notepad ++ and view your work in firefox/Chrome etc. using the toolbar. Great Tut though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 17:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445915-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915.rss">Ruby&#39;s PHP Tutorial Series - Lesson 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ruby&#39;s PHP Tutorial Series - Lesson 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@justaguy justaguy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/justaguy">@justaguy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Even though it’s the basics, you should also include using single quotation characters to echo data and the difference between string interpolation with double-quotes versus just single-quotes.</p>
<p>I have mixed opinions about outputting $moparscape in just double-quotes in the tutorial, but I will lay back on that one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 22:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445915-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915.rss">Ruby&#39;s PHP Tutorial Series - Lesson 1</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ruby&#39;s PHP Tutorial Series - Lesson 1</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, so I thought it was about time I started creating the tutorials for this, as found in my index post, this is lesson 1 of my 11 lessons on PHP.</p>
<p>I’ll recap what this lesson is going to cover;<br>
An introduction to PHP.<br>
Creating your first PHP page.<br>
Variables and their uses.</p>
<p>So without further ado, here’s the first step of the tutorial!<br>
[hr]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">PHP 101 - An introduction to PHP.</span><br>
PHP is the abbreviation for <span class="bbcode-i">Hypertext Pre-Processor</span>. You may be thinking “but that’s then HPP?” Yes, HPP was re-arranged to PHP for a whole manner of reasons that don’t matter. PHP is probably the most widely used scripting language on the internet today. With PHP, you can do things like create username and password login pages, check details from a form, create forums, picture galleries, surveys, and a whole lot more. If you’ve come across a web page that ends in PHP, then this page usually has some programming code to liven up the plain, old HTML.</p>
<p>PHP is what’s known as a server-sided language. This is because PHP doesn’t get executed on your computer, it gets executed on the computer that requested the page. They’re then displayed in the browser.</p>
<p>Okay, so that’s more or less the introduction to PHP, it isn’t required that you know all of that information, that’s just for people who don’t know what it’s for. So, moving swiftly on;</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Your first PHP page.</span><br>
Okay, so here’s how you would go about creating your first page in PHP.</p>
<p>First of all, unlike HTML, PHP doesn’t show up by just simply clicking the file. With PHP, you either need web space, or a server. If you don’t have web space, I suggest you download <a href="http://www.wampserver.com/en/download.php" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">this.</a></p>
<p>Okay, so hopefully now you have downloaded and installed wampserver. This basically creates a server on your PC, so you can now test your scripts.</p>
<p>So, if the download and installation worked correctly, you’ll now have a new icon in your tray, next to the clock. You can control your server from here, stop it, start it, whatever.<br>
You  now want to click on <span class="bbcode-b">localhost</span> and a page should appear. Click the link under Tools called phpinfo().</p>
<p>If a page appears showing you all your information associated with PHP, congratulations, you’ve done it all correctly!</p>
<p>Some tips;<br>
When saving your PHP files, save them to the WWW directory.<br>
When launching your PHP files, type in the address bar of your browser “<a href="http://localhost/SCRIPTNAME.php" rel="nofollow noopener">http://localhost/SCRIPTNAME.php</a>” your server knows where the www folder is and it doesn’t need to be told where the “wamp” folder is. Obviously, replace SCRIPTNAME with your file name.</p>
<p>If you have any problems, redo the previous steps. If that doesn’t work visit the <a href="http://www.wampserver.com/phorum/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">wampserver forums</a>.</p>
<p>So now, on to actually writing a script!</p>
<p>What you want to do is create a new file named <span class="bbcode-b">test.php</span> and place it in your WWW directory of wamp. We’re going to create a file that displays the text “Hello there, moparians!”</p>
<p>First step - open up test.php in your preferred text editor.</p>
<p>Second step - making it display the text.</p>
<p>So, whenever you’re trying to display PHP code, you need to tell the browser you’re using PHP coding at this point. You do this by the use of the &lt;?php parameter. So put that at the top of your file. Now, move on to a different line and type the word [b]echo[/b] followed by "Hello there, Moparians!"; you then want to go to a new line again and tell your browser that you no longer want to use PHP coding, you do that by typing [b]?&gt;[/b] so now your whole code will look like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php
echo "Hello there, Moparians!";
?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>Save the file, then open it in your browser by typing “<a href="http://localhost/test.php" rel="nofollow noopener">http://localhost/test.php</a>” this should now bring up a page that says - Hello there, Moparians!</p>
<p>If it doesn’t, you’ve not completed all of the steps, go back and read over it.<br>
Otherwise, congratulations, you’ve just created your first PHP script!<br>
[hr]</p>
<p>So now on to the next part of the tutorial;</p>
<p>In this section of the tutorial, we’re going to work on <span class="bbcode-b">Variables</span>. For those of you who don’t know what a variable is, a variable is more or less a storage point. You put code into these to use and manipulate throughout your code, these can store both numbers and text.</p>
<p>Here’s how you’d go about storing a number in a PHP Variable;<br>
In PHP, variables are defined by a dollar sign “$” so i’ll show you what the variable code should look like and then I’ll talk you through it.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php

$moparscape = 10;

echo "$moparscape";

?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>So, what the above code is doing.</p>
<p>at $moparscape, it’s defining the variable moparscape. So that anywhere in your code that you type $moparscape, the code is going to see it as the value on the right of your equals sign.</p>
<p>Also, I should’ve said this earlier, but I’m saying it now, end your php coding lines with a semicolon “<span class="bbcode-b">;</span>” unless instructed otherwise, or you know it’s wrong.</p>
<p>Back to explaining the code;<br>
Then after the variable of moparscape has been assigned the value of 10, we want to test our variable. So, remember the echo function we tried out before this? We use that again. We echo the variable $moparscape, this being assigned the value of 10 means the browser reads it as 10, understand?</p>
<p>Congratulations, you’ve just created your first variable!</p>
<p>Obviously, this isn’t the only variable in PHP, this is only for assigning numbers to. I’ll now show you how to assign text to a variable.</p>
<p>So, what you want to do is most of the above, but the difference here is that instead of just doing &gt;</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">$moparscape = the best community ever!;</code></pre>
<p>We’re going to wrap the text we want to be assigned to the $moparscape variable in speech marks - " ".<br>
So it’d look like;</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">$moparscape = "the best community ever!";</code></pre>
<p>So now, your whole code will look like;</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php

$moparscape = "The best community ever!";

echo "$moparscape";

?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>So there you go, you can now assign both text and numbers to variables in PHP, congratulations!</p>
<p>Until tomorrow, I suggest you mess around with your variables and practise them by doing stuff like this;</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;?php
$community = "Moparscape!";
$rate = "10 out of 10";

echo "What's the best community ever? $community";
echo "&lt;br /&gt;";
echo "What would you rate $community?";
echo "&lt;br /&gt;";
echo "I'd rate it $rate!";

?&gt;</code></pre>
<p>So now, you can screw around with variables until tomorrow, when I release my second lesson which is slightly more advanced with statements, take a look at my index found [urlhttp://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,548780.0.html]here[/url] for more information on my lessons.</p>
<p>Now, that’s all I’m going to speak about today, hang in there until tomorrow!</p>
<p>Ruby.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 20:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445915-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rubys-php-tutorial-series-lesson-1/445915.rss">Ruby&#39;s PHP Tutorial Series - Lesson 1</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
