<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can someone please help fix this dupe</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-please-help-fix-this-dupe/260768</link>
    <description>Okay if anyone knows how to put a trade timer in can you help me please. I&#39;ve worked on my devo server forever now and I need to fix the trading dupe. If I cant do this I dont know what I&#39;m going to do I really dont, can someone please give me a walk through on how to add a trade timer so that players have to wait in between adding items to the trade window. If anyone can do this (I&#39;m not saying you want it this is not a bribe consider it a reward) I am offering you my source with all working skills and co owner on my server.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 00:00:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-please-help-fix-this-dupe/260768.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can someone please help fix this dupe</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Halflingblade Halflingblade]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/halflingblade">@Halflingblade</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay if anyone knows how to put a trade timer in can you help me please. I’ve worked on my devo server forever now and I need to fix the trading dupe. If I cant do this I dont know what I’m going to do I really dont, can someone please give me a walk through on how to add a trade timer so that players have to wait in between adding items to the trade window. If anyone can do this (I’m not saying you want it this is not a bribe consider it a reward) I am offering you my source with all working skills and co owner on my server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-please-help-fix-this-dupe/260768/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-please-help-fix-this-dupe/260768/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 00:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-260768-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/can-someone-please-help-fix-this-dupe/260768.rss">Can someone please help fix this dupe</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
