<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>NRS3 V4 Big Problem - Please Help!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nrs3-v4-big-problem-please-help/520668</link>
    <description>So I use to run my own server for me and my friends, and it was awesome, i loved adding new things and whatnot, So recently after my old computer broke, I got the files back, but they do not work anymore, For some Reason there are no walls, and all that, I&#39;m almost 100% Positive its not the cache, I Have tried over 40 Caches, and i&#39;m not even joking, I Think its the client, but i cant seem to find one that works, I&#39;m trying to run it local btw, since my new router no longer lets me host for some reason, anyways if you know why im getting this problem please help! and if you have a working client for NRS3 V4 Could you send it to me or post a link? tyvm if someone does help me!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 22:52:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nrs3-v4-big-problem-please-help/520668.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>NRS3 V4 Big Problem - Please Help!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IHitSpecs IHitSpecs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ihitspecs">@IHitSpecs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I use to run my own server for me and my friends, and it was awesome, i loved adding new things and whatnot, So recently after my old computer broke, I got the files back, but they do not work anymore, For some Reason there are no walls, and all that, I’m almost 100% Positive its not the cache, I Have tried over 40 Caches, and i’m not even joking, I Think its the client, but i cant seem to find one that works, I’m trying to run it local btw, since my new router no longer lets me host for some reason, anyways if you know why im getting this problem please help! and if you have a working client for NRS3 V4 Could you send it to me or post a link? tyvm if someone does help me!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nrs3-v4-big-problem-please-help/520668/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nrs3-v4-big-problem-please-help/520668/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 22:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520668-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/nrs3-v4-big-problem-please-help/520668.rss">NRS3 V4 Big Problem - Please Help!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
