<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Few qustions, if you may</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890</link>
    <description>Hey guys,
This is few years i&#39;m following Mopar servers, and still there&#39;s a lot of things i&#39;m just being confused about:

1. what&#39;s that numbering for the client? (508, 517...) I can guess it&#39;s some kind of version of the base code or something like that, but i see people moving from an high version to low version.. so.. what&#39;s that?

2. I see guides of how to add that and how to change that, but i can&#39;t find guides for changing the base, like the making new items (not just adding, but making), how to copy things from the last RS to the server/client (the current client theme, new monsters, items, animations, sounds, etc.)

3. for some reason i can&#39;t find even not one server that tries to just have all the features from RS and to stay updated all the time. i believe that after having all the features it is much more easier to make things the way you want. (i&#39;m talking about features and bug fixes, not RS clone! features as dual arena or all skills working)

4. how&#39;s that there are servers that can&#39;t run on linux?! i mean, it&#39;s Java after all, and if it can&#39;t run on linux it means nothing but bad coding.

I&#39;m hoping to have serious answers, if you got something negative/childish to say i&#39;d be glad you to keep it to yourself as it doesn&#39;t do nothing but saying you&#39;re fool.

Thanks guys :)
Dor.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 14:12:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Few qustions, if you may</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ahyo Ahyo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ahyo">@Ahyo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Umm for question 3, if you are planning on staying updated with runescape thats fine, just make sure you dont copy thier exact deob, and make sure u dont have 3+ worlds on ur server, It could lead to legal action taken on you by jagex themselves. It happened to frugoscape and to silab, but silab changed thier client.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 14:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352890-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890.rss">Few qustions, if you may</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Few qustions, if you may</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ddorda Ddorda]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ddorda">@Ddorda</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“supernovarsps, post:2, topic:352890”]the first question is the deob. The graphics and the higher it is the more closer / recent it is to runescape so having new runescape items without them being considered customs.</p>
<p>the second question is models. You have to make your own models and ints with it. Whats that? Ints turns the models into the ingame items for players can use.</p>
<p>third question is it can take a few months like 2 months for a new item or feature to come out on runescape private server. Then thats reffering to question one when a new feature comes out then it will be raised e.g 317 474 508 525 and so on. The bigger the update is the higher the number is it goes up on its deob.</p>
<p>fourth question you have to portforward and make class paths. If your sure that you cant run on it, it’s because you cant portforward and you will have to find a hoster or a vps.[/quote]</p>
<p>hey there and thanks for your fast respond <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>so… actually anyone can invite an higher deob? if i take 601 with 602 cache (…?) an make things work closer to RS and fix bugs it will be called 603?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>modules - how do i make these? i guess i need some 3d editor like Blender? what’s the most used one for Mopars?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>and who decides the deob number? check what i wrote on 1. who adds the things? from where they come from?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>of course linux can port forward. i’m not sure i can;t run on it, i just see it is written everywhere. people makes .exe files only instead of making a compiled java, and for that reason Mopar servers/clients on Linux is still behind (IMHO).</p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 13:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352890-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890.rss">Few qustions, if you may</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Few qustions, if you may</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@supernovarsps supernovarsps]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/supernovarsps">@supernovarsps</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>the first question is the deob. The graphics and the higher it is the more closer / recent it is to runescape so having new runescape items without them being considered customs.</p>
<p>the second question is models. You have to make your own models and ints with it. Whats that? Ints turns the models into the ingame items for players can use.</p>
<p>third question is it can take a few months like 2 months for a new item or feature to come out on runescape private server. Then thats reffering to question one when a new feature comes out then it will be raised e.g 317 474 508 525 and so on. The bigger the update is the higher the number is it goes up on its deob.</p>
<p>fourth question you have to portforward and make class paths. If your sure that you cant run on it, it’s because you cant portforward and you will have to find a hoster or a vps.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 13:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352890-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890.rss">Few qustions, if you may</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Few qustions, if you may</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ddorda Ddorda]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ddorda">@Ddorda</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,<br>
This is few years i’m following Mopar servers, and still there’s a lot of things i’m just being confused about:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>what’s that numbering for the client? (508, 517…) I can guess it’s some kind of version of the base code or something like that, but i see people moving from an high version to low version… so… what’s that?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>I see guides of how to add that and how to change that, but i can’t find guides for changing the base, like the making new items (not just adding, but making), how to copy things from the last RS to the server/client (the current client theme, new monsters, items, animations, sounds, etc.)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>for some reason i can’t find even not one server that tries to just have all the features from RS and to stay updated all the time. i believe that after having all the features it is much more easier to make things the way you want. (i’m talking about features and bug fixes, not RS clone! features as dual arena or all skills working)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>how’s that there are servers that can’t run on linux?! i mean, it’s Java after all, and if it can’t run on linux it means nothing but bad coding.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I’m hoping to have serious answers, if you got something negative/childish to say i’d be glad you to keep it to yourself as it doesn’t do nothing but saying you’re fool.</p>
<p>Thanks guys <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
Dor.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 13:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352890-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/few-qustions-if-you-may/352890.rss">Few qustions, if you may</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
