<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315</link>
    <description>So like I made a thing. It&#39;s pretty cool and I&#39;ve completed my goal for a rough demo before sitting down and designing a full-fledged game. Here&#39;s a little backstory on it.

I researched the marching cubes algorithm for a long time, because I didn&#39;t understand how it worked. After making a C#/XNA version of it, I realized how simple it was. I wanted to migrate it to the GPU, so since I had little knowledge of C++ I decided to use SlimDX to use DirectX 10/11. When it came time to implement MC, it occurred to me that C# wasn&#39;t made for the DirectX API in a thin wrapper. So I switched to C++ and wrote down a series of major steps I would take, and if I succeeded I would sit down and design a true optimized and flexible engine. I did. Those steps were, taken from the word document:

1.	C++ Marching Cubes (direct conversion of C# version)
2.	C++ Marching Cubes on GPU
3.	C++ Marching Cubes Mesh Modifying
4.	C++ Marching Cubes Lighting

Step 1 turned out to be more than just a direct conversion because I had to completely write everything essentially from scratch. There were no basic shaders to use, no simple shader wrappers, no one-line texture loading/setting (well, you can sort of load textures with one line via D3DX11CreateShaderResourceViewFromFile but you&#39;re still responsible for the sampler state and error handling), no automatic window creation, etc.

But enough of that. Here&#39;s a screenshot with super basic terrain generation and modification. I dug into a mountain and build a sort of entrance around it. Notice how it&#39;s dark inside the cave ;) There is light occluding for sky and point light.
[img]http://img18.imageshack.us/img18/2167/bktn.png[/img]

NOTE: I didn&#39;t make the textures. The grass is Riemer&#39;s and the rock texture is the first one that appeared on Google Images.

So why am I posting this here? Well I originally planned on keeping the development secret after finishing all 4 steps (I&#39;ve been posting videos for each one), but I realized I really like talking about what I made. It&#39;s great motivation and gives the feel of an accomplishment for a step. It&#39;s also really important to build up a community if there is any interest in popularizing/commercializing a game. If I went away and months down the road showed off an alpha, it wouldn&#39;t magically become widespread, so I must build it up over time.

In conclusion of the boring stuff: I made this entirely with C++ using nothing but the standard library, the Windows API, the DirectX SDK/DirectX 11, a conversion of some C# simplex noise code I used in my old voxel engine (I don&#39;t remember where I found it), and some public marching cubes tables. No one with any sanity would create those themselves. I used Visual Studio 2013 because it has some helpful features, like C++ 11 (more extensively than 2012) and build-in HLSL compiling support.



Okay. So this engine is completely unoptimized. There are no &quot;chunks&quot;, level of detail support, CPU- and GPU-combined mesh generation, or anything like that. It&#39;s very straight-forward. Not to say it performs terribly, but for example, all mesh is generated every frame. When you modify the terrain, the entire &#39;noise map&#39; texture is sent for the whole map. If you have a high-performing graphics card that supports high bandwidth transfers, this won&#39;t be an issue for you.

[b]Requirements[/b]
-A graphics card supporting DirectX 11 and Shader Model 4. I&#39;ve run this on a school computer with an integrated chip supporting DirectX 11 and the screen flickered on and off until the computer blue screened. This might happen to you, so be cautious.
-About 32MB memory for the program (high, I know)
-At least like 16MB RAM for your graphics card. This is a rounded-up estimate. You probably really only need like 8 to store the textures. I&#39;m not sure how the geometry shader output will affect the memory.
-A graphics card/slot that supports high bandwidth operations is recommended
-Support for Direct Input 8
-You can likely get away with a poor CPU. The only &quot;heavy&quot; work being done on the CPU is the initial generation and the light calculations.
[size=10pt][b]-Visual C++ 2013 x86 redistributable - http://www.microsoft.com/en-us/download/details.aspx?id=40784 (The 64-bit build has no benefits over the 32-bit, so there&#39;s no point in releasing a 64-bit build)[/b][/size]
[u]-If it doesn&#39;t run for you, install this: http://www.microsoft.com/en-us/download/details.aspx?id=8109[/u]

 [b]Controls[/b]
-WASD to move
-Left click to remove mesh, right click to place
--If holding shift, it will remove/place whole blocks at a time. If not, it will do so gradually
--If holding control, it will just attempt to update the light. This was for testing purposes and has no use
-Space to move the point light
--You can hold space and it will follow you. It has a delay that will allow it to only update every 4 frames. It doesn&#39;t impact performance much if it&#39;s every frame, but I wanted to see how smooth it would look with a delay and I think it&#39;s fine. It also has a light level of about 50%. Again, not that it&#39;ll really impact performance if it was at 100%, but I wanted to differentiate it from the sky light. The engine has support for an infinite amount of point lights, but I was too lazy to implement multiple light placement, so this is all there is.

[b]My specs as a reference (I get over 300 fps)[/b]
-AMD Radeon HD 7870 (2GB GDDR5 RAM)
-AMD FX-8350 @ 4.00GHz
-8GB DDR3 RAM

[b]Download:[/b] http://www.mediafire.com/download/ort47r8vq2jatr0/Freeform%20Terrain

[b]Notes[/b]
I&#39;ve tested it and I think everything works fine. I&#39;ve had pretty bad luck with the lighting though, so if anything seems like it&#39;s wrong, let me know. As for artifacts regarding the lighting, I&#39;m aware that the mesh might need to be about 2 blocks dense for the light to completely cut off. If the mesh is thin, it&#39;ll look like the light is bleeding through but it doesn&#39;t travel through the rest of the dark area. This is okay, since I haven&#39;t tweaked that part much. It doesn&#39;t actually impact the lighting either.

I&#39;m also aware that resizing the window doesn&#39;t resize the internal resolution. The code says it should, but the program suggests otherwise. What happens is the image just gets stretched and there is a weird offset with the camera position and target. I&#39;d recommend just keeping it as the default resolution (720p).

Also the mouse doesn&#39;t get centered or hidden. This is because it was faster to put the mouse at a random position that is [i]likely[/i] to be inside the window rather than add the window&#39;s position to half the size.

Finally, vsync is enabled and there&#39;s no way to turn it off. I never added my own framerate limiter and this was the easiest way to do it. That said, there is no frame-skipping or any other method of benchmarking. I&#39;ve just been using Fraps to measure my framerate because, even though it might be a little off, it&#39;s accurate enough to determine if I&#39;m getting 60fps or not.



Anyway, enjoy and let me know what you guys think. I do have plans to develop a full-fledged game out of this and have a lot already planned. Since you people are doing me a favor by testing it, provided I do get to a commercial release at some point, everyone here would get it for free.

~Lin</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 04:27:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lin!!! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/31</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 04:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taharok, post:29, topic:538315”][quote author=Lin link=topic=657139.msg4397187#msg4397187 date=1389486369]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>One thing you can do is change your linking to MSVCR to be static rather than dynamic, that way it won’t lead to a dependence on msvcr10.dll or whichever version of Visual Studio you’re using (this is the dll installed by the redistributable, among a few others). You want to set it from /MD or /MDd to /MT or /MTd, respectively. Can be done in Visual Studio project settings somewhere, not sure where off the top of my head. Probably system or code generation or something. If it leads to linker errors, then you won’t be able to do it. It’s not uncommon to get linker errors because if you’re statically linking to a library that was compiled with MSVCR, then you’ll get multiple definitions and stuff.<br>
[/quote]Yeah I assumed as much. For some reason though, even after installing the redist, depends.exe reported missing MSVCPxx.DLL. I thought about statically linking it but it was much easier to just include the DLL than go through the frustration of dealing with linker errors.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m assuming you’re using Visual Studio 2013 to build it. Also, is your project in /MD or /MDd mode? Better yet: did provide us with the debug or release builds?[/quote]Yes, 2013. /MDd on the debug, /MD in the release. I provided the 32-bit release build.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 05:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Lin, post:28, topic:538315”][quote author=Taharok link=topic=657139.msg4397103#msg4397103 date=1389473363]<br>
One thing you can do is change your linking to MSVCR to be static rather than dynamic, that way it won’t lead to a dependence on msvcr10.dll or whichever version of Visual Studio you’re using (this is the dll installed by the redistributable, among a few others). You want to set it from /MD or /MDd to /MT or /MTd, respectively. Can be done in Visual Studio project settings somewhere, not sure where off the top of my head. Probably system or code generation or something. If it leads to linker errors, then you won’t be able to do it. It’s not uncommon to get linker errors because if you’re statically linking to a library that was compiled with MSVCR, then you’ll get multiple definitions and stuff.<br>
[/quote]Yeah I assumed as much. For some reason though, even after installing the redist, depends.exe reported missing MSVCPxx.DLL. I thought about statically linking it but it was much easier to just include the DLL than go through the frustration of dealing with linker errors.[/quote]</p>
<p>I’m assuming you’re using Visual Studio 2013 to build it. Also, is your project in /MD or /MDd mode? Better yet: did provide us with the debug or release builds?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 03:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taharok, post:27, topic:538315”]One thing you can do is change your linking to MSVCR to be static rather than dynamic, that way it won’t lead to a dependence on msvcr10.dll or whichever version of Visual Studio you’re using (this is the dll installed by the redistributable, among a few others). You want to set it from /MD or /MDd to /MT or /MTd, respectively. Can be done in Visual Studio project settings somewhere, not sure where off the top of my head. Probably system or code generation or something. If it leads to linker errors, then you won’t be able to do it. It’s not uncommon to get linker errors because if you’re statically linking to a library that was compiled with MSVCR, then you’ll get multiple definitions and stuff.[/quote]Yeah I assumed as much. For some reason though, even after installing the redist, depends.exe reported missing MSVCPxx.DLL. I thought about statically linking it but it was much easier to just include the DLL than go through the frustration of dealing with linker errors.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 00:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>One thing you can do is change your linking to MSVCR to be static rather than dynamic, that way it won’t lead to a dependence on msvcr10.dll or whichever version of Visual Studio you’re using (this is the dll installed by the redistributable, among a few others). You want to set it from /MD or /MDd to /MT or /MTd, respectively. Can be done in Visual Studio project settings somewhere, not sure where off the top of my head. Probably system or code generation or something. If it leads to linker errors, then you won’t be able to do it. It’s not uncommon to get linker errors because if you’re statically linking to a library that was compiled with MSVCR, then you’ll get multiple definitions and stuff.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 20:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@silabsoft RuneAgent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silabsoft">@silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>commands not working tried ::item 995 100000 no results please help1</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 20:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>does this have ponies in it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 10:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“HcoJustin, post:23, topic:538315”]The controls work much better now, but it seems if I try to raise the terrain too high it crashes.[/quote]This is to be expected, as I never added any checks to see if the terrain being added exceeded the map’s boundaries. Like I stated in the original post, this is just a rough build testing the main features. There is no polish or optimization.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 07:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@HcoJustin HcoJustin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hcojustin">@HcoJustin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The controls work much better now, but it seems if I try to raise the terrain too high it crashes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 07:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lin you should get on irc and chat about your progress Evil_ is also back too!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 05:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Jmood, post:20, topic:538315”]Lin what happened to your other project that Voxel engine?[/quote]It turned out to be the product of bad planning and overall game design. I had visions for it, but they kept changing and eventually by the time I dropped it I was left with an engine that went through so many changes that it wasn’t what I wanted it to be anymore. There were so many things I wanted to implement, like for example, destroying part of an enemy and making the enemy work without the destroyed parts. When I made my model editor for it, I created bones that would have been able to have been destroyed but only one bounding box for the whole thing. It was a major letdown and with my vision constantly changing, it was best it got scrapped.</p>
<p>This game is sort of a “sequel” of sorts to that one. The way I see it is it’s voxel engine take 2. Same cool ideas I originally had, but managed much better and with more opportunities. I’ve got lots of plans and I’m actually writing everything down. Between how the core engine will work with dividing the work between the CPU and GPU, to how I’ll make enemies, to how items will work; it’s all being written down and I’m going to begin writing the code when I know exactly what I want to make.</p>
<p>Also a sidenote. I started using Twitter entirely for the purpose of mentioning this game’s progress. If you’re interested, <a href="https://twitter.com/ProgrammerLin" rel="nofollow noopener">https://twitter.com/ProgrammerLin</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 04:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@doom_j doom_j]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/doom_j">@doom_j</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lin what happened to your other project that Voxel engine?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 04:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Interesting. It seems to be computer-specific. It works for me and my friend, but my roommate experiences the same issue. An initial guess is the volume texture’s stride is varying between computers. Rather than send the data in the size of the texture, I have to do (x+2)<em>(y+2)</em>(z+2). I’ve noticed I only need to do this for the current dimensions. With higher dimensions I don’t need the +2. Very interesting. I’ll have to look into why that is.</p>
<p>EDIT: That was the problem. Here is the fixed version. <a href="http://www.mediafire.com/download/ort47r8vq2jatr0/Freeform%20Terrain" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.mediafire.com/download/ort47r8vq2jatr0/Freeform%20Terrain</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 22:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="17" data-topic="538315">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/hcojustin/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> HcoJustin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I can move just fine, but any other form of input crashes. Runs beautifully up until then though</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Exactly the same as what’s happening to me</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 19:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@HcoJustin HcoJustin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hcojustin">@HcoJustin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can move just fine, but any other form of input crashes. Runs beautifully up until then though</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 19:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="15" data-topic="538315">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/lin/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Lin:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Has anyone actually managed to download and run this? If so, what are your specs and what was your performance like?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I got it running but it crashed as soon as I clicked anywhere <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 16:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Terraforming, post:14, topic:538315”][quote author=Flame_ link=topic=657139.msg4396329#msg4396329 date=1389232388]<br>
Is that what you’ve been working on this whole time?<br>
I can’t test this because Apple is the clearly superior operating system, but from what I read and the image you showed it looks pretty cool. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Lol’ed…</p>
<p>I love you say Apple is the best but you can’t play it on it? lol wat?[/quote]It clearly sarcasm. Please, try to keep the posts on-topic.</p>
<p>Has anyone actually managed to download and run this? If so, what are your specs and what was your performance like?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 09:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Terraforming Terraforming]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/terraforming">@Terraforming</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Flame_, post:2, topic:538315”]Is that what you’ve been working on this whole time?<br>
I can’t test this because Apple is the clearly superior operating system, but from what I read and the image you showed it looks pretty cool. :-)[/quote]</p>
<p>Lol’ed…</p>
<p>I love you say Apple is the best but you can’t play it on it? lol wat?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 09:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great work Lin, I will test it later!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 08:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Pwnd, post:11, topic:538315”][quote author=sinisoul link=topic=657139.msg4396642#msg4396642 date=1389322787]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>i thought you died</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[/quote]</p>
<p>TIME FOR SPAM[/quote]</p>
<p>I thought he did die! Great job Lin.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 03:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“sinisoul, post:10, topic:538315”][quote author=The Soul link=topic=657139.msg4396637#msg4396637 date=1389320900]<br>
i thought you died<br>
[/quote][/quote]</p>
<p>TIME FOR SPAM</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sinisoul sini]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sinisoul">@sinisoul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="538315">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 The Soul:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i thought you died</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 02:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_soul The Soul]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_soul">@the_soul</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i thought you died</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 02:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is really cool, you’ve been sending me pics here and there while you were working on but this picture looks way more complete</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 01:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hi MoparScape</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice work.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 18:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-538315-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hi-moparscape/538315.rss">Hi MoparScape</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
