<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please Read Important</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-important/409146</link>
    <description>For some reason I&#39;ve been having trouble with adding an autocatche downloader, so I&#39;ve been unable to .jar my client. If someone can .jar my client, I&#39;m willing to pay 6m and 350 XATS for them to do so. If you&#39;re interested, please PM me or leave a comment and I&#39;ll send you a private message with a link for the client download. The server is currently online and everything is working, I just need someone to .jar it for me. I understand that people are supposed to do it for free, but it seems like a difficult job and I&#39;m willing to pay a reward.

Many Thanks,

Resent</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 19:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-important/409146.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please Read Important</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Resent Resent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/resent">@Resent</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For some reason I’ve been having trouble with adding an autocatche downloader, so I’ve been unable to .jar my client. If someone can .jar my client, I’m willing to pay 6m and 350 XATS for them to do so. If you’re interested, please PM me or leave a comment and I’ll send you a private message with a link for the client download. The server is currently online and everything is working, I just need someone to .jar it for me. I understand that people are supposed to do it for free, but it seems like a difficult job and I’m willing to pay a reward.</p>
<p>Many Thanks,</p>
<p>Resent</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-important/409146/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-important/409146/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-409146-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-read-important/409146.rss">Please Read Important</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
