<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Standard base source?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standard-base-source/268857</link>
    <description>Alright. Just a quick post, and my first post. :D

Anyhow, I&#39;m looking for a base for a server and client that I can use for mine and a friends server. We want it to be completely standard though. Meaning it has all the maps, but not much else. We want all the information there, but none of it applied to the game so we can just completely rebuild it how we want. I had one of these before but seem to have lost it. Any help is appreciated.

And another simple question. I&#39;m just going to play around with Delta to learn the extreme basics, just wondering if it&#39;s possible to change the level cap from 99 to something else? I was planning on allowing combat skills to be levelled up to 120, to give some people an edge in PvP. If it is possible, can you just give me the line which says what the level cap is? I&#39;ll figure it out myself from there.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 09:58:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standard-base-source/268857.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Standard base source?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Murderbox Murderbox]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/murderbox">@Murderbox</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright. Just a quick post, and my first post. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Anyhow, I’m looking for a base for a server and client that I can use for mine and a friends server. We want it to be completely standard though. Meaning it has all the maps, but not much else. We want all the information there, but none of it applied to the game so we can just completely rebuild it how we want. I had one of these before but seem to have lost it. Any help is appreciated.</p>
<p>And another simple question. I’m just going to play around with Delta to learn the extreme basics, just wondering if it’s possible to change the level cap from 99 to something else? I was planning on allowing combat skills to be levelled up to 120, to give some people an edge in PvP. If it is possible, can you just give me the line which says what the level cap is? I’ll figure it out myself from there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standard-base-source/268857/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standard-base-source/268857/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 09:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-268857-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/standard-base-source/268857.rss">Standard base source?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
