<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864</link>
    <description>I just discovered the FBI&#39;s website for these scams, and they have a &#39;story&#39; section, I read them and am sharing the ones I thought were the funniest here:

&lt;blockquote&gt;VICTIM JAILED FOR PARTICIPATING IN A WORK-AT-HOME SCAM

I am on disability and I don&#39;t have a car. I was looking for extra money for the month, because I don&#39;t receive a lot of money from disability. So when an email came to me offering me a job that I could work from home I jumped at the chance. The job was to receive cashier checks and money orders and cash them at my bank and wire the money to another country. I took the checks to my bank and deposited them and the bank called me and told me that they were fakes and I was shocked. I told the people that emailed about the checks that they were fake and I never heard from again! Big surprise. A few months later I was arrested with 7 counts of criminal possession of a forged instrument-all felonies. A long story short I served 150+ days in jail and ended up on pre-trial diversion for an internet scam. Please don&#39;t end up like me! BEWARE ON ANY EMAIL THAT OFFERS A JOB!!

Kelly, KY&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;SOMEONE YOU DON&#39;T KNOW WANTS TO SEND YOU HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS

I was contacted by an individual in Abidjan, Cote D Ivoire regarding a bank draft for $400,000.00USD to be delivered to me in the US (Miami, FL). According the attorney in Abidjan, I must send a service fee $200.00USD, plus insurance for the draft of $1,000USD. The draft was seized by the money-laundering squad of Abidjan and now I had to send $4,000USD to retrieve the draft. The draft was retrieved and then sent to a bank of in Spain. I was advised of the wire transfer fee $5120.00USD. After that fee was paid, I was advised that the Spanish government requested $6,400USD for document stamps and government taxes. After this was paid $11,000USD was requested from the Spanish government again. At that time my friends and I started investigating and discovered that this was a Nigerian Fraud. The copy of the bank draft I sent to the bank in Abidjan and they advised me that this draft is fraud. I am devastated!!

Jackie, FL&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;WHO&#39;S WHO

I received a letter that stated that I was being considered for inclusion into a Who&#39;s Who registry for executives and professionals. They sent the letter to my work address. It stated that the registry will include biographies of accomplished people and recognition is an honor. I completed application and a representative called me about 3 weeks later. She conducted a phone interview asking about my job title, job description, goals, hobbies, level of education, company web site, reasons that I wanted to be included in the registry, and some other questions. She then congratulated me on my acceptance into the Registry and told that there were 2 levels of membership: 5 years for $589 or a lifetime membership for $789. She explained that the lifetime membership included gift cards for jewelry and airline vouchers. The company&#39;s web site and my conversation with the representative led me to believe that this was a prestigious organization and a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity that would help me with networking, career advancement, and recognition. I paid $818.95 for the lifetime membership: $789 + $29.95 shipping and handling for the directory. After I hung up I realized that this company seemed like a fraud. I did an Internet search on the company and saw that there were many complaints about them on different web sites. They&#39;re actually just a marketing company that sells the personal information of their victims/members to other marketers. On one consumer web site I even found information from former employees. I called and told them over and over that I want a full refund, but they told me that they could only give me a discount. When I found the original letter that they mailed a month before they called me, I saw that it said &quot;There is no cost to be included in the Registry&quot;. On the site with info from former employees, 2 of them had written that if you use the phrase &quot;unwilling to negotiate&quot; they&#39;ll give you a full refund. I called back, used that phrase, and threatened to take legal action. Then they agreed to give me a full refund, which I received 2 days later.

E., NY&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;APARTMENT FOR RENT AT AN UNBELIEVABLE LOW RATE

Someone listed my apartment on-line, using my name and actual apartment address. The rental offer was &quot;too good to be true&quot; - very cheap. The perpetrator then waits for people to respond, tells them he is out of state and will have to mail the keys to them. Once the victim responds - ok, send me the keys, the perpetrator says he is having &quot;second thoughts&quot; and needs to be sure the victim is trustworthy and has the money to rent the place. To &quot;verify&quot; the victim&#39;s ability to pay/trustworthiness, the perpetrator asks that the victim send money to a &quot;trusted friend/relative&quot;, in the full cash amount of the first month rent &amp; deposit. All the victim has to do, is to e-mail a copy of the receipt to the perpetrator to &quot;prove&quot; they are trustworthy and have the money. The victim, who is still enticed by the ridiculously low rent for the area, sends the money to their trusted friend/relative, and pays the large amount in cash. The perpetrator then can actually use the receipt the victim sends them, along with likely a fake ID, to pick up the cash anywhere in the world. This fraud is made worse because the unsuspecting real apartment owner may be blamed for the scam and be sued, or perhaps physically harmed by a disgruntled victim. Please post this - it is a recurring and increasingly frequent scam in the San Francisco Bay Area and people should be made aware of it.

Steve, CA&lt;/blockquote&gt;

All of them are here:
http://www.lookstoogoodtobetrue.com/stories.aspx</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 14:51:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MujaheD Radeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mujahed">@MujaheD</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I pity the Africans in that video more than the gullibles being scammed</p>
<p>edit - wtf are you that arga girl? sup?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 14:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506864-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864.rss">&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Taios Taios]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/taios">@Taios</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="506864">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Echo_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The internet has really opened up an outlet for retards to be taken advantage of.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think in general there’s a lot of vulnerable people targeted, not just over the internet but through post. Especially, I notice the older generation who are not used to this sorta thing. I’ve seen retired people’s life savings cleared out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 02:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506864-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864.rss">&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Blunts_n_Bricks Blunts n Bricks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blunts_n_bricks">@Blunts_n_Bricks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="o26Eks801oc" data-youtube-title="Internet Scamming in Ghana" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p>View from the other side.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 02:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506864-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864.rss">&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Interesting stories. It’s amusing how credulous some individuals are.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506864-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864.rss">&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Echo3 Echo_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/echo3">@Echo3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The internet has really opened up an outlet for retards to be taken advantage of.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 07:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506864-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864.rss">&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>People can be easily misled sometimes when they are caught off-balance. A prime example would <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kevin_Mitnick" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Kevin Mitnick</a>, at one point the most wanted cybercriminal in the United States. His most commonly used technique for gaining usernames and passwords? He asked for them. Never underestimate how willing people are to do what they are told, even if it defies common sense. Sometimes it doesn’t need to be “Too good to be true” it can sound boring and everyday, and the victim will just go with the flow. It’s funny how many cybercriminals end up being hired back by the same government that takes them down…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 22:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506864-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864.rss">&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I always do research when I believe something to be too good to be true. I’ve had people call my old landline/home phone saying I’ve won a brand new 2013 Jeep and they need my card information to confirm my identity. I ended up asking whoever was calling some personal information about the business and how exactly I won the Jeep, they couldn’t answer so they hung up. Haha.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 19:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506864-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864.rss">&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I just discovered the FBI’s website for these scams, and they have a ‘story’ section, I read them and am sharing the ones I thought were the funniest here:</p>
<blockquote>VICTIM JAILED FOR PARTICIPATING IN A WORK-AT-HOME SCAM
<p>I am on disability and I don’t have a car. I was looking for extra money for the month, because I don’t receive a lot of money from disability. So when an email came to me offering me a job that I could work from home I jumped at the chance. The job was to receive cashier checks and money orders and cash them at my bank and wire the money to another country. I took the checks to my bank and deposited them and the bank called me and told me that they were fakes and I was shocked. I told the people that emailed about the checks that they were fake and I never heard from again! Big surprise. A few months later I was arrested with 7 counts of criminal possession of a forged instrument-all felonies. A long story short I served 150+ days in jail and ended up on pre-trial diversion for an internet scam. Please don’t end up like me! BEWARE ON ANY EMAIL THAT OFFERS A JOB!!</p>
<p>Kelly, KY</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>SOMEONE YOU DON'T KNOW WANTS TO SEND YOU HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS
<p>I was contacted by an individual in Abidjan, Cote D Ivoire regarding a bank draft for $400,000.00USD to be delivered to me in the US (Miami, FL). According the attorney in Abidjan, I must send a service fee $200.00USD, plus insurance for the draft of $1,000USD. The draft was seized by the money-laundering squad of Abidjan and now I had to send $4,000USD to retrieve the draft. The draft was retrieved and then sent to a bank of in Spain. I was advised of the wire transfer fee $5120.00USD. After that fee was paid, I was advised that the Spanish government requested $6,400USD for document stamps and government taxes. After this was paid $11,000USD was requested from the Spanish government again. At that time my friends and I started investigating and discovered that this was a Nigerian Fraud. The copy of the bank draft I sent to the bank in Abidjan and they advised me that this draft is fraud. I am devastated!!</p>
<p>Jackie, FL</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>WHO'S WHO
<p>I received a letter that stated that I was being considered for inclusion into a Who’s Who registry for executives and professionals. They sent the letter to my work address. It stated that the registry will include biographies of accomplished people and recognition is an honor. I completed application and a representative called me about 3 weeks later. She conducted a phone interview asking about my job title, job description, goals, hobbies, level of education, company web site, reasons that I wanted to be included in the registry, and some other questions. She then congratulated me on my acceptance into the Registry and told that there were 2 levels of membership: 5 years for $589 or a lifetime membership for $789. She explained that the lifetime membership included gift cards for jewelry and airline vouchers. The company’s web site and my conversation with the representative led me to believe that this was a prestigious organization and a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity that would help me with networking, career advancement, and recognition. I paid $818.95 for the lifetime membership: $789 + $29.95 shipping and handling for the directory. After I hung up I realized that this company seemed like a fraud. I did an Internet search on the company and saw that there were many complaints about them on different web sites. They’re actually just a marketing company that sells the personal information of their victims/members to other marketers. On one consumer web site I even found information from former employees. I called and told them over and over that I want a full refund, but they told me that they could only give me a discount. When I found the original letter that they mailed a month before they called me, I saw that it said “There is no cost to be included in the Registry”. On the site with info from former employees, 2 of them had written that if you use the phrase “unwilling to negotiate” they’ll give you a full refund. I called back, used that phrase, and threatened to take legal action. Then they agreed to give me a full refund, which I received 2 days later.</p>
<p>E., NY</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>APARTMENT FOR RENT AT AN UNBELIEVABLE LOW RATE
<p>Someone listed my apartment on-line, using my name and actual apartment address. The rental offer was “too good to be true” - very cheap. The perpetrator then waits for people to respond, tells them he is out of state and will have to mail the keys to them. Once the victim responds - ok, send me the keys, the perpetrator says he is having “second thoughts” and needs to be sure the victim is trustworthy and has the money to rent the place. To “verify” the victim’s ability to pay/trustworthiness, the perpetrator asks that the victim send money to a “trusted friend/relative”, in the full cash amount of the first month rent &amp; deposit. All the victim has to do, is to e-mail a copy of the receipt to the perpetrator to “prove” they are trustworthy and have the money. The victim, who is still enticed by the ridiculously low rent for the area, sends the money to their trusted friend/relative, and pays the large amount in cash. The perpetrator then can actually use the receipt the victim sends them, along with likely a fake ID, to pick up the cash anywhere in the world. This fraud is made worse because the unsuspecting real apartment owner may be blamed for the scam and be sued, or perhaps physically harmed by a disgruntled victim. Please post this - it is a recurring and increasingly frequent scam in the San Francisco Bay Area and people should be made aware of it.</p>
<p>Steve, CA</p>
</blockquote>
<p>All of them are here:<br>
<a href="http://www.lookstoogoodtobetrue.com/stories.aspx" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://www.lookstoogoodtobetrue.com/stories.aspx</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 18:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-506864-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/too-good-to-be-true-scams/506864.rss">&#39;Too good to be true&#39; Scams</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
