<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Answer]Sexual Organs</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248</link>
    <description>I felt like making a new topic so JME would actually read it.

He posts this:
[quote=&quot;jme, post:8, topic:253046&quot;]It&#39;s the result of evolution. Over time our bodies have evolved into what nature finds best for us to survive. We will continue to evolve and maybe our sexual organs will look completely different over a long period of time assuming our species hasn&#39;t died yet. 

I ask though, why do we like sexual organs to be big (well, maybe not the vagina). I really don&#39;t know if it&#39;s instinct or a result of society.[/quote]

Later on, he clarifies &quot;sexual organs&quot; to be both the penis and the awesome titties.  The answer is very simple, and JME actually answered it himself.  It is the result of evolution.  Most of you are aware of what natural selection is, but for those who don&#39;t, natural selection is &quot;survival of the fittest/fit enough.&quot;  A strong snake will survive better than a weak snake, so the strong snake survives while the weak snake dies.  After this happens, the weak snake cannot pass down his genes because he is dead, while the strong snake can, so the strong snake&#39;s genes have a better chance of being passed down.  This is the &quot;survival&quot; part of natural selection.  The other part is reproduction.  A lion with a .2cm penis will not be able to pass down his traits as well as a lion with a &quot;normal&quot; sized penis, so of course a &quot;normal&quot; sized penis becomes more common.  In today&#39;s society, it seems women are much more willing to have sex, and therefore reproduce, with men with a larger penis.  So, men with genes for a larger penis pass down the &quot;large penis&quot; gene while the &quot;small penis&quot; gene dies off.  Over time this leaves a community with men only with &quot;large penis&quot; genes.  Of course, the women only want bigger penises, and so penises get bigger on average every generation.  Not only that, but, humans are becoming taller every generation, and since the penis is like any other part of the body, it also increases in size with a bigger person, as expected.

Now, for breasts, this situation is a bit more complicated.  As one may guess, there are no real benefits to having large breasts, in fact they hinder the person with large breasts, resulting in some women actually getting breast reduction surgeries.  It may be hard to see why women with large breasts are actually the &quot;fittest&quot; of women when looking at what breasts really do.  In most species of apes/monkeys/whatever, females&#39; breasts only stay swelled while breast feeding, and return to being not swelled afterwards.  [b]So, the simple answer is that men will more willingly reproduce with women with larger breasts, and therefore the &quot;large breast&quot; gene is passed down, similar the way explained above.[/b]  Behavior psychologists theorize that men actually view the breasts as a &quot;mock buttocks&quot; and are attracted to them, sexually.  This is of course why cleavage is so prevalent in fashion.  So, the larger the breast the more it resembles the ass on a girl.  As for why a women with a large ass is attractive, I have no idea and I&#39;d have to read up a little more on it.  I&#39;m willing to answer any questions some random nig has on this shit, thanks y&#39;all.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 02:19:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Answer]Sexual Organs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@master_silabsoft master silabsoft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/master_silabsoft">@master_silabsoft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>pretty good topic lol penises r sexy cause u can suck them =]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 02:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253248-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248.rss">[Answer]Sexual Organs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Answer]Sexual Organs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@phonnygoblin phonnygoblin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phonnygoblin">@phonnygoblin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That’s why I said JME clarified to include both penises and tits.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 10:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253248-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248.rss">[Answer]Sexual Organs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Answer]Sexual Organs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uriko Uriko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uriko">@Uriko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>an awesome tittie… i don’t think is a sexual organ and dont make a topic just for jme cuz he’ll feel special</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253248-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248.rss">[Answer]Sexual Organs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Answer]Sexual Organs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@phonnygoblin phonnygoblin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phonnygoblin">@phonnygoblin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Of course, but I was answering the question of <span class="bbcode-i">why</span> methinks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 08:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253248-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248.rss">[Answer]Sexual Organs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Answer]Sexual Organs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Worx `Worx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_worx">@_Worx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can has summary = big cocks over ages?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 08:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253248-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248.rss">[Answer]Sexual Organs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Answer]Sexual Organs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PeterMan PeterMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/peterman">@PeterMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow… just wow</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 08:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253248-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248.rss">[Answer]Sexual Organs</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Answer]Sexual Organs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@phonnygoblin phonnygoblin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phonnygoblin">@phonnygoblin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I felt like making a new topic so JME would actually read it.</p>
<p>He posts this:</p>
<p>[quote=“jme, post:8, topic:253046”]It’s the result of evolution. Over time our bodies have evolved into what nature finds best for us to survive. We will continue to evolve and maybe our sexual organs will look completely different over a long period of time assuming our species hasn’t died yet.</p>
<p>I ask though, why do we like sexual organs to be big (well, maybe not the vagina). I really don’t know if it’s instinct or a result of society.[/quote]</p>
<p>Later on, he clarifies “sexual organs” to be both the penis and the awesome titties.  The answer is very simple, and JME actually answered it himself.  It is the result of evolution.  Most of you are aware of what natural selection is, but for those who don’t, natural selection is “survival of the fittest/fit enough.”  A strong snake will survive better than a weak snake, so the strong snake survives while the weak snake dies.  After this happens, the weak snake cannot pass down his genes because he is dead, while the strong snake can, so the strong snake’s genes have a better chance of being passed down.  This is the “survival” part of natural selection.  The other part is reproduction.  A lion with a .2cm penis will not be able to pass down his traits as well as a lion with a “normal” sized penis, so of course a “normal” sized penis becomes more common.  In today’s society, it seems women are much more willing to have sex, and therefore reproduce, with men with a larger penis.  So, men with genes for a larger penis pass down the “large penis” gene while the “small penis” gene dies off.  Over time this leaves a community with men only with “large penis” genes.  Of course, the women only want bigger penises, and so penises get bigger on average every generation.  Not only that, but, humans are becoming taller every generation, and since the penis is like any other part of the body, it also increases in size with a bigger person, as expected.</p>
<p>Now, for breasts, this situation is a bit more complicated.  As one may guess, there are no real benefits to having large breasts, in fact they hinder the person with large breasts, resulting in some women actually getting breast reduction surgeries.  It may be hard to see why women with large breasts are actually the “fittest” of women when looking at what breasts really do.  In most species of apes/monkeys/whatever, females’ breasts only stay swelled while breast feeding, and return to being not swelled afterwards.  <span class="bbcode-b">So, the simple answer is that men will more willingly reproduce with women with larger breasts, and therefore the “large breast” gene is passed down, similar the way explained above.</span>  Behavior psychologists theorize that men actually view the breasts as a “mock buttocks” and are attracted to them, sexually.  This is of course why cleavage is so prevalent in fashion.  So, the larger the breast the more it resembles the ass on a girl.  As for why a women with a large ass is attractive, I have no idea and I’d have to read up a little more on it.  I’m willing to answer any questions some random nig has on this shit, thanks y’all.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 08:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253248-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/answer-sexual-organs/253248.rss">[Answer]Sexual Organs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
