<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Road (2009)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-road-2009/520180</link>
    <description>[b]Description[/b]
A compelling story about a man and his son travelling across land that was once a country and is now a barren wasteland. Years have pasted since an apocalypse has passed by. Food is scarce and animals are no where to be found so you are to either choose cannibalism or starvation.

[b]After movie thoughts[/b] (may contain spoilers)
I can&#39;t express out bang on perfect they got this movie. Every detail, every decision is realistic and everything has meaning. Throughout the movie you begin to make a connection with the father and son which most movies tend to fail at these days and the end will just leave you heart broken, it was actually the first movie to leave me teary eyed. Though there really isn&#39;t enough encounters with the cannibals, the scenes with encounters leave suspense and that oh my godish feeling. Before the ending came I knew someone was going to die, it was inevitable but it actually still hits you like a brick when it happens. Also if you&#39;re a midnight movie watcher then a heads up would be that you probably wont sleep tonight, the connection made with and one of the characters just pulls you in and after it happens you&#39;ll be left thinking how it could have been resolved earlier on in the movie. Kind of an ending like The Mist if you have seen it.
P.S. Best post apocalyptic movie yet

Overall I would actually give this movie an 8/10</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 18:05:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-road-2009/520180.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Road (2009)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@3lv3n_snip3r 3lv3n snip3r]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/3lv3n_snip3r">@3lv3n_snip3r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve seen this a couple of times on TV and I thought it was a good movie.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-road-2009/520180/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-road-2009/520180/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 18:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520180-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-road-2009/520180.rss">The Road (2009)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Road (2009)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Description</span><br>
A compelling story about a man and his son travelling across land that was once a country and is now a barren wasteland. Years have pasted since an apocalypse has passed by. Food is scarce and animals are no where to be found so you are to either choose cannibalism or starvation.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">After movie thoughts</span> (may contain spoilers)<br>
I can’t express out bang on perfect they got this movie. Every detail, every decision is realistic and everything has meaning. Throughout the movie you begin to make a connection with the father and son which most movies tend to fail at these days and the end will just leave you heart broken, it was actually the first movie to leave me teary eyed. Though there really isn’t enough encounters with the cannibals, the scenes with encounters leave suspense and that oh my godish feeling. Before the ending came I knew someone was going to die, it was inevitable but it actually still hits you like a brick when it happens. Also if you’re a midnight movie watcher then a heads up would be that you probably wont sleep tonight, the connection made with and one of the characters just pulls you in and after it happens you’ll be left thinking how it could have been resolved earlier on in the movie. Kind of an ending like The Mist if you have seen it.<br>
P.S. Best post apocalyptic movie yet</p>
<p>Overall I would actually give this movie an 8/10</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-road-2009/520180/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-road-2009/520180/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 11:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-520180-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-road-2009/520180.rss">The Road (2009)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
