<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SCM-Craft[Factions][Suvival][Planetoids][Multiverse][Economy]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scm-craft-factions-suvival-planetoids-multiverse-economy/441619</link>
    <description>Welcome!

IP: 178.33.226.114:25599

ShortCutMining is a youtube channel with an epic 24/7 server, loaded with tons of plugins, features, and has a skilled trained staff playing on this powerful dedicated server with no lag.


The server is broken into two parts... Survival, and Planetoids. Survival is the side where everyone starts off at... its the PvP, Looting, &amp; Griefing side of the server... the side with factions running. To get onto the planetoid side of the server you have to mine/get resources and sell them at the mall for money, and you use the money to buy a planetoid (which are expensive), your planetoid is your own, and only you can build on it.... with no worries of griefing, looting, or pvp... anyone who tries will be banned, and normally they can&#39;t even if they wanted to. Contact an Admin or hub owner to by a &quot;planet&quot; in their galaxy.

Important people on the server to watch out for are : Bobby555 (Owner), Zax66 (Owner), Muffinjello (Co-owner), Jsizzlefresh (Co-owner), Junglebunyslayr (Co-owner), Osammy (Admin), Spiron20 (Mod)

On the server we have tons of fun &amp; easy plugins that make the game overall more interesting.
We have 3 main plugins/groups of plugins...
These are Economy, Factions, &amp; Mob arena

Factions

Factions is a group plugin on our server that we got recently, it has tons of fun commands which allow you to protect you &amp; your friends builds and at the same time wage war with other factions for a chance to destroy, loot, and kill them.
Factions on our server also works with the economy, so certain faction commands / functions cost money.... ( /balance )
Some commands you might find useful for factions are:
/f home
/f join
/f list
/f show [faction name]
/f help
/f chat
/f mod
/f claim
/f declaim

NOTE: Joining factions costs money! Creating factions also costs ALOT of money, so you will have to play on the server for a while before you can create a faction! We are still constantly changing faction prices!

Economy

On the server we have a bunch of &quot;economy&quot; plugins, which allow you to use &quot;money&quot; to buy/sell items, and do specialized commands.
To name a few of these plugins, they are Vault, Chestshop, Iconomy, Simpleregionmarket... ect..

Once you get the hang of it, it&#39;s pretty fun... You can use your money at our MASSIVE mall which allows you to buy almost all of the items in minecraft... ranging from monster eggs, chainmail armor.. to different types of wool and wood.

Mob Arena
Mob arena is a fun, &amp; epic plugin which allows players to &#39;join&#39; an arena choose a &#39;class&#39;, which equips &amp; gives them armor &amp; items to fight against mobs, and once everyone who has joined is ready, the game starts!
You will fight against mobs of all different kinds, for valuable items, ranging from coal and iron to diamond swords!
Mob arena is a very fun plugin! We liked it so much we decided to make a video on it for our youtube channel! The video might be a bit outdated but it is still pretty great Posted Image
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RVi9hfqctuM
I&#39;m not entirely sure how to embed videos from youtube on the new forums so....</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 22:59:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scm-craft-factions-suvival-planetoids-multiverse-economy/441619.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SCM-Craft[Factions][Suvival][Planetoids][Multiverse][Economy]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shortcutmining shortcutmining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shortcutmining">@shortcutmining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Welcome!</p>
<p>IP: 178.33.226.114:25599</p>
<p>ShortCutMining is a youtube channel with an epic 24/7 server, loaded with tons of plugins, features, and has a skilled trained staff playing on this powerful dedicated server with no lag.</p>
<p>The server is broken into two parts… Survival, and Planetoids. Survival is the side where everyone starts off at… its the PvP, Looting, &amp; Griefing side of the server… the side with factions running. To get onto the planetoid side of the server you have to mine/get resources and sell them at the mall for money, and you use the money to buy a planetoid (which are expensive), your planetoid is your own, and only you can build on it… with no worries of griefing, looting, or pvp… anyone who tries will be banned, and normally they can’t even if they wanted to. Contact an Admin or hub owner to by a “planet” in their galaxy.</p>
<p>Important people on the server to watch out for are : Bobby555 (Owner), Zax66 (Owner), Muffinjello (Co-owner), Jsizzlefresh (Co-owner), Junglebunyslayr (Co-owner), Osammy (Admin), Spiron20 (Mod)</p>
<p>On the server we have tons of fun &amp; easy plugins that make the game overall more interesting.<br>
We have 3 main plugins/groups of plugins…<br>
These are Economy, Factions, &amp; Mob arena</p>
<p>Factions</p>
<p>Factions is a group plugin on our server that we got recently, it has tons of fun commands which allow you to protect you &amp; your friends builds and at the same time wage war with other factions for a chance to destroy, loot, and kill them.<br>
Factions on our server also works with the economy, so certain faction commands / functions cost money… ( /balance )<br>
Some commands you might find useful for factions are:<br>
/f home<br>
/f join<br>
/f list<br>
/f show [faction name]<br>
/f help<br>
/f chat<br>
/f mod<br>
/f claim<br>
/f declaim</p>
<p>NOTE: Joining factions costs money! Creating factions also costs ALOT of money, so you will have to play on the server for a while before you can create a faction! We are still constantly changing faction prices!</p>
<p>Economy</p>
<p>On the server we have a bunch of “economy” plugins, which allow you to use “money” to buy/sell items, and do specialized commands.<br>
To name a few of these plugins, they are Vault, Chestshop, Iconomy, Simpleregionmarket… ect…</p>
<p>Once you get the hang of it, it’s pretty fun… You can use your money at our MASSIVE mall which allows you to buy almost all of the items in minecraft… ranging from monster eggs, chainmail armor… to different types of wool and wood.</p>
<p>Mob Arena<br>
Mob arena is a fun, &amp; epic plugin which allows players to ‘join’ an arena choose a ‘class’, which equips &amp; gives them armor &amp; items to fight against mobs, and once everyone who has joined is ready, the game starts!<br>
You will fight against mobs of all different kinds, for valuable items, ranging from coal and iron to diamond swords!<br>
Mob arena is a very fun plugin! We liked it so much we decided to make a video on it for our youtube channel! The video might be a bit outdated but it is still pretty great Posted Image<br>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="RVi9hfqctuM" data-youtube-title="Minecraft: Mob Arena Gameplay - Online Server" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div><br>
I’m not entirely sure how to embed videos from youtube on the new forums so…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scm-craft-factions-suvival-planetoids-multiverse-economy/441619/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scm-craft-factions-suvival-planetoids-multiverse-economy/441619/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 22:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-441619-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/scm-craft-factions-suvival-planetoids-multiverse-economy/441619.rss">SCM-Craft[Factions][Suvival][Planetoids][Multiverse][Economy]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
