<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317] Strangest thing</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-strangest-thing/542269</link>
    <description>For some reason, when I try to equip an item that is not a custom item, it won&#39;t let me. But any item&#39;s that were put into my source-through the client, (e.g. Dragon claws-14464) I can equip, or wear just fine.

I know this is the case because if I use an old 317 client, which is basic, and does not support custom&#39;s yet. I am able to equip/wear any item I desire.

Would anyone happen to know why this is? I am positive this is a server-side problem, because I haven&#39;t done any client work yet, I&#39;m just using the client that came with this source. It&#39;s your typical Delta source.

[b][size=14pt]Note: I&#39;m sorry if this was the wrong section, it is a server-side problem. But, I believe the client is causing this server-side problem. Which is weird. I wasn&#39;t sure or not. If this is the wrong section, please move this thread. [/size][/b]

Anyone who can help, I appreciate it!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 19:39:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-strangest-thing/542269.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317] Strangest thing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MyNameIsDylan MyNameIsDylan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mynameisdylan">@MyNameIsDylan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For some reason, when I try to equip an item that is not a custom item, it won’t let me. But any item’s that were put into my source-through the client, (e.g. Dragon claws-14464) I can equip, or wear just fine.</p>
<p>I know this is the case because if I use an old 317 client, which is basic, and does not support custom’s yet. I am able to equip/wear any item I desire.</p>
<p>Would anyone happen to know why this is? I am positive this is a server-side problem, because I haven’t done any client work yet, I’m just using the client that came with this source. It’s your typical Delta source.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=14pt]Note: I’m sorry if this was the wrong section, it is a server-side problem. But, I believe the client is causing this server-side problem. Which is weird. I wasn’t sure or not. If this is the wrong section, please move this thread. [/size]</span></p>
<p>Anyone who can help, I appreciate it!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-strangest-thing/542269/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-strangest-thing/542269/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 19:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542269-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-strangest-thing/542269.rss">[317] Strangest thing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
