<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&#39;The Sound and the Fury&#39; Essay</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-sound-and-the-fury-essay/71104</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;“It is a tale / told by an idiot, full of sound and fury, / signifying nothing.”  That is what The Sound and the Fury is.  In the opening section of The Sound and the Fury, William Faulkner tells his tale from the point of view of an idiot—namely, Benjamin Compson.  ‘Benjy’ blurs thirty-three years of his life into the roughly twelve hours that he recounts.  Obsessed with his long-gone sister, Benjy responds longingly even to the very mention of her name, Caddy.  The following passage, detailed by Quentin Compson eighteen years earlier, is resplendent with remorse and sorrow for his sister’s lost virginity.  Unable to regain his family’s lost honor and driven mad by his love for his sister, he drowns himself.  The third and youngest brother, Jason Compson, recites his side of the story from the day before Benjy’s narrative.  Jason is characterized by malevolence towards the world and particularly, Caddy’s bastard daughter—Quentin.  Caddy named her daughter Quentin for her late brother of the same name.  The fourth segment of the novel is told in the third-person omniscient point of view, initially following the black maid, Dilsey.  Near the heart of the novel is the character foil of Caddy and her illegitimate child, Quentin.  While Caddy represents the positive attributes of compassion, accountability, and sensitivity, Miss Quentin symbolizes the negative characteristics of lust, insolence, and irresponsibility.

Candace Compson is the epitome of southern elegance and beauty.  One night, during Damuddy’s funeral, the adults leave the children to their own devices.  Caddy eagerly petitions, “Let them mind me tonight, Father.”  (Faulkner 24)  Even at a young age, Caddy is capable of assuming responsibility and taking charge of the other children.  Later that night, Jason learns that Damuddy passed away and proceeds to cry.  Despite his vindictive behavior earlier that night, Caddy still soothes him.  “Hush up Jason.  How can buzzards get in where Damuddy is.”  (Faulkner 36)  Her reaction manifests her empathy, regardless of past grievances and enmity.  As the children restlessly move about the house, Benjy begins to moan.  Caddy senses Benjy’s thoughts:  “He wants your lightning bugs, T.P.  Let him hold it a while.”  (Faulkner 36)  Though Benjy is unable to speak or convey his thoughts, Caddy is sensitive to Benjy’s jumbled feelings.  In another flashback, Benjy is discontented with Caddy.  Unable to discern Benjy’s muddled thoughts, she solicits, “What is it, Benjy… Tell Caddy.  She’ll do it.  Try.”  (Faulkner 41)  When she finally concludes that her perfume is the source of Benjy’s discomfort, she washes off the scent and presents the unwanted perfume to a grateful Dilsey.  She is affectionate and selfless in deferring her own emotions to Benjy’s.  Mrs. Compson complains about Benjy as a burden in a different flashback.  Caddy fondly answers, “You dont need to bother with him… I like to take care of him.  Dont I.  Benjy.”  (Faulkner 63)  She is motherly and patient, treating Benjy not as a pet or an animal, but as a human being.  Having a less-developed mind does not make him any less of a human, and Caddy recognizes this undeniable fact.  Later, on the night Caddy loses her virginity, Quentin asks her if she loves Dalton, with whom she had sex.  “I would die for him Ive already died for him I die for him over and over again everytime this goes.”  (Faulkner 151)  She is unshakable devoted to the ones she loves.  In a later scene, Quentin recalls a conversation during Caddy’s wedding.  She begs, “Yes I can after that it’ll be all right it wont matter dont let them send him to Jackson promise.”  (Faulkner 112)  On what should be the happiest day of her life, Caddy is distressed over Benjy’s welfare.  She refuses to let the Compsons send Benjy to an asylum, because she cares too much for him.  Caddy is the ideal southern belle—loving and kind—though a tad bawdy.

While Caddy does appear promiscuous, she does not revel in pure lust itself as much as she enjoys the giving of love.  It is not the thought of having sex that moves her; rather, it is the pleasure she can grant others that goads her toward her lewd actions.  When Quentin gets upset over her lost virginity, Caddy responds with “yes Ill do anything you want me to anything yes,” (Faulkner 156) hinting that she is willing to commit incest with him.  She offers herself to him not as an obscene display of lust, but rather as an intimate show of affection.  Caddy loves her numerous boyfriends all too much, bending to their desires and bedding them to satisfy their desires.  In contrast, Miss Quentin is bristling with indecent lechery and worldly lusts.  Caddy at the very least had the modesty to have one partner at a time.  Benjy and his black caretaker, Luster, find Miss Quentin and her red-tied lover by some swings.  Miss Quentin storms away in undisguised disgust as Luster uncovers a shiny box in a bush.  Her boyfriend examines the box to find the words, “Agnes Mabel Becky.”  (Faulkner 50)  Agnes Mabel Becky was a popular brand of condoms at the time, so he interrogates Luster about whether anyone had visited her last night.  “I dont know….  They comes every night she can climb down that tree.”  (Faulkner 50)  Miss Quentin simply is a prostitute—a slave to lust, not love, as in Caddy’s case.  She is southern decadence personified, whereas Caddy was southern beauty epitomized.  Furthermore, sexuality is not the only quality in which Miss Quentin has been corrupted.

While Caddy is the archetypal lady, Miss Quentin’s character is a warning to all women.  Miss Quentin is a brat, a liar, and a foul-mouth.  When Luster and Benjy stumble upon Miss Quentin and her lover in the red tie by the swing set, she pouts, “If you dont take him right away this minute and keep him away, I’m going to make Jason whip you.”  (Faulkner 48)  While Caddy was more than happy to care for Benjy, Miss Quentin views him as a pest and an annoyance.  Ever the brat, Miss Quentin unfairly accuses Luster of spying on her.  When Jason learns of the man in the red tie, he storms, “What did I tell you I was going to do if I saw you with that show fellow again…Did you hear me,” (Faulkner 67) to which she retorts, “I heard you… Why dont you do it, then.”  (Faulkner 67)  She taunts him, daring him to follow through with his threat.  Her stubborn insolence nearly drives him to whip her.  One day, when Benjy is particularly aggravated, Miss Quentin becomes irritated.  “He needs to be sent to Jackson, Quentin said.  How can anybody live in a house like this.”  (Faulkner 69)  The words of her own mother had been to let Benjy stay at the Compson’s residence, while Miss Quentin is hoping for his removal.  Later, Mrs. Compson laments Miss Quentin’s deception:  “I didn’t even know she had a report card.  She told me last fall that they had quit using them this year.”  (Faulkner 180)  The blatant trickery gives proof to Miss Quentin’s corruption.  Along with her deceitful tongue, her speech drips contempt.  Jason warns, “‘I’ll give you ten seconds to put that cup down like I told you….’  ‘What time is it, Dilsey?’ she says.  ‘When its ten seconds, you whistle.’”  (Faulkner 183)  Her defiant replies provoke the ill-tempered Jason to violence.  Jason then accuses her of spending time with ‘the wrong crowd,’ with which she retorts with vulgarity.  “You—you old goddam…!  You damn old goddam!”  (Faulkner 184)  Finally, Dilsey steps in to protect her, receiving not a word of thanks, but an insult:  “You damn old nigger.”  (Faulkner 185)  Miss Quentin is the physical embodiment of the dilapidated South.  She symbolizes the perversion of the formerly elegant South, once a beauty, now a bawd.  However, it would be unfair to attribute these misgivings to her own doing.  
Grandmother… Grandmother—….  Why does he treat me like this, Grandmother?...  I never hurt him.…  It’s his fault….  He wont let me alone, and I have to.  If he doesn’t want me here, why wont he let me go back to—….  Then why wont he let me alone?...  He—he just—…  Whatever I do, it’s your fault….  If I’m bad, it’s because I had to be.  You made me.  I wish I was dead.  I wish we were all dead.  (Faulkner 260)
Her wretched circumstances, in addition to Jason’s cruel upbringing, molded her from the soft clay from her mother’s womb to the tough, brash sculpture that defines her.  She does not willingly want to act the way she does, but she cannot help it any more than Romeo could help being a Montague.

Regardless of fairness or choice, Faulkner intended for Caddy to be Miss Quentin’s foil.  Caddy is incredibly patient, kind, and nurturing.  She is like a pleasant dream that leaves you satisfied and personable the following day.  In contrast, Miss Quentin is a nightmare that pervades and corrupts.  She leaves you feeling like death and wishing for life.  Faulkner portrays her as an ‘anti-role model,’ a potent and corporeal message.  This tale was told by an idiot, but the moral signified much more than nothing.

--Written by James Q.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

My intro is a bit iffy atm, so a lot of this book may not make sense if you haven&#39;t read it already.  Still need to proofread, but tell me what you think so far.  Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2007 18:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-sound-and-the-fury-essay/71104.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&#39;The Sound and the Fury&#39; Essay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> , If I Ever Need An Essay On “The Sound And The Fury” , Im Defitnely Going To Use This Hehe <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-sound-and-the-fury-essay/71104/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-sound-and-the-fury-essay/71104/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2007 18:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-71104-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-sound-and-the-fury-essay/71104.rss">&#39;The Sound and the Fury&#39; Essay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&#39;The Sound and the Fury&#39; Essay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>“It is a tale / told by an idiot, full of sound and fury, / signifying nothing.”  That is what The Sound and the Fury is.  In the opening section of The Sound and the Fury, William Faulkner tells his tale from the point of view of an idiot—namely, Benjamin Compson.  ‘Benjy’ blurs thirty-three years of his life into the roughly twelve hours that he recounts.  Obsessed with his long-gone sister, Benjy responds longingly even to the very mention of her name, Caddy.  The following passage, detailed by Quentin Compson eighteen years earlier, is resplendent with remorse and sorrow for his sister’s lost virginity.  Unable to regain his family’s lost honor and driven mad by his love for his sister, he drowns himself.  The third and youngest brother, Jason Compson, recites his side of the story from the day before Benjy’s narrative.  Jason is characterized by malevolence towards the world and particularly, Caddy’s bastard daughter—Quentin.  Caddy named her daughter Quentin for her late brother of the same name.  The fourth segment of the novel is told in the third-person omniscient point of view, initially following the black maid, Dilsey.  Near the heart of the novel is the character foil of Caddy and her illegitimate child, Quentin.  While Caddy represents the positive attributes of compassion, accountability, and sensitivity, Miss Quentin symbolizes the negative characteristics of lust, insolence, and irresponsibility.
<p>Candace Compson is the epitome of southern elegance and beauty.  One night, during Damuddy’s funeral, the adults leave the children to their own devices.  Caddy eagerly petitions, “Let them mind me tonight, Father.”  (Faulkner 24)  Even at a young age, Caddy is capable of assuming responsibility and taking charge of the other children.  Later that night, Jason learns that Damuddy passed away and proceeds to cry.  Despite his vindictive behavior earlier that night, Caddy still soothes him.  “Hush up Jason.  How can buzzards get in where Damuddy is.”  (Faulkner 36)  Her reaction manifests her empathy, regardless of past grievances and enmity.  As the children restlessly move about the house, Benjy begins to moan.  Caddy senses Benjy’s thoughts:  “He wants your lightning bugs, T.P.  Let him hold it a while.”  (Faulkner 36)  Though Benjy is unable to speak or convey his thoughts, Caddy is sensitive to Benjy’s jumbled feelings.  In another flashback, Benjy is discontented with Caddy.  Unable to discern Benjy’s muddled thoughts, she solicits, “What is it, Benjy… Tell Caddy.  She’ll do it.  Try.”  (Faulkner 41)  When she finally concludes that her perfume is the source of Benjy’s discomfort, she washes off the scent and presents the unwanted perfume to a grateful Dilsey.  She is affectionate and selfless in deferring her own emotions to Benjy’s.  Mrs. Compson complains about Benjy as a burden in a different flashback.  Caddy fondly answers, “You dont need to bother with him… I like to take care of him.  Dont I.  Benjy.”  (Faulkner 63)  She is motherly and patient, treating Benjy not as a pet or an animal, but as a human being.  Having a less-developed mind does not make him any less of a human, and Caddy recognizes this undeniable fact.  Later, on the night Caddy loses her virginity, Quentin asks her if she loves Dalton, with whom she had sex.  “I would die for him Ive already died for him I die for him over and over again everytime this goes.”  (Faulkner 151)  She is unshakable devoted to the ones she loves.  In a later scene, Quentin recalls a conversation during Caddy’s wedding.  She begs, “Yes I can after that it’ll be all right it wont matter dont let them send him to Jackson promise.”  (Faulkner 112)  On what should be the happiest day of her life, Caddy is distressed over Benjy’s welfare.  She refuses to let the Compsons send Benjy to an asylum, because she cares too much for him.  Caddy is the ideal southern belle—loving and kind—though a tad bawdy.</p>
<p>While Caddy does appear promiscuous, she does not revel in pure lust itself as much as she enjoys the giving of love.  It is not the thought of having sex that moves her; rather, it is the pleasure she can grant others that goads her toward her lewd actions.  When Quentin gets upset over her lost virginity, Caddy responds with “yes Ill do anything you want me to anything yes,” (Faulkner 156) hinting that she is willing to commit incest with him.  She offers herself to him not as an obscene display of lust, but rather as an intimate show of affection.  Caddy loves her numerous boyfriends all too much, bending to their desires and bedding them to satisfy their desires.  In contrast, Miss Quentin is bristling with indecent lechery and worldly lusts.  Caddy at the very least had the modesty to have one partner at a time.  Benjy and his black caretaker, Luster, find Miss Quentin and her red-tied lover by some swings.  Miss Quentin storms away in undisguised disgust as Luster uncovers a shiny box in a bush.  Her boyfriend examines the box to find the words, “Agnes Mabel Becky.”  (Faulkner 50)  Agnes Mabel Becky was a popular brand of condoms at the time, so he interrogates Luster about whether anyone had visited her last night.  “I dont know….  They comes every night she can climb down that tree.”  (Faulkner 50)  Miss Quentin simply is a prostitute—a slave to lust, not love, as in Caddy’s case.  She is southern decadence personified, whereas Caddy was southern beauty epitomized.  Furthermore, sexuality is not the only quality in which Miss Quentin has been corrupted.</p>
<p>While Caddy is the archetypal lady, Miss Quentin’s character is a warning to all women.  Miss Quentin is a brat, a liar, and a foul-mouth.  When Luster and Benjy stumble upon Miss Quentin and her lover in the red tie by the swing set, she pouts, “If you dont take him right away this minute and keep him away, I’m going to make Jason whip you.”  (Faulkner 48)  While Caddy was more than happy to care for Benjy, Miss Quentin views him as a pest and an annoyance.  Ever the brat, Miss Quentin unfairly accuses Luster of spying on her.  When Jason learns of the man in the red tie, he storms, “What did I tell you I was going to do if I saw you with that show fellow again…Did you hear me,” (Faulkner 67) to which she retorts, “I heard you… Why dont you do it, then.”  (Faulkner 67)  She taunts him, daring him to follow through with his threat.  Her stubborn insolence nearly drives him to whip her.  One day, when Benjy is particularly aggravated, Miss Quentin becomes irritated.  “He needs to be sent to Jackson, Quentin said.  How can anybody live in a house like this.”  (Faulkner 69)  The words of her own mother had been to let Benjy stay at the Compson’s residence, while Miss Quentin is hoping for his removal.  Later, Mrs. Compson laments Miss Quentin’s deception:  “I didn’t even know she had a report card.  She told me last fall that they had quit using them this year.”  (Faulkner 180)  The blatant trickery gives proof to Miss Quentin’s corruption.  Along with her deceitful tongue, her speech drips contempt.  Jason warns, “‘I’ll give you ten seconds to put that cup down like I told you….’  ‘What time is it, Dilsey?’ she says.  ‘When its ten seconds, you whistle.’”  (Faulkner 183)  Her defiant replies provoke the ill-tempered Jason to violence.  Jason then accuses her of spending time with ‘the wrong crowd,’ with which she retorts with vulgarity.  “You—you old goddam…!  You damn old goddam!”  (Faulkner 184)  Finally, Dilsey steps in to protect her, receiving not a word of thanks, but an insult:  “You damn old nigger.”  (Faulkner 185)  Miss Quentin is the physical embodiment of the dilapidated South.  She symbolizes the perversion of the formerly elegant South, once a beauty, now a bawd.  However, it would be unfair to attribute these misgivings to her own doing.<br>
Grandmother… Grandmother—….  Why does he treat me like this, Grandmother?..  I never hurt him.…  It’s his fault….  He wont let me alone, and I have to.  If he doesn’t want me here, why wont he let me go back to—….  Then why wont he let me alone?..  He—he just—…  Whatever I do, it’s your fault….  If I’m bad, it’s because I had to be.  You made me.  I wish I was dead.  I wish we were all dead.  (Faulkner 260)<br>
Her wretched circumstances, in addition to Jason’s cruel upbringing, molded her from the soft clay from her mother’s womb to the tough, brash sculpture that defines her.  She does not willingly want to act the way she does, but she cannot help it any more than Romeo could help being a Montague.</p>
<p>Regardless of fairness or choice, Faulkner intended for Caddy to be Miss Quentin’s foil.  Caddy is incredibly patient, kind, and nurturing.  She is like a pleasant dream that leaves you satisfied and personable the following day.  In contrast, Miss Quentin is a nightmare that pervades and corrupts.  She leaves you feeling like death and wishing for life.  Faulkner portrays her as an ‘anti-role model,’ a potent and corporeal message.  This tale was told by an idiot, but the moral signified much more than nothing.</p>
<p>–Written by James Q.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>My intro is a bit iffy atm, so a lot of this book may not make sense if you haven’t read it already.  Still need to proofread, but tell me what you think so far.  Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-sound-and-the-fury-essay/71104/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-sound-and-the-fury-essay/71104/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2007 01:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-71104-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-sound-and-the-fury-essay/71104.rss">&#39;The Sound and the Fury&#39; Essay</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
