<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fishing</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294</link>
    <description>I am trying to make a fishing base for my server, i have added a fishing void and many methods for it such as a void for catching the fish, requirements, requirements for levels, adding fish to the inventory and deleting bait, etc. Now the only problem is that i am trying to get the second option for the fishing spot to work, now since the fishing spots i am using are npc&#39;s i have to use case 17: which is a method for the clicking of the second option on an npc, which for me, the second option is &quot;Bait.&quot;

Now the fishing spot has two options for clicking (not including examine,) which are &quot;Lure,&quot; and &quot;Bait,&quot; i have lure working properly as with all the other fishing spots first options, but i can&#39;t get any of the fishing spots second options to work.

From my prospective, i highly doubt i will get help with this, which is why i will keep trying to get it working, so if someone can be arsed and knows how to get the second option on fishing spots to work thanks, a lot.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 16:27:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@11167 _™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/11167">@11167</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The second click NPC packet should work, which is why I’d have to agree with Chassy and ask for the codes used.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-287294-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294.rss">Fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chassy13 Chassy13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chassy13">@chassy13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Can you show us any attempts of written code you have tried? There might just be something wrong on how you wrote it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 15:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-287294-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294.rss">Fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@r34p4g3pk r34p4g3pk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r34p4g3pk">@r34p4g3pk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am trying to make a fishing base for my server, i have added a fishing void and many methods for it such as a void for catching the fish, requirements, requirements for levels, adding fish to the inventory and deleting bait, etc. Now the only problem is that i am trying to get the second option for the fishing spot to work, now since the fishing spots i am using are npc’s i have to use case 17: which is a method for the clicking of the second option on an npc, which for me, the second option is “Bait.”</p>
<p>Now the fishing spot has two options for clicking (not including examine,) which are “Lure,” and “Bait,” i have lure working properly as with all the other fishing spots first options, but i can’t get any of the fishing spots second options to work.</p>
<p>From my prospective, i highly doubt i will get help with this, which is why i will keep trying to get it working, so if someone can be arsed and knows how to get the second option on fishing spots to work thanks, a lot.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 11:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-287294-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fishing/287294.rss">Fishing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
