<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129</link>
    <description>Man I hate people. They are greedy, stupid, vain, fake, and many other things I can’t think of right now. I’m not anti-social, but I pretty much hate everyone that I’m not friends with, until they get my respect somehow. I just had to get this off my chest so it’s pretty badly written. Last night does make a good story though.

My friend rang me last night and said he was having a few friends over for some beers. I felt like crap because I was training that whole day, and I had a torrential weight training session the day before and was exhausted, sick and hurting all over. (keep this in mind, I&#39;m already in a bad mood, hurting, and feeling like crap.) However I figured a catch up night with the boys would turn out alright. I get there and we crack a few cans and play guitar hero for a while, then some chick texted me and invited me to a party she was going to. The boys were keen so I figured what the hell, I downed like 4 shots of coffee to keep me going, we packed the esky and left.

We get to the train station where our friends are at, and hang around a while because we heard the party hadn’t really started yet. Their friends rock up, and soon we have 3 carloads of people looking to party. We get there, and the party turns out to be 4 people drinking out the back of a house listening to music. By now we have 6 carloads of drunk people, and our group only knows 2 of them.

Another girl says she knows of another party in a suburb 20 minutes away, by now I’ve had a bit to drink and didn’t want to risk a dui so my friend (let’s call him Chris) drove as he hadn’t been drinking. We get to the suburb, and everybody is following us because they think we know where the hell we’re going. After pulling over it quickly becomes apparent that the chick had no idea of the street or anything. So much for that.

By now it’s around 10:30, and people are starting to think about bailing. Finally we get a hold of a party, and it’s someone I used to know. He also lives another 25 minutes away back across from where we came. After getting there, driving around in the middle of nowhere (the guy lives way out in the acreage) we find the house, and it’s just a couple of mates having some beers. Our group could have stayed as we knew them, but there were 4 other carloads of drunk people we don’t even know wanting to party.

We decide to bail, and go back to the original plan of just the few of us at a friend’s house. The people following us leave, and the chicks in the car with us ask for a lift to McDonalds, so they can get picked up from there.

Some guy in another car decides to start being stupid, amongst other things he swerves in front of us and we nearly slide off the road at 100kmph trying to avoid him. Chris miraculously manages to get the car to gain traction again, and speeds up and overtakes the guy to get away from him. He takes the hint and drops back. I guessed he realized that nearly killing 5 people is a little over the line. Everyone in our car is fuming.

We get to McDonalds at 11:30 and chat for a few minutes, the other guys finally go away. While I’m inside talking a leak some huge guy called David tries to climb up a wall drunk, he falls and smashes his head on my bonnet. Sometime later we realize he has wondered off, and go after him. We find him climbing up a wall a few hundred meters away, across a roundabout and near some shops. We arrive to see him fall and dislocate his arm, and smash his head again. I really felt like leaving him there, in my defense I didn’t know the guy, he was loud drunk and obnoxious, and he kept trying to walk, only to fall within a couple steps, hurting his shoulder more and smashing his head again.

The guy was concussed, drunk and has a dislocated shoulder. He then starts going into shock and hyperventilating. Someone calls an ambulance, we figure since the hospital is only 5 minutes away and it’s 12 midnight it shouldn’t take too long. We get told by the fountain of all knowledge on the phone to keep him on the ground still so he doesn’t hurt himself again.

This might seem like an easy task: Keep a drunk sick guy with a dislocated shoulder pinned to the ground. The fun part was the fact that he was a 150+kg Maori muscle, and he was crying whilst raging, trying to get up. Apparently he already forgot about the other 5 times he tried to get up and walk.

Now I’m not a little person. I’m a 6ft 4 athlete weighting in at 90kg, but this guy is huge, and is still hard to control even in his state with 2 people.

I bear hug him and lie on the ground to keep him there, but he isn’t going down without a fight. Swearing at us and struggling to get up, he was apparently oblivious to the fact that we were trying to help him. At least he was blacking out, so I had 30 seconds rest every minute or so before I had to start wrestling him again. We are now in the gutter, lucky me it’s been raining so I’m now wrestling in a puddle, in the middle of the night in winter. I’m being punched and kicked, however I hold on because if I have to watch him run 5 meters, fall over and start crying one more time I’m going to lose it.

Most people who drives past doesn’t see what’s going on, and think we are just a bunch of punks loitering at 2am. The things they said were too explicit for these forums so I’ll leave it to your imagination. I am now so pissed off I want to head butt myself in the face. I take it out on the guy’s shoulder.

Let me recap on this. Some massive drunk Maori I don&#39;t know has a dislocated shoulder and concussion, he is in shock and hyperventilating as well as blacking out occasionally. I have him in a bear hug in a puddle on the road because we can&#39;t get him out of it, and Chris is trying to stop him from hurting me, which is causing him to also get punched and kicked in the struggle. The guy is ridiculously strong and loud, and beating my already sore and exhausted body around. It is winter at midnight, we are all soaking and freezing, we have been waiting for an ambulance for hours, whilst getting physically abused by the drunk idiot on the ground, and verbally abused by drunk idiots driving past. Me and Chris were both in a bad mood BEFORE this happened.

A car full of what looks like drunk 20 year old guys stops to give us an earful. Apparently this idiot doesn’t think the night is bad enough and starts talking crap to them, it takes a few minutes for my friends to calm them down, and for the guys to drive off.

Somebody calls back the ambulance a few times within the next 2 and a half hours, and each time we get ‘the ambulance will be there soon.’ Finally I lose it and start yelling in the direction of the phone. I can’t comprehend how difficult it is to pick up some guy 5-10 minutes down the road within a few hours. It’s a 30 minute job to get him to the hospital, how can there possibly be THAT many emergencies in the middle of the night?

We finally see an ambulance, which keeps driving. Apparently it’s for somebody else, who is probably having a better night than we are.

I am now being strangled by the guy while freezing to death, and it’s taking 2 people to keep his arm from tightening around my neck and even then I’m having my throat crushed. I punch him in the face a few times hoping it will make him let go, and it seems he has lost feeling because he doesn&#39;t seem to mind, he has also stopped complaining about his shoulder.

After 3 hours of wrestling he finally gets tired, and is struggling less, and blacking out more. We do all we can to keep him awake for his own health, to be rewarded with more struggling and elbows flying, legs kicking. We pull him out of the gutter and I hold him again up on the footpath.

Somebody pulls over, apparently they are a group of volunteers who drive around at night and help out people. They give the guy a blanket, tell us a stream of what we already know to help him, gives everyone else Gatorade and hang around for a half hour before leaving.

Now the guy looks like he is in trouble, he starts having a seizure and is frothing at the mouth. Fun. Somebody rings up the ambulance for the 5th or so time, and I tell myself that if we get told ‘the ambulance is on it’s way,’ then I am ditching this idiot, driving up to the station and killing everybody. The seizure finally gets their attention and they decide to stay on the phone until the ambo gets there.

The ambulance arrives at 4am, a full 4 hours after we rang, he is finally incapable of struggling, I’m going to call that a good thing. They do a quick checkup, get the guy on oxygen, we warn them about some special medical condition he has, and about the shifty looking home brew vodka bottle he drank, and they finally take the idiot away.

To cap it off my car now reeks of beer because someone forgot they left a half full bottle on the floor and then knocked it over.

I’ve decided I’m going to live as a hermit.

So… How has your weekend been?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 04:17:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original_Daniel Original Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original_daniel">@Original_Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="39" data-topic="214129">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Starting up ...:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>/care</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ban evading?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 04:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Starting_up Starting up ...]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/starting_up">@Starting_up</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>/care</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 03:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uriko Uriko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uriko">@Uriko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“goatee, post:34, topic:214129”]I knew this was old as fuck as soon as I saw the title. Funny story thinking back.</p>
<p>Oh and fuck you “john5689”, if that is your real name.[/quote]doubt it, that’d be a weird real name.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 03:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PeterMan PeterMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/peterman">@PeterMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for bumping this. It was a really good read and I haven’t seen it before.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 01:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nohope nohope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nohope">@nohope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“TheBeanie, post:33, topic:214129”][quote author=.Unlimited link=topic=281787.msg2898176#msg2898176 date=1249344642]<br>
Year old*<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Meh… didnt see that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Coulda sworn i read this not not long ago :S</p>
<p>Correction.</p>
<p>Why have you bumped a thread over a year old???[/quote]it didnt seem that long to me either</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 00:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original_Daniel Original Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original_daniel">@Original_Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol… good times.</p>
<p>I have way better stories than this now, we got on the national news at schoolies week for starters <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 00:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I knew this was old as fuck as soon as I saw the title. Funny story thinking back.</p>
<p>Oh and fuck you “john5689”, if that is your real name.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 00:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thebeanie TheBeanie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thebeanie">@Thebeanie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="32" data-topic="214129">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 .Unlimited:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Year old*</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Meh… didnt see that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Coulda sworn i read this not not long ago :S</p>
<p>Correction.</p>
<p>Why have you bumped a thread over a year old???</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 00:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unlimited1 .Unlimited]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unlimited1">@Unlimited1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Year old*</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 00:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thebeanie TheBeanie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thebeanie">@Thebeanie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“john5689, post:30, topic:214129”][quote author=Original Daniel link=topic=281787.msg2288915#msg2288915 date=1214050481]<br>
Man I hate people. They are greedy, stupid, vain, fake, and many other things I can’t think of right now. I’m not anti-social, but I pretty much hate everyone that I’m not friends with, until they get my respect somehow. I just had to get this off my chest so it’s pretty badly written. Last night does make a good story though.</p>
<p>My friend rang me last night and said he was having a few friends over for some beers. I felt like crap because I was training that whole day, and I had a torrential weight training session the day before and was exhausted, sick and hurting all over. (keep this in mind, I’m already in a bad mood, hurting, and feeling like crap.) However I figured a catch up night with the boys would turn out alright. I get there and we crack a few cans and play guitar hero for a while, then some chick texted me and invited me to a party she was going to. The boys were keen so I figured what the hell, I downed like 4 shots of coffee to keep me going, we packed the esky and left.</p>
<p>We get to the train station where our friends are at, and hang around a while because we heard the party hadn’t really started yet. Their friends rock up, and soon we have 3 carloads of people looking to party. We get there, and the party turns out to be 4 people drinking out the back of a house listening to music. By now we have 6 carloads of drunk people, and our group only knows 2 of them.</p>
<p>Another girl says she knows of another party in a suburb 20 minutes away, by now I’ve had a bit to drink and didn’t want to risk a dui so my friend (let’s call him Chris) drove as he hadn’t been drinking. We get to the suburb, and everybody is following us because they think we know where the hell we’re going. After pulling over it quickly becomes apparent that the chick had no idea of the street or anything. So much for that.</p>
<p>By now it’s around 10:30, and people are starting to think about bailing. Finally we get a hold of a party, and it’s someone I used to know. He also lives another 25 minutes away back across from where we came. After getting there, driving around in the middle of nowhere (the guy lives way out in the acreage) we find the house, and it’s just a couple of mates having some beers. Our group could have stayed as we knew them, but there were 4 other carloads of drunk people we don’t even know wanting to party.</p>
<p>We decide to bail, and go back to the original plan of just the few of us at a friend’s house. The people following us leave, and the chicks in the car with us ask for a lift to McDonalds, so they can get picked up from there.</p>
<p>Some guy in another car decides to start being stupid, amongst other things he swerves in front of us and we nearly slide off the road at 100kmph trying to avoid him. Chris miraculously manages to get the car to gain traction again, and speeds up and overtakes the guy to get away from him. He takes the hint and drops back. I guessed he realized that nearly killing 5 people is a little over the line. Everyone in our car is fuming.</p>
<p>We get to McDonalds at 11:30 and chat for a few minutes, the other guys finally go away. While I’m inside talking a leak some huge guy called David tries to climb up a wall drunk, he falls and smashes his head on my bonnet. Sometime later we realize he has wondered off, and go after him. We find him climbing up a wall a few hundred meters away, across a roundabout and near some shops. We arrive to see him fall and dislocate his arm, and smash his head again. I really felt like leaving him there, in my defense I didn’t know the guy, he was loud drunk and obnoxious, and he kept trying to walk, only to fall within a couple steps, hurting his shoulder more and smashing his head again.</p>
<p>The guy was concussed, drunk and has a dislocated shoulder. He then starts going into shock and hyperventilating. Someone calls an ambulance, we figure since the hospital is only 5 minutes away and it’s 12 midnight it shouldn’t take too long. We get told by the fountain of all knowledge on the phone to keep him on the ground still so he doesn’t hurt himself again.</p>
<p>This might seem like an easy task: Keep a drunk sick guy with a dislocated shoulder pinned to the ground. The fun part was the fact that he was a 150+kg Maori muscle, and he was crying whilst raging, trying to get up. Apparently he already forgot about the other 5 times he tried to get up and walk.</p>
<p>Now I’m not a little person. I’m a 6ft 4 athlete weighting in at 90kg, but this guy is huge, and is still hard to control even in his state with 2 people.</p>
<p>I bear hug him and lie on the ground to keep him there, but he isn’t going down without a fight. Swearing at us and struggling to get up, he was apparently oblivious to the fact that we were trying to help him. At least he was blacking out, so I had 30 seconds rest every minute or so before I had to start wrestling him again. We are now in the gutter, lucky me it’s been raining so I’m now wrestling in a puddle, in the middle of the night in winter. I’m being punched and kicked, however I hold on because if I have to watch him run 5 meters, fall over and start crying one more time I’m going to lose it.</p>
<p>Most people who drives past doesn’t see what’s going on, and think we are just a bunch of punks loitering at 2am. The things they said were too explicit for these forums so I’ll leave it to your imagination. I am now so pissed off I want to head butt myself in the face. I take it out on the guy’s shoulder.</p>
<p>Let me recap on this. Some massive drunk Maori I don’t know has a dislocated shoulder and concussion, he is in shock and hyperventilating as well as blacking out occasionally. I have him in a bear hug in a puddle on the road because we can’t get him out of it, and Chris is trying to stop him from hurting me, which is causing him to also get punched and kicked in the struggle. The guy is ridiculously strong and loud, and beating my already sore and exhausted body around. It is winter at midnight, we are all soaking and freezing, we have been waiting for an ambulance for hours, whilst getting physically abused by the drunk idiot on the ground, and verbally abused by drunk idiots driving past. Me and Chris were both in a bad mood BEFORE this happened.</p>
<p>A car full of what looks like drunk 20 year old guys stops to give us an earful. Apparently this idiot doesn’t think the night is bad enough and starts talking crap to them, it takes a few minutes for my friends to calm them down, and for the guys to drive off.</p>
<p>Somebody calls back the ambulance a few times within the next 2 and a half hours, and each time we get ‘the ambulance will be there soon.’ Finally I lose it and start yelling in the direction of the phone. I can’t comprehend how difficult it is to pick up some guy 5-10 minutes down the road within a few hours. It’s a 30 minute job to get him to the hospital, how can there possibly be THAT many emergencies in the middle of the night?</p>
<p>We finally see an ambulance, which keeps driving. Apparently it’s for somebody else, who is probably having a better night than we are.</p>
<p>I am now being strangled by the guy while freezing to death, and it’s taking 2 people to keep his arm from tightening around my neck and even then I’m having my throat crushed. I punch him in the face a few times hoping it will make him let go, and it seems he has lost feeling because he doesn’t seem to mind, he has also stopped complaining about his shoulder.</p>
<p>After 3 hours of wrestling he finally gets tired, and is struggling less, and blacking out more. We do all we can to keep him awake for his own health, to be rewarded with more struggling and elbows flying, legs kicking. We pull him out of the gutter and I hold him again up on the footpath.</p>
<p>Somebody pulls over, apparently they are a group of volunteers who drive around at night and help out people. They give the guy a blanket, tell us a stream of what we already know to help him, gives everyone else Gatorade and hang around for a half hour before leaving.</p>
<p>Now the guy looks like he is in trouble, he starts having a seizure and is frothing at the mouth. Fun. Somebody rings up the ambulance for the 5th or so time, and I tell myself that if we get told ‘the ambulance is on it’s way,’ then I am ditching this idiot, driving up to the station and killing everybody. The seizure finally gets their attention and they decide to stay on the phone until the ambo gets there.</p>
<p>The ambulance arrives at 4am, a full 4 hours after we rang, he is finally incapable of struggling, I’m going to call that a good thing. They do a quick checkup, get the guy on oxygen, we warn them about some special medical condition he has, and about the shifty looking home brew vodka bottle he drank, and they finally take the idiot away.</p>
<p>To cap it off my car now reeks of beer because someone forgot they left a half full bottle on the floor and then knocked it over.</p>
<p>I’ve decided I’m going to live as a hermit.</p>
<p>So… How has your weekend been?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>WOW i sceriousley feel sorry for you because you was up for like the whole night tackling this drunken idot and the ambulence was 4 hours late. If that was me i would just go in th hospital and like kill everyone there cuse it was late for 4 hours.</p>
<p>Good Job holding that druken guy cuse i wouden’t of held him lol but good job[/quote]<br>
Why have you bumped a thread thats over a month old?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 00:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@john5689 john5689]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/john5689">@john5689</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Original Daniel, post:1, topic:214129”]Man I hate people. They are greedy, stupid, vain, fake, and many other things I can’t think of right now. I’m not anti-social, but I pretty much hate everyone that I’m not friends with, until they get my respect somehow. I just had to get this off my chest so it’s pretty badly written. Last night does make a good story though.</p>
<p>My friend rang me last night and said he was having a few friends over for some beers. I felt like crap because I was training that whole day, and I had a torrential weight training session the day before and was exhausted, sick and hurting all over. (keep this in mind, I’m already in a bad mood, hurting, and feeling like crap.) However I figured a catch up night with the boys would turn out alright. I get there and we crack a few cans and play guitar hero for a while, then some chick texted me and invited me to a party she was going to. The boys were keen so I figured what the hell, I downed like 4 shots of coffee to keep me going, we packed the esky and left.</p>
<p>We get to the train station where our friends are at, and hang around a while because we heard the party hadn’t really started yet. Their friends rock up, and soon we have 3 carloads of people looking to party. We get there, and the party turns out to be 4 people drinking out the back of a house listening to music. By now we have 6 carloads of drunk people, and our group only knows 2 of them.</p>
<p>Another girl says she knows of another party in a suburb 20 minutes away, by now I’ve had a bit to drink and didn’t want to risk a dui so my friend (let’s call him Chris) drove as he hadn’t been drinking. We get to the suburb, and everybody is following us because they think we know where the hell we’re going. After pulling over it quickly becomes apparent that the chick had no idea of the street or anything. So much for that.</p>
<p>By now it’s around 10:30, and people are starting to think about bailing. Finally we get a hold of a party, and it’s someone I used to know. He also lives another 25 minutes away back across from where we came. After getting there, driving around in the middle of nowhere (the guy lives way out in the acreage) we find the house, and it’s just a couple of mates having some beers. Our group could have stayed as we knew them, but there were 4 other carloads of drunk people we don’t even know wanting to party.</p>
<p>We decide to bail, and go back to the original plan of just the few of us at a friend’s house. The people following us leave, and the chicks in the car with us ask for a lift to McDonalds, so they can get picked up from there.</p>
<p>Some guy in another car decides to start being stupid, amongst other things he swerves in front of us and we nearly slide off the road at 100kmph trying to avoid him. Chris miraculously manages to get the car to gain traction again, and speeds up and overtakes the guy to get away from him. He takes the hint and drops back. I guessed he realized that nearly killing 5 people is a little over the line. Everyone in our car is fuming.</p>
<p>We get to McDonalds at 11:30 and chat for a few minutes, the other guys finally go away. While I’m inside talking a leak some huge guy called David tries to climb up a wall drunk, he falls and smashes his head on my bonnet. Sometime later we realize he has wondered off, and go after him. We find him climbing up a wall a few hundred meters away, across a roundabout and near some shops. We arrive to see him fall and dislocate his arm, and smash his head again. I really felt like leaving him there, in my defense I didn’t know the guy, he was loud drunk and obnoxious, and he kept trying to walk, only to fall within a couple steps, hurting his shoulder more and smashing his head again.</p>
<p>The guy was concussed, drunk and has a dislocated shoulder. He then starts going into shock and hyperventilating. Someone calls an ambulance, we figure since the hospital is only 5 minutes away and it’s 12 midnight it shouldn’t take too long. We get told by the fountain of all knowledge on the phone to keep him on the ground still so he doesn’t hurt himself again.</p>
<p>This might seem like an easy task: Keep a drunk sick guy with a dislocated shoulder pinned to the ground. The fun part was the fact that he was a 150+kg Maori muscle, and he was crying whilst raging, trying to get up. Apparently he already forgot about the other 5 times he tried to get up and walk.</p>
<p>Now I’m not a little person. I’m a 6ft 4 athlete weighting in at 90kg, but this guy is huge, and is still hard to control even in his state with 2 people.</p>
<p>I bear hug him and lie on the ground to keep him there, but he isn’t going down without a fight. Swearing at us and struggling to get up, he was apparently oblivious to the fact that we were trying to help him. At least he was blacking out, so I had 30 seconds rest every minute or so before I had to start wrestling him again. We are now in the gutter, lucky me it’s been raining so I’m now wrestling in a puddle, in the middle of the night in winter. I’m being punched and kicked, however I hold on because if I have to watch him run 5 meters, fall over and start crying one more time I’m going to lose it.</p>
<p>Most people who drives past doesn’t see what’s going on, and think we are just a bunch of punks loitering at 2am. The things they said were too explicit for these forums so I’ll leave it to your imagination. I am now so pissed off I want to head butt myself in the face. I take it out on the guy’s shoulder.</p>
<p>Let me recap on this. Some massive drunk Maori I don’t know has a dislocated shoulder and concussion, he is in shock and hyperventilating as well as blacking out occasionally. I have him in a bear hug in a puddle on the road because we can’t get him out of it, and Chris is trying to stop him from hurting me, which is causing him to also get punched and kicked in the struggle. The guy is ridiculously strong and loud, and beating my already sore and exhausted body around. It is winter at midnight, we are all soaking and freezing, we have been waiting for an ambulance for hours, whilst getting physically abused by the drunk idiot on the ground, and verbally abused by drunk idiots driving past. Me and Chris were both in a bad mood BEFORE this happened.</p>
<p>A car full of what looks like drunk 20 year old guys stops to give us an earful. Apparently this idiot doesn’t think the night is bad enough and starts talking crap to them, it takes a few minutes for my friends to calm them down, and for the guys to drive off.</p>
<p>Somebody calls back the ambulance a few times within the next 2 and a half hours, and each time we get ‘the ambulance will be there soon.’ Finally I lose it and start yelling in the direction of the phone. I can’t comprehend how difficult it is to pick up some guy 5-10 minutes down the road within a few hours. It’s a 30 minute job to get him to the hospital, how can there possibly be THAT many emergencies in the middle of the night?</p>
<p>We finally see an ambulance, which keeps driving. Apparently it’s for somebody else, who is probably having a better night than we are.</p>
<p>I am now being strangled by the guy while freezing to death, and it’s taking 2 people to keep his arm from tightening around my neck and even then I’m having my throat crushed. I punch him in the face a few times hoping it will make him let go, and it seems he has lost feeling because he doesn’t seem to mind, he has also stopped complaining about his shoulder.</p>
<p>After 3 hours of wrestling he finally gets tired, and is struggling less, and blacking out more. We do all we can to keep him awake for his own health, to be rewarded with more struggling and elbows flying, legs kicking. We pull him out of the gutter and I hold him again up on the footpath.</p>
<p>Somebody pulls over, apparently they are a group of volunteers who drive around at night and help out people. They give the guy a blanket, tell us a stream of what we already know to help him, gives everyone else Gatorade and hang around for a half hour before leaving.</p>
<p>Now the guy looks like he is in trouble, he starts having a seizure and is frothing at the mouth. Fun. Somebody rings up the ambulance for the 5th or so time, and I tell myself that if we get told ‘the ambulance is on it’s way,’ then I am ditching this idiot, driving up to the station and killing everybody. The seizure finally gets their attention and they decide to stay on the phone until the ambo gets there.</p>
<p>The ambulance arrives at 4am, a full 4 hours after we rang, he is finally incapable of struggling, I’m going to call that a good thing. They do a quick checkup, get the guy on oxygen, we warn them about some special medical condition he has, and about the shifty looking home brew vodka bottle he drank, and they finally take the idiot away.</p>
<p>To cap it off my car now reeks of beer because someone forgot they left a half full bottle on the floor and then knocked it over.</p>
<p>I’ve decided I’m going to live as a hermit.</p>
<p>So… How has your weekend been?[/quote]</p>
<p>WOW i sceriousley feel sorry for you because you was up for like the whole night tackling this drunken idot and the ambulence was 4 hours late. If that was me i would just go in th hospital and like kill everyone there cuse it was late for 4 hours.</p>
<p>Good Job holding that druken guy cuse i wouden’t of held him lol but good job</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/30</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 22:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEnt xEnt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xent">@xEnt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="26" data-topic="214129">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/stork/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> Stork:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>rugby player?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If hes Maori (NZ) i bet hes a rugby player.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 08:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="27" data-topic="214129">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Aryst Bledel:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>RAWR! Long story. If you don’t want to risk DUI, don’t drink at all…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Or just don’t drive?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 21:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Aryst_Bledel Aryst Bledel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aryst_bledel">@Aryst_Bledel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>RAWR! Long story. If you don’t want to risk DUI, don’t drink at all…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 03:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Stork Stork]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stork">@Stork</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rugby player?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 18:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original_Daniel Original Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original_daniel">@Original_Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="24" data-topic="214129">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/stork/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> Stork:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also your friend wasn’t 150kg cuz that’s fuckin’ jacked… unless he was mad fat or 7’ tall. Strong exaggeration.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>He was 120 at the very minimum. The guy was almost my height, and really wide. Both a lot of muscle and a lot of fat, just big really. The kind of person you do a double take when you see them. I knew someone around his size in grade 8, and he said he was 120. But the guy I used to know had much more fat and less muscle so that’s why I said higher.</p>
<p>150 is an exaggeration, but not by a stretch.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 15:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Stork Stork]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stork">@Stork</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Five star story, definitely worth reading. Needs cliffs though.</p>
<p>Also your friend wasn’t 150kg cuz that’s fuckin’ jacked… unless he was mad fat or 7’ tall. Strong exaggeration.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 03:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“exps35, post:22, topic:214129”][quote author=cooper link=topic=281787.msg2294172#msg2294172 date=1214310249]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>We, in the UK, get it too <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[center]<img src="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnwarn.gif" alt> [/center]</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why the warn sphere?<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I believe a sphere would make it 3-dimensional.<br>
It’s more of a dot, in my personal opinion.[/quote]<br>
You’re right, I need to pay more attention to my posts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@exps35 exps35]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exps35">@exps35</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“cooper, post:21, topic:214129”][quote author=magma828 link=topic=281787.msg2290857#msg2290857 date=1214142654]<br>
We, in the UK, get it too <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[center]<img src="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnwarn.gif" alt width="" height=""> [/center]<br>
[/quote]<br>
Why the warn sphere?[/quote]</p>
<p>I believe a sphere would make it 3-dimensional.<br>
It’s more of a dot, in my personal opinion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 12:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“magma828, post:1, topic:214414”][quote author=Unhandled link=topic=281787.msg2290161#msg2290161 date=1214108422]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>In America we sue for an ambulance being 2 minutes late.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s cause you have privatized health care. Fucking americans.<br>
[/quote]<br>
We, in the UK, get it too <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
[center]<img src="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnwarn.gif" alt width="" height=""> [/center][/quote]<br>
Why the warn dot?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 12:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tr3v0r TR3V0R]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tr3v0r">@tr3v0r</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That’s one hell of a story.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 04:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“magma828, post:1, topic:214414”][quote author=Unhandled link=topic=281787.msg2290161#msg2290161 date=1214108422]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>In America we sue for an ambulance being 2 minutes late.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s cause you have privatized health care. Fucking americans.<br>
[/quote]<br>
We, in the UK, get it too :)[/quote]</p>
<p>Yeh but in America they have to pay no matter what. At least we get it free, private if you’re willing to spend actual money. Who the hell does that?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 20:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>quote author=Unhandled link=topic=281787.msg2290161#msg2290161 date=1214108422]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="13" data-topic="214129">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 casey.:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In America we sue for an ambulance being 2 minutes late.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s cause you have privatized health care. Fucking americans.<br>
[/quote]<br>
No its cause they are too lazy to work and need to earn money so they get it off the back of an ambulance driver its kinda stupid</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 15:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cruzer Cruzer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruzer">@Cruzer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Look on the bright side, you got free Gatorade.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 05:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Man I hate people (my weekend story)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="13" data-topic="214129">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 casey.:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In America we sue for an ambulance being 2 minutes late.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s cause you have privatized health care. Fucking americans.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2008 04:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-214129-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/man-i-hate-people-my-weekend-story/214129.rss">Man I hate people (my weekend story)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
