<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Runescape Classic Server Advertisement Rules - READ BEFORE POSTING!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-classic-server-advertisement-rules-read-before-posting/265170</link>
    <description>[b][size=16pt]Runescape Classic Advertisement Rules[/size][/b]

[u][b]Foreward:[/b][/u] The staff at moparisthebest.com has the right to change these at any time without &quot;notifying&quot; any &quot;normal&quot; member.  It is your duty to check these regulary.  Depending on the rule, all topics posted [u][b]BEFORE[/b][/u] a rule is added/changed will be exempt from said rule.  We also don&#39;t want you looking for loopholes in these rules.  Instead you should be looking for ways to abide by them correctly, and &quot;get along with them&quot;. Please also note that this is not a full listing of the rules in this section. Additional punishment may be handed out for excessively idiotic behavior on a case-by-case basis. If you have common sense, use it.

Punishments are to be handed out at the moderators discretion for breaching any of the following guidelines.
[u][b]Rules:[/b][/u]

[ul][li]All [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,354311.0.html]global forum rules[/url] still apply.[/li]
[li]Do not advertise your website here unless it is directly linked to your server (but you may have a link to it in your signature).[/li]
[li]You are only allowed one advertisement topic per server.[/li] 
[li]Do not advertise your server in other people&#39;s topics (outside of your own signature).[/li]
[li]Do not advertise servers associated with DDoSing, network attacks, or other online antisocial behavior.[/li]
[li]Only the owner of a server may post an advertisement. Getting another person to post for a banned members server is strictly prohibited, and will result in a server censorship.[/li]
[li]Do not advertise Runescape 2 servers. (This includes &#39;317&#39; servers, and anything that does [u]not[/u] look like the picture below)[/li]
[li]When posting negative comments on server topics, leave constructive criticism instead of responses like &quot;This server sucks&quot; &quot;I&#39;m not playing this server&quot; state the reasons why you feel a server is not worth playing or do not post at all.[/li][/ul]



[img]http://img522.imageshack.us/img522/2245/ss20090301184642.png[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 15:32:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-classic-server-advertisement-rules-read-before-posting/265170.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Runescape Classic Server Advertisement Rules - READ BEFORE POSTING!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEnt xEnt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xent">@xEnt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=16pt]Runescape Classic Advertisement Rules[/size]</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Foreward:</span></span> The staff at <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a> has the right to change these at any time without “notifying” any “normal” member.  It is your duty to check these regulary.  Depending on the rule, all topics posted <span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">BEFORE</span></span> a rule is added/changed will be exempt from said rule.  We also don’t want you looking for loopholes in these rules.  Instead you should be looking for ways to abide by them correctly, and “get along with them”. Please also note that this is not a full listing of the rules in this section. Additional punishment may be handed out for excessively idiotic behavior on a case-by-case basis. If you have common sense, use it.</p>
<p>Punishments are to be handed out at the moderators discretion for breaching any of the following guidelines.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Rules:</span></span></p>
<p>[ul][li]All <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,354311.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">global forum rules</a> still apply.[/li]<br>
[li]Do not advertise your website here unless it is directly linked to your server (but you may have a link to it in your signature).[/li]<br>
[li]You are only allowed one advertisement topic per server.[/li]<br>
[li]Do not advertise your server in other people’s topics (outside of your own signature).[/li]<br>
[li]Do not advertise servers associated with DDoSing, network attacks, or other online antisocial behavior.[/li]<br>
[li]Only the owner of a server may post an advertisement. Getting another person to post for a banned members server is strictly prohibited, and will result in a server censorship.[/li]<br>
[li]Do not advertise Runescape 2 servers. (This includes ‘317’ servers, and anything that does <span class="bbcode-u">not</span> look like the picture below)[/li]<br>
[li]When posting negative comments on server topics, leave constructive criticism instead of responses like “This server sucks” “I’m not playing this server” state the reasons why you feel a server is not worth playing or do not post at all.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><img src="http://img522.imageshack.us/img522/2245/ss20090301184642.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-classic-server-advertisement-rules-read-before-posting/265170/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-classic-server-advertisement-rules-read-before-posting/265170/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 15:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-265170-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runescape-classic-server-advertisement-rules-read-before-posting/265170.rss">Runescape Classic Server Advertisement Rules - READ BEFORE POSTING!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
