<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>/Windows/SYSTEM/Vgaoem.fonis missing?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-system-vgaoem-fonis-missing/424536</link>
    <description>I have a friend who was having some problems with her laptop so she shut it down and turned it back on and she can&#39;t run it in safe mode or anything because it says that the File (Title) is missing. I read up and did some research to find out it generally occurs when users are moving over to XP from Windows 98. I found no other causes to this and I was wondering what might of caused this and how it can be fixed. She dosen&#39;t have the Setup XP CD or anything to reinstall it has it was preinstalled when she got it and she has no money. Somy more information you might need possibly is its a Dell laptop. I am not sure what kind of dell it is nor am I sure what year. Thanks for your time for reading this and helping me if you do. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 07:50:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-system-vgaoem-fonis-missing/424536.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>/Windows/SYSTEM/Vgaoem.fonis missing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew_Ferguson The317Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew_ferguson">@Andrew_Ferguson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Download an install disk online and burn it to a fresh dvd (cost maybe $0.60 for one? Idk somewhere around that). But before you burn it to the disk search through the files it will install for something along the lines of this, that will give you the product key that goes with the disk. <a href="http://techie-buzz.com/tips-and-tricks/find-windows-xp-product-key-from-installation-disc.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://techie-buzz.com/tips-and-tricks/find-windows-xp-product-key-from-installation-disc.html</a>  Good luck mate.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-system-vgaoem-fonis-missing/424536/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-system-vgaoem-fonis-missing/424536/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 07:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424536-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-system-vgaoem-fonis-missing/424536.rss">/Windows/SYSTEM/Vgaoem.fonis missing?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>/Windows/SYSTEM/Vgaoem.fonis missing?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RiiPiiNFtW RiiPiiNFtW]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/riipiinftw">@RiiPiiNFtW</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have a friend who was having some problems with her laptop so she shut it down and turned it back on and she can’t run it in safe mode or anything because it says that the File (Title) is missing. I read up and did some research to find out it generally occurs when users are moving over to XP from Windows 98. I found no other causes to this and I was wondering what might of caused this and how it can be fixed. She dosen’t have the Setup XP CD or anything to reinstall it has it was preinstalled when she got it and she has no money. Somy more information you might need possibly is its a Dell laptop. I am not sure what kind of dell it is nor am I sure what year. Thanks for your time for reading this and helping me if you do. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-system-vgaoem-fonis-missing/424536/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-system-vgaoem-fonis-missing/424536/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 04:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-424536-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/windows-system-vgaoem-fonis-missing/424536.rss">/Windows/SYSTEM/Vgaoem.fonis missing?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
