<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Rs United</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896</link>
    <description>[size=30pt]¥ Rs United ¥[/size]

Welcome to my topic on my development of ¥ Rs United ¥

This is a dodain source I have been working on for a few months now.


PM me if you would like to join my forums


~Range - Range should be about 99% done. I have working D bow with real gfx and it hits high. Also added crossbows except I dont have bolts so I cannot make them work yet. There is blessed D hides that you get from clues. Msb spec works. All arrows including dragon.

~Prayer - Most bones work except dagganoth bones. I will make them work by the time server is out. You can bury the bones or you can use on the altar for more exp.

~Magic - Magic is pretty much done. Have real splashing depending on your magic bonus. Teles work and you get mage exp and they take you to the right places, you also need the correct amount of runes and the gfx works. There is magic tabs that tele you. Teleblock works and is on a timer. There is also autocasting with staffs including ancient staff.

~Runecrrafting - Havent worked on yet. So far you use ess on altar, you get certian amount of runes depending on your level. Dont have all the altars working properly yet.

~Agility - There is that one course that is used in Gnome Stronghold and the Wilderness one. Agility is pretty boring so I didint really go full out on it.

~Herblore - O a goodie. I have most pots working. You need certian levels and you need the right items (same ones in rs) you use the herb on water vial, get unfinished pot than use the item onthe unfinished pot for the real pot. Took a while getting all of them right and the levels etc.. There is also working herblore cleaning. You will get grimy herbs and must clean them before you can get a clean one to use on pots.

~Theif - I am not going to have stalls because people can just click and thats no fun. All there are is people that you can pickpocket. You actually get more from the person depending on your thief lvl. There is about 6 or 7 different people to pickpocket from and the higher one can be pretty wealthy.

~Craft - Havent really worked on it. You cut the gem, you get a cut one. You can also craft dragon hides and stuff with wool and leather and all that good stuff.

~Fletching - Here is a VERY high money maker on here. The only way to get addy, rune, and dragon arrows are by fletching. You need the right amount of level. The interface pops up and you select how many you want to make of the log you are cutting. Use feathers on shaft, get headless arrows and use headles arrow on the arrow tips and you get arrows if you have the right level.

~Slayer - Slayer is just you talk to guy, get a task, get xp for every kill, get more when you finish task. The gem works, tells you your kills left. Slayer is not done yet. Only added about 2 different npcs to slay. Which are dark beasts and abby demons. One drops d bow, other drops whip. I plan on having a really good slayer with good npcs to slay not stupid stuff. You also pick if you want low,med,or high task.

~Mining - Mining is well on here. The ore rocks are all over not a certian spot. All ores have auto mining. They stop when you have a full inv. Real ess mining, teleport aubury and he teles you there. Mine and there is the portal that takes you out. Rune ores are worth good cash in shops but are all the way in the wilderness.

~Smith - I am not too sure what I am going to do about smithing. I am either just going to do like delta and just give cash because smithing is really glitch and hard to get it to work right. It will probally just give good money if you use bar on anvil and if you have a hammer. Not sure yet.

~Fish - I havent added all fish spots yet,and I dont have all kinds of fish. Just basic ones So I need to work on this a lot. But it is auto fishing I got that done.

~Cook - Added auto cooking and working on making them have a random burn. Shouldnt take too long

~Firemaking - Basic firemaking. Use lighter on log, it lights log, log appears on floor. Done lol

~Woodcutting - Can cut any tree. Auto wcing, slower and faster depending on what tree and what you level is. No certian area for wc, just all over.

~Farming - Farming was easy. Just and item on object. You get seed, you need rake, use seed on patch and get herb yay!

That was all the skills now heres the good stuff.

~Fightcaves - Im sorry but I had to use deltas fightcaves because they are REALLY good. realistic, hard and pretty long. I couldnt resist =p

~Daggs - What you do is kill little daggs until they drop a key and you use the key on the gate. you go all the way through (use your run energy and prayer wisely) You get to kings and there in the same spot as rs and they are aggressive, one ranges,mages,and melees. You must go with a team or it will be very hard. If you have about 5 people should be really easy. They drop rings,dragon wc axe, clue scrolls, all the good stuff.

~Clue Scrolls - I didint bother adding 3 different kinds of clues although I may later. What you do is get a clue, click it and it will open up and show you your clue and you need to find the right spot. Dig there with that clue and get a casket like rs. Open casket and get your reward yay! You can get godarmor, blessed d hides tons of stuff.

~Godwars - Yay my favorite! When you get there you kill one type and an interface will pop up saying your killcount. Lets say zammy. You get a 40 killcount of zammy, go through cave exit thing and will tele you to other side with different entrances and each is for each type. So you enter zammy and your zammy kills will go away and it will tele you to the zammy boss. That boss will drop zammy hilt only. and thats it. To get to general you need to have a killcount of 20 from all 4 kinds to enter and he drops gs blade. I made it so you CAN solo the bosses if you are strong but there is no way you can solo the general. You need atleast 5-8 people. There will be an altar at each boss to get your prayer back.

~Destroy Item - If you drop an untradeable item the interface will show up asking if you would like to destroy the item if you hit yes the item will vanish. If you hit no the interface will close.

~Chinchompas - Real chinchompas are here and are pretty well. Only thing is I dont have the gfx working but I will when server comes out.

~DFS/KBD - If you kill KBD he can drop a visage which if you have the req smith level you can use on an anti drag shield and will get a DFS. I took deltas idea on how to get a special effect. It is not the same but I tried to get it close. His is still better.

~Barrows - The barrows brothers just stand above the hill. You kill them and it saves you killcount (i will make it show an interface later) and you must have 1 kill of each to open chest and get a barrow reward. The reward is a pretty good chance so it shouldnt be that hard.

~Working Veng - If you have the right runes and the right level you can use veng. I think I made it pretty nice. Hard to explain I will just show it further down with videos.

~Assault - To get there you need to click on that hay stack near varrock east bank. You need a combined attack and strength of 130 to enter. When you get there you kill the cyclops and get a killcount/point Than you trade the guy there and he will have defenders and torso there and you can exchange.

~Client Updates - Friends that are online will appear at the top. If you add a friend and they are not on, do not fear. The client will not crash. When you click on an item the color will be a different color same with objects. You wull have to find out what colors when you play =p

~Quests - 2 quests so far. Lost city and desert treasure. They are pretty well so far. Ill add video later.

~Perfect 1v1 Pking
~Void Works(my own)
~All Godswords with real spec/gfx and they all do real effect.
~Working Prayer
~Piety and Chiv work ( all they do is bump up str like burst of str, except they do it more)
~Working K Queen (Dosent have second form yet)
~All Dupes Fixed So gl Duping
[b]VIDEOS[/b]
Client Preview - http://tinypic.com/player.php?v=mizcpi&amp;s=4

[b]PICTURES[/b]
[IMG]http://img407.imageshack.us/img407/4237/thiefnr2.jpg[/img]
By [URL=http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26]bowlerboi26[/URL] at 2008-11-07
[IMG]http://img220.imageshack.us/img220/7775/prayerri1.jpg[/img]
By [URL=http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26]bowlerboi26[/URL] at 2008-11-07
[IMG]http://img99.imageshack.us/img99/1118/miningoutofspacenr3.jpg[/img]
By [URL=http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26]bowlerboi26[/URL] at 2008-11-07
[IMG]http://img411.imageshack.us/img411/6569/miningyu2.jpg[/img]
By [URL=http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26]bowlerboi26[/URL] at 2008-11-07
[IMG]http://img518.imageshack.us/img518/6797/herbsnr8.jpg[/img]
By [URL=http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26]bowlerboi26[/URL] at 2008-11-07
[IMG]http://img407.imageshack.us/img407/1191/cleanherbzg1.jpg[/img]
By [URL=http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26]bowlerboi26[/URL] at 2008-11-07
[IMG]http://img521.imageshack.us/img521/7546/dragarrowsgp8.jpg[/img]
By [URL=http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26]bowlerboi26[/URL] at 2008-11-07
[IMG]http://img407.imageshack.us/img407/3566/deadbq1.jpg[/img]
By [URL=http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26]bowlerboi26[/URL] at 2008-11-07
[IMG]http://img521.imageshack.us/img521/2189/clientbackgroundtr9.png[/img]
By [URL=http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26]bowlerboi26[/URL] at 2008-11-07


I am sure I forgot a lot of things but I will update as I remember

Some Credits not giving percentages
Delta-Helping/Using a few things from yours
&#39;Rich-Interface
And some poeple that help me on here

P.S This is NOT DS SOURCE.[b][/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 06:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sheeba sheeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sheeba">@sheeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im going to change the client gameframe back after all this feedback =p</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 06:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@King_Redrum King Redrum]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/king_redrum">@King_Redrum</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks nice, not diggin’ the client though :s Still good job.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 16:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sheeba sheeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sheeba">@sheeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks, new video uploaded about client</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 00:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Godsent Godsent]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/godsent">@Godsent</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Credits to Jukk for the game frame. Yeah, that’s right. Can’t hide from me. That’s right, <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 00:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gimmeyoshoez Gimmeyoshoez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gimmeyoshoez">@Gimmeyoshoez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good job</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 23:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kingblitz kingblitz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kingblitz">@kingblitz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i can’t wait to play this server</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 22:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sheeba sheeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sheeba">@sheeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>few client updates</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 00:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Reaper_X The Reaper X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_reaper_x">@The_Reaper_X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You seem pretty dedicated. Nice job, hope it turns out well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 23:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sheeba sheeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sheeba">@sheeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks =)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 22:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jjones10 jjones10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jjones10">@jjones10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>looks good so far but lots can be done still<br>
Good Work =]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 23:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kingblitz kingblitz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kingblitz">@kingblitz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>whens release date?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 00:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@curry_muncha curry muncha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/curry_muncha">@curry_muncha</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>looks pretty nice <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 22:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kingblitz kingblitz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kingblitz">@kingblitz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this server is gonna be really great! sheeba is amazing coder</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 21:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sheeba sheeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sheeba">@sheeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well if you want to help me with client that would be nice. I am not good at clients just server side stuff</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 15:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cocoa cocoa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cocoa">@cocoa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ya… Your client sucks but from what I’ve seen from you so far sounds good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 05:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sheeba sheeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sheeba">@sheeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks guys</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 03:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@primadude Primadude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/primadude">@primadude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Inventory back is Ugly…[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 08, 2008, 08:53:18 pm[/size][hr]If it is as good as it sound’s then it is A pretty nice server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 22:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Uk_0wn4g3_I I Uk 0wn4g3 I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_uk_0wn4g3_i">@I_Uk_0wn4g3_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>fucking fail</blockquote>
<p>K03d m8 Chassy is right you fucking fail gtfo, No need to spam his topic, ANYWAYS, GJ =]]</p>
<p>Hope all goes well p.s. check my topic out huh =p</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 19:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lesterknome lesterknome]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lesterknome">@lesterknome</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Looks smexi, <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chassy13 Chassy13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chassy13">@chassy13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like it. An k03d, you fucking fail.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 04:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_k03d_xx xx k03d xx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_k03d_xx">@xx_k03d_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>fucking fail</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 04:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kaeli Kaeli]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kaeli">@Kaeli</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>very nice <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> whats website?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 04:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Rs United</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sheeba sheeba]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sheeba">@sheeba</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=30pt]¥ Rs United ¥[/size]</p>
<p>Welcome to my topic on my development of ¥ Rs United ¥</p>
<p>This is a dodain source I have been working on for a few months now.</p>
<p>PM me if you would like to join my forums</p>
<p>~Range - Range should be about 99% done. I have working D bow with real gfx and it hits high. Also added crossbows except I dont have bolts so I cannot make them work yet. There is blessed D hides that you get from clues. Msb spec works. All arrows including dragon.</p>
<p>~Prayer - Most bones work except dagganoth bones. I will make them work by the time server is out. You can bury the bones or you can use on the altar for more exp.</p>
<p>~Magic - Magic is pretty much done. Have real splashing depending on your magic bonus. Teles work and you get mage exp and they take you to the right places, you also need the correct amount of runes and the gfx works. There is magic tabs that tele you. Teleblock works and is on a timer. There is also autocasting with staffs including ancient staff.</p>
<p>~Runecrrafting - Havent worked on yet. So far you use ess on altar, you get certian amount of runes depending on your level. Dont have all the altars working properly yet.</p>
<p>~Agility - There is that one course that is used in Gnome Stronghold and the Wilderness one. Agility is pretty boring so I didint really go full out on it.</p>
<p>~Herblore - O a goodie. I have most pots working. You need certian levels and you need the right items (same ones in rs) you use the herb on water vial, get unfinished pot than use the item onthe unfinished pot for the real pot. Took a while getting all of them right and the levels etc… There is also working herblore cleaning. You will get grimy herbs and must clean them before you can get a clean one to use on pots.</p>
<p>~Theif - I am not going to have stalls because people can just click and thats no fun. All there are is people that you can pickpocket. You actually get more from the person depending on your thief lvl. There is about 6 or 7 different people to pickpocket from and the higher one can be pretty wealthy.</p>
<p>~Craft - Havent really worked on it. You cut the gem, you get a cut one. You can also craft dragon hides and stuff with wool and leather and all that good stuff.</p>
<p>~Fletching - Here is a VERY high money maker on here. The only way to get addy, rune, and dragon arrows are by fletching. You need the right amount of level. The interface pops up and you select how many you want to make of the log you are cutting. Use feathers on shaft, get headless arrows and use headles arrow on the arrow tips and you get arrows if you have the right level.</p>
<p>~Slayer - Slayer is just you talk to guy, get a task, get xp for every kill, get more when you finish task. The gem works, tells you your kills left. Slayer is not done yet. Only added about 2 different npcs to slay. Which are dark beasts and abby demons. One drops d bow, other drops whip. I plan on having a really good slayer with good npcs to slay not stupid stuff. You also pick if you want low,med,or high task.</p>
<p>~Mining - Mining is well on here. The ore rocks are all over not a certian spot. All ores have auto mining. They stop when you have a full inv. Real ess mining, teleport aubury and he teles you there. Mine and there is the portal that takes you out. Rune ores are worth good cash in shops but are all the way in the wilderness.</p>
<p>~Smith - I am not too sure what I am going to do about smithing. I am either just going to do like delta and just give cash because smithing is really glitch and hard to get it to work right. It will probally just give good money if you use bar on anvil and if you have a hammer. Not sure yet.</p>
<p>~Fish - I havent added all fish spots yet,and I dont have all kinds of fish. Just basic ones So I need to work on this a lot. But it is auto fishing I got that done.</p>
<p>~Cook - Added auto cooking and working on making them have a random burn. Shouldnt take too long</p>
<p>~Firemaking - Basic firemaking. Use lighter on log, it lights log, log appears on floor. Done lol</p>
<p>~Woodcutting - Can cut any tree. Auto wcing, slower and faster depending on what tree and what you level is. No certian area for wc, just all over.</p>
<p>~Farming - Farming was easy. Just and item on object. You get seed, you need rake, use seed on patch and get herb yay!</p>
<p>That was all the skills now heres the good stuff.</p>
<p>~Fightcaves - Im sorry but I had to use deltas fightcaves because they are REALLY good. realistic, hard and pretty long. I couldnt resist =p</p>
<p>~Daggs - What you do is kill little daggs until they drop a key and you use the key on the gate. you go all the way through (use your run energy and prayer wisely) You get to kings and there in the same spot as rs and they are aggressive, one ranges,mages,and melees. You must go with a team or it will be very hard. If you have about 5 people should be really easy. They drop rings,dragon wc axe, clue scrolls, all the good stuff.</p>
<p>~Clue Scrolls - I didint bother adding 3 different kinds of clues although I may later. What you do is get a clue, click it and it will open up and show you your clue and you need to find the right spot. Dig there with that clue and get a casket like rs. Open casket and get your reward yay! You can get godarmor, blessed d hides tons of stuff.</p>
<p>~Godwars - Yay my favorite! When you get there you kill one type and an interface will pop up saying your killcount. Lets say zammy. You get a 40 killcount of zammy, go through cave exit thing and will tele you to other side with different entrances and each is for each type. So you enter zammy and your zammy kills will go away and it will tele you to the zammy boss. That boss will drop zammy hilt only. and thats it. To get to general you need to have a killcount of 20 from all 4 kinds to enter and he drops gs blade. I made it so you CAN solo the bosses if you are strong but there is no way you can solo the general. You need atleast 5-8 people. There will be an altar at each boss to get your prayer back.</p>
<p>~Destroy Item - If you drop an untradeable item the interface will show up asking if you would like to destroy the item if you hit yes the item will vanish. If you hit no the interface will close.</p>
<p>~Chinchompas - Real chinchompas are here and are pretty well. Only thing is I dont have the gfx working but I will when server comes out.</p>
<p>~DFS/KBD - If you kill KBD he can drop a visage which if you have the req smith level you can use on an anti drag shield and will get a DFS. I took deltas idea on how to get a special effect. It is not the same but I tried to get it close. His is still better.</p>
<p>~Barrows - The barrows brothers just stand above the hill. You kill them and it saves you killcount (i will make it show an interface later) and you must have 1 kill of each to open chest and get a barrow reward. The reward is a pretty good chance so it shouldnt be that hard.</p>
<p>~Working Veng - If you have the right runes and the right level you can use veng. I think I made it pretty nice. Hard to explain I will just show it further down with videos.</p>
<p>~Assault - To get there you need to click on that hay stack near varrock east bank. You need a combined attack and strength of 130 to enter. When you get there you kill the cyclops and get a killcount/point Than you trade the guy there and he will have defenders and torso there and you can exchange.</p>
<p>~Client Updates - Friends that are online will appear at the top. If you add a friend and they are not on, do not fear. The client will not crash. When you click on an item the color will be a different color same with objects. You wull have to find out what colors when you play =p</p>
<p>~Quests - 2 quests so far. Lost city and desert treasure. They are pretty well so far. Ill add video later.</p>
<p>~Perfect 1v1 Pking<br>
~Void Works(my own)<br>
~All Godswords with real spec/gfx and they all do real effect.<br>
~Working Prayer<br>
~Piety and Chiv work ( all they do is bump up str like burst of str, except they do it more)<br>
~Working K Queen (Dosent have second form yet)<br>
~All Dupes Fixed So gl Duping<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">VIDEOS</span><br>
Client Preview - <a href="http://tinypic.com/player.php?v=mizcpi&amp;s=4" rel="nofollow noopener">http://tinypic.com/player.php?v=mizcpi&amp;s=4</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">PICTURES</span><br>
<img src="http://img407.imageshack.us/img407/4237/thiefnr2.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
By <a href="http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">bowlerboi26</a> at 2008-11-07<br>
<img src="http://img220.imageshack.us/img220/7775/prayerri1.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
By <a href="http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">bowlerboi26</a> at 2008-11-07<br>
<img src="http://img99.imageshack.us/img99/1118/miningoutofspacenr3.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
By <a href="http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">bowlerboi26</a> at 2008-11-07<br>
<img src="http://img411.imageshack.us/img411/6569/miningyu2.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
By <a href="http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">bowlerboi26</a> at 2008-11-07<br>
<img src="http://img518.imageshack.us/img518/6797/herbsnr8.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
By <a href="http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">bowlerboi26</a> at 2008-11-07<br>
<img src="http://img407.imageshack.us/img407/1191/cleanherbzg1.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
By <a href="http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">bowlerboi26</a> at 2008-11-07<br>
<img src="http://img521.imageshack.us/img521/7546/dragarrowsgp8.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
By <a href="http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">bowlerboi26</a> at 2008-11-07<br>
<img src="http://img407.imageshack.us/img407/3566/deadbq1.jpg" alt width="" height=""><br>
By <a href="http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">bowlerboi26</a> at 2008-11-07<br>
<img src="http://img521.imageshack.us/img521/2189/clientbackgroundtr9.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
By <a href="http://profile.imageshack.us/user/bowlerboi26" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">bowlerboi26</a> at 2008-11-07</p>
<p>I am sure I forgot a lot of things but I will update as I remember</p>
<p>Some Credits not giving percentages<br>
Delta-Helping/Using a few things from yours<br>
'Rich-Interface<br>
And some poeple that help me on here</p>
<p>P.S This is NOT DS SOURCE.<span class="bbcode-b"></span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 01:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-241896-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rs-united/241896.rss">Rs United</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
