<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248</link>
    <description>[size=45pt][center][center]Welcome to the Debate of Call of duty and Halo.
Post what you think of Call of duty or Halo!
What I think:[/center]

I found this on a Website named _--_  Reviews.Teambox It is exactly what i think Of [center][i]/Call of duty 4: Modern Warfare/[/i][/center][/size]

[center]The World War II first-person shooter genre is officially dead and buried. So sayeth the folks at Infinity Ward, developers of the celebrated Call of Duty series. This is the franchise (along with EA’s Medal of Honor series) that brought the genre to a new level of immersion and intensity that we had never seen before. However, thanks to a glut of imitators (some quite good, some terrible), gamers quickly tired of the WWII shooter, especially ones that didn’t offer any new gameplay mechanics or innovations. Now, with the upcoming release of Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare, they’re about to relegate the WWII shooter to history’s dustbin. Infinity Ward has succeeded in creating a masterpiece of the first-person shooter genre, adeptly blending an intense, story-driven single-player campaign with an addictive multiplayer mode. 

Modern Warfare kicks off with a brief tutorial designed to teach the player about the game’s controls, followed by a trip through a testing area. Though this was created to determine which difficulty level the player should attempt, this editor highly recommends that hardcore shooter fans play on the Hardened difficultly level. Like Halo 3, the normal level is just a bit too easy, and most players will be able to get through it without too much trouble. There have been a lot of people questioning how long Call of Duty 4 is, and the answer depends mainly on how you want to experience the game. Personally, I found that 8-10 extremely intense hours on Hardened was more fun than 6-7 very intense hours on Regular. As you might have gathered, this is one hell of an intense ride no matter what difficultly you play on. 
[/center]

[img]http://media.teamxbox.com/games/ss/1719/1194292285.jpg[/img]

[center]While the previous Call of Duty games simply followed characters through their particular WWII campaigns, Infinity Ward decided to scrap that approach in favor of a tight narrative structure. The plot is seemingly ripped right out of the headlines, touching on everything from Islamic fundamentalism to missing Soviet-era warheads, as well as a number of other hot-button issues. I have to admit, I wasn’t expecting too much from the story, as I’ve seen all of this Tom Clancyesque stuff before. However, I’m happy to say that I was blown away by just how engaging and immersive it was. Modern Warfare features a number of stunning plot-driven sequences, and the fact that many of these scenes are shown from the first-person perspective only makes them that much more gripping. 

Part of what makes the story so great is the fact that you’ll actually feel an emotional attachment to the soldiers fighting alongside you. These aren’t just a bunch of random dudes who run into battle with you, although there are a few of them here and there. Instead, you’ll spend the majority of your time watching their backs as they watch yours, and you’ll likely come to enjoy the interplay between your teammates. The British S.A.S. squad is particularly memorable, and we’re sure that Capt. Price and Gaz will go down as two of the most beloved supporting characters in the history of the Xbox 360. To say that Capt. Price is one of gaming’s biggest badasses is an understatement, and we really hope that he gets a spin-off of his very own in the future. 

Although some people out there might gripe that they can’t give orders to their teammates or some such nonsense, we found that not only could our squadmates hold their own in battle, they were actually too good at times. There were some sequences in which my teammates took out a room of enemies before I could even enter. The squad AI is remarkably impressive, perhaps the best seen in a video game to date. I found that whenever I couldn’t figure out where the enemies were, all I had to do was take a breath and watch my teammates. They’re really on top of things, even managing to save your life on many occasions. [/center]

[center]That’s right, they’ll save your life, even if you don’t always deserve it. For instance, during one of the game most intense firefights (in game with dozens of intense firefights, this one is particularly memorable), I was being overwhelmed by enemies, yet I was managing to hold my own. However, once I heard the clink of a grenade a few feet away, I knew that I was probably a goner. Suddenly, I saw one of my squadmates run out from behind the rubble he had taken cover behind, grab the grenade, and throw it into the air, where it exploded. This is just one example of the excellent Team AI, and we’ve heard of a number of other “oh man, did he just do that?” moments. 

As anyone who’s played a Call of Duty game before knows, the missions are fairly linear, featuring a good deal of scripted moments to enhance the cinematic quality of the proceedings. This is the case with Modern Warfare, although the battlefields are a bit more open than they were before. You’ll still be given an objective to carry out but, in many cases, how you complete it is up to you. You might choose to charge right through the middle of the battle (note: Not a good idea!), slowly move from cover to cover, or try to sneak around the outside. There are more options in combat than ever before, although you’ll still be funneled into the story-driven moments to keep the narrative flowing smoothly. 
[/center]
[img]http://media.teamxbox.com/games/ss/1719/1194292414.jpg[/img]

[center]Of course, the most important element of a Call of Duty game is the gameplay, and we’re happy to say that Modern Warfare feature some of the best first-person action ever seen in a game. The combat is amazingly intense from beginning to end, and you’ll likely need to take a break to catch your breath from time to time. As I mentioned near the beginning of this article, longtime shooter fans may want to play the game on the Hardened difficulty, as it makes the game much more intense. Still, no matter what difficulty you choose to play on, you’ll be blown away by the cinematic intensity of this one. For a real test, see how long you can stay alive in Veteran mode, especially on the last level (stick around after the credits!). 

Once you’re done with the single-player campaign mode, you can head into Arcade Mode in an attempt to prove your skills to the unwashed masses on Xbox Live. In this mode, you’ll earn points for killing enemies in rapid succession, as you’ll be given multipliers from time to time. The interesting twist is that not only will the level be timed (meaning if you don’t finish in time, you won’t get the points), you’ll have a limited number of “lives” to expend. This mean that you’ll want to push yourself as hard as possible get as many kills as you can, but not so hard that you die frequently. Once you finish the mission, you’ll be rewarded with bonuses for extra live, the amount of time remaining, and a multiplier based on the difficulty level. The Arcade Mode isn’t groundbreaking or anything like that, but it’s definitely a lot of fun. 

While the single-player mode is excellent and the Arcade Mode adds a bit of replay value, it’s likely that we’ll still be playing the multiplayer mode for months to come. As anyone who was able to play the Beta already knows, the Multiplayer features the same intense action we’ve come to expect from the Call of Duty franchise. The best part of this aspect is the tiered approach, which rewards players for spending time with the game. As you play and move up in rank, you’ll unlock new weapons and gear (and Perks!) that will give you the upper hand over your opponents. It’s a solid system that’s been designed to give the player just enough to keep them coming back for more.  [/center] 

[color=red][center]During the Beta, we only had the chance to check out 3 maps and a few game modes, so we were wondering just how many options would be available when the game was released. Well, we’re happy to say that there are a whopping 16 multiplayer maps (be sure to watch our walkthroughs for a look at each of them) and a bunch of game modes to keep you busy. We particularly enjoyed Sabotage, in which both teams must try to grab a bomb and deliver it to the enemy’s base. The interesting twist here is the fact that the player holding the bomb has a big, red “KILL” indicator over his head. So, yeah, that makes for some pretty stressful moments. 

Aside from the Perks and “Create a Class” system, the coolest part of the multiplayer mode is the ability to tweak the options to your liking. Yes, we realize that plenty of games have done this before, but there are a couple of fun little wrinkles in the Game Rules options. By turning on Old School Mode, you’ll increase player health and give everyone the ability to jump twice as high (shades of Halo 3?). Rather than having custom classes, players can pick up perks as they play, so staying alive for a long time will let you turn into a multi-perked supersoldier. Hardcore Mode, on the other hand, makes the action one-hit-one-kill and turns off all radar… even the grenade indicator. Friendly fire is also enabled, so you’ll have to check your fire if you can’t tell friend from foe. Both of these modes are a lot of fun, and while it would be easy to set them up on your own, this is a lot quicker. 

[/center]
[center][img]http://media.teamxbox.com/games/ss/1719/1194292371.jpg[/img][/center]

[color=red][center]Visually, Call of Duty 4 is a treat, offering some of the most impressive visuals seen on the system to date. The developers wanted to make the game look as realistic as possible, and in many ways they succeeded. The character models look particularly excellent, especially when they are moving. The animation system is top-notch, and we didn’t notice any weird sliding or clipping or anything like that. Basically, characters move exactly as you’d expect them to. The environments are highly detailed, although it’s not like you’ll have much time to stop and admire the grass or stare at the wallpaper. Best of all, the game runs at a beautifully smooth 60 frames per second, although there were some blips here and there during the in-game loads. 

The folks at Infinity Ward have long been lauded for their work in the field of game audio, and Modern Warfare is a perfect showcase for their substantial store of knowledge. The game sounds absolutely awesome when cranked out on a 5.1 surround sound system, particularly during the heat of combat. I was particularly impressed by the way explosions basically shook the entire room I was playing in, as well as the way enemies screamed when shot. The score by Harry Gregson-William is also excellent, managing to be epic and sweeping without ever being too overwhelming. 

Simply put, Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare is an instant classic. The fact that Infinity Ward has created a modern-day masterpiece probably isn’t surprising given their impressive track record to date, but our lofty expectations were actually surpassed in many ways. The single-player game was particularly surprising, as none of us expected the game to have such a compelling, narrative-driven campaign. It’s one of the best stories of the year, and it instantly thrusts Infinity Ward into the storytelling pantheon with developers like Valve and Irrational. Of course, one can’t forget the multiplayer, which is just as addictive as we hoped it would be. Infinity Ward has officially killed off the WWII FPS genre, and we can’t wait to see what they have in store for us next. [/center]
[size=30pt]
RATING BOARD:[/size]

[IMG]http://i35.tinypic.com/f29bte.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 21:11:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I prefer Battlefield: Bad Company for console, CS for computer.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 21:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@FastBallz FastBawlz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fastballz">@FastBallz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The answer is pretty obvious.<br>
CS &gt; *<br>
With the exception of TF2.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 03:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_bank the bank]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_bank">@the_bank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kevin3654, post:20, topic:232248”]This is a debate … you dumb hick.[/quote]Go die already.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 17:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kevin3654 Kevin3654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kevin3654">@Kevin3654</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is a debate … you dumb hick.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 17:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_bank the bank]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_bank">@the_bank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“davidude36, post:18, topic:232248”]Fuck sake, why do you think they made a games section?[/quote]So that it can be ignored by idiots and retards around the world.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 13:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Fuck sake, why do you think they made a games section?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 12:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Will someone ban this spamming noob (Kevin)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 11:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kevin3654 Kevin3654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kevin3654">@Kevin3654</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Uh I havent heard of them lol… V-V</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 06:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What about Battlefield 1942/Vietnam/2/2:SF/2:EF&amp;AF? Also, Counter-Strike is with a dash, not an underscore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 05:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kevin3654 Kevin3654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kevin3654">@Kevin3654</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ooooo Ill add Battle-Field Bad Company and Counter-Strike thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 05:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What about the Battlefield series, or Counter-Strike [Source]?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 04:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kevin3654 Kevin3654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kevin3654">@Kevin3654</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>COD2 my ballsac…!<br>
Halo does suck u are right</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 04:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chrisn2323 chrisn2323]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrisn2323">@chrisn2323</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>cod2</p>
<p>halo sucks and is easy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 03:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kevin3654 Kevin3654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kevin3654">@Kevin3654</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have a freakin LIFE you idiot!<br>
Weekend is my spare time</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 02:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cruzer Cruzer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruzer">@Cruzer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kevin3654, post:8, topic:232248”]Yea dude its okay that i posted it though right…??<br>
And why cant you get on Xbox?[/quote]<br>
Some people unlike you have lives</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 02:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kevin3654 Kevin3654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kevin3654">@Kevin3654</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yea dude its okay that i posted it though right…??<br>
And why cant you get on Xbox?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 02:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxKanexX Kane.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxkanexx">@XxKanexX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kevin3654, post:6, topic:232248”][quote author=Kane. link=topic=305927.msg2450704#msg2450704 date=1221957421]<br>
It’s all down to a matter of preference. There is no better game, it’s what you like to play more.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Actually I have heard alot of Debates between these 2 games…<br>
I really don’t care if you want to move it.[/quote]<br>
Yeah, there’s a ton of Debates, but there really is no “better” game, persay.<br>
Some people prefer to play CoD, while some would rather play Halo.<br>
It’s just what we find more fun.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 02:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kevin3654 Kevin3654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kevin3654">@Kevin3654</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="232248">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Kane.:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s all down to a matter of preference. There is no better game, it’s what you like to play more.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Actually I have heard alot of Debates between these 2 games…<br>
I really don’t care if you want to move it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 00:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxKanexX Kane.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxkanexx">@XxKanexX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s all down to a matter of preference. There is no better game, it’s what you like to play more.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 00:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uriko Uriko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uriko">@Uriko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kevin3654, post:3, topic:232248”]I know but i like showing off posts lol…[/quote]That’s dumb…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 00:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kevin3654 Kevin3654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kevin3654">@Kevin3654</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I know but i like showing off posts lol…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://reviews.teamxbox.com/xbox-360/1421/Call-of-Duty-4-Modern-Warfare/p1/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://reviews.teamxbox.com/xbox-360/1421/Call-of-Duty-4-Modern-Warfare/p1/</a></p>
<p>You could of just linked us.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 00:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kevin3654 Kevin3654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kevin3654">@Kevin3654</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=45pt][center][center]Welcome to the Debate of Call of duty and Halo.<br>
Post what you think of Call of duty or Halo!<br>
What I think:[/center]</p>
<p>I found this on a Website named <em>–</em>  Reviews.Teambox It is exactly what i think Of [center]<span class="bbcode-i">/Call of duty 4: Modern Warfare/</span>[/center][/size]</p>
<p>[center]The World War II first-person shooter genre is officially dead and buried. So sayeth the folks at Infinity Ward, developers of the celebrated Call of Duty series. This is the franchise (along with EA’s Medal of Honor series) that brought the genre to a new level of immersion and intensity that we had never seen before. However, thanks to a glut of imitators (some quite good, some terrible), gamers quickly tired of the WWII shooter, especially ones that didn’t offer any new gameplay mechanics or innovations. Now, with the upcoming release of Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare, they’re about to relegate the WWII shooter to history’s dustbin. Infinity Ward has succeeded in creating a masterpiece of the first-person shooter genre, adeptly blending an intense, story-driven single-player campaign with an addictive multiplayer mode.</p>
<p>Modern Warfare kicks off with a brief tutorial designed to teach the player about the game’s controls, followed by a trip through a testing area. Though this was created to determine which difficulty level the player should attempt, this editor highly recommends that hardcore shooter fans play on the Hardened difficultly level. Like Halo 3, the normal level is just a bit too easy, and most players will be able to get through it without too much trouble. There have been a lot of people questioning how long Call of Duty 4 is, and the answer depends mainly on how you want to experience the game. Personally, I found that 8-10 extremely intense hours on Hardened was more fun than 6-7 very intense hours on Regular. As you might have gathered, this is one hell of an intense ride no matter what difficultly you play on.<br>
[/center]</p>
<p><img src="http://media.teamxbox.com/games/ss/1719/1194292285.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[center]While the previous Call of Duty games simply followed characters through their particular WWII campaigns, Infinity Ward decided to scrap that approach in favor of a tight narrative structure. The plot is seemingly ripped right out of the headlines, touching on everything from Islamic fundamentalism to missing Soviet-era warheads, as well as a number of other hot-button issues. I have to admit, I wasn’t expecting too much from the story, as I’ve seen all of this Tom Clancyesque stuff before. However, I’m happy to say that I was blown away by just how engaging and immersive it was. Modern Warfare features a number of stunning plot-driven sequences, and the fact that many of these scenes are shown from the first-person perspective only makes them that much more gripping.</p>
<p>Part of what makes the story so great is the fact that you’ll actually feel an emotional attachment to the soldiers fighting alongside you. These aren’t just a bunch of random dudes who run into battle with you, although there are a few of them here and there. Instead, you’ll spend the majority of your time watching their backs as they watch yours, and you’ll likely come to enjoy the interplay between your teammates. The British S.A.S. squad is particularly memorable, and we’re sure that Capt. Price and Gaz will go down as two of the most beloved supporting characters in the history of the Xbox 360. To say that Capt. Price is one of gaming’s biggest badasses is an understatement, and we really hope that he gets a spin-off of his very own in the future.</p>
<p>Although some people out there might gripe that they can’t give orders to their teammates or some such nonsense, we found that not only could our squadmates hold their own in battle, they were actually too good at times. There were some sequences in which my teammates took out a room of enemies before I could even enter. The squad AI is remarkably impressive, perhaps the best seen in a video game to date. I found that whenever I couldn’t figure out where the enemies were, all I had to do was take a breath and watch my teammates. They’re really on top of things, even managing to save your life on many occasions. [/center]</p>
<p>[center]That’s right, they’ll save your life, even if you don’t always deserve it. For instance, during one of the game most intense firefights (in game with dozens of intense firefights, this one is particularly memorable), I was being overwhelmed by enemies, yet I was managing to hold my own. However, once I heard the clink of a grenade a few feet away, I knew that I was probably a goner. Suddenly, I saw one of my squadmates run out from behind the rubble he had taken cover behind, grab the grenade, and throw it into the air, where it exploded. This is just one example of the excellent Team AI, and we’ve heard of a number of other “oh man, did he just do that?” moments.</p>
<p>As anyone who’s played a Call of Duty game before knows, the missions are fairly linear, featuring a good deal of scripted moments to enhance the cinematic quality of the proceedings. This is the case with Modern Warfare, although the battlefields are a bit more open than they were before. You’ll still be given an objective to carry out but, in many cases, how you complete it is up to you. You might choose to charge right through the middle of the battle (note: Not a good idea!), slowly move from cover to cover, or try to sneak around the outside. There are more options in combat than ever before, although you’ll still be funneled into the story-driven moments to keep the narrative flowing smoothly.<br>
[/center]<br>
<img src="http://media.teamxbox.com/games/ss/1719/1194292414.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[center]Of course, the most important element of a Call of Duty game is the gameplay, and we’re happy to say that Modern Warfare feature some of the best first-person action ever seen in a game. The combat is amazingly intense from beginning to end, and you’ll likely need to take a break to catch your breath from time to time. As I mentioned near the beginning of this article, longtime shooter fans may want to play the game on the Hardened difficulty, as it makes the game much more intense. Still, no matter what difficulty you choose to play on, you’ll be blown away by the cinematic intensity of this one. For a real test, see how long you can stay alive in Veteran mode, especially on the last level (stick around after the credits!).</p>
<p>Once you’re done with the single-player campaign mode, you can head into Arcade Mode in an attempt to prove your skills to the unwashed masses on Xbox Live. In this mode, you’ll earn points for killing enemies in rapid succession, as you’ll be given multipliers from time to time. The interesting twist is that not only will the level be timed (meaning if you don’t finish in time, you won’t get the points), you’ll have a limited number of “lives” to expend. This mean that you’ll want to push yourself as hard as possible get as many kills as you can, but not so hard that you die frequently. Once you finish the mission, you’ll be rewarded with bonuses for extra live, the amount of time remaining, and a multiplier based on the difficulty level. The Arcade Mode isn’t groundbreaking or anything like that, but it’s definitely a lot of fun.</p>
<p>While the single-player mode is excellent and the Arcade Mode adds a bit of replay value, it’s likely that we’ll still be playing the multiplayer mode for months to come. As anyone who was able to play the Beta already knows, the Multiplayer features the same intense action we’ve come to expect from the Call of Duty franchise. The best part of this aspect is the tiered approach, which rewards players for spending time with the game. As you play and move up in rank, you’ll unlock new weapons and gear (and Perks!) that will give you the upper hand over your opponents. It’s a solid system that’s been designed to give the player just enough to keep them coming back for more.  [/center]</p>
<p>[color=red][center]During the Beta, we only had the chance to check out 3 maps and a few game modes, so we were wondering just how many options would be available when the game was released. Well, we’re happy to say that there are a whopping 16 multiplayer maps (be sure to watch our walkthroughs for a look at each of them) and a bunch of game modes to keep you busy. We particularly enjoyed Sabotage, in which both teams must try to grab a bomb and deliver it to the enemy’s base. The interesting twist here is the fact that the player holding the bomb has a big, red “KILL” indicator over his head. So, yeah, that makes for some pretty stressful moments.</p>
<p>Aside from the Perks and “Create a Class” system, the coolest part of the multiplayer mode is the ability to tweak the options to your liking. Yes, we realize that plenty of games have done this before, but there are a couple of fun little wrinkles in the Game Rules options. By turning on Old School Mode, you’ll increase player health and give everyone the ability to jump twice as high (shades of Halo 3?). Rather than having custom classes, players can pick up perks as they play, so staying alive for a long time will let you turn into a multi-perked supersoldier. Hardcore Mode, on the other hand, makes the action one-hit-one-kill and turns off all radar… even the grenade indicator. Friendly fire is also enabled, so you’ll have to check your fire if you can’t tell friend from foe. Both of these modes are a lot of fun, and while it would be easy to set them up on your own, this is a lot quicker.</p>
<p>[/center]<br>
[center]<img src="http://media.teamxbox.com/games/ss/1719/1194292371.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p>[color=red][center]Visually, Call of Duty 4 is a treat, offering some of the most impressive visuals seen on the system to date. The developers wanted to make the game look as realistic as possible, and in many ways they succeeded. The character models look particularly excellent, especially when they are moving. The animation system is top-notch, and we didn’t notice any weird sliding or clipping or anything like that. Basically, characters move exactly as you’d expect them to. The environments are highly detailed, although it’s not like you’ll have much time to stop and admire the grass or stare at the wallpaper. Best of all, the game runs at a beautifully smooth 60 frames per second, although there were some blips here and there during the in-game loads.</p>
<p>The folks at Infinity Ward have long been lauded for their work in the field of game audio, and Modern Warfare is a perfect showcase for their substantial store of knowledge. The game sounds absolutely awesome when cranked out on a 5.1 surround sound system, particularly during the heat of combat. I was particularly impressed by the way explosions basically shook the entire room I was playing in, as well as the way enemies screamed when shot. The score by Harry Gregson-William is also excellent, managing to be epic and sweeping without ever being too overwhelming.</p>
<p>Simply put, Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare is an instant classic. The fact that Infinity Ward has created a modern-day masterpiece probably isn’t surprising given their impressive track record to date, but our lofty expectations were actually surpassed in many ways. The single-player game was particularly surprising, as none of us expected the game to have such a compelling, narrative-driven campaign. It’s one of the best stories of the year, and it instantly thrusts Infinity Ward into the storytelling pantheon with developers like Valve and Irrational. Of course, one can’t forget the multiplayer, which is just as addictive as we hoped it would be. Infinity Ward has officially killed off the WWII FPS genre, and we can’t wait to see what they have in store for us next. [/center]<br>
[size=30pt]<br>
RATING BOARD:[/size]</p>
<p><img src="http://i35.tinypic.com/f29bte.jpg" alt width="140" height="120"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2008 23:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-232248-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cod-counter-strike-battlefield-bc-battlefield-series-halo/232248.rss">COD -- Counter_Strike -- Battlefield BC -- Battlefield Series -- -- Halo --</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
