<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994</link>
    <description>[center]Well.. what can I say? If you want to flourish in Runescape, you can NOT do it without lots, and lots of money.
How can we make money?
Well, the possibilities are endless, really, but lots of money making methods are focused around the grand exchange, and that will be a BIG part of the lesson.
I. [size=12pt][b]Managing Prices[/b][/size]
A. [b]Studying the Prices[/b]
 Managing prices is, well, the heart of all money making. And this can be done by using the grand exchange feature on the website to look at the price and price history of items @ Home &gt; Game Guide &gt; Grand Exchange. And if you search an item in the said area, and your desired item will come up in the results, and you can see the price, and the price drop. Click on this item, to see the history of it, for either 30, 90, or 180 days, and the graph is very friendly.
[img]http://services.runescape.com/m=itemdb_rs/3410_obj_big.gif?id=1059[/img]
[img]http://services.runescape.com/m=itemdb_rs/3413c_graphimg3.gif?id=1059&amp;scale=0[/img]
B. [b]But how do we know prices will rise?[/b]
 Supply and Demand. You need to know everything, if a double exp weekend is coming up, what do you think will happen to herb prices? Seed prices? They will definitely rise. This also applies to updates, for example, lets say a sword much better than the godsword is released, what do you think will happen then? Godsword prices will drop, and it would be harder to make money at godwars. Basically, when an update is announced, but not yet released, you&#39;ll want to think carefully about what will happen.... Take the example above.. maybe you had 100 godswords, waiting for prices to rise? But with this update with a &quot;stronger weapon&quot; coming, then you would loose a lot of money, and might not even sell your swords.
II. [size=12pt][b]Rares[/b][/size]
A. [b]Explanation [/b]
What are rares? In other words, basically discontinued items, such as the party hat, the Halloween mask, the pumpkin, Easter egg, etc, meaning there is a limited amount of them and will never be released again by Jagex in any type of event. Surely you must have heard one of those… Most of these items were released early in Runescape, in holiday events, and some were just discontinued because of the lack of its use, or being obsolete, etc. Lets go back Runescape, in December 2001. You could walk around, and find a Christmas Cracker on the floor, and get a partyhat out of it! Soon, everyone had a partyhat, going for even only 50k, almost like a junk item. BUT, soon, in time, less, and less party hats existed… In turn, prices went up. And kept rising… 
Do you know why this happened? Now if you look at an average item that can be lets say obtained from a drop, the prices would fluctuate a lot, or be stable at one point. But rare items, they might crash in price some times, but ultimately, they keep rising, and rising, and rising… Now look at party hats! They are in the billions!
So if you have the money and ONLY if you have the money, I would recommend buying an rare item, because it will eventually keep on rising. Now you may be discouraged by things like Halloween masks, being only a fraction of a party hats price, but as stated above, check the 180 day graph.. and you will then know what I mean about a rare items’ price…
B. [b]So... you are saying we should buy rare items?[/b]
Precisely! But not if you have exactly the price to buy the rare item you want, but only if you sell all your items and your entire bank…. No, you will not make millions every day by keeping it.. It is more of a long term investment, but it will always rise.
C. [b]How do we know when an item will be discontinued?[/b]
Jagex said they will not make any other items discontinued, or given at a holiday event, and be sellable, because they said it is “Unfair” to other players, so don’t go around buying everything hoping it will become a rare item..
III. [size=12pt][b]Grand Exchange Properties[/b][/size]
A. [b]Limits[/b]
The grand exchange has limits to how many of a certain type of item you can buy per 4 hours, unless you sell them back/buy more depending on what you do with the limit of items.
Below are the limits:
[img]http://img839.imageshack.us/img839/9374/fsdfn.png[/img]
[img]http://img194.imageshack.us/img194/5877/sdfae.png[/img]
Thank you to the runescape wikia for those two images :).
B, [b]You too can control the prices![/b]
Selling prices for under the medium price will cause item prices to drop, 1 or 2 of the item may not make a big difference, but in bulk, it will hit the economy hard.
Effectively, the same principle goes for selling higher than medium price.
IV. [b][size=12pt]Making Money[/size][/b]
Well, now that we have all the basics down… We can get started!
So now that you know about supply and demand, we can talk about merchanting and flipping!
A. [b]Merchanting[/b]
If you know how to merchant right, you can make tons of money. But basically, you need to know the first chapter the most.
Well.. let me just start off with some basic things…
1. [b]NEVER[/b] try to merchant an item that doesn’t really change in price (Stable), though you can, I’m not a wizard at merchanting, so I might add to this later from knowledge of expert merchants. 
2. Don’t merch an item crashing.. I mean really?...
Anyways, so this will be like an investment, if you will.
You can do the following:
A short term investment
Or..
A long term investment
Now, your goal, basically, is to keep the item until it rises, then sell it, so let me get an example.. You buy 10 torva sets. The overall prices increases 30k. You sell the sets back for a 300k profit. And the same principle applies for loosing money.
And as an ending note, merchanting is more or less gambling, because of prices changing, so be aware of that!
B. [b]Merchanting Clans[/b]
I don’t know if these exist anymore.. I personally don’t see them as much.. but let me give you an explanation.
You see, most of the time, its an manipulation/scam, which the scammer is the owner, but its not reportable. Let me give an example.
So in this “clan” the owner says to buy out all of a certain item in the ge, lets say raw tuna. And then, like stated above, supply and demand kicks in. People start trying to buy for higher prices, more people in general try buying and failing, and prices rise. And when the clan dumps the item at the high price, they usually sell.
BUT, here is were the scamming comes in.. So the owner tells the clan to sell when the tunas reach 30k, but he sells his/hers at 25k, and the prices drop dramatically, and no one can sell their raw tuna, and they overall loose their money, and the owner gains it. That is why merchanting clans are never a good idea.
C. [b]Flipping[/b]
My personal favorite… you can make an infinite amount of money like this!
Basically, you are buying an item (At their limit, for example, 25k of a certain rune) and selling them for higher than you buy them.
Even if you buy 25k of a certain type of runes, and sell them 4 gp higher than for what you bought them, that’s a 100k profit!
The only hard part is determining buying/selling prices… And here is how you find both of those:
1.  Attempt to buy the item at medium price (In this case, a rune), and if it buys, try 1 gp lower. If it still buys, try another gp lower, and so on, until you see it does not buy any more, the lowest it bought for is your buying price (Allow the item 1-5 minutes before determining it is the lowest you can buy for). Now lets say medium price is 480 gp, and I bought them for 472 gp, around lets say 8 of them.
2. Now, repeat, except sell them, starting from medium, if it sells, take it up another gp, then take it up another, and another, until lets say it stopped at 488, and the 8 we bought are sold, if not, just sell them at some random price so you can buy all 25k of the death runes. Now give it some time, and buy at 472, once it buys, sell at 488. 
Now we do the math…
488-472= 16gp. Multiplied by the amount of the item we bought.. 25000…
400k profit!
V. [b][size=12pt]Other methods[/size][/b]
A. [b]“Picking” items.[/b]
1. Blue dragon scales, the way I do it.
Required skills:
70+ hp recommended
70+ defense recommended 
70 agility
50 construction (45 if you have only a butler)
43+ Prayer

Required items:
Home teleport tab(alot) 
Required items at house:
A butler/demon butler (50, or 40 for regular butler)
a prayer altar (lvl 45 for oak altar, lowest level altar)
A Falador portal (not required, but saves space for dragon scales, requires 50 construction)

Required armor
Antifire shield
Ring of life (not recommended)
Armor of any type, but it WILL slow you down (again, not recommended)
Any anti-weight equipment, like boots of lightness, etc.

Make sure you have 50/45 construction
Move your house to Taverly
Make sure you have a butler/demon butler
Make sure you have any kind of prayer altar
Get the required items/weapons
Teleport to your house with your house teleport teletab (If you do not have full prayer, restore at your altar)
And exit your home, then go south to the taverly dungeon, enter the pipe, turn on protect from melee, if you have a antifire potion, now would be the time to use it, again not recommended.
Collect your scales, then teletab to your house, turn off prayer, store your scales with your butler (pay him if needed, from your bank.), and repeat.
Once you run out of cash/supplies, go to your home, go to the falador portal, restock at a falador bank, tele to your home, and repeat!

2. Mort Myre Fungus
Required Skills:
60+ Prayer
Desert Treasure
High hp never hurts..
An familiar (If so, use a mini obelisk in your house), but not required.
An altar at home.
Canfis Teleport at home.
Anti-weight gear
Blessed sickle
Prayer potion if you are under 70 prayer.
House teleport tabs

1. Summon your familiar.
2. Go to Canifis, and the then the Mort Myre Swamp.
3. Find a place with a good amount of logs laying around
4. Right click and use the option “Bloom” with the silver sickle.
5.Pick the fungus. 
6. Store in your familiar when full/ use your potions.
7. When done, tele to home, restore prayer and summoning, and go through your canfis portal, go to the bank, and repeat!
Thank you for reading my guide!
Might add more later.[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 15:43:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="401994">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/devilscape/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> DevilsCape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Awesome guide ^^ tho i dont guess i understood all of it …  but atleast some of it… thx dude this Might HELP in the future</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks.</p>
<p>Could you say which parts you didn’t understand?<br>
Only so i can work on it and make it simpler :).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 15:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DevilsCape DevilsCape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/devilscape">@DevilsCape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Awesome guide ^^ tho i dont guess i understood all of it …  but atleast some of it… thx dude this Might HELP in the future</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 09:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:9, topic:401994”][quote author=drubrkletern link=topic=499048.msg3650691#msg3650691 date=1309716240]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Just so you know drub, you don’t need to verify the guide with him unless that’s your choice, he doesn’t own the tutorial market or anything <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, yeah, but I want it to be a part of the guide though :).<br>
[/quote]Why, when you could have your own? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>But yea, you really should work on formatting. Center-all isn’t really working for this… :|[/quote]<br>
[center]Why not? :s.[/center]<br>
Oh well, its the first draft, kind of, ill add information, update it, and make it pretty as it goes on.</p>
<blockquote>[b]Why when you can have your own?[/b]</blockquote>
It will fail horribly :P.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 01:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“drubrkletern, post:5, topic:401994”][quote author=Davidi2 link=topic=499048.msg3650667#msg3650667 date=1309714548]<br>
Just so you know drub, you don’t need to verify the guide with him unless that’s your choice, he doesn’t own the tutorial market or anything <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
[/quote]<br>
Well, yeah, but I want it to be a part of the guide though :).[/quote]Why, when you could have your own? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>But yea, you really should work on formatting. Center-all isn’t really working for this… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 19:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 I Vain I:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I demand I get a subsection since I’ve loaned out over 30m so far. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>wtfbbq<br>
nevar.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 18:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“I Vain I”]Nice money making guide.</p>
<p>Does the include the part where you borrowed 5M from me? :|[/quote]<br>
there is a part about scamming ppl when you loan them :). still haven’t gotten to it yet though lol. dun worry, i pay you back soon :).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 18:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew_Ferguson The317Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew_ferguson">@Andrew_Ferguson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="401994">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just so you know drub, you don’t need to verify the guide with him unless that’s your choice, he doesn’t own the tutorial market or anything <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do own the guide topic though haha :3</p>
<p>[quote=“drubrkletern, post:5, topic:401994”][quote author=Davidi2 link=topic=499048.msg3650667#msg3650667 date=1309714548]<br>
Just so you know drub, you don’t need to verify the guide with him unless that’s your choice, he doesn’t own the tutorial market or anything <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
[/quote]<br>
Well, yeah, but I want it to be a part of the guide though :).[/quote]<br>
pm meh when you finish it and ill add it to the list (:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 18:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="401994">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just so you know drub, you don’t need to verify the guide with him unless that’s your choice, he doesn’t own the tutorial market or anything <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, yeah, but I want it to be a part of the guide though :).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just so you know drub, you don’t need to verify the guide with him unless that’s your choice, he doesn’t own the tutorial market or anything <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 17:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh, sorry.</p>
<p>In that case, I’ll finish typing it else were.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 16:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew_Ferguson The317Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew_ferguson">@Andrew_Ferguson</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You must verify the guide with me so i can spell check it, check it for misinformed information and check how much effort was put into it first before I will claim it part of the main guide.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Well… what can I say? If you want to flourish in Runescape, you can NOT do it without lots, and lots of money.<br>
How can we make money?<br>
Well, the possibilities are endless, really, but lots of money making methods are focused around the grand exchange, and that will be a BIG part of the lesson.<br>
I. [size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Managing Prices</span>[/size]<br>
A. <span class="bbcode-b">Studying the Prices</span><br>
Managing prices is, well, the heart of all money making. And this can be done by using the grand exchange feature on the website to look at the price and price history of items @ Home &gt; Game Guide &gt; Grand Exchange. And if you search an item in the said area, and your desired item will come up in the results, and you can see the price, and the price drop. Click on this item, to see the history of it, for either 30, 90, or 180 days, and the graph is very friendly.<br>
<img src="http://services.runescape.com/m=itemdb_rs/3410_obj_big.gif?id=1059" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://services.runescape.com/m=itemdb_rs/3413c_graphimg3.gif?id=1059&amp;scale=0" alt width="" height=""><br>
B. <span class="bbcode-b">But how do we know prices will rise?</span><br>
Supply and Demand. You need to know everything, if a double exp weekend is coming up, what do you think will happen to herb prices? Seed prices? They will definitely rise. This also applies to updates, for example, lets say a sword much better than the godsword is released, what do you think will happen then? Godsword prices will drop, and it would be harder to make money at godwars. Basically, when an update is announced, but not yet released, you’ll want to think carefully about what will happen… Take the example above… maybe you had 100 godswords, waiting for prices to rise? But with this update with a “stronger weapon” coming, then you would loose a lot of money, and might not even sell your swords.<br>
II. [size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Rares</span>[/size]<br>
A. <span class="bbcode-b">Explanation </span><br>
What are rares? In other words, basically discontinued items, such as the party hat, the Halloween mask, the pumpkin, Easter egg, etc, meaning there is a limited amount of them and will never be released again by Jagex in any type of event. Surely you must have heard one of those… Most of these items were released early in Runescape, in holiday events, and some were just discontinued because of the lack of its use, or being obsolete, etc. Lets go back Runescape, in December 2001. You could walk around, and find a Christmas Cracker on the floor, and get a partyhat out of it! Soon, everyone had a partyhat, going for even only 50k, almost like a junk item. BUT, soon, in time, less, and less party hats existed… In turn, prices went up. And kept rising…<br>
Do you know why this happened? Now if you look at an average item that can be lets say obtained from a drop, the prices would fluctuate a lot, or be stable at one point. But rare items, they might crash in price some times, but ultimately, they keep rising, and rising, and rising… Now look at party hats! They are in the billions!<br>
So if you have the money and ONLY if you have the money, I would recommend buying an rare item, because it will eventually keep on rising. Now you may be discouraged by things like Halloween masks, being only a fraction of a party hats price, but as stated above, check the 180 day graph… and you will then know what I mean about a rare items’ price…<br>
B. <span class="bbcode-b">So… you are saying we should buy rare items?</span><br>
Precisely! But not if you have exactly the price to buy the rare item you want, but only if you sell all your items and your entire bank…. No, you will not make millions every day by keeping it… It is more of a long term investment, but it will always rise.<br>
C. <span class="bbcode-b">How do we know when an item will be discontinued?</span><br>
Jagex said they will not make any other items discontinued, or given at a holiday event, and be sellable, because they said it is “Unfair” to other players, so don’t go around buying everything hoping it will become a rare item…<br>
III. [size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Grand Exchange Properties</span>[/size]<br>
A. <span class="bbcode-b">Limits</span><br>
The grand exchange has limits to how many of a certain type of item you can buy per 4 hours, unless you sell them back/buy more depending on what you do with the limit of items.<br>
Below are the limits:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://img839.imageshack.us/img839/9374/fsdfn.png" title="fsdfn.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img839.imageshack.us/img839/9374/fsdfn.png" alt width="493" height="500"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">fsdfn.png</span><span class="informations">649×658</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div><br>
<img src="http://img194.imageshack.us/img194/5877/sdfae.png" alt width="647" height="449"><br>
Thank you to the runescape wikia for those two images :).<br>
B, <span class="bbcode-b">You too can control the prices!</span><br>
Selling prices for under the medium price will cause item prices to drop, 1 or 2 of the item may not make a big difference, but in bulk, it will hit the economy hard.<br>
Effectively, the same principle goes for selling higher than medium price.<br>
IV. <span class="bbcode-b">[size=12pt]Making Money[/size]</span><br>
Well, now that we have all the basics down… We can get started!<br>
So now that you know about supply and demand, we can talk about merchanting and flipping!<br>
A. <span class="bbcode-b">Merchanting</span><br>
If you know how to merchant right, you can make tons of money. But basically, you need to know the first chapter the most.<br>
Well… let me just start off with some basic things…</p>
<ol>
<li>
<span class="bbcode-b">NEVER</span> try to merchant an item that doesn’t really change in price (Stable), though you can, I’m not a wizard at merchanting, so I might add to this later from knowledge of expert merchants.</li>
<li>Don’t merch an item crashing… I mean really?..<br>
Anyways, so this will be like an investment, if you will.<br>
You can do the following:<br>
A short term investment<br>
Or…<br>
A long term investment<br>
Now, your goal, basically, is to keep the item until it rises, then sell it, so let me get an example… You buy 10 torva sets. The overall prices increases 30k. You sell the sets back for a 300k profit. And the same principle applies for loosing money.<br>
And as an ending note, merchanting is more or less gambling, because of prices changing, so be aware of that!<br>
B. <span class="bbcode-b">Merchanting Clans</span><br>
I don’t know if these exist anymore… I personally don’t see them as much… but let me give you an explanation.<br>
You see, most of the time, its an manipulation/scam, which the scammer is the owner, but its not reportable. Let me give an example.<br>
So in this “clan” the owner says to buy out all of a certain item in the ge, lets say raw tuna. And then, like stated above, supply and demand kicks in. People start trying to buy for higher prices, more people in general try buying and failing, and prices rise. And when the clan dumps the item at the high price, they usually sell.<br>
BUT, here is were the scamming comes in… So the owner tells the clan to sell when the tunas reach 30k, but he sells his/hers at 25k, and the prices drop dramatically, and no one can sell their raw tuna, and they overall loose their money, and the owner gains it. That is why merchanting clans are never a good idea.<br>
C. <span class="bbcode-b">Flipping</span><br>
My personal favorite… you can make an infinite amount of money like this!<br>
Basically, you are buying an item (At their limit, for example, 25k of a certain rune) and selling them for higher than you buy them.<br>
Even if you buy 25k of a certain type of runes, and sell them 4 gp higher than for what you bought them, that’s a 100k profit!<br>
The only hard part is determining buying/selling prices… And here is how you find both of those:</li>
<li>Attempt to buy the item at medium price (In this case, a rune), and if it buys, try 1 gp lower. If it still buys, try another gp lower, and so on, until you see it does not buy any more, the lowest it bought for is your buying price (Allow the item 1-5 minutes before determining it is the lowest you can buy for). Now lets say medium price is 480 gp, and I bought them for 472 gp, around lets say 8 of them.</li>
<li>Now, repeat, except sell them, starting from medium, if it sells, take it up another gp, then take it up another, and another, until lets say it stopped at 488, and the 8 we bought are sold, if not, just sell them at some random price so you can buy all 25k of the death runes. Now give it some time, and buy at 472, once it buys, sell at 488.<br>
Now we do the math…<br>
488-472= 16gp. Multiplied by the amount of the item we bought… 25000…<br>
400k profit!<br>
V. <span class="bbcode-b">[size=12pt]Other methods[/size]</span><br>
A. <span class="bbcode-b">“Picking” items.</span>
</li>
<li>Blue dragon scales, the way I do it.<br>
Required skills:<br>
70+ hp recommended<br>
70+ defense recommended<br>
70 agility<br>
50 construction (45 if you have only a butler)<br>
43+ Prayer</li>
</ol>
<p>Required items:<br>
Home teleport tab(alot)<br>
Required items at house:<br>
A butler/demon butler (50, or 40 for regular butler)<br>
a prayer altar (lvl 45 for oak altar, lowest level altar)<br>
A Falador portal (not required, but saves space for dragon scales, requires 50 construction)</p>
<p>Required armor<br>
Antifire shield<br>
Ring of life (not recommended)<br>
Armor of any type, but it WILL slow you down (again, not recommended)<br>
Any anti-weight equipment, like boots of lightness, etc.</p>
<p>Make sure you have 50/45 construction<br>
Move your house to Taverly<br>
Make sure you have a butler/demon butler<br>
Make sure you have any kind of prayer altar<br>
Get the required items/weapons<br>
Teleport to your house with your house teleport teletab (If you do not have full prayer, restore at your altar)<br>
And exit your home, then go south to the taverly dungeon, enter the pipe, turn on protect from melee, if you have a antifire potion, now would be the time to use it, again not recommended.<br>
Collect your scales, then teletab to your house, turn off prayer, store your scales with your butler (pay him if needed, from your bank.), and repeat.<br>
Once you run out of cash/supplies, go to your home, go to the falador portal, restock at a falador bank, tele to your home, and repeat!</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>Mort Myre Fungus<br>
Required Skills:<br>
60+ Prayer<br>
Desert Treasure<br>
High hp never hurts…<br>
An familiar (If so, use a mini obelisk in your house), but not required.<br>
An altar at home.<br>
Canfis Teleport at home.<br>
Anti-weight gear<br>
Blessed sickle<br>
Prayer potion if you are under 70 prayer.<br>
House teleport tabs</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Summon your familiar.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Go to Canifis, and the then the Mort Myre Swamp.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Find a place with a good amount of logs laying around</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Right click and use the option “Bloom” with the silver sickle.<br>
5.Pick the fungus.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Store in your familiar when full/ use your potions.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When done, tele to home, restore prayer and summoning, and go through your canfis portal, go to the bank, and repeat!<br>
Thank you for reading my guide!<br>
Might add more later.[/center]</p>
</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 16:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401994-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/guide-of-runescape-ch-2-money-making/401994.rss">Guide of RuneScape [Ch-2 Money Making]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
