<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mass DC?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-dc/462986</link>
    <description>For some reason, out of the blue, my server just kicks everyone off.  What could be causing this?  I have a 562 RS2HD base and I&#39;m thinking that the cause might be the MySQL connection I have? Or maybe is it my VPS?  I only use this much of RAM if this has anything to do with it: 136.32 MB of 1.25 GB Used  I set my maximum ram usage to 1.25 gb &quot;-Xmx1250m&quot;  I have my sql connection on the server startup and then run various query&#39;s such as hiscores update, voting, and donation which are all on a 60 second timer I believe and I never close and reopen the connection unless the server has a restart and when a player levels up it also runs a query for an adventure log also when a player kills another player it runs a query to update adventures log.  Does anyone know what my problem is?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 22:54:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-dc/462986.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mass DC?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sageofmali sageofmali]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sageofmali">@sageofmali</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For some reason, out of the blue, my server just kicks everyone off.  What could be causing this?  I have a 562 RS2HD base and I’m thinking that the cause might be the MySQL connection I have? Or maybe is it my VPS?  I only use this much of RAM if this has anything to do with it: 136.32 MB of 1.25 GB Used  I set my maximum ram usage to 1.25 gb “-Xmx1250m”  I have my sql connection on the server startup and then run various query’s such as hiscores update, voting, and donation which are all on a 60 second timer I believe and I never close and reopen the connection unless the server has a restart and when a player levels up it also runs a query for an adventure log also when a player kills another player it runs a query to update adventures log.  Does anyone know what my problem is?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-dc/462986/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-dc/462986/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 22:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-462986-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mass-dc/462986.rss">Mass DC?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
