<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fight Caves. (v1)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fight-caves-v1/226808</link>
    <description>Well I decided to make fight caves for something to do. It has [b]all 63 waves[/b]. It uses [b]no cases[/b], so it uses [b]one newNPC[/b] line for spawning most wave NPC&#39;s (exception to level-22 Tz-Kek), probably making it more efficient than most others fight caves.
Managing the waves is simple, I can remove [b]any[/b] NPC or [b]add any amount of waves or NPCs to existing waves[/b] I would want, without modifying any of the core code. I could even create any amount of new waves.

So far it is working perfectly, with a few bugs that I haven&#39;t fixed yet. In version two the proper NPC&#39;s will mage and range. So Tok-Xil will range, jad mage/range randomly, 360 will mage, etc. In the end of the video the Xil died really fast, in reality it won&#39;t, this is just a first version. And in reality, in the next version waves won&#39;t go that fast, maybe for the first ones, but it&#39;ll get slower. I&#39;ll also note that in v2 prayers will be a must, unless you want to get fucked to hell and back (you&#39;ll just see a quick prayer switching in the video, as well).


So, here are links to videos.
RapidShare: http://rapidshare.com/files/138340384/fightcaves.wmv.html
YouTube: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=09ms0MH3x10

YouTube one is bad quality, and you won&#39;t be able to see a lot, so I recommend you download the rapidshare one, instead.


Lastly, the server base is rs2e.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 23:05:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fight-caves-v1/226808.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fight Caves. (v1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zhaedara Zhaedara]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zhaedara">@Zhaedara</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow nice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fight-caves-v1/226808/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fight-caves-v1/226808/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 23:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-226808-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fight-caves-v1/226808.rss">Fight Caves. (v1)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fight Caves. (v1)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hidendra Hidendra]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hidendra">@hidendra</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well I decided to make fight caves for something to do. It has <span class="bbcode-b">all 63 waves</span>. It uses <span class="bbcode-b">no cases</span>, so it uses <span class="bbcode-b">one newNPC</span> line for spawning most wave NPC’s (exception to level-22 Tz-Kek), probably making it more efficient than most others fight caves.<br>
Managing the waves is simple, I can remove <span class="bbcode-b">any</span> NPC or <span class="bbcode-b">add any amount of waves or NPCs to existing waves</span> I would want, without modifying any of the core code. I could even create any amount of new waves.</p>
<p>So far it is working perfectly, with a few bugs that I haven’t fixed yet. In version two the proper NPC’s will mage and range. So Tok-Xil will range, jad mage/range randomly, 360 will mage, etc. In the end of the video the Xil died really fast, in reality it won’t, this is just a first version. And in reality, in the next version waves won’t go that fast, maybe for the first ones, but it’ll get slower. I’ll also note that in v2 prayers will be a must, unless you want to get fucked to hell and back (you’ll just see a quick prayer switching in the video, as well).</p>
<p>So, here are links to videos.<br>
RapidShare: <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/138340384/fightcaves.wmv.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/138340384/fightcaves.wmv.html</a><br>
YouTube: <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=09ms0MH3x10" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=09ms0MH3x10</a></p>
<p>YouTube one is bad quality, and you won’t be able to see a lot, so I recommend you download the rapidshare one, instead.</p>
<p>Lastly, the server base is rs2e.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fight-caves-v1/226808/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fight-caves-v1/226808/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 22:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-226808-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fight-caves-v1/226808.rss">Fight Caves. (v1)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
