<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Running A Better Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071</link>
    <description>If you would like any further advice added to this topic, simply leave a comment and I will add it as soon as possible.

[size=14pt]Your Advertisements[/size]


[ul]     [li]The biggest flaw I see with today&#39;s advertisements is the lack of effort put into them. You want to attract players by creating a visually appealing advertisement. What are your players going to think of a owner who couldn&#39;t even take the time to create a decent advertisement?

    [/li][li]When writing your advertisements make sure your grammar is on point. You want to appear intelligent so your players will have faith that you can manage a good community.

     [/li][li]Your feature list should contain UNIQUE features. Why would some-one want to play your server when there are 50 others exactly like it with the exact same features listed?

     [/li][li]Posting media alongside your advertisement is a must. It allows people to see the creative things you&#39;ve incorporated into your server. But just like above, your media should contain UNIQUE features. It seems that now a-days every server owner wants to post pictures of GodWars, 614 Item Specials, or mini-games that all servers have. DON&#39;T DO THIS! Instead why not take a picture of something that you can truly call your own feature? Even if it&#39;s something small like a group of monsters somewhere or custom NPC Dialogue.[/li][/ul]


[size=14pt]Your In-Game Behavior[/size]

[ul]     [li]You may think since it&#39;s your server you can act however you want without any consequences. This is a terrible mistake and your player base will reflect it. When speaking in-game try to always speak with fair grammar for the same purposes as explained in the above topic, although in-game you could be a little more lenient.

     [/li][li]When approached by a player (Old or New) and asked a question it is very important to be responsive and enthusiastic to help them, instead of just telling them where something is, why not take them there? Small things like this will show your players that you care enough to take ten seconds out of your day and assist them fully. This should be second nature to you and your staff members.

     [/li][li]No matter how much content is in your server you need to accept the fact that players will get bored. You need to keep the updates coming. This doesn&#39;t have to happen everyday but it should happen at least once a week. This shows your players you care about the community and want them to enjoy the time they spend on your server.

[/li][/ul]

[size=14pt]Your Staff Members[/size]

[ul]     [li]Every player wants to earn a staff roll, but only a select few are appropriate for the job. Understand that if one single staff member goes crazy and starts banning players that your server will take a hard hit and so will your credibility.

     [/li][li]Your players will compete for staff positions and become disappointed if they don&#39;t receive them. I have personally had the best success with just randomly awarding players who I know want the position a rank. Applications on the forums can be good and bad and in the long run it&#39;s your choice to make.

[/li][/ul]

[size=14pt]Your Content[/size]

[ul]     [li]Some players enjoy a challenge, some just want everything handed to them. I recommend focusing on the players who actually want a challenge as they will most likely be the ones to stick around.

     [/li][li]When choosing an experience rate its important to keep it very balanced. 2 - 3 days for a 99 skill on a private server would be my primary choice as it allows players to stay entertained with numerous skills but also doesn&#39;t drive them away because of the RuneScape style experience.

     [/li][li]Your economy should always be your biggest concern. Keep it balanced! If you drop 2147 million blue party hats and one player gets them, this item is no longer rare and is now all but removed from the economy. Keep this in mind when choosing your NPC Drops also.

     [/li][li]Introducing rares into the economy can be tricky, its important that you slowly introduce them over time to keep them RARE. Holiday events or just Server wide events have always been my first choice.

     [/li][li]When designing your shops you need to remember to provide only the essentials to get started. If everything is in a shop, or a reward from a minigame, then you will have no economy and your players will start to grow tired of having everything handed to them.

     [/li][li]Your starter should also only be the bare minimum, if you spawn with 500 Dragon Scimitars your not going to need to work for anything and once again, your players will get bored.

[/li][/ul]

[size=14pt]Donations[/size]

[ul]     [li]Donations can make or break a server, but in most cases - break. If you allow players to buy in-game items for real money your economy will suffer, your average players will find it unfair, and no-one will be interested in actually playing the game when they can buy their way through it.

[/li]

[li] If your accepting donations, its important to not give the donator any in-game advantage. Small things such as: A Yell title (If your server has global shouts), A symbol next to their name, or maybe a non-tradeable hat. This will ensure no unfair advantages and still motivate players to work hard.[/li][/ul]


[size=14pt]Your Website and Miscellaneous Advice[/size]


[ul][li] There are three important things to incorporate when building your website, a forum, a web based client, and a downloadable client. The web client will be used more than the downloadable client and players really seem to like them. On the other hand, some players prefer to play from their desktop so be sure to provide a downloadable client as well. And finally the forum will be your center of attention where players can post guides, receive help, or trade items under the supervision of a ranked member.

[/li][li]Buying a domain - This will make your server look professional and increase the speed of your website tremendously compared to the free websites you where probably using before.

[/li][li]Combat can also be another threshold to pass, be sure to extensively test your formulas to prevent any overpowered weapons which could hold an unfair advantage.

[/li][li]Unless you have taken a fair amount of times to go through and fix all your dupes (Most responsible server owners have) you will face item duplicators. This is one of the biggest but easiest to avoid problems faced by servers. In the long run, just fix the possible item duplication&#39;s before hosting the server.

[/li][li]Of course, to manage a server you will need knowledge of Java. It&#39;s important to take the time to learn the language instead of putting it off or hiring a programmer. It will pay off when you have the ability to keep your players happy and faithful.

[/li][/ul]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 22:39:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Running A Better Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Si Force, post:6, topic:525071”][quote author=asshole_rule link=topic=643764.msg4332933#msg4332933 date=1373921561]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Constant new content updates is also pretty important, apparently.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>All of them are pretty important, imo. I just commented on ones that stood out to me. Lol.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I know, I wasn’t referring to your post when I mentioned that. Just a past experience. :P[/quote]</p>
<p>Oh, right, sorry <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 22:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-525071-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071.rss">Running A Better Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Running A Better Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:5, topic:525071”][quote author=Si Force link=topic=643764.msg4332924#msg4332924 date=1373920375]<br>
Constant new content updates is also pretty important, apparently.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>All of them are pretty important, imo. I just commented on ones that stood out to me. Lol.[/quote]</p>
<p>I know, I wasn’t referring to your post when I mentioned that. Just a past experience. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 21:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-525071-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071.rss">Running A Better Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Running A Better Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="525071">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Si Force:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Constant new content updates is also pretty important, apparently.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>All of them are pretty important, imo. I just commented on ones that stood out to me. Lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 20:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-525071-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071.rss">Running A Better Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Running A Better Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@iz3_legend iz3 legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/iz3_legend">@iz3_legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:2, topic:525071”]I wish there was a clear cut board for stuff like this, as I don’t think it really belongs in the Server Tutorials, but I guess it’s alright for the time being. Anyway I like this thread, it’s pretty informative (maybe an informative threads board…)</p>
<p>I do think staff applications are a good thing though, just have it to where players cannot respond to anyone’s but there own. I like to see who actually wants to be a staff member, because not everyone does, and you don’t want to promote someone who doesn’t really want to be in that position. Plus it gives you a little more insight into the player, how they might handle different situations, and how badly they really want it.</p>
<p>I also cannot stress enough how bad giving tradable items to donators is. Might aswell kiss your economy, and player base goodbye.[/quote]</p>
<p>I’m aware of the dangers or providing trade-able items to donators, which is why I protested against it. As for the staff applications I like the idea of not being able to respond to other user’s threads. Ill adjust the topic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 20:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-525071-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071.rss">Running A Better Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Running A Better Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Constant new content updates is also pretty important, apparently.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 20:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-525071-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071.rss">Running A Better Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Running A Better Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wish there was a clear cut board for stuff like this, as I don’t think it really belongs in the Server Tutorials, but I guess it’s alright for the time being. Anyway I like this thread, it’s pretty informative (maybe an informative threads board…)</p>
<p>I do think staff applications are a good thing though, just have it to where players cannot respond to anyone’s but there own. I like to see who actually wants to be a staff member, because not everyone does, and you don’t want to promote someone who doesn’t really want to be in that position. Plus it gives you a little more insight into the player, how they might handle different situations, and how badly they really want it.</p>
<p>I also cannot stress enough how bad giving tradable items to donators is. Might aswell kiss your economy, and player base goodbye.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 20:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-525071-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071.rss">Running A Better Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Running A Better Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@iz3_legend iz3 legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/iz3_legend">@iz3_legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you would like any further advice added to this topic, simply leave a comment and I will add it as soon as possible.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]Your Advertisements[/size]</p>
<p>[ul]     [li]The biggest flaw I see with today’s advertisements is the lack of effort put into them. You want to attract players by creating a visually appealing advertisement. What are your players going to think of a owner who couldn’t even take the time to create a decent advertisement?</p>
<pre><code>[/li][li]When writing your advertisements make sure your grammar is on point. You want to appear intelligent so your players will have faith that you can manage a good community.

 [/li][li]Your feature list should contain UNIQUE features. Why would some-one want to play your server when there are 50 others exactly like it with the exact same features listed?

 [/li][li]Posting media alongside your advertisement is a must. It allows people to see the creative things you've incorporated into your server. But just like above, your media should contain UNIQUE features. It seems that now a-days every server owner wants to post pictures of GodWars, 614 Item Specials, or mini-games that all servers have. DON'T DO THIS! Instead why not take a picture of something that you can truly call your own feature? Even if it's something small like a group of monsters somewhere or custom NPC Dialogue.[/li][/ul]
</code></pre>
<p>[size=14pt]Your In-Game Behavior[/size]</p>
<p>[ul]     [li]You may think since it’s your server you can act however you want without any consequences. This is a terrible mistake and your player base will reflect it. When speaking in-game try to always speak with fair grammar for the same purposes as explained in the above topic, although in-game you could be a little more lenient.</p>
<pre><code> [/li][li]When approached by a player (Old or New) and asked a question it is very important to be responsive and enthusiastic to help them, instead of just telling them where something is, why not take them there? Small things like this will show your players that you care enough to take ten seconds out of your day and assist them fully. This should be second nature to you and your staff members.

 [/li][li]No matter how much content is in your server you need to accept the fact that players will get bored. You need to keep the updates coming. This doesn't have to happen everyday but it should happen at least once a week. This shows your players you care about the community and want them to enjoy the time they spend on your server.
</code></pre>
<p>[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]Your Staff Members[/size]</p>
<p>[ul]     [li]Every player wants to earn a staff roll, but only a select few are appropriate for the job. Understand that if one single staff member goes crazy and starts banning players that your server will take a hard hit and so will your credibility.</p>
<pre><code> [/li][li]Your players will compete for staff positions and become disappointed if they don't receive them. I have personally had the best success with just randomly awarding players who I know want the position a rank. Applications on the forums can be good and bad and in the long run it's your choice to make.
</code></pre>
<p>[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]Your Content[/size]</p>
<p>[ul]     [li]Some players enjoy a challenge, some just want everything handed to them. I recommend focusing on the players who actually want a challenge as they will most likely be the ones to stick around.</p>
<pre><code> [/li][li]When choosing an experience rate its important to keep it very balanced. 2 - 3 days for a 99 skill on a private server would be my primary choice as it allows players to stay entertained with numerous skills but also doesn't drive them away because of the RuneScape style experience.

 [/li][li]Your economy should always be your biggest concern. Keep it balanced! If you drop 2147 million blue party hats and one player gets them, this item is no longer rare and is now all but removed from the economy. Keep this in mind when choosing your NPC Drops also.

 [/li][li]Introducing rares into the economy can be tricky, its important that you slowly introduce them over time to keep them RARE. Holiday events or just Server wide events have always been my first choice.

 [/li][li]When designing your shops you need to remember to provide only the essentials to get started. If everything is in a shop, or a reward from a minigame, then you will have no economy and your players will start to grow tired of having everything handed to them.

 [/li][li]Your starter should also only be the bare minimum, if you spawn with 500 Dragon Scimitars your not going to need to work for anything and once again, your players will get bored.
</code></pre>
<p>[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]Donations[/size]</p>
<p>[ul]     [li]Donations can make or break a server, but in most cases - break. If you allow players to buy in-game items for real money your economy will suffer, your average players will find it unfair, and no-one will be interested in actually playing the game when they can buy their way through it.</p>
<p>[/li]</p>
<p>[li] If your accepting donations, its important to not give the donator any in-game advantage. Small things such as: A Yell title (If your server has global shouts), A symbol next to their name, or maybe a non-tradeable hat. This will ensure no unfair advantages and still motivate players to work hard.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[size=14pt]Your Website and Miscellaneous Advice[/size]</p>
<p>[ul][li] There are three important things to incorporate when building your website, a forum, a web based client, and a downloadable client. The web client will be used more than the downloadable client and players really seem to like them. On the other hand, some players prefer to play from their desktop so be sure to provide a downloadable client as well. And finally the forum will be your center of attention where players can post guides, receive help, or trade items under the supervision of a ranked member.</p>
<p>[/li][li]Buying a domain - This will make your server look professional and increase the speed of your website tremendously compared to the free websites you where probably using before.</p>
<p>[/li][li]Combat can also be another threshold to pass, be sure to extensively test your formulas to prevent any overpowered weapons which could hold an unfair advantage.</p>
<p>[/li][li]Unless you have taken a fair amount of times to go through and fix all your dupes (Most responsible server owners have) you will face item duplicators. This is one of the biggest but easiest to avoid problems faced by servers. In the long run, just fix the possible item duplication’s before hosting the server.</p>
<p>[/li][li]Of course, to manage a server you will need knowledge of Java. It’s important to take the time to learn the language instead of putting it off or hiring a programmer. It will pay off when you have the ability to keep your players happy and faithful.</p>
<p>[/li][/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 19:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-525071-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/running-a-better-server/525071.rss">Running A Better Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
