<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>MoparScrape Pro Graphix Artits Tutor Ya All</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391</link>
    <description>How Two Became Good Graphics Artits

Well It Was Only A Phew Months Ago When I Writing Mine Very First Graphics Tutorials. However, It Was Recently Deleting By A Few Mods Due To His Extreme Disrespects. I Hates This. My First Tutorial Gone. Hideous. Horrifying. Atrocious. Stupids Condescending Moderapers. In Light Off That, I Will Make Another Graphics Tutorial For Everybody. No More Bad Pictures Or Deleted Threads, Just Good Tuts.

Since I Am A Professional Graphics Artits I Will Give You Professional Tips That Only Professionals Know How To Using. There Tips Will Help You Mostest.

Firstly, Make Sure You Have Good Equipment. Do Not Use Photoshop. Has You Seen That Every Bad Graphics Artist Maker Uses Photoshop? You Got Too Be Unique. Don&#39;t Use Microsoft Paint Either. They Are Bad And Instead, Use Eclipse Or Visual Studio To Make Pictures. It Is Simply The Best And I Cannot State This Morest.

Secondly, Your Have Too Practice. Practice Makes Perfect. If You Want Two Be Perfect, You Must Practice A Lot. Serious. Do It A Lots. I Mean, Practice Drawing Even In The Toilets. If You Truly Are Dedicated To Making Graphics Then You Will Have To Do It All The Time. Otherwise Noobs From Everywhere Will Become Better Then You. Your Don&#39;t Want That, Right? Ok. I&#39;m Glad You Can Agree With Me.

Thirdly, Make Insurance That You&#39;re Final Result Uses Maximum Stylistic Distortion And Practical Technique. Abusing Stuff Like Liquify. Use Every Effect Possible So That The End Result Looks Nothing Like The Original. That Way You Can Truly Impress Everybody. If It Is Hard To See Or Look At The Picture, Then It Will Be Loved By Everyone.

If You&#39;re Trainer Too Be As Good As I (Perfect), You&#39;re Pics Will Look Professionals Like This:

[img width=333 height=250]http://i.imgur.com/cm51oL0.png[/img]

Do Not Leech Or I Will Report You For Leeching. I Should Of Put An Watermark For Anti-Leech But Since I&#39;m Nice I Will Not Doing That This Tim. But Do Knot Taker Advantages Off I Or Me Will Madder.

Thanks For The Support Guise. This Is Only Mine Second Tutorial. Bee Sure Two Rep++ Me And Vote Me For Graphics Artits Cup Because I Deserve It. :)

Mods: If This Post Are Wrong Sectioning Please Moving It. Thanks! :)

Edit: We Got Approval From The Triangle Man! Woot!

&lt;blockquote&gt;[10:30:06] &lt;&amp;_^_&gt;	 i am _^_ and i endorse whackatree&#39;s tutorial&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 03:26:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>MoparScrape Pro Graphix Artits Tutor Ya All</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks for the troll thread…?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 03:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532391-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391.rss">MoparScrape Pro Graphix Artits Tutor Ya All</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MoparScrape Pro Graphix Artits Tutor Ya All</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wow, his tutorial literally changed my life. Before I read this, I was using Photoshop for all my GFX projects. Oh, how silly I was. Part of me felt like a cheap imitation. I knew deep down that Visual Studio was the way to go, yet I couldn’t overcome my lack of dedication. I hit the alcohol hard, trying to drink away the pain. Liquify effects were my bottle, MS paint was my liquor. This tutorial sobered me up.</p>
<p>I really have to compliment your ability. At first glance, I saw your artistic take on the sun as being a photograph. I lost sense of reality, time and my need to pee. I really hope that one day I can reach the level that you’re at. You’re an inspiration and comparable to Jesus. I’d also like to show my appreciation for the charitable decision to not watermark your tiny piece of art.<br>
I’ll give credit when I use it as my loading screen for TreeScape Void Edition v5.69.</p>
<p>Once again, thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 02:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532391-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391.rss">MoparScrape Pro Graphix Artits Tutor Ya All</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MoparScrape Pro Graphix Artits Tutor Ya All</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>good job wit hthis tutorial</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 02:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532391-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391.rss">MoparScrape Pro Graphix Artits Tutor Ya All</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MoparScrape Pro Graphix Artits Tutor Ya All</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>How Two Became Good Graphics Artits</p>
<p>Well It Was Only A Phew Months Ago When I Writing Mine Very First Graphics Tutorials. However, It Was Recently Deleting By A Few Mods Due To His Extreme Disrespects. I Hates This. My First Tutorial Gone. Hideous. Horrifying. Atrocious. Stupids Condescending Moderapers. In Light Off That, I Will Make Another Graphics Tutorial For Everybody. No More Bad Pictures Or Deleted Threads, Just Good Tuts.</p>
<p>Since I Am A Professional Graphics Artits I Will Give You Professional Tips That Only Professionals Know How To Using. There Tips Will Help You Mostest.</p>
<p>Firstly, Make Sure You Have Good Equipment. Do Not Use Photoshop. Has You Seen That Every Bad Graphics Artist Maker Uses Photoshop? You Got Too Be Unique. Don’t Use Microsoft Paint Either. They Are Bad And Instead, Use Eclipse Or Visual Studio To Make Pictures. It Is Simply The Best And I Cannot State This Morest.</p>
<p>Secondly, Your Have Too Practice. Practice Makes Perfect. If You Want Two Be Perfect, You Must Practice A Lot. Serious. Do It A Lots. I Mean, Practice Drawing Even In The Toilets. If You Truly Are Dedicated To Making Graphics Then You Will Have To Do It All The Time. Otherwise Noobs From Everywhere Will Become Better Then You. Your Don’t Want That, Right? Ok. I’m Glad You Can Agree With Me.</p>
<p>Thirdly, Make Insurance That You’re Final Result Uses Maximum Stylistic Distortion And Practical Technique. Abusing Stuff Like Liquify. Use Every Effect Possible So That The End Result Looks Nothing Like The Original. That Way You Can Truly Impress Everybody. If It Is Hard To See Or Look At The Picture, Then It Will Be Loved By Everyone.</p>
<p>If You’re Trainer Too Be As Good As I (Perfect), You’re Pics Will Look Professionals Like This:</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/cm51oL0.png" alt width="640" height="480"></p>
<p>Do Not Leech Or I Will Report You For Leeching. I Should Of Put An Watermark For Anti-Leech But Since I’m Nice I Will Not Doing That This Tim. But Do Knot Taker Advantages Off I Or Me Will Madder.</p>
<p>Thanks For The Support Guise. This Is Only Mine Second Tutorial. Bee Sure Two Rep++ Me And Vote Me For Graphics Artits Cup Because I Deserve It. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Mods: If This Post Are Wrong Sectioning Please Moving It. Thanks! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Edit: We Got Approval From The Triangle Man! Woot!</p>
<blockquote>[10:30:06] &lt;&amp;_^_&gt;	 i am _^_ and i endorse whackatree's tutorial</blockquote>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 01:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-532391-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/moparscrape-pro-graphix-artits-tutor-ya-all/532391.rss">MoparScrape Pro Graphix Artits Tutor Ya All</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
