<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please help me!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/263467</link>
    <description>okay i&#39;ve made me my own server and it&#39;s online. but i would to have more people on their. So that my server will be useful for other people. but i&#39;ve been trying to change the Owner&#39;s Name that&#39;s already on the server... but i want to change that to my name so that the people who logs on will know who the owner is.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
I&#39;ve been trying to find a server source that i can download and use that has a higher level than just 126 and 127. I want to find a server that the max level is like (level-222) so people will really work for that level. If there&#39;s anyone that can help me with this I would really appreciate your help. for making my server more better and more interesting to other&#39;s who logs on. If you can post the URL or the person&#39;s name that made the download. =O
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------







                                                                                    By: ImMikeyIrock
                                                                               Posted: For MoparScape&#39;s Help.
                                                                                  Date: Februrary 21st, 2009</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 08:46:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/263467.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please help me!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moh moh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moh">@moh</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Dude if you want to have admin on your server or owner/mod just go to character map and find your name click on it you see playerights = 0 change to 1 for mod 2 for admin 3 for owner 4 for hiddenadmin(so no one can see your owner).<br>
And the server with 126+ combat is not easy to find just use search button at help section ppl asked before how to make 126+ lvl <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> got any question pm me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/263467/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/263467/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 08:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-263467-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/263467.rss">Please help me!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please help me!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ImMikeyIrock ImMikeyIrock]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/immikeyirock">@ImMikeyIrock</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <h2>okay i’ve made me my own server and it’s online. but i would to have more people on their. So that my server will be useful for other people. but i’ve been trying to change the Owner’s Name that’s already on the server… but i want to change that to my name so that the people who logs on will know who the owner is.</h2>
<h2>I’ve been trying to find a server source that i can download and use that has a higher level than just 126 and 127. I want to find a server that the max level is like (level-222) so people will really work for that level. If there’s anyone that can help me with this I would really appreciate your help. for making my server more better and more interesting to other’s who logs on. If you can post the URL or the person’s name that made the download. =O</h2>
<pre><code>                                                                                By: ImMikeyIrock
                                                                           Posted: For MoparScape's Help.
                                                                              Date: Februrary 21st, 2009</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/263467/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/263467/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 06:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-263467-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/263467.rss">Please help me!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
