<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please Help Me</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/36712</link>
    <description>Please help me i need to know how to make  bitmaps and how there used and what there even for please tell me i realy woudl like to know</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2006 13:23:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/36712.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please Help Me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@scarscaper4life scarscaper4life]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scarscaper4life">@scarscaper4life</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><em>sigh</em> i got this out of tutorial x a very good scar tutorial</p>
<p>Bitmaps? Aren’t Those Pictures?</p>
<p>Yes, they are pictures! But they have been given a better use than floating around on your desktop. SCAR can look for a bitmap the same way you would use SCAR to look for a color, since bitmaps are just a bunch of colors anyway. This lets you look for certain pictures, even text.</p>
<p>How Do I Use Bitmaps?</p>
<p>Using bitmaps is pretty easy to learn how to do. First thing’s first. Go into paint, and paint yourself a little picture (about 10px x 10px will do). Save it somewhere where you won’t lose it. Now go into SCAR, go to script, and go to Picture to String. From that menu, go to open. Open the bitmap you just made. You should see the bitmap in that box in the menu that cam up. Make sure it is selected (it will have a flashing dotted recatangle around it). If it’s not selected, drag from one corner of the picture to the other. You can start dragging from the gray space around the picture (in fact, I suggest it). Then, hit Ok. Copy the code from the debug box in SCAR and paste it after the begin in the script. Then, declare the title of the bitmap as an integer at the top of the script. There are quite a few functions that you can use to find a bitmap. To introduce you to this topic, I’ll show you the most simple one. After the code that you copied from the debug box, hit enter and type in:</p>
<p>FindBitmap(name of your bitmap,x,y);<br>
MoveMouse(x,y);</p>
<p>Replace “name of your bitmap” with the name of your bitmap. You will also need to declare x and y as integers at this point. Now go into paint and open up the bitmap you used. Choose the paint window as your client using the crosshairs. Run the script and your mouse should move to the bitmap. Now, if you want to move the mouse to somewhere other than the top left-hand corner of the bitmap, you can do things like:</p>
<p>MoveMouse(x+5,y+5);<br>
{or}<br>
MoveMouse(x+random(10),y+random(20));</p>
<p>There are also functions that let you search for the bitmap in a certain area, which work like FindColor, and even functions that look for deformed bitmaps. For a nice description on those, you can go into SCAR and hit F1, followed by hitting ctrl + f and searching for the names of the functions <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>The one thing you should always remember about bitmaps is that SCAR ignores anything that is black. Any pixel that is black, SCAR will ignore in a bitmap. Therefore, when you’re making a bitmap, you should remember not to take pictures of black things, and you should almost always make the background of a bitmap black, while keeping the object you’re looking for the only thing in color. Also, try to keep bitmaps as small as possible. The bigger the bitmap is, the longer it will take for SCAR to find, and the less of a chance SCAR has of finding it.</p>
<p>How Do I Know What to Use as a Bitmap?</p>
<p>A lot of times after I’ve taught someone how to use bitmaps, they ask what they should use as the bitmap. Your very best shot would be something that doesn’t rotate or change at all. Sometimes rotations distort the bitmap in a weird way and you end up doing more work to find it. If there isn’t anything like that, then choose something that stands out a bit from the rest of the things near it. Like, if you’re going through a large portion of woods in RuneScape, I wouldn’t suggest looking for trees on the minimap, but rather an oddly large portion of clear land on the minimap. A nice rule to think about if you think the object may rotate is that taking a picture of it in a more natural position will help your script find it. Say you’re taking a picture of something on the RuneScape minimap, and you know it could (or rather, will) rotate. I would take the picture while the compass is facing directly north.</p>
<p>Un-Named edit: Removed quotes, looked bad.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/36712/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/36712/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2006 13:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-36712-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/36712.rss">Please Help Me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Please Help Me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@emodude emodude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/emodude">@emodude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Please help me i need to know how to make  bitmaps and how there used and what there even for please tell me i realy woudl like to know</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/36712/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/36712/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2006 12:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-36712-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-help-me/36712.rss">Please Help Me</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
