<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Client wont connect to server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-wont-connect-to-server/359991</link>
    <description>Alright so here&#39;s the problem, i cannot get my client to connect to my server.

I have tried hosting on [u]no-ip[/u]. Didn&#39;t work.
I have tried using [u]hamachi[/u]. Didn&#39;t work.

I have edited my server and client as needed to properly connect to each other, both locally and remotely. It does work when i connect [u]locally[/u] in my own network using a [b]router[/b] ([i]not hamachi[/i]), but no way will it connect if i use hamachi ip address or a no-ip address. And i think i may have came to a conclusion to my problem. 

I have a router with [u]NAT[/u], and assigned both the client &amp; server to use both port 43594. I have setup port forwarding on my Linksys router to forward port 43594 ([i]TCP/UDP[/i]) to 192.168.10.5 ([i]server[/i]). I have read online that only 1 computer can use a given port on a network at a time ([i]e.g 43594[/i]). So if i have my server activated and using port 43594, and try to run a client to connect to the server on a different computer (in the same router network), [b]that will not work[/b]? But if i would try to connect to the server at a different location using the client, [b]it should work[/b]?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 22:55:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-wont-connect-to-server/359991.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Client wont connect to server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@desion desion]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/desion">@desion</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright so here’s the problem, i cannot get my client to connect to my server.</p>
<p>I have tried hosting on <span class="bbcode-u">no-ip</span>. Didn’t work.<br>
I have tried using <span class="bbcode-u">hamachi</span>. Didn’t work.</p>
<p>I have edited my server and client as needed to properly connect to each other, both locally and remotely. It does work when i connect <span class="bbcode-u">locally</span> in my own network using a <span class="bbcode-b">router</span> (<span class="bbcode-i">not hamachi</span>), but no way will it connect if i use hamachi ip address or a no-ip address. And i think i may have came to a conclusion to my problem.</p>
<p>I have a router with <span class="bbcode-u">NAT</span>, and assigned both the client &amp; server to use both port 43594. I have setup port forwarding on my Linksys router to forward port 43594 (<span class="bbcode-i">TCP/UDP</span>) to 192.168.10.5 (<span class="bbcode-i">server</span>). I have read online that only 1 computer can use a given port on a network at a time (<span class="bbcode-i">e.g 43594</span>). So if i have my server activated and using port 43594, and try to run a client to connect to the server on a different computer (in the same router network), <span class="bbcode-b">that will not work</span>? But if i would try to connect to the server at a different location using the client, <span class="bbcode-b">it should work</span>?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-wont-connect-to-server/359991/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-wont-connect-to-server/359991/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 22:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-359991-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/client-wont-connect-to-server/359991.rss">Client wont connect to server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
