<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572</link>
    <description>Ok well I dont know if I spelled WYSIWYG correctly, but anyways here were go.

Note: Before we start I want to note that working with WYSIWYG editors is a very bad way to create a profesional website. If you want a really good looking website, try dreamweaver. This is mostly for fun websites. But with enough work and practice, you can make a preety snazzy looking WYSIWYG website :P.

First off get a good WYSIWYG editor (lol oxi-moron)
Here is a good one: [url=http://www.webpage-maker.com/]http://www.webpage-maker.com/[/url]

Next, I would get a key for it, but I am not going to supply, so dont ask -.-

Ok now that your got the program make sure you have your photshop ready. Now in photshop make a number of different pictures starting with a background. Next make a header/banner. Now make a box, with the color you would like for your text to be in. Now that you are done with that save them all to JPG format, unless your banner has transperant areas, if so then save as a PNG picture format.

Ok well now open up your WYSIWYG (I love this fucking word!) and double click the big white area. Now you will see something that says bckground picture. Check the box enableing it, if you havnt already, and browse for you background picture and add it. Another option is the background color, but thats oldschool dude..
Now will want to become familiarized with the toolbar. Here is how it works:

[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m187/xspikeyhairx/bar.jpg[/img]

1. Make a new website
2.Open project
3.Save current project
4. Undo
5. Redo
6. Add Text
7.Add Image
8. Add a Navigation Bar
9. Add Shape
10. Set Background color
11. Create Hyperlink
12. Preview in Browser
13. Publish

[hr]

Well out of those 13 buttons these are the ones you will be using:

3.
6.
7.
8.(one time only)
9.
11. (seldom)
12.
[hr]

Ok well now to get started, add an image. Browse for you header. 

OH WAIT! Before we go on go into Edit&gt;Show Guide Border
This will be important as it shows you a little guide box that is useful at times.

Now find your header and drag to the top middle. Try and get it as close to the center as possible. 
After you got it, preview it in the browser. Now look and see if it is correctly centered. It most likely is not. Now repeat this process until you get it in the center: Move to center you see fit, and preview in browser.

Now thats the banner.. Next upload your text box image. Now stretch this image to the size you see fit. Remember not to big as this is only for the center. Now make sure your background is still visible on the sides for about 2 inches each. (estimate) Now that you got that right click the image and go to properties. Now on the tabs, find the &quot;colors and borders&quot; tab. Now find the area that says &quot;borders.&quot; Click the drop down and click which one you want. I am going to pick Solid. Now on the colors, pick the color you want. Remember a good website does not have all the basic colors. They have custom colors that they fool around with. So fool around with them by going to &quot;more colors&quot; on the color chooser. Now make the border the desired size in pixels. I usualy do 1-2. Too big is ugle, remember that. Now your done with the text box

[IMG]http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m187/xspikeyhairx/properties.jpg[/img]



Ok now for the next part. Make a navigation bar. Now when you press this, a button will pop up. There will be many different choices to choise from, so find one that seems to be close to or compliments the colors you already have on your website. Now once you add this it is time for the next part. Note do not add links yet. We will get to this in just a second.

Now Go to Page&gt;Clone Page, and make a considerable amount of copies. Now name all those pages to what you wish them to be. Always leave the index page&#39;s name the same! Ok Now you need to check each on and make sure it made the copy. It will 99.9% of the time make the copy. Sometimes it screws up. It hasn&#39;t happened to me yet though.

Ok now moving along... Now double click the navigation bar on you index page. Now for each link, choose the page you want it to go to, and change the text on the bar. Now you can also change the color of the text, mouseover sound, etc. But I won&#39;t go into that, I&#39;ll let you explore that for youself.

Now wonce your done with that, click the navigation bar so that it is outline in white. Now clickt he buttons together: ctrl+c Now you need to delete the nav bar on each of the other pages. Now what you do it go to back to eahc page and press this: ctrl+v Now you will each time see a new navbar on the page. You may ask, why the hell did he just make me delete the damn nav bars then remake them?... Well because now you don&#39;t have to fill in the navbar options on each one. 

Ok now that you got that go back to photshop. Make yourself another box. Make it a different shade of the same color you made the first box in the beginning of this guide. Now save those and go back to your WYSIWYG.

Ok now add the box you just made. Stretch to fit inside the other box you stretched earlier. Remember to leave some space on the sides, as this makes it easier on the eyes. Ok now go to the properties of that image, the same way you did the first time. Now add the desired border. Make the border like a darker or lighter shade of you background color. Ok now on to the next step.

Ok now what you need to do it add some text inside that box you just added. Ok now press the button that is used for adding text and double click the text. Now inside the box that just popped up, put in the desired text. Now press ok and drag the text to the box you just added. Ok well that is a fairly simple template you just made. If you want, go to File&gt;Save as Template, and now you can use this layout on a number of websites. Ok well its time to upload the website to a hoast.

I use ulimitedmb (ulmb.com), but you can use whichever one fits your needs. You can find a number of hosts by searching google. Ok well log into your account. Now go back to your WYSIWYG and go to File&gt;Export to HTML

Ok now pick the spot to save your files. I suggest making a new folder for everytime you do this one a site, so that you have a backup of an ealier version. Ok now go to where you saved it via My Doccuments. Now go to that folor and make sure you have WinRar. This can be found by searching google as well. It is not free, so youll get a 30-day trial, but they actualy force to buy it. And it never becomes uninstalled after the trial, so you can continue using it. Ok well right click the file contating your website. Now select the option &quot;Add to Archieve.&quot; Now in the window that popped up, select the .zip format, not the .rar. Ok now go back to your host account, and click the selection of files and folders. Now make sure you have a subdomain, or a domain. Go into the desired websites file, and scroll down a bit. Now where it says upload and browse, click browse. Now find your .zip file contatining your website files. Now click ok. Before uploading the file, check the box saying &quot;Automatically unzip zip files&quot; or seomething to that extent. Ok now upload.

Now go and type in your websites adress in your browser and check it out.


Now using this knowlegde, go and make a real website of your own. Remember, first websites are not always so great, so keep trying until you get the hang of it.


Again I note: WYSIWYG editors are not very good for creating a profesional looking or working website. If you want one like this, then learn HTML, PHP, and CSS.. It is not that difficult. And also use Adobe Dreamweaver. 

Thanks for reading. Hope it helped some people..

Please dont flame my thread if you have a problem with WYSIWYG editors. If you do, thats nice, but I am not going to care about your saying &quot;WYSIWYG editors suck. No use in posting this...&quot; Ok well I think thats everything.


CREDITS:   100% Me (Spikey Hair)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 03:49:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spikey_Hair Spikey Hair]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spikey_hair">@Spikey_Hair</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ThatOneServer, post:12, topic:175572”]XxKanexX i laughed at the image in your sig.</p>
<p>Sorry for being a dick, I just woke up that day.</p>
<p>Seriously though, I dont think we should have any more wysiwyg posts on this forum.[/quote]<br>
Ok, np. It is my frist guide anyway. Just trying to help some people.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 03:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThatOneServer Mike_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thatoneserver">@ThatOneServer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>XxKanexX i laughed at the image in your sig.</p>
<p>Sorry for being a dick, I just woke up that day.</p>
<p>Seriously though, I dont think we should have any more wysiwyg posts on this forum.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 20:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxKanexX Kane.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxkanexx">@XxKanexX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote author=Spikey Hair link=topic=236164.msg2012161#msg2012161 date=1201196302]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="9" data-topic="175572">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/kloplop321/40/181_1.png" class="avatar"> kloplop321:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>At least someone isnt an ass on these forums.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A rare species.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 17:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spikey_Hair Spikey Hair]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spikey_hair">@Spikey_Hair</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“kloplop321, post:9, topic:175572”]helping people learn is accepted <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
not pointing out the obvious, as real web designers don’t use WYSIWYG 99% of the time to get what they want accomplished(unless they are in a hurry for a standard html document) because they know what it “should” look like before they test it :D[/quote]<br>
Yes but that is why a stated that it is not wise to use WYSIWYG editor. I said they should use dreamweaver. But anyways, thanks for you feedback. At least someone isnt an ass on these forums.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kloplop321 kloplop321]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kloplop321">@kloplop321</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>helping people learn is accepted <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
not pointing out the obvious, as real web designers don’t use WYSIWYG 99% of the time to get what they want accomplished(unless they are in a hurry for a standard html document) because they know what it “should” look like before they test it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spikey_Hair Spikey Hair]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spikey_hair">@Spikey_Hair</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ThatOneServer, post:7, topic:175572”][quote author=Spikey Hair link=topic=236164.msg2011737#msg2011737 date=1201161621]<br>
So please, no more useless posts…<br>
[/quote]<br>
Such as this topic?[/quote]</p>
<p>So I guess helping people is useless now?.. Maby you could just be quiet and let the people who actualy want to read this guide, read it instead of flaming it because you find WYSIYWYG bad. So gtfo and go back to moparscape.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThatOneServer Mike_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thatoneserver">@ThatOneServer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="6" data-topic="175572">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Spikey Hair:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So please, no more useless posts…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Such as this topic?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spikey_Hair Spikey Hair]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spikey_hair">@Spikey_Hair</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, well incase none of you can read, I stated in my thread, please do not flame or spam this thread just because you don’t like WYSIWYG. I have no sympathy for you disliking WYSIWYG… And I don’t really care… So please, no more useless posts…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 08:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThatOneServer Mike_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thatoneserver">@ThatOneServer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Calling WYSIWYG art is like calling a picture of a painting art. There is no art.</p>
<p>And if you cannot use a wysiwyg without a tutorial, you need to gtfo.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 07:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kloplop321 kloplop321]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kloplop321">@kloplop321</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I still say there is no art to it as people hardly learn from it except seeing the code after it was made…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 07:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spikey_Hair Spikey Hair]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spikey_hair">@Spikey_Hair</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“kloplop321, post:2, topic:175572”]there is no art to WYSIWYG <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
scripting it is better unless doing stuff like sizing tables[/quote]<br>
Well I would have to disagree, because you must not know what “art” is. It is creativeness… And I do agree that scripting is better… Thats y I stated twice that its better to actualy script in CSS, PHP, or HTML than it is to use a WYSIWYG, editor.</p>
<p>But thanks for the feedback anyways.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 04:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kloplop321 kloplop321]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kloplop321">@kloplop321</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>there is no art to WYSIWYG <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
scripting it is better unless doing stuff like sizing tables</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 04:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Spikey_Hair Spikey Hair]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spikey_hair">@Spikey_Hair</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok well I dont know if I spelled WYSIWYG correctly, but anyways here were go.</p>
<p>Note: Before we start I want to note that working with WYSIWYG editors is a very bad way to create a profesional website. If you want a really good looking website, try dreamweaver. This is mostly for fun websites. But with enough work and practice, you can make a preety snazzy looking WYSIWYG website :P.</p>
<p>First off get a good WYSIWYG editor (lol oxi-moron)<br>
Here is a good one: <a href="http://www.webpage-maker.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.webpage-maker.com/</a></p>
<p>Next, I would get a key for it, but I am not going to supply, so dont ask -.-</p>
<p>Ok now that your got the program make sure you have your photshop ready. Now in photshop make a number of different pictures starting with a background. Next make a header/banner. Now make a box, with the color you would like for your text to be in. Now that you are done with that save them all to JPG format, unless your banner has transperant areas, if so then save as a PNG picture format.</p>
<p>Ok well now open up your WYSIWYG (I love this fucking word!) and double click the big white area. Now you will see something that says bckground picture. Check the box enableing it, if you havnt already, and browse for you background picture and add it. Another option is the background color, but thats oldschool dude…<br>
Now will want to become familiarized with the toolbar. Here is how it works:</p>
<p><img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m187/xspikeyhairx/bar.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<ol>
<li>Make a new website<br>
2.Open project<br>
3.Save current project</li>
<li>Undo</li>
<li>Redo</li>
<li>Add Text<br>
7.Add Image</li>
<li>Add a Navigation Bar</li>
<li>Add Shape</li>
<li>Set Background color</li>
<li>Create Hyperlink</li>
<li>Preview in Browser</li>
<li>Publish</li>
</ol>
<p>[hr]</p>
<p>Well out of those 13 buttons these are the ones you will be using:</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>8.(one time only)<br>
9.<br>
11. (seldom)<br>
12.<br>
[hr]</p>
<p>Ok well now to get started, add an image. Browse for you header.</p>
<p>OH WAIT! Before we go on go into Edit&gt;Show Guide Border<br>
This will be important as it shows you a little guide box that is useful at times.</p>
<p>Now find your header and drag to the top middle. Try and get it as close to the center as possible.<br>
After you got it, preview it in the browser. Now look and see if it is correctly centered. It most likely is not. Now repeat this process until you get it in the center: Move to center you see fit, and preview in browser.</p>
<p>Now thats the banner… Next upload your text box image. Now stretch this image to the size you see fit. Remember not to big as this is only for the center. Now make sure your background is still visible on the sides for about 2 inches each. (estimate) Now that you got that right click the image and go to properties. Now on the tabs, find the “colors and borders” tab. Now find the area that says “borders.” Click the drop down and click which one you want. I am going to pick Solid. Now on the colors, pick the color you want. Remember a good website does not have all the basic colors. They have custom colors that they fool around with. So fool around with them by going to “more colors” on the color chooser. Now make the border the desired size in pixels. I usualy do 1-2. Too big is ugle, remember that. Now your done with the text box</p>
<p><img src="http://i104.photobucket.com/albums/m187/xspikeyhairx/properties.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Ok now for the next part. Make a navigation bar. Now when you press this, a button will pop up. There will be many different choices to choise from, so find one that seems to be close to or compliments the colors you already have on your website. Now once you add this it is time for the next part. Note do not add links yet. We will get to this in just a second.</p>
<p>Now Go to Page&gt;Clone Page, and make a considerable amount of copies. Now name all those pages to what you wish them to be. Always leave the index page’s name the same! Ok Now you need to check each on and make sure it made the copy. It will 99.9% of the time make the copy. Sometimes it screws up. It hasn’t happened to me yet though.</p>
<p>Ok now moving along… Now double click the navigation bar on you index page. Now for each link, choose the page you want it to go to, and change the text on the bar. Now you can also change the color of the text, mouseover sound, etc. But I won’t go into that, I’ll let you explore that for youself.</p>
<p>Now wonce your done with that, click the navigation bar so that it is outline in white. Now clickt he buttons together: ctrl+c Now you need to delete the nav bar on each of the other pages. Now what you do it go to back to eahc page and press this: ctrl+v Now you will each time see a new navbar on the page. You may ask, why the hell did he just make me delete the damn nav bars then remake them?.. Well because now you don’t have to fill in the navbar options on each one.</p>
<p>Ok now that you got that go back to photshop. Make yourself another box. Make it a different shade of the same color you made the first box in the beginning of this guide. Now save those and go back to your WYSIWYG.</p>
<p>Ok now add the box you just made. Stretch to fit inside the other box you stretched earlier. Remember to leave some space on the sides, as this makes it easier on the eyes. Ok now go to the properties of that image, the same way you did the first time. Now add the desired border. Make the border like a darker or lighter shade of you background color. Ok now on to the next step.</p>
<p>Ok now what you need to do it add some text inside that box you just added. Ok now press the button that is used for adding text and double click the text. Now inside the box that just popped up, put in the desired text. Now press ok and drag the text to the box you just added. Ok well that is a fairly simple template you just made. If you want, go to File&gt;Save as Template, and now you can use this layout on a number of websites. Ok well its time to upload the website to a hoast.</p>
<p>I use ulimitedmb (<a href="http://ulmb.com" rel="nofollow noopener">ulmb.com</a>), but you can use whichever one fits your needs. You can find a number of hosts by searching google. Ok well log into your account. Now go back to your WYSIWYG and go to File&gt;Export to HTML</p>
<p>Ok now pick the spot to save your files. I suggest making a new folder for everytime you do this one a site, so that you have a backup of an ealier version. Ok now go to where you saved it via My Doccuments. Now go to that folor and make sure you have WinRar. This can be found by searching google as well. It is not free, so youll get a 30-day trial, but they actualy force to buy it. And it never becomes uninstalled after the trial, so you can continue using it. Ok well right click the file contating your website. Now select the option “Add to Archieve.” Now in the window that popped up, select the .zip format, not the .rar. Ok now go back to your host account, and click the selection of files and folders. Now make sure you have a subdomain, or a domain. Go into the desired websites file, and scroll down a bit. Now where it says upload and browse, click browse. Now find your .zip file contatining your website files. Now click ok. Before uploading the file, check the box saying “Automatically unzip zip files” or seomething to that extent. Ok now upload.</p>
<p>Now go and type in your websites adress in your browser and check it out.</p>
<p>Now using this knowlegde, go and make a real website of your own. Remember, first websites are not always so great, so keep trying until you get the hang of it.</p>
<p>Again I note: WYSIWYG editors are not very good for creating a profesional looking or working website. If you want one like this, then learn HTML, PHP, and CSS… It is not that difficult. And also use Adobe Dreamweaver.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading. Hope it helped some people…</p>
<p>Please dont flame my thread if you have a problem with WYSIWYG editors. If you do, thats nice, but I am not going to care about your saying “WYSIWYG editors suck. No use in posting this…” Ok well I think thats everything.</p>
<p>CREDITS:   100% Me (Spikey Hair)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 03:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-175572-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-art-of-wysiwyg-with-pics-p-noob-friendly/175572.rss">The Art of WYSIWYG with pics :P(noob friendly)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
