<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Removing Antileech?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467</link>
    <description>As i&#39;m hosing my PI server, I totally forgot about the antileech, can someone tell me (or post a code) on how I can turn it off? If you can tyvm. :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 19:34:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Removing Antileech?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I suggest you be more specific, an anti-leach is to stop people like you.</p>
<p>[quote=“Miss Silabsoft, post:1, topic:202972”]This means be specific, State what you want clearly, and show the attempts you have made to finding your answer.</p>
<p><a href="http://catb.org/~esr/faqs/smart-questions.html" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://catb.org/~esr/faqs/smart-questions.html</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Edit by TeleNubby:</span><br>
It seems as if you guys are not understanding the message and meaning behind this post. Therefore, I will elaborate for you.</p>
<p>When you ask a question, pretend we are seven-year-old kids (that’s very easy to do as most of you guys are) that have no idea what’s going on. That’s how much you’ll have to explain. When asking the question, you must clearly ask it, just like Silabsoft said. This means use proper grammer and spelling, as this makes our job easier, and make sure you’re question is understandable.</p>
<p>Next, you’ll have to show us what you’ve already done. <span class="bbcode-b">THIS IS A MUST!</span> If we want to get anywhere as a community, we’re going to have to quit the spoon-feeding. So if you ask something like “how do I get food healing to work” and show us no previous attempts, you’re not going to get an answer. You may be wondering how a question like this is considered bad. Well, the question asker did not make an attempt to solve the problem him or herself, and is indirectly asking the same question as “tell me how to get food healing work so I can continue my effortless server.” So, remember, <span class="bbcode-b">show us what you’ve done, what you’ve tried to do, or what you think may work.</span></p>
<p>After you have all of that, you’ll have to identify the problem. Its not our job to add your snippet into our own servers and test it for any inconveniences, its YOURS. Usually, its a compilation problem, and it can be solved very easily by glancing at the JavaDocs. Something like <span class="bbcode-i">NullPointerException</span> can be found by typing <span class="bbcode-i">NullPointerException java.sun</span> in the Google search bar. This will return results with links to the JavaDocs about your problem.</p>
<p>Remember, this is just the bare minimum. Try and keep your questions as elaborate as possible. This will benefit yourself and the community as a whole, as you will be learning in the process and we will be able to help solve your problem faster.</p>
<p>Edit: Seeing as most of you think this is a joke, warnings will now be handed out if you disobey this.[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 19:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365467-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467.rss">[PI] Removing Antileech?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Removing Antileech?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ye_Im_Ace Ye Im Ace]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ye_im_ace">@Ye_Im_Ace</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Find it in your files, Delete it in your files.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 19:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365467-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467.rss">[PI] Removing Antileech?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Removing Antileech?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lord_Typhis Lord Typhis]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lord_typhis">@Lord_Typhis</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As i’m hosing my PI server, I totally forgot about the antileech, can someone tell me (or post a code) on how I can turn it off? If you can tyvm. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 04:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365467-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-removing-antileech/365467.rss">[PI] Removing Antileech?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
