<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Rules [4/15/11]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-4-15-11/391052</link>
    <description>[b]Foreword:[/b]

The staff reserve the right to interpret these rules any way they see fit. The following rules are more like guidelines. You shouldn&#39;t be looking for loopholes in them, rather, you should just get along with them. We&#39;re looking for users that use common sense. For example, we would prefer a user that knows, just because something isn&#39;t on the rules, that it it isn&#39;t necessarily allowed.
 
[size=10pt][b][u]Ideals:[/u][/b][/size]

[ul][li]We are not anti-leech. If you respect our community and our ideas, feel free to ask questions and they will be kindly answered if you follow the rules. Answer to questions that others ask if you know the answer or offer useful content, [b]otherwise remain silent[/b].[/li]
[li]We don&#39;t talk about things we don&#39;t know. This is an informative community.[/li]
[li] We do not care about post count alone. If someone has high post count but most of it is spam, we hate them. If someone has a high post count with informative posts, we love them. The higher count, the more we hate/love them.[/li]
[li]We do [b]not[/b] make spelling mistakes on purpose. We use &quot;you&quot; not &quot;u&quot;, we use &quot;why&quot; not &quot;y&quot; etc.[/li][/ul]


[size=10pt][b][u]Rules:[/u][/b][/size]
[b]Rule 1:[/b]
Moderators lock topics/remove posts and topics/hand infractions to users at their own discretion as required to foster a positive community. Any disagreement with a staff member&#39;s decision is to be resolved through the use of the PM system. Any public disputes are [b]unacceptable[/b] and punishable.

[b] Rule 2:[/b]
Everybody is equal, don&#39;t treat people worse than you do others(E.G., don&#39;t isolate someone and flame them).

[b]Rule 3:[/b]
Posts should be knowledgeable, try to put some effort into them, it&#39;ll save hassle and stop you from looking like an idiot.

[b]Rule 4:[/b]
We only have [b]one[/b] forum account per person, you can use the same account for [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf]Moparscape[/url], [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf]Moparisthebest[/url], and [url=http://moparcraft.net/smf]MoparCraft[/url]

[b]Rule 5:[/b]
Do not advertise without permission from a Global Moderator or an Administrator. Anyone advertising maliciously will be permanently banned.

[b]Rule 6:[/b]
We don&#39;t post misleading links, put appropriate warnings(while there&#39;s no specific rules on adult content, if you don&#39;t use [b]N[/b]ot [b]S[/b]afe [b]F[/b]or [b]W[/b]ork(NSFW) warnings, you will be punished).

[b]Rule 7:[/b]
A moderators decision is final, if you have a problem with it, pm an administrator. Trying to resolve it through a thread will result in a heavier punishment.

[b]Rule 8:[/b]
We do not sell anything on this site with the exception of SCAR scripts. SCAR Scripts must be verified, check the script sales board for more info.
[b]
Rule 9:[/b]
Do not post or upload any copyrighted material.

[b]Rule 10:[/b]
We never advertise via the PM system whether the site is approved or not. If your site is approved than you must advertise through appropriate means.

[b]Rule 11:[/b]
Never ask for reputation(rep). Reputation is to be handed out, at the forum members digression, as a reward for adding quality content to a thread, or the forum in general. Reputation abuse is punished. 

[b]Rule 12:[/b]
We respect each other and other communities. We do [b]not[/b] flame. There is to be no fighting on the forums.

All of the rules stated in this post apply to [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf]Moparscape[/url], [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf]Moparisthebest[/url], and [url=http://moparcraft.net/smf]MoparCraft[/url], they apply to all topics and all messages, failure to comply to these rules with result in punishment handed out at the staff members&#39; digression.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 01:26:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-4-15-11/391052.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Rules [4/15/11]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Foreword:</span></p>
<p>The staff reserve the right to interpret these rules any way they see fit. The following rules are more like guidelines. You shouldn’t be looking for loopholes in them, rather, you should just get along with them. We’re looking for users that use common sense. For example, we would prefer a user that knows, just because something isn’t on the rules, that it it isn’t necessarily allowed.</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Ideals:</span></span>[/size]</p>
<p>[ul][li]We are not anti-leech. If you respect our community and our ideas, feel free to ask questions and they will be kindly answered if you follow the rules. Answer to questions that others ask if you know the answer or offer useful content, <span class="bbcode-b">otherwise remain silent</span>.[/li]<br>
[li]We don’t talk about things we don’t know. This is an informative community.[/li]<br>
[li] We do not care about post count alone. If someone has high post count but most of it is spam, we hate them. If someone has a high post count with informative posts, we love them. The higher count, the more we hate/love them.[/li]<br>
[li]We do <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> make spelling mistakes on purpose. We use “you” not “u”, we use “why” not “y” etc.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Rules:</span></span>[/size]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Rule 1:</span><br>
Moderators lock topics/remove posts and topics/hand infractions to users at their own discretion as required to foster a positive community. Any disagreement with a staff member’s decision is to be resolved through the use of the PM system. Any public disputes are <span class="bbcode-b">unacceptable</span> and punishable.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"> Rule 2:</span><br>
Everybody is equal, don’t treat people worse than you do others(E.G., don’t isolate someone and flame them).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 3:</span><br>
Posts should be knowledgeable, try to put some effort into them, it’ll save hassle and stop you from looking like an idiot.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 4:</span><br>
We only have <span class="bbcode-b">one</span> forum account per person, you can use the same account for <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true">Moparscape</a>, <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true">Moparisthebest</a>, and <a href="http://moparcraft.net/smf" data-bbcode="true">MoparCraft</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 5:</span><br>
Do not advertise without permission from a Global Moderator or an Administrator. Anyone advertising maliciously will be permanently banned.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 6:</span><br>
We don’t post misleading links, put appropriate warnings(while there’s no specific rules on adult content, if you don’t use <span class="bbcode-b">N</span>ot <span class="bbcode-b">S</span>afe <span class="bbcode-b">F</span>or <span class="bbcode-b">W</span>ork(NSFW) warnings, you will be punished).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 7:</span><br>
A moderators decision is final, if you have a problem with it, pm an administrator. Trying to resolve it through a thread will result in a heavier punishment.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 8:</span><br>
We do not sell anything on this site with the exception of SCAR scripts. SCAR Scripts must be verified, check the script sales board for more info.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b"><br>
Rule 9:</span><br>
Do not post or upload any copyrighted material.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 10:</span><br>
We never advertise via the PM system whether the site is approved or not. If your site is approved than you must advertise through appropriate means.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 11:</span><br>
Never ask for reputation(rep). Reputation is to be handed out, at the forum members digression, as a reward for adding quality content to a thread, or the forum in general. Reputation abuse is punished.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Rule 12:</span><br>
We respect each other and other communities. We do <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> flame. There is to be no fighting on the forums.</p>
<p>All of the rules stated in this post apply to <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true">Moparscape</a>, <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf" data-bbcode="true">Moparisthebest</a>, and <a href="http://moparcraft.net/smf" data-bbcode="true">MoparCraft</a>, they apply to all topics and all messages, failure to comply to these rules with result in punishment handed out at the staff members’ digression.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-4-15-11/391052/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-4-15-11/391052/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 01:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-391052-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-rules-4-15-11/391052.rss">The Rules [4/15/11]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
