<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking for Coder for New PK Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-coder-for-new-pk-server/477961</link>
    <description>Hi and thanks for taking the time to look here

Me and Kurupt (well known and respected person/Admin of RSCR/other servers) have seen PK servers come and go through this RSC community like wildfire.

Being PKers ourselves, since RSC and playing just about every one of these servers we know its the most enjoyable thing in the RSC community and why each and every one of these servers have failed, miserably. It is hugely in part to the staff running these servers, and the failure to implement what the PKing community is wanting.

We have planned a PKing server that satisfies what the PKing community is craving and being level-headed, mature people are well equipped and experienced to run a successful server.

When i say &#39;planned&#39; we have edited the map completely to serve PKing needs and designed documentation outlining drops, rates, NPC locations, Sub benefits, Shops and what they will sell, Quests (revolved around PKing and wild NPCs) for wearing rune plate and much more. Whilst some is reminiscent of servers come and gone, there are many original ideas that long-time PKers will absolutely enjoy.

We have the skills to add/remove/change NPCs and objects, however tThe only problem is we don&#39;t have the skills to program and code new stuff into a server - which is where you come in!

We are willing to provide the source of funds to buy a dedicated server, however we do not currently have enough money to pay someone to code a server fully for us.

In saying this, we are willing to provide the profits from subscriptions (after dedi money is taken out to continue the server) up to an agreed amount or provide a percentage from subscription over an amount of time.

We are solely doing this so we have a stable and lasting server for ourselves to PK on and share with the entire community. Although we would like to be remunerated for our initial outlay in the longrun, there is no profit incentive for us and all profits from this server will be used to buy better protection/dedicated server or to enhance the server with additional coding.

We are looking for someone that will be reliable, honest and helpful in our endeavour to make the best PK server to ever hit the RSC scene. It will be great experience for someone that is an amateur coder (yet with enough skill to help us) whilst also being involved in something that we hope to consider very unique and special in the RSC community.

For further information please PM me on here with your skype/msn.

Thanks guys, and hope to hear from someone soon.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 06:34:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-coder-for-new-pk-server/477961.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking for Coder for New PK Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@oldy oldy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/oldy">@oldy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi and thanks for taking the time to look here</p>
<p>Me and Kurupt (well known and respected person/Admin of RSCR/other servers) have seen PK servers come and go through this RSC community like wildfire.</p>
<p>Being PKers ourselves, since RSC and playing just about every one of these servers we know its the most enjoyable thing in the RSC community and why each and every one of these servers have failed, miserably. It is hugely in part to the staff running these servers, and the failure to implement what the PKing community is wanting.</p>
<p>We have planned a PKing server that satisfies what the PKing community is craving and being level-headed, mature people are well equipped and experienced to run a successful server.</p>
<p>When i say ‘planned’ we have edited the map completely to serve PKing needs and designed documentation outlining drops, rates, NPC locations, Sub benefits, Shops and what they will sell, Quests (revolved around PKing and wild NPCs) for wearing rune plate and much more. Whilst some is reminiscent of servers come and gone, there are many original ideas that long-time PKers will absolutely enjoy.</p>
<p>We have the skills to add/remove/change NPCs and objects, however tThe only problem is we don’t have the skills to program and code new stuff into a server - which is where you come in!</p>
<p>We are willing to provide the source of funds to buy a dedicated server, however we do not currently have enough money to pay someone to code a server fully for us.</p>
<p>In saying this, we are willing to provide the profits from subscriptions (after dedi money is taken out to continue the server) up to an agreed amount or provide a percentage from subscription over an amount of time.</p>
<p>We are solely doing this so we have a stable and lasting server for ourselves to PK on and share with the entire community. Although we would like to be remunerated for our initial outlay in the longrun, there is no profit incentive for us and all profits from this server will be used to buy better protection/dedicated server or to enhance the server with additional coding.</p>
<p>We are looking for someone that will be reliable, honest and helpful in our endeavour to make the best PK server to ever hit the RSC scene. It will be great experience for someone that is an amateur coder (yet with enough skill to help us) whilst also being involved in something that we hope to consider very unique and special in the RSC community.</p>
<p>For further information please PM me on here with your skype/msn.</p>
<p>Thanks guys, and hope to hear from someone soon.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-coder-for-new-pk-server/477961/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-coder-for-new-pk-server/477961/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 06:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-477961-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/looking-for-coder-for-new-pk-server/477961.rss">Looking for Coder for New PK Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
