<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNN.com</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031</link>
    <description>Check out the difference between &quot;CNN.com&quot; and &quot;CNN.com International&quot;...

[img]http://img207.imageshack.us/img207/5274/17ez3.jpg[/img]

Subtle.

[img]http://img162.imageshack.us/img162/9563/27tk1.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2006 21:40:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yah some of the old black and white movies own</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2006 21:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I saw the movie for All Quiet on the Western front. It was an old movie, pretty good though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2006 16:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you see in like Al Jazeera you get to see alot of cool stuff, but I don’t understand arabic so <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> [br][size=1]Posted at: June 03, 2006, 03:35:37 am[/size][hr][quote=“PaulT, post:39, topic:3031”]Yeah. I had fun :).</p>
<p>You really should try All Quiet on the Western Front, it’s not an American book, and I think you would agree with alot of the conclusions the author comes to.[/quote]</p>
<p>Will do that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2006 10:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol maybe there really scared hes gonna burn them all with nukes</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/45</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>and obviously all media is controlled not by the govt tho by whoever owns it if the guys a democrat then hes gonna be pro democrat but isnt
americas media mostly liberal?</blockquote>
<p>You’re very right.</p>
<p>A good example is Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad. He has no power. Iran is controlled by a council of Clerics. But who do you see in the news all the time? Why does the US news continue to prop him up?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/44</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 03:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yah thats what my teacher showed in class the black and white version it was awesome</p>
<p>and obviously all media is controlled not by the govt tho by whoever owns it if the guys a democrat then hes gonna be pro democrat but isnt<br>
americas media mostly liberal?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/43</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 03:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ron Ron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ron">@Ron</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>All news on tv is controlled in the US anyways. The only way to get actual news is to get it from foreign websites such as <a href="http://bbc.co.uk" rel="nofollow noopener">bbc.co.uk</a>, or yahoo, which is suprisingly not as controlled as other medias.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/42</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 02:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes, there were two movies. I think the old black and white one is better.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/41</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 02:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>isnt that a movie to? from the gerrmans point of view?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/40</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 01:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah. I had fun :).</p>
<p>You really should try All Quiet on the Western Front, it’s not an American book, and I think you would agree with alot of the conclusions the author comes to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/39</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 00:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeye. I am too lazy to reply all the time, the discussion will be on if USA is a free country etc, I have my own opionon and you have your own, so not worth talking about that, and same with the other stuff… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Good discussion tho. &lt;3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/38</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2006 20:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>"However, the US is the closest thing there is to a free country"
Still, that's your OPIONON, so write that its your opionon and don't write that. If it's the closest thing there is to a free country. I hardly doubt that. Hardly. You say this because you live at USA; because you are probably born there etc, if you were from Iraq you would say Iraq is the best. So shush and don't spread USA propoganda in this forum k? You just make people hate it even more.</blockquote>
<p>No that’s a fact. And I would not say Iraq was the best country even if I was from Iraq. Think about it; how strong is nationalism in Iraq? It’s nonexistent. You can see that by the daily death toll of Iraqi police and soldiers.</p>
<p>I have stated the reasons the US is the best country in the world and you have chosen to ignore them and say it is because I grew up here. I of all people know how many problems the US has, and I am well aware that many other countries compete with the US in different areas. However, you are ignoring the content of my posts and repeating your same conviction that I am simply a stupid American.</p>
<blockquote>How do you know suicide bombers kill people because their insane? You don't know. All you do is writing a bunch of crap.</blockquote>
<p>I know suicide bombers are insane because they are suicide bombers.</p>
<blockquote>After all the bomb attents and such, I say one of the reason is they kill the people who co operate with the US soldiers etc. Bush wants to spread peace, he should start with his own country first. He kills his own people and blame it on so called "terrorists" which I hardly believe they are so powerful to blow WTC, when they say USA got such a high security with all the new technology.</blockquote>
<p>Yes, they do kill US collaborators, but they also kill, as I have said, everyone but radical muslims. I share your skepticism of the official story of what happened on 9/11, but I’m not prepared to make stupid blanket statements.</p>
<blockquote>He attacks every country he wants, at first,</blockquote>
<p>With approval of the other branches of the US government.</p>
<blockquote>they put people like Saddam in power and then they get rid of him, they talked about mass-thingy-weapons, none found. If you see TV, not USA TV's. You see how the Iraqs/Afghans are mad that US and the others are in their OWN country and ruleing it.</blockquote>
<p>Yes, it’s a fucked up situation, and the US has a history of these kind of failed operations. I’m aware the Iraqi’s and the Afghani’s don’t want us their. I don’t think we should be their either. I think we should leave them to kill eachother, as they have been doing for thousands of years. I repeat, learn the history of the middle east, and it will become clear to you the US is just another tribe.</p>
<blockquote>If the people want rid of someone, let them do a revolution.</blockquote>
<p>To have a revolution, you need a strong middle class. Example: South Korea, or China. Once you have an established middle class they will revolt and create a democratic government. However, this will probably never happen in the middle east, where the people with the most weapons are the people in charge. This just happens to be the US tribe at this point.</p>
<blockquote>They say Saddam killed alot of people, proof? Saddam and USA have played many games and co-operated together alot, for example in the war against Iran, Iraq got lots of weapons from other countries.. and the same to Iran.</blockquote>
<p>Ok, so? I agree with you 100% the war in Iraq is pointless and based upon lies.</p>
<blockquote>I prefer not reading USA propoganda books or w/e.</blockquote>
<p>All Quiet on the Western Front is written by a german about the german side in WW1. Slaughterhouse five is distinctly anti-war and anti-American in many ways, as is a Rumour of War. All three of the books I have recommended show the pointlessness of war, and a Rumour of War provides a great example of how world powers can’t interfere with small nations for their own purposes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/37</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2006 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“PaulT, post:33, topic:3031”]No country will have <span class="bbcode-b">complete</span> freedom. However, the US is the closest thing there is to a free country. In the US people have more rights than anywhere else in the world.</p>
<p>[quote]There are countries who have as much freedom as USA, or even more, for example Sweden, or Norway, etc.</p>
<p>What you saying is bullshit and it’s all crap…“USA owns, US is blahblah…”[/quote]</p>
<p>It’s my opinion that the US is the best country in the world. However, it is a fact that the laws and traditions of the US make it the most free country in the world. Yes, Norway and Sweden have laws that make them free countries comparable to the US, however we in America have the Constitution fo the United States of America, which is the most powerful and important document that has ever existed. It guarantees our right not only to freedom of speech, press, and religion, but also our right to violently overthrow our government if we don’t like what’s going on.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
“Also, the people who do suicide bombings, they kill the Iraqs becaus they co-operate with the american soldiers etc.”[/quote]</p>
<p>Suicide bombers kill people because they are insane, and believe they will recieve 42 virgins upon blowing themselves up. The suicide bombers target anyone who isn’t a radical muslim, basically. Jews, Americans, Iraqi soldiers and police, are their favorite targets, but they don’t give a fuck who they kill as long as it isn’t a radical muslim.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
That was another suggestion/idea, also, I told you something else and you didn’t comment that<br>
because you got owned okthx go home and learn some history.[/quote]</p>
<p>Some things you say make so little sense that I don’t understand them. Sorry.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
Don’t come here and talk shit except you know anything from Asia, go back to your little USA and tell how great is. You’re living cool, you ain’t at war, you ain’t seeing all the trouble, your sitting comfortable in your chair and making 500 stupid topics.[/quote]</p>
<p>My country (the US) is at war. I haven’t made 500 topics, I haven’t even broken 100 at that.</p>
<p>I think you should read “All Quiet on the Western Front”, “Slaughterhouse Five”, and/or “A Rumour of War”, any or all of which will give you some idea of what war and freedom are really about.[/quote]</p>
<p>“However, the US is the closest thing there is to a free country”<br>
Still, that’s your OPIONON, so write that its your opionon and don’t write that. If it’s the closest thing there is to a free country. I hardly doubt that. Hardly. You say this because you live at USA; because you are probably born there etc, if you were from Iraq you would say Iraq is the best. So shush and don’t spread USA propoganda in this forum k? You just make people hate it even more.</p>
<p>How do you know suicide bombers kill people because their insane? You don’t know. All you do is writing a bunch of crap.</p>
<p>“The suicide bombers target anyone who isn’t a radical muslim, basically. Jews, Americans, Iraqi soldiers and police, are their favorite targets, but they don’t give a fuck who they kill as long as it isn’t a radical muslim.” Where you got that from? But sure, it can be tha too.</p>
<p>After all the bomb attents and such, I say one of the reason is they kill the people who co operate with the US soldiers etc. Bush wants to spread peace, he should start with his own country first. He kills his own people and blame it on so called “terrorists” which I hardly believe they are so powerful to blow WTC, when they say USA got such a high security with all the new technology. He attacks every country he wants, at first, they put people like Saddam in power and then they get rid of him, they talked about mass-thingy-weapons, none found. If you see TV, not USA TV’s. You see how the Iraqs/Afghans are mad that US and the others are in their OWN country and ruleing it. If the people want rid of someone, let them do a revolution. They say Saddam killed alot of people, proof? Saddam and USA have played many games and co-operated together alot, for example in the war against Iran, Iraq got lots of weapons from other countries… and the same to Iran.</p>
<p>“I think you should read “All Quiet on the Western Front”, “Slaughterhouse Five”, and/or “A Rumour of War”, any or all of which will give you some idea of what war and freedom are really about.”</p>
<p>I prefer not reading USA propoganda books or w/e.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2006 13:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>u confused me</blockquote>
 :|
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2006 05:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im sure its 70 virgins or 72 i dont know u confused me</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2006 00:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No country will have <span class="bbcode-b">complete</span> freedom. However, the US is the closest thing there is to a free country. In the US people have more rights than anywhere else in the world.</p>
<blockquote>There are countries who have as much freedom as USA, or even more, for example Sweden, or Norway, etc.
<p>What you saying is bullshit and it’s all crap…“USA owns, US is blahblah…”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>It’s my opinion that the US is the best country in the world. However, it is a fact that the laws and traditions of the US make it the most free country in the world. Yes, Norway and Sweden have laws that make them free countries comparable to the US, however we in America have the Constitution fo the United States of America, which is the most powerful and important document that has ever existed. It guarantees our right not only to freedom of speech, press, and religion, but also our right to violently overthrow our government if we don’t like what’s going on.</p>
<blockquote>"Also, the people who do suicide bombings, they kill the Iraqs becaus they co-operate with the american soldiers etc."</blockquote>
<p>Suicide bombers kill people because they are insane, and believe they will recieve 42 virgins upon blowing themselves up. The suicide bombers target anyone who isn’t a radical muslim, basically. Jews, Americans, Iraqi soldiers and police, are their favorite targets, but they don’t give a fuck who they kill as long as it isn’t a radical muslim.</p>
<blockquote>That was another suggestion/idea, also, I told you something else and you didn't comment that 
because you got owned okthx go home and learn some history.</blockquote>
<p>Some things you say make so little sense that I don’t understand them. Sorry.</p>
<blockquote>Don't come here and talk shit except you know anything from Asia, go back to your little USA and tell how great is. You're living cool, you ain't at war, you ain't seeing all the trouble, your sitting comfortable in your chair and making 500 stupid topics.</blockquote>
<p>My country (the US) is at war. I haven’t made 500 topics, I haven’t even broken 100 at that.</p>
<p>I think you should read “All Quiet on the Western Front”, “Slaughterhouse Five”, and/or “A Rumour of War”, any or all of which will give you some idea of what war and freedom are really about.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/33</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 21:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Got_Shine, post:31, topic:3031”]Xerves, you obviously hate america for some reason, whatever it is I really don’t care, but the thing is you weren’t involved in the disagreement what so ever, and all countries have their faults, all you did was name some. Also, how do you know this about other countries, have you lived there? I’m guessing no.</p>
<p>And hemeny, I don’t see where you’re coming from either, you seem to just spout random things.</p>
<p>And by army deserters, Paul means people that signed up for RATC (College funded by the army, in turn for the scholar taking part as an active duty solider) and as soon as a war comes up (they joined RATC because they didn’t think they’d have to take part in a war) they ditch america and go to canada. He doesn’t mean people leaving because of a forced draft.[/quote]</p>
<p>I know. I just know their are freedom there too, maybe even more than USA. No country have actually REAL freedom, tho…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 20:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Got_Shine Got_Shine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/got_shine">@Got_Shine</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Xerves, you obviously hate america for some reason, whatever it is I really don’t care, but the thing is you weren’t involved in the disagreement what so ever, and all countries have their faults, all you did was name some. Also, how do you know this about other countries, have you lived there? I’m guessing no.</p>
<p>And hemeny, I don’t see where you’re coming from either, you seem to just spout random things.</p>
<p>And by army deserters, Paul means people that signed up for RATC (College funded by the army, in turn for the scholar taking part as an active duty solider) and as soon as a war comes up (they joined RATC because they didn’t think they’d have to take part in a war) they ditch america and go to canada. He doesn’t mean people leaving because of a forced draft.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 20:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There are countries who have as much freedom as USA, or even more, for example Sweden, or Norway, etc.</p>
<p>What you saying is bullshit and it’s all crap…“USA owns, US is blahblah…”</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
<p>“Also, the people who do suicide bombings, they kill the Iraqs becaus they co-operate with the american soldiers etc.”</p>
<p>That was another suggestion/idea, also, I told you something else and you didn’t comment that because you got owned okthx go home and learn some history.</p>
<p>Don’t come here and talk shit except you know anything from Asia, go back to your little USA and tell how great is. You’re living cool, you ain’t at war, you ain’t seeing all the trouble, your sitting comfortable in your chair and making 500 stupid topics.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/30</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 20:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>1) USA is not the best country, nor the country that has freedom.</blockquote>
<p>Which country has more freedom than the US? If I wanted to go on a street corner and tell everyone that the Jews were controlling the world, that the White race must remain pure and kill all the brown devils, police officers would <span class="bbcode-b">protect me</span> from anyone trying to stop me from saying whatever I wanted.</p>
<blockquote>2) The Iraqis is different, there is Shias and Sunnis, they have a war, if I am not wrong. Also, the people who do suicide bombings, they kill the Iraqs becaus they co-operate with the american soldiers etc.</blockquote>
<p>Different religious sects have been killing eachother over who worships god better for thousands of years in the middle east. Learn some history or go away. It’s not a war, it’s a cycle.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/29</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 17:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>smooth move exlax<br>
nice play shakespear</p>
<p>seriously nice you just owned us both</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/28</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 17:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xerxes Xerxes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerxes">@Xerxes</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="25" data-topic="3031">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/pault/40/5_8504b32b4165840149d2c3dd52eb0686.png" class="avatar"> PaulT:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]Iwhite man please health care is not good for all not everyone can afford it and they cant just rush to canada cuz they need to apply for citizenship</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s why I said they can <span class="bbcode-b">move</span> to Canada if they don’t like it here. Social darwinism is part of the US culture, get over it.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>army deserters meh i got nothin to say to them the army wont let em quit so they leave they have a right to leave when they want</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>When you join the army, you agree not to just “Quit” whenever you want. In fact, you sign something. Deserters are the worst people on earth.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
and health care in the us aint good i saw a stupid fuck whats it called<br>
a news clip or somthin on cbc saying canadas healthcare was betetr then usa’s this was yesterday[/quote]</p>
<p>Do you have a link?</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
i just read that story and its gay so one story hes accused of was false there are many more like i said my dad was living proof the guy had issues how didnt i  adress what you said[/quote]</p>
<p>Yeah that’s pretty homosexual.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
gack what happened to you saying theres no point in arguing online<br>
because whoever wins blah blah ur still retarted blah blah[/quote]</p>
<p>This is a discussion and a debate, not an argument.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Rofl. Good joke. Jerk.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It seems pretty clear that the Iraqis don’t give a fuck about eachother. How many suicide bombings occur in the US?[/quote]</p>
<p>Looks like you have no idea.</p>
<ol>
<li>USA is not the best country, nor the country that has freedom.</li>
<li>The Iraqis is different, there is Shias and Sunnis, they have a war, if I am not wrong. Also, the people who do suicide bombings, they kill the Iraqs becaus they co-operate with the american soldiers etc.</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/27</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 17:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>paul no i dont have a link ill find one i saw it on tv not the site</p>
<p>army deserters go fuckin nuts because of what they see and sometimes the psychologists say there faking so they commit suicide like that one guy cant remember his name he was a nobody</p>
<p>debates are fun <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>and i agree with you not all muslims but some (not just iraqis iranis do that to) plus most of the suicide bombers are saudi very few are iraqis once again the news this time cnn(tv)</p>
<p>and …i got nothin im empty</p>
<p>edit::sorry dude couldnt find a link but i saw it anyways heres a link pretaining to the debate<br>
<a href="http://www.cbc.ca/story/world/national/2006/05/31/haditha-families.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.cbc.ca/story/world/national/2006/05/31/haditha-families.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/26</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 17:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PaulT PaulT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pault">@PaulT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Iwhite man please health care is not good for all not everyone can afford it and they cant just rush to canada cuz they need to apply for citizenship</blockquote>
<p>That’s why I said they can <span class="bbcode-b">move</span> to Canada if they don’t like it here. Social darwinism is part of the US culture, get over it.</p>
<blockquote>army deserters meh i got nothin to say to them the army wont let em quit so they leave they have a right to leave when they want</blockquote>
<p>When you join the army, you agree not to just “Quit” whenever you want. In fact, you sign something. Deserters are the worst people on earth.</p>
<blockquote>and health care in the us aint good i saw a stupid fuck whats it called
a news clip or somthin on cbc saying canadas healthcare was betetr then usa's this was yesterday</blockquote>
<p>Do you have a link?</p>
<blockquote>i just read that story and its gay so one story hes accused of was false there are many more like i said my dad was living proof the guy had issues how didnt i  adress what you said</blockquote>
<p>Yeah that’s pretty homosexual.</p>
<blockquote>gack what happened to you saying theres no point in arguing online
because whoever wins blah blah ur still retarted blah blah</blockquote>
<p>This is a discussion and a debate, not an argument.</p>
<blockquote>Rofl. Good joke. Jerk.</blockquote>
It seems pretty clear that the Iraqis don't give a fuck about eachother. How many suicide bombings occur in the US?
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/25</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>CNN.com</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>white man please health care is not good for all not everyone can afford it and they cant just rush to canada cuz they need to apply for citizenship</p>
<p>army deserters meh i got nothin to say to them the army wont let em quit so they leave they have a right to leave when they want</p>
<p>and health care in the us aint good i saw a stupid fuck whats it called<br>
a news clip or somthin on cbc saying canadas healthcare was betetr then usa’s this was yesterday</p>
<p>i just read that story and its gay so one story hes accused of was false there are many more like i said my dad was living proof the guy had issues how didnt i  adress what you said</p>
<p>gack what happened to you saying theres no point in arguing online<br>
because whoever wins blah blah ur still retarted blah blah</p>
<p>xerxes u laghin at paul?</p>
<p>::plus america isnt the best in the world id rather be in italy france england and yes iraq the parts that arent fighting then the us  …the us has nothing to offer me to go there except cheap inexpensive labour</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 16:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-3031-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cnn-com/3031.rss">CNN.com</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
