<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317/474 PI] JigloScape | 2007 OldSchool | PK-PVP Server | NO CUSTOMS | Login&amp;PK</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-474-pi-jigloscape-2007-oldschool-pk-pvp-server-no-customs-login-pk/547575</link>
    <description>[center][IMG]http://i.imgur.com/m8LgSul.png[/img]

________

CLIENT DOWNLOAD: http://uppit.com/y5g4kx8rknfu/JigloScape_-_2007_PK.rar
________

Yea, I know about the name. You may say words like: &quot;leecher, stealer, fan-boy, etc.&quot;, but sorry. That doesn&#39;t offend me. I just don&#39;t care, I&#39;m just trying to do something better for the RSPS world. :) Anyways, not much to say about the server, just that it&#39;s seriously awesome. No sht with customs (no dragon claws, chaotics, torva), just oldcshool 2007 style. I know that RuneScape 2007 (OSRS) is back, but I wanted to make a server, where legends PKed in 2007. To enjoy the server, you just need to Login, type ::master, buy some stuff and get rollin&#39; to the wild. Well, you also need to get some players, because the server just launched moments ago and it doesn&#39;t have players. You will get a nice starter, so you could walk on your own. If you run out of money, there&#39;s always shops to sell items and you can also use Thieving stalls for money. Well, I don&#39;t do much of these Advertisements, I guess that&#39;s all what I needed to tell. Oh, and the server is on a host, so it&#39;s 24/7, don&#39;t worry about DCs.
___________

Owner: Jiglo

Owner&#39;s Skype: i.unknown.i

E-Mail: viteo.mail@gmail.com

Website: http://www.jigloscape.webs.com/

____________

&quot;Wassup, people! Do you remember the oldschool 2007 pk times? The old Runescape times... I know that there is OldSchool Runescape back, but what about getting the stats up? Getting money? That&#39;s the problem. Well, you can just log-in the server, get all skills instantly 99s, get a starter (with money and stuff) and go PK. If you will run out of thieving, there&#39;s always Thieving. Now, you may think, why the name is: JigloScape. Why? Because, in about 2007 a PK God was born, he was one of the best, so I just got addicted to his videos and in many of them I saw when a Jiglojays enemy dies, many people say: &quot;Welcome to JigloScape!&quot;, so that&#39;s how I came up with the name. Well, there&#39;s not much to tell, but the server is really entertaining and fun to play.&quot;

[IMG]http://i.imgur.com/PLWcUf1.png[/img] [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/yaVcVo9.png[/img]

PKP Shop - [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/p3424Xz.png[/img]
Prayers - [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/D7u8Mo0.png[/img]
Starter - [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/w29vsBl.png[/img]
Barrows - [IMG]http://i.imgur.com/UaJVnoL.png[/img]

________

CLIENT DOWNLOAD: http://uppit.com/y5g4kx8rknfu/JigloScape_-_2007_PK.rar
________


[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 23:15:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-474-pi-jigloscape-2007-oldschool-pk-pvp-server-no-customs-login-pk/547575.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317/474 PI] JigloScape | 2007 OldSchool | PK-PVP Server | NO CUSTOMS | Login&amp;PK</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ViTEO ViTEO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/viteo">@ViTEO</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://i.imgur.com/m8LgSul.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<hr>
<p>CLIENT DOWNLOAD: <a href="http://uppit.com/y5g4kx8rknfu/JigloScape_-_2007_PK.rar" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/y5g4kx8rknfu/JigloScape_-_2007_PK.rar</a></p>
<hr>
<p>Yea, I know about the name. You may say words like: “leecher, stealer, fan-boy, etc.”, but sorry. That doesn’t offend me. I just don’t care, I’m just trying to do something better for the RSPS world. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Anyways, not much to say about the server, just that it’s seriously awesome. No sht with customs (no dragon claws, chaotics, torva), just oldcshool 2007 style. I know that RuneScape 2007 (OSRS) is back, but I wanted to make a server, where legends PKed in 2007. To enjoy the server, you just need to Login, type ::master, buy some stuff and get rollin’ to the wild. Well, you also need to get some players, because the server just launched moments ago and it doesn’t have players. You will get a nice starter, so you could walk on your own. If you run out of money, there’s always shops to sell items and you can also use Thieving stalls for money. Well, I don’t do much of these Advertisements, I guess that’s all what I needed to tell. Oh, and the server is on a host, so it’s 24/7, don’t worry about DCs.</p>
<hr>
<p>Owner: Jiglo</p>
<p>Owner’s Skype: i.unknown.i</p>
<p>E-Mail: <a href="mailto:viteo.mail@gmail.com">viteo.mail@gmail.com</a></p>
<p>Website: <a href="http://www.jigloscape.webs.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.jigloscape.webs.com/</a></p>
<hr>
<p>“Wassup, people! Do you remember the oldschool 2007 pk times? The old Runescape times… I know that there is OldSchool Runescape back, but what about getting the stats up? Getting money? That’s the problem. Well, you can just log-in the server, get all skills instantly 99s, get a starter (with money and stuff) and go PK. If you will run out of thieving, there’s always Thieving. Now, you may think, why the name is: JigloScape. Why? Because, in about 2007 a PK God was born, he was one of the best, so I just got addicted to his videos and in many of them I saw when a Jiglojays enemy dies, many people say: “Welcome to JigloScape!”, so that’s how I came up with the name. Well, there’s not much to tell, but the server is really entertaining and fun to play.”</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/PLWcUf1.png" alt width="" height=""> <img src="http://i.imgur.com/yaVcVo9.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>PKP Shop - <img src="http://i.imgur.com/p3424Xz.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Prayers - <img src="http://i.imgur.com/D7u8Mo0.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Starter - <img src="http://i.imgur.com/w29vsBl.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Barrows - <img src="http://i.imgur.com/UaJVnoL.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<hr>
<p>CLIENT DOWNLOAD: <a href="http://uppit.com/y5g4kx8rknfu/JigloScape_-_2007_PK.rar" rel="nofollow noopener">http://uppit.com/y5g4kx8rknfu/JigloScape_-_2007_PK.rar</a></p>
<hr>
<p>[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-474-pi-jigloscape-2007-oldschool-pk-pvp-server-no-customs-login-pk/547575/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-474-pi-jigloscape-2007-oldschool-pk-pvp-server-no-customs-login-pk/547575/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 23:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-547575-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-474-pi-jigloscape-2007-oldschool-pk-pvp-server-no-customs-login-pk/547575.rss">[317/474 PI] JigloScape | 2007 OldSchool | PK-PVP Server | NO CUSTOMS | Login&amp;PK</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
