<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Trying to figure out a story line for a game</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962</link>
    <description>So I&#39;m working on my game still. It&#39;s been a while since I have though. The thread is [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,477738.0.htm]here[/url] though if you haven&#39;t seen it. So with the little story that&#39;s in, 
&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;The God&#39;s have punished you. For what, you do not know. However, you do know that you are stuck in this place. Wherever this place is. You know not the name of the place, the name of this world, or even your own name. You have but one quest: Discover your path, and answer the questions left unanswered by the God&#39;s, For a great story is about to unfold.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
and (talking to the guy in the shop)
&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;You don&#39;t look like your from around here are you? Well I&#39;ll tell you the whole story. I&#39;ve resided in this town for twelve years. I noticed a large influx of travelers passing through throughout the past few years. They were all looking for a shop to trade and resupply with so I decided to make this here shop. The town&#39;s called Ventalurok. We are a humble mining town based off of the old Lurok mine over there. If you go down there be sure to watch out for the zombies and gas pockets! Well hey, I&#39;ve done enough talking. You come back here whenever you need to buy or sell something. The names Rindle by the way.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
I&#39;m trying to work out some more bits to add in. This is really just to see if you guys think what I just came up with is good or not. So here is what I want just working on.
(a mysterious letter found in the forest)
&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;The horrible things you have done cannot be undone. What happened is set in stone. The Gods will never forgive you for the suffering and pain that you have caused the world. You have been punished. This place is dreadful, though it may not seem it yet. You will soon discover many secrets lurking in this town. It&#39;s evil, this is your hell. Here you shall stay until the end of your days unless the Gods deem it fit to pardon your sins.

Sincerely,
Anonymous&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
and
&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;While in the realm of Roalend, you were a humble man. A man with a great promise of becoming legendary. Your accomplishments were leading you on a divine path, you were to become a God. Whilst in a Church the fateful day that you were punished, you were given a proposition from a man of very strange sorts. He asked you to take from him, an amulet. This amulet, you had no knowledge of, however the man gave you fair warning. The man offered you 20,000 gold to take the amulet off of his hands. You took the Amulet of Destruction, not knowing the power it held. It was out of sheer greed that you took this amulet. This was your downfall. Like the downfall of all men, greed is a powerful thing. Now the Amulet of Destruction seemed to you an ordinary amulet, however once touched by a God or person on the divine path, it would unleash havoc upon the world. The moment the transaction occurred, the very moment the amulet touched your finger tips, all hope for the realm of Roalend was lost. Soon beasts came to ravage the land, beasts of great power, knowing only destruction. They went to every town, city, and settlement,  killing all in their path. The Gods, in this grave hour, brought you to their Council of the Divine. It was here that you were deemed unfit to be a God. As punishment  for the hell that you had unleashed upon Roalend, it seemed only fitting that you too would be placed in your own hell. As the meeting of the Council of the Divine came to a close, the Gods joined together is saying, &quot;Rot in hell Lucifer!&quot; and with that you were punished.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

I&#39;m not much of a writer so tell me what you guys think of it.  :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 18:22:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Trying to figure out a story line for a game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asyo4 asyo4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asyo4">@asyo4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Him taking an amulet is… too original. You should’ve made it a sacred relic of some sort, amulets are overrused in stories. Just a suggestion  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 18:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-400962-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962.rss">Trying to figure out a story line for a game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Trying to figure out a story line for a game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sp11k3t3ht3rd sp11k3t3ht3rd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sp11k3t3ht3rd">@sp11k3t3ht3rd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m developing a text - based game. It’s been in the works for a while. I’m just trying to add a story to it. The last 2 quotes are stuff I thought of over the past couple days, the first 2 were already in. This was just to see what people thought of the story line I made up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 06:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-400962-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962.rss">Trying to figure out a story line for a game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Trying to figure out a story line for a game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jerico_Pimpinbro Jerico Pimpinbro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jerico_pimpinbro">@Jerico_Pimpinbro</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What type of game are you looking to develop?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 06:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-400962-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962.rss">Trying to figure out a story line for a game</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Trying to figure out a story line for a game</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sp11k3t3ht3rd sp11k3t3ht3rd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sp11k3t3ht3rd">@sp11k3t3ht3rd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I’m working on my game still. It’s been a while since I have though. The thread is <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,477738.0.htm" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a> though if you haven’t seen it. So with the little story that’s in,</p>
<blockquote>"The God's have punished you. For what, you do not know. However, you do know that you are stuck in this place. Wherever this place is. You know not the name of the place, the name of this world, or even your own name. You have but one quest: Discover your path, and answer the questions left unanswered by the God's, For a great story is about to unfold."</blockquote>
and (talking to the guy in the shop)
<blockquote>"You don't look like your from around here are you? Well I'll tell you the whole story. I've resided in this town for twelve years. I noticed a large influx of travelers passing through throughout the past few years. They were all looking for a shop to trade and resupply with so I decided to make this here shop. The town's called Ventalurok. We are a humble mining town based off of the old Lurok mine over there. If you go down there be sure to watch out for the zombies and gas pockets! Well hey, I've done enough talking. You come back here whenever you need to buy or sell something. The names Rindle by the way."</blockquote>
I'm trying to work out some more bits to add in. This is really just to see if you guys think what I just came up with is good or not. So here is what I want just working on.
(a mysterious letter found in the forest)
<blockquote>"The horrible things you have done cannot be undone. What happened is set in stone. The Gods will never forgive you for the suffering and pain that you have caused the world. You have been punished. This place is dreadful, though it may not seem it yet. You will soon discover many secrets lurking in this town. It's evil, this is your hell. Here you shall stay until the end of your days unless the Gods deem it fit to pardon your sins.
<p>Sincerely,<br>
Anonymous"</p>
</blockquote><br>
and
<blockquote>"While in the realm of Roalend, you were a humble man. A man with a great promise of becoming legendary. Your accomplishments were leading you on a divine path, you were to become a God. Whilst in a Church the fateful day that you were punished, you were given a proposition from a man of very strange sorts. He asked you to take from him, an amulet. This amulet, you had no knowledge of, however the man gave you fair warning. The man offered you 20,000 gold to take the amulet off of his hands. You took the Amulet of Destruction, not knowing the power it held. It was out of sheer greed that you took this amulet. This was your downfall. Like the downfall of all men, greed is a powerful thing. Now the Amulet of Destruction seemed to you an ordinary amulet, however once touched by a God or person on the divine path, it would unleash havoc upon the world. The moment the transaction occurred, the very moment the amulet touched your finger tips, all hope for the realm of Roalend was lost. Soon beasts came to ravage the land, beasts of great power, knowing only destruction. They went to every town, city, and settlement,  killing all in their path. The Gods, in this grave hour, brought you to their Council of the Divine. It was here that you were deemed unfit to be a God. As punishment  for the hell that you had unleashed upon Roalend, it seemed only fitting that you too would be placed in your own hell. As the meeting of the Council of the Divine came to a close, the Gods joined together is saying, "Rot in hell Lucifer!" and with that you were punished."</blockquote>
<p>I’m not much of a writer so tell me what you guys think of it.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 03:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-400962-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trying-to-figure-out-a-story-line-for-a-game/400962.rss">Trying to figure out a story line for a game</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
