<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462</link>
    <description>[center]This Is my first post on MoparScape :) I am &#39;Tricky&#39; from R-S. I hope you enjoy my project![/center]

[CENTER]
Please take 2 minutes to read below before you scroll down to the pictures.

So after a few days of thinking, I have decided to come back and give RSPS another go. Before I left I started a 508 project called Varrador. It seemed to be quite popular (not as popular as Gilenor 508) but was getting some recognition. It eventually turned to dust and I lost motivation with it all. Hopefully this time, things will be different!. 
I was hoping to see more 508&#39;s but sadly there are only a few good server projects running the 508 framework. I shall be releasing versions of &#39;Debug&#39; to the public in stages. This means when I create a new big update, I will upload the source to Rune-Server.

What Is my aim? Why am I doing this?

Many people have forgotten about 508&#39;s and how good they could potentially be. I am [B]not [/B]doing this for fame nor to show of my rubbish Java knowledge. I&#39;m only here to entertain everyone and give people ideas for there servers. I do this for fun and even when I get hate on this thread, It will not knock me down.

I code my own way. Everyone has there own way to code. Mine may not be the most neatest or smartest code, but It gets the job done!. I want people to learn from my Mistakes and also learn from some of my neater code. Life is a learning curve, We have to do something wrong in order to learn.

I will not be hosting this project to the public. Once I have completed my goals, the full source and client will be released and people can leech, host - do what ever they want with it :).

Without further ado, Lets get Into the fun stuff.

Skills

Cooking- Cooking Is near enough done. All fish are coded and there Is a chance that you can burn fish at a low level. I do however, need to add the correct Interfaces and string locations to get cooking near enough 100%.

Fletching - Fletching was the first skill I worked on. All logs are able to be cut but I have not started with Stringing, Arrows/Darts and crossbow stocks. I also need to add level requirements which Is a easy job. I have added the correct Interfaces but I cant seem to find the correct strings.

Summoning - This Is the skill I have worked most on. One of the best updates about 508 Is the Summoning skill so It needed to be detailed and Impressive. You are able to create pouches (With the correct Interfaces) and also able to create scrolls. You are also able to Summon your pouches but for some reason, familars don&#39;t follow at the moment. 

Other

Trading - Trading Is added but seems to cause some problems. I have added everything but the lend option, as well as offer x. These updates will come but they don&#39;t seem important at the moment.
Shop Handler - Shopping base has been added but there really Isn&#39;t any need to create any shops at the moment.
Banking- Bank tabs, Noting works. Deposit x is a little glitchy at the moment so I have removed it for the moment.
High Definition + Full Screen - All working nicely.
Level up- Leveling up interfaces have been updated with the correct text and skill icons. Also flashing skill when you level up has been added and greets you with the interface on what you have unlocked ect.
Cleaning up - I have cleaned up a lot of code in process. This has hopefully improved stability.
Items lost on death- Items Lost on death has been added as well as the Interface that shows what you are keeping and loosing.
Weapon Anims - All weapon special attacks and bonuses are added.


If you have read this far, Congratulations! :) Below Is the content I want to add next. I am not setting a time date, taking it as it comes :).
Future Content


Runecrafting - Runecrafting has got to be my favoruite skill. I want Runecrafting to be near enough perfect but will take me some time.
Fishing- Should be quite easy to add. 
Cooking- I want to finish off cooking by adding the Interfaces.
Woodcutting- Tree decaying and stuff like that Is annoying but It needs to be done

Duel Arena - I&#39;m not sure If I am going to add this yet or not. Seems like a waste of space.
Character Customization - I have a small base I started work on but need to add saving.
Player vs Monster - I need to add a strong base. Of course I cant make it 100% as it is virtually Impossible but I want it close. (I&#39;m a bit of a perfectionist)


These will be updated slowly but surely. 

Well, here Is some media so far. Remember to post your thoughts and I am always open for constructive criticism.

[spoiler]
Updates as off - 21/05/2015:

The updates you are about to read about are the best updates so far. I have gone through a lot of stress getting these bits of content to work and they are far off from completion.


[ul][B]Construction[/B]

Construction has been a very difficult skill to work with and has gotten very annoying. I have finally managed to create POH (Player owned houses) that save and you can actually build new objects.
I have configured witch Interfaces belong to each object, but I still need to add room creation. I have started work on gardens as this Is a fairly simple process as It is only creating a few global objects (Which the server can deal with) Its when I go to the more bigger rooms the server seems to struggle. I will eventually find a fix, but for now I am burnt out with construction.
[B]
Of course, as Construction Is still getting developed there are a few bugs. The bugs/glitches are as follows.[/B]

[*] Players can not leave their house via the &#39;Leave house&#39; Button.
[*] When players enter building mode, the button doesn&#39;t turn red.
[*] Players cant create rooms at the moment.
[*] Some Interfaces have black borders around them.

[B]Woodcutting[/B]
Alongside Construction, I have been creating a stable Woodcutting handler which I am now pleased to say Is &#39;Flawless&#39;. Of course, I still need to do the configuration, e.g, adding the correct tree stump ID&#39;s and exp rates ect ect.. Tree stumps are spawned as a GlobalObject when the tree is destroyed. The stumps take over the tree location and the tree spawns back quicker or slower depending what tree It is (I can set a custom delay If I want to). Normal trees are only able to produce the player 1 log (Just like Runescape) and the higher trees produce more logs which run on random calculations. 
[B]I am yet to create Bird&#39;s Nest droppings but It is next on my to do list.[/B][/ul]

[B]Here are the recent pictures. Remember to share this project around and lets get It some love!.[/B]

[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p1Fjzp85p][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/901/Fjzp85.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0IK7YyXp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/IK7YyX.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0tbRtIHp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/tbRtIH.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0rjWesgp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/rjWesg.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p1rWjZtEp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/901/rWjZtE.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eyPsZhPap][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/PsZhPa.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipAAqzWLp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/AAqzWL.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eyXpwyU1p][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/XpwyU1.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/idZDmfrjp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/661/ZDmfrj.png[/img][/URL]

[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipeG6ZS1p][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/eG6ZS1.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0Ux8BMyp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/Ux8BMy.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ex6Dp43vp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/537/6Dp43v.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/hl8xZAC9p][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/633/8xZAC9.png[/img][/URL][/spoiler]

[SPOILER=05/05/2015][URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipSL4JQkp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/SL4JQk.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/exUDZ09wp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/537/UDZ09w.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f02nedZ2p][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/2nedZ2.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/pcJIheQap][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/912/JIheQa.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0HUKPzAp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/HUKPzA.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/exRcPv88p][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/537/RcPv88.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p7eBH71Ip][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/907/eBH71I.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/paNCcOzxp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/910/NCcOzx.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p5bLz1iVp][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/905/bLz1iV.png[/img][/URL]
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipAXOxbop][IMG]http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/AXOxbo.png[/img][/URL][/SPOILER]

[SPOILER=09/05/2015 Updates:][CENTER]So the past day, I have made a lot of progress!. 

I have started on a Magic base which works on NPC&#39;s but I need to make MagicOnPlayer. The Magic On NPC Is still a little buggy but will get sorted soon.
MagicOnItem is very buggy and I am going to re-write this as soon as possible.
Range on NPC/Player is working. RangeOnNPC don&#39;t seem to like crossbows so I need to re code that. Some of your arrows also drop on the floor.
I worked on Dh effects. Low hp now makes you hit higher.
I have added all the correct animations to most weapons.
Skilling Interface level up now shows the correct skill when leveling up as well as the interface that shows what you can now make.
I added a really shit woodcutting handler. I will eventually re write this as It is so horrid.
I have also changed the spawn location to those who may want to know. :P

What I have removed

I have removed my Summoning handler as It was causing some weird bug when players create pouches. I will re write this probably tomorrow and make it much better.
I removed cooking for now as the handler I created was really shit.

What Next:

I need to add NPC agression and also give all NPC&#39;s there correct HP, Strength, Defense, Attack properties and also correct combat animations.
NPC Dialogue base.
RuneCrafting
Re-create Summoning
Re-create Cooking

[B]Here is some media for you guys! - Enjoy.[/B]


[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4714376/Level_Up_interfaces.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714376/Level_Up_interfaces.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4714378/more_level_up.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714378/more_level_up.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4714379/Range.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714379/Range.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4714381/Arrows_on_floor.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714381/Arrows_on_floor.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4714384/MagicOnNPC.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714384/MagicOnNPC.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4714387/PVP.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714387/PVP.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4714390/Dharocks.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714390/Dharocks.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4714392/AGS.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714392/AGS.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4714396/Mining.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714396/Mining.png[/img][/url][/CENTER][/SPOILER]


[SPOILER=10/05/2015][CENTER]10/05/2015

Here are a few more updates! There Is also a video to enjoy!.

Cooking updated: Now burns fish depending on your Cooking level!. The reason why It&#39;s only 95% Is because there Is no Interface at the moment.

[url=http://www.upload.ee/image/4716897/95__cooking.png][img]http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4716897/95__cooking.png[/img][/url]


NPC Dialogue + Clan Chat video! - Enjoy!
[video=youtube;Xq0Ok4SLjV4]https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xq0Ok4SLjV4[/video][/CENTER][/SPOILER]



[/CENTER]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 21:14:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DJ_Kool_Aid DJ_Kool_Aid]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dj_kool_aid">@DJ_Kool_Aid</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>damn baby…you smart.</p>
<p>You very smart.</p>
<p>Nah matter of fact you a genius…look baby u do whatchu need to do on the streets aight?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 21:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tricy Tricy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tricy">@Tricy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Updates as off - 21/05/2015:</p>
<p>The updates you are about to read about are the best updates so far. I have gone through a lot of stress getting these bits of content to work and they are far off from completion.</p>
<p>[ul][B]Construction[/B]<br>
Construction has been a very difficult skill to work with and has gotten very annoying. I have finally managed to create POH (Player owned houses) that save and you can actually build new objects.<br>
I have configured witch Interfaces belong to each object, but I still need to add room creation. I have started work on gardens as this Is a fairly simple process as It is only creating a few global objects (Which the server can deal with) Its when I go to the more bigger rooms the server seems to struggle. I will eventually find a fix, but for now I am burnt out with construction.<br>
[B]<br>
Of course, as Construction Is still getting developed there are a few bugs. The bugs/glitches are as follows.[/B]</p>
<p>[<em>] Players can not leave their house via the ‘Leave house’ Button.<br>
[</em>] When players enter building mode, the button doesn’t turn red.<br>
[<em>] Players cant create rooms at the moment.<br>
[</em>] Some Interfaces have black borders around them.</p>
<p>[B]Woodcutting[/B]<br>
Alongside Construction, I have been creating a stable Woodcutting handler which I am now pleased to say Is ‘Flawless’. Of course, I still need to do the configuration, e.g, adding the correct tree stump ID’s and exp rates ect ect… Tree stumps are spawned as a GlobalObject when the tree is destroyed. The stumps take over the tree location and the tree spawns back quicker or slower depending what tree It is (I can set a custom delay If I want to). Normal trees are only able to produce the player 1 log (Just like Runescape) and the higher trees produce more logs which run on random calculations.<br>
[B]I am yet to create Bird’s Nest droppings but It is next on my to do list.[/B]</p>
<p>[B]Here are the recent pictures. Remember to share this project around and lets get It some love!.[/B]</p>
<p>[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p1Fjzp85p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/901/Fjzp85.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0IK7YyXp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/IK7YyX.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0tbRtIHp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/tbRtIH.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0rjWesgp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/rjWesg.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p1rWjZtEp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/901/rWjZtE.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eyPsZhPap]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/PsZhPa.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipAAqzWLp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/AAqzWL.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eyXpwyU1p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/XpwyU1.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/idZDmfrjp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/661/ZDmfrj.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]</p>
<p>[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipeG6ZS1p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/eG6ZS1.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0Ux8BMyp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/Ux8BMy.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ex6Dp43vp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/537/6Dp43v.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/hl8xZAC9p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/633/8xZAC9.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL][/ul]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 13:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bl3nd Bl3nd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bl3nd">@Bl3nd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This looks really good!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 22:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tricy Tricy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tricy">@Tricy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thank’s for all the messages. Sorry I havent updated. I have been away working and working on the project along side. Anyway here is the recent project updates! Enjoy!</p>
<p>[SIZE=5][B]DEBUG - 508 REVISION[/B][/SIZE]</p>
<p>[COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#F0FFFF</span>"]It’s me! Tricky from Rune-Server, I will make sure I post about this new thread on my Tricky account so more people can know about the new Debug project.</p>
<p>Anyway, I have decided to start fresh with my 508 server. Start again, and this time do a lot of things differently and more efficient. There isn’t a specific reason why I wanted to start fresh, I just thought It was needed.<br>
I have started from a clean base and I am going to add even better content than I did last time.</p>
<p>Debug Is a 508 RuneScape Private Server running Dark Regen’s Palidino76 frame work. (A reworked version of Palidino76’s source). My aim is to create a fully playable source for people to download and enjoy If they wish. I am attempting to recreate RuneScape but with custom features a private server should have. I shall not be hosting this project, It’s only for educational purposes. Yes, some people have problems with Palidino76’s source but It isn’t their problem that I am using It to create my project.[/COLOR]</p>
<p>I will improve the layout of this post when I am back from work. but for now enjoy.</p>
<p>[B][COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FFFFFF</span>"]Developers:[/COLOR][/B]</p>
<p>[ul][COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FFFF</span>"][*]Dbug[/COLOR][/ul]</p>
<p>[COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#F0FFFF</span>"]Skill Progression[/COLOR]<br>
I have only worked on Fletching/Fishing &amp; Cooking.</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Fletching]<br>
[B][U][CENTER][COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#F0FFFF</span>"]Fletching[/COLOR][/CENTER][/U][/B]</p>
<p>[ul][<em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]Interfaces[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]All Interfaces are correctly configured.[/COLOR]<br>
[</em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FFA500</span>"]Bow Stringing[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]All (u) bows are able to be strung[/COLOR]. [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]The stringing animation doesn’t show the correct bow.[/COLOR]<br>
[<em>][COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FFA500</span>"] Log/Crossbow Cutting[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FFA500</span>"]Almost all logs are able to be cut. Just finishing off a few things.[/COLOR]<br>
[</em>][COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FFA500</span>"] Bolt making[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FFA500</span>"]All bolts are makeable, Just need to add opal tips ect.[/COLOR]<br>
[<em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Crossbow Stringing[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Haven’t started work on this yet.[/COLOR]<br>
[</em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Jade Cutting[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Haven’t started on this yet.[/COLOR]<br>
[<em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Messages[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Still needs to be constructed In the Fletching class.[/COLOR]<br>
[</em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]Skill level requirements[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]All level requirements has been added[/COLOR][/ul]</p>
<p>[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Cooking]<br>
[B][U][CENTER][COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#800080</span>"]Cooking[/COLOR][/CENTER][/U][/B]</p>
<p>[ul][<em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Interfaces[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Haven’t worked on this yet.[/COLOR]<br>
[</em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]Cooking Fish[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]All fish can be cooked[/COLOR]<br>
[<em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Other cook-able food[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Haven’t worked on this yet.[/COLOR]<br>
[</em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FFA500</span>"]Burning Fish[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FFA500</span>"]Structure added, Need to add the skill based calculation.[/COLOR]<br>
[*] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Purpose Burning[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Haven’t worked on this yet.[/COLOR][/ul]</p>
<p>[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Fishing]<br>
[B][U][CENTER][COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#800080</span>"]Fishing[/COLOR][/CENTER][/U][/B]</p>
<p>[ul][<em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]All fish[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]All fish is able to be caught. Including Fly fishing.[/COLOR]<br>
[</em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]Multi Catching[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]When you reach certain level’s, you can catch 2 different fish. ie, Shrimps &amp; Anchovies, Swordfish &amp; Tuna.[/COLOR]<br>
[<em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]Fishing Timers[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#00FF00</span>"]Fishing Timers based on your level.[/COLOR]<br>
[</em>] [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]De-spawning Fishing spots[/COLOR] - [COLOR="<span class="hashtag">#FF0000</span>"]Haven’t worked on this[/COLOR][/ul]</p>
<p>[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>To view the recent progress, click the spoilers below. I shall not be updating the above.</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Updates as of: 18/05/15]<br>
Update’s as of 18/05/2015.</p>
<p>Here are a few updated pictures of the progress .</p>
<p>[ul][<em>] NPC Dialogue has been added (With player Dialogue).<br>
[</em>] Continuous chat has also been added with the Dialogue system. Quests can now be made.<br>
[*] Dialogue choice text has been setup. You can now choose what you want your player to say from the options to the NPC.</p>
<p>[<em>] Added the Level up Interfaces. I now need to work on the flashing Icon.<br>
[</em>] Combat now calculates Summoning. 138 combat Is now max combat.<br>
[<em>] Started working on Magic. - I have only started working on the Interfaces.<br>
[</em>] I have finished bone burying. - There Is a delay when you dig a hole In the ground, and then bury the bone.<br>
[<em>] I started work on Prayer Icons.<br>
[</em>] A small Woodcutting base has been added. - Trees are not deleting at the moment.[/ul]</p>
<p>Pictures:</p>
<p>[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/hlwQKhkmp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/633/wQKhkm.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eymB7uoIp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/mB7uoI.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p9iTyTAEp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/909/iTyTAE.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/idoo4EJep]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/661/oo4EJe.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f09TC4gCp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/9TC4gC.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/pc2BmW4Gp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/912/2BmW4G.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p8TDKqN4p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/908/TDKqN4.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ip1ZC515p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/1ZC515.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/id6djs0Yp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/661/6djs0Y.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/pduR04q8p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/913/uR04q8.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0j6ZHYMp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/j6ZHYM.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/idMYaRcOp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/661/MYaRcO.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]</p>
<p>More updates tomorrow. Hopefully I can keep these amount of updates each day. :)[/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Updates as of - 20/05/2015:]<br>
Here are a few screenshots: - I have to get of to work, so the Images are not arranged properly and some are missing. I will add more media on today’s updates later on this evening.</p>
<p>[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/idUtAS6up]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/661/UtAS6u.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/idy1IPxYp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/661/y1IPxY.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ey1lFJQ3p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/1lFJQ3.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0WYQqDxp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/WYQqDx.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p9GcxcFyp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/909/GcxcFy.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ip4zvTr5p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/4zvTr5.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/pdkmxB7lp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/913/kmxB7l.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p9lrrqSPp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/909/lrrqSP.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p1jKoYYvp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/901/jKoYYv.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p9iyA76Qp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/909/iyA76Q.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL][/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=Fletching + Banking + Clanchat Pictures][URL=https://imageshack.com/i/idj3VFSXp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/661/j3VFSX.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p8NTauE6p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/908/NTauE6.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]</p>
<p>[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0B1bLqFp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/B1bLqF.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]</p>
<p>[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eyzSFFBrp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/zSFFBr.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ey0pzfnNp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/0pzfnN.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/hlBBza6np]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/633/BBza6n.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/pbPqhfbrp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/911/Pqhfbr.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p8QmzB2Np]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/908/QmzB2N.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eyVi2tHqp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/Vi2tHq.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipxbMDMEp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/xbMDME.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p7yEsVWZp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/907/yEsVWZ.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eyodAE86p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/odAE86.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL][/SPOILER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 21:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have to ask, why have you decided to not host this publicly? I assumed it was because of school, work, etc., makes sense but it’s a shame still.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 22:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DemonWars DemonWars]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/demonwars">@DemonWars</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Great to see some 508 development!<br>
~DemonWars</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 18:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tricy Tricy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tricy">@Tricy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="551462">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/tinyscape/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> TinyScape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I wish you luck with the project.[/quote][quote=“Soulcist, post:3, topic:551462”]I personally have always liked the 508 era of RuneScape (it didn’t seem that complicated to me at least). And this is bringing that back, I like this. I hope to see a near to finish if not a finished product in the future, I wish for the best of luck![/quote][quote=“g0d of war1, post:2, topic:551462”]It seems like you are committed to your project, curious what base you use if you dont mind me asking? love the 508s rev nonetheless, goodluck!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> be sure to keep updated!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 06:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tinyscape TinyScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tinyscape">@tinyscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wish you luck with the project.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 21:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I personally have always liked the 508 era of RuneScape (it didn’t seem that complicated to me at least). And this is bringing that back, I like this. I hope to see a near to finish if not a finished product in the future, I wish for the best of luck!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 21:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@g0d_of_war1 g0d of war1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/g0d_of_war1">@g0d_of_war1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It seems like you are committed to your project, curious what base you use if you dont mind me asking? love the 508s rev nonetheless, goodluck!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 21:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tricy Tricy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tricy">@Tricy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]This Is my first post on MoparScape <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I am ‘Tricky’ from R-S. I hope you enjoy my project![/center]</p>
<p>[CENTER]<br>
Please take 2 minutes to read below before you scroll down to the pictures.</p>
<p>So after a few days of thinking, I have decided to come back and give RSPS another go. Before I left I started a 508 project called Varrador. It seemed to be quite popular (not as popular as Gilenor 508) but was getting some recognition. It eventually turned to dust and I lost motivation with it all. Hopefully this time, things will be different!.<br>
I was hoping to see more 508’s but sadly there are only a few good server projects running the 508 framework. I shall be releasing versions of ‘Debug’ to the public in stages. This means when I create a new big update, I will upload the source to Rune-Server.</p>
<p>What Is my aim? Why am I doing this?</p>
<p>Many people have forgotten about 508’s and how good they could potentially be. I am [B]not [/B]doing this for fame nor to show of my rubbish Java knowledge. I’m only here to entertain everyone and give people ideas for there servers. I do this for fun and even when I get hate on this thread, It will not knock me down.</p>
<p>I code my own way. Everyone has there own way to code. Mine may not be the most neatest or smartest code, but It gets the job done!. I want people to learn from my Mistakes and also learn from some of my neater code. Life is a learning curve, We have to do something wrong in order to learn.</p>
<p>I will not be hosting this project to the public. Once I have completed my goals, the full source and client will be released and people can leech, host - do what ever they want with it :).</p>
<p>Without further ado, Lets get Into the fun stuff.</p>
<p>Skills</p>
<p>Cooking- Cooking Is near enough done. All fish are coded and there Is a chance that you can burn fish at a low level. I do however, need to add the correct Interfaces and string locations to get cooking near enough 100%.</p>
<p>Fletching - Fletching was the first skill I worked on. All logs are able to be cut but I have not started with Stringing, Arrows/Darts and crossbow stocks. I also need to add level requirements which Is a easy job. I have added the correct Interfaces but I cant seem to find the correct strings.</p>
<p>Summoning - This Is the skill I have worked most on. One of the best updates about 508 Is the Summoning skill so It needed to be detailed and Impressive. You are able to create pouches (With the correct Interfaces) and also able to create scrolls. You are also able to Summon your pouches but for some reason, familars don’t follow at the moment.</p>
<p>Other</p>
<p>Trading - Trading Is added but seems to cause some problems. I have added everything but the lend option, as well as offer x. These updates will come but they don’t seem important at the moment.<br>
Shop Handler - Shopping base has been added but there really Isn’t any need to create any shops at the moment.<br>
Banking- Bank tabs, Noting works. Deposit x is a little glitchy at the moment so I have removed it for the moment.<br>
High Definition + Full Screen - All working nicely.<br>
Level up- Leveling up interfaces have been updated with the correct text and skill icons. Also flashing skill when you level up has been added and greets you with the interface on what you have unlocked ect.<br>
Cleaning up - I have cleaned up a lot of code in process. This has hopefully improved stability.<br>
Items lost on death- Items Lost on death has been added as well as the Interface that shows what you are keeping and loosing.<br>
Weapon Anims - All weapon special attacks and bonuses are added.</p>
<p>If you have read this far, Congratulations! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Below Is the content I want to add next. I am not setting a time date, taking it as it comes :).<br>
Future Content</p>
<p>Runecrafting - Runecrafting has got to be my favoruite skill. I want Runecrafting to be near enough perfect but will take me some time.<br>
Fishing- Should be quite easy to add.<br>
Cooking- I want to finish off cooking by adding the Interfaces.<br>
Woodcutting- Tree decaying and stuff like that Is annoying but It needs to be done</p>
<p>Duel Arena - I’m not sure If I am going to add this yet or not. Seems like a waste of space.<br>
Character Customization - I have a small base I started work on but need to add saving.<br>
Player vs Monster - I need to add a strong base. Of course I cant make it 100% as it is virtually Impossible but I want it close. (I’m a bit of a perfectionist)</p>
<p>These will be updated slowly but surely.</p>
<p>Well, here Is some media so far. Remember to post your thoughts and I am always open for constructive criticism.</p>
<p>[spoiler]<br>
Updates as off - 21/05/2015:</p>
<p>The updates you are about to read about are the best updates so far. I have gone through a lot of stress getting these bits of content to work and they are far off from completion.</p>
<p>[ul][B]Construction[/B]</p>
<p>Construction has been a very difficult skill to work with and has gotten very annoying. I have finally managed to create POH (Player owned houses) that save and you can actually build new objects.<br>
I have configured witch Interfaces belong to each object, but I still need to add room creation. I have started work on gardens as this Is a fairly simple process as It is only creating a few global objects (Which the server can deal with) Its when I go to the more bigger rooms the server seems to struggle. I will eventually find a fix, but for now I am burnt out with construction.<br>
[B]<br>
Of course, as Construction Is still getting developed there are a few bugs. The bugs/glitches are as follows.[/B]</p>
<p>[<em>] Players can not leave their house via the ‘Leave house’ Button.<br>
[</em>] When players enter building mode, the button doesn’t turn red.<br>
[<em>] Players cant create rooms at the moment.<br>
[</em>] Some Interfaces have black borders around them.</p>
<p>[B]Woodcutting[/B]<br>
Alongside Construction, I have been creating a stable Woodcutting handler which I am now pleased to say Is ‘Flawless’. Of course, I still need to do the configuration, e.g, adding the correct tree stump ID’s and exp rates ect ect… Tree stumps are spawned as a GlobalObject when the tree is destroyed. The stumps take over the tree location and the tree spawns back quicker or slower depending what tree It is (I can set a custom delay If I want to). Normal trees are only able to produce the player 1 log (Just like Runescape) and the higher trees produce more logs which run on random calculations.<br>
[B]I am yet to create Bird’s Nest droppings but It is next on my to do list.[/B][/ul]</p>
<p>[B]Here are the recent pictures. Remember to share this project around and lets get It some love!.[/B]</p>
<p>[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p1Fjzp85p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/901/Fjzp85.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0IK7YyXp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/IK7YyX.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0tbRtIHp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/tbRtIH.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0rjWesgp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/rjWesg.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p1rWjZtEp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/901/rWjZtE.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eyPsZhPap]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/PsZhPa.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipAAqzWLp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/AAqzWL.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/eyXpwyU1p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/538/XpwyU1.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/idZDmfrjp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/661/ZDmfrj.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]</p>
<p>[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipeG6ZS1p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/eG6ZS1.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0Ux8BMyp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/Ux8BMy.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ex6Dp43vp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/537/6Dp43v.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/hl8xZAC9p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/633/8xZAC9.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL][/spoiler]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=05/05/2015][URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipSL4JQkp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/SL4JQk.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/exUDZ09wp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/537/UDZ09w.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f02nedZ2p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/2nedZ2.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/pcJIheQap]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/912/JIheQa.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/f0HUKPzAp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/540/HUKPzA.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/exRcPv88p]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/537/RcPv88.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p7eBH71Ip]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/907/eBH71I.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/paNCcOzxp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/910/NCcOzx.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/p5bLz1iVp]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/905/bLz1iV.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL]<br>
[URL=https://imageshack.com/i/ipAXOxbop]<img src="http://imagizer.imageshack.us/v2/xq90/673/AXOxbo.png" alt width="" height="">[/URL][/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=09/05/2015 Updates:][CENTER]So the past day, I have made a lot of progress!.</p>
<p>I have started on a Magic base which works on NPC’s but I need to make MagicOnPlayer. The Magic On NPC Is still a little buggy but will get sorted soon.<br>
MagicOnItem is very buggy and I am going to re-write this as soon as possible.<br>
Range on NPC/Player is working. RangeOnNPC don’t seem to like crossbows so I need to re code that. Some of your arrows also drop on the floor.<br>
I worked on Dh effects. Low hp now makes you hit higher.<br>
I have added all the correct animations to most weapons.<br>
Skilling Interface level up now shows the correct skill when leveling up as well as the interface that shows what you can now make.<br>
I added a really shit woodcutting handler. I will eventually re write this as It is so horrid.<br>
I have also changed the spawn location to those who may want to know. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>What I have removed</p>
<p>I have removed my Summoning handler as It was causing some weird bug when players create pouches. I will re write this probably tomorrow and make it much better.<br>
I removed cooking for now as the handler I created was really shit.</p>
<p>What Next:</p>
<p>I need to add NPC agression and also give all NPC’s there correct HP, Strength, Defense, Attack properties and also correct combat animations.<br>
NPC Dialogue base.<br>
RuneCrafting<br>
Re-create Summoning<br>
Re-create Cooking</p>
<p>[B]Here is some media for you guys! - Enjoy.[/B]</p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4714376/Level_Up_interfaces.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714376/Level_Up_interfaces.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4714378/more_level_up.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714378/more_level_up.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4714379/Range.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714379/Range.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4714381/Arrows_on_floor.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714381/Arrows_on_floor.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4714384/MagicOnNPC.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714384/MagicOnNPC.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4714387/PVP.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714387/PVP.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4714390/Dharocks.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714390/Dharocks.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4714392/AGS.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714392/AGS.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4714396/Mining.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4714396/Mining.png" alt width="" height=""></a>[/CENTER][/SPOILER]</p>
<p>[SPOILER=10/05/2015][CENTER]10/05/2015</p>
<p>Here are a few more updates! There Is also a video to enjoy!.</p>
<p>Cooking updated: Now burns fish depending on your Cooking level!. The reason why It’s only 95% Is because there Is no Interface at the moment.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.upload.ee/image/4716897/95__cooking.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.upload.ee/thumb/4716897/95__cooking.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>NPC Dialogue + Clan Chat video! - Enjoy!<br>
[video=youtube;Xq0Ok4SLjV4]<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xq0Ok4SLjV4%5B/video%5D%5B/CENTER%5D%5B/SPOILER%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xq0Ok4SLjV4[/video][/CENTER][/SPOILER]</a></p>
<p>[/CENTER]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 19:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551462-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/debug-508-a-new-508-project/551462.rss">Debug 508 - A New 508 Project</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
