<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Internal or external error</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/internal-or-external-error/244883</link>
    <description>Once again... I&#39;m here about the internal and external.. error.... When i click runserver it comes up with a box and closes so quickly. that  i gotta print screen what it says in the box.in the box it says[code]&#39;java&#39; is not recoginzed as an internal or external command, operable program or  batch file.[/code] All i no that it is most probaly that the classpaths are incorrect.. rite.. this is what my clathpass and path exactly says in the input box so rite i click environment variables then theres 2 boxes 1 at the top and 1 at the bottom ... now i clik edit the very bottom edit and choose class path and says [code]CLASSPATH=C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_07\bin;%CLASSPATH%;[/code]
I then cancel that and click on path and click edit at the bottom and it says 
[code]C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_07\bin;[/code] if any of the paths are rong plz tell me... or anything please[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 18, 2008, 10:32:25 am[/size][hr]GIVIN ADMIN/Modship who ever helps##@@@</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 16:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/internal-or-external-error/244883.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Internal or external error</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kalvin Kalvin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kalvin">@Kalvin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Once again… I’m here about the internal and external… error… When i click runserver it comes up with a box and closes so quickly. that  i gotta print screen what it says in the box.in the box it says<code>'java' is not recoginzed as an internal or external command, operable program or  batch file.</code> All i no that it is most probaly that the classpaths are incorrect… rite… this is what my clathpass and path exactly says in the input box so rite i click environment variables then theres 2 boxes 1 at the top and 1 at the bottom … now i clik edit the very bottom edit and choose class path and says <code>CLASSPATH=C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_07\bin;%CLASSPATH%;</code><br>
I then cancel that and click on path and click edit at the bottom and it says</p>
<p><code>C:\Program Files\Java\jdk1.6.0_07\bin;</code> if any of the paths are rong plz tell me… or anything please[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 18, 2008, 10:32:25 am[/size][hr]GIVIN ADMIN/Modship who ever helps##@@@</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/internal-or-external-error/244883/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/internal-or-external-error/244883/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 16:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-244883-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/internal-or-external-error/244883.rss">Internal or external error</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
