<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Society</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153</link>
    <description>What do you guys think of society nowadays? Stable, unstable, broken?

Personally in my opinion I think society was built and designed to be broken. The bullshit that the media and hollywood feeds us.

Discuss.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 17:34:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Normal employees (Let us forget non-working people for a moment) do all the hard work, they would never get as rich as those hiring them. It doesn't matter how hard you work, you must over to the "evil side". The only way to get rich is to be lucky or make other people work for you. As an capitalist you would get the surplus value of what your employees produce. The only way to get rich is to pay your workers less than the value they create. The entitled one is the rich capitalists. So if you think the big problem with society is people demanding money from others, abolish capitalism.</blockquote>
<p>Your picture looks more like feudalism than capitalism. Feudalism makes it impossible to move up in class. Capitalism is easier.</p>
<blockquote>Normal employees (Let us forget non-working people for a moment) do all the hard work, they would never get as rich as those hiring them. It doesn't matter how hard you work, you must over to the "evil side".</blockquote>
<p>The “evil side”? The people who make more money than their employees? I don’t understand how that is evil. Normal employees do get paid more depending on how hard they work. They won’t become a millionaire (as I have already established numerous times) but they will move up in the middle class as t4 stated: upper middle, middle, and lower middle class. They won’t be super duper insane rich as you want them to be, but they will be making good money.</p>
<blockquote>The only way to get rich is to be lucky or make other people work for you. As an capitalist you would get the surplus value of what your employees produce. The only way to get rich is to pay your workers less than the value they create.</blockquote>
<p>Well first I would like to say: Luck is where preparation meets opportunity. And yes, as the owner of a business you will make more than the employee because you own the business, it was your idea and you put the money into the business. An employer can choose to pay his employees more money if he likes their performance. Many employers have it written into their employee’s contracts that they will get a 5% pay raise each year. I would also like to point out that you make it seem as though employers don’t do anything. Most employers do actually work and earn their salary. Paying workers less value than they create? Is this evil? It’s called making a profit. A smart employer pays his workers enough to keep them. If the employer isn’t paying enough the employee will either leave or another competitive company will snatch him up to earn them money.</p>
<blockquote>PS: Is this thread still on track?</blockquote>
<p>I think so <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/56</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@T41 t4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/t41">@T41</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i don’t think that picture is accurate… the way i see it:</p>
<p>the upper class has the most wealth and it is almost impossible to transcend to this status unless luck/inheritance/evil are used.</p>
<p>the middle class is divided into upper/middle/lower; upper being the rich with a net worth of a few million, middle being the average white collar worker, and lower being the low-paying white collar/high-paying blue collar. going up through these classes usually entails higher education/luck.</p>
<p>the lower class is obviously anyone who falls below the high-paying blue collar mark.</p>
<p>depending on the area, the majority of the people who inhabit are most likely of the lower class or lower-middle/middle middle class.</p>
<p>edit: to make it clear, the upper class has pretty much all the power in a capitalist society/corrupt government. there is also a HUGE gap between upper-class and upper-middle class.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/55</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 15:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>M1lkman:<br>
One picture says 1000 words:</p>
<p><img src="http://r%C3%B8dungdom.no/image/klassepyramiden.jpeg?w=580&amp;h=400" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>Normal employees (Let us forget non-working people for a moment) do all the hard work, they would never get as rich as those hiring them. It doesn’t matter how hard you work, you must over to the “evil side”. The only way to get rich is to be lucky or make other people work for you. As an capitalist you would get the surplus value of what your employees produce. The only way to get rich is to pay your workers less than the value they create. The entitled one is the rich capitalists. So if you think the big problem with society is people demanding money from others, abolish capitalism.</p>
<p>PS: Is this thread still on track?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/54</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 14:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-54</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:52, topic:447153”][quote author=ytuio9` link=topic=550051.msg4035002#msg4035002 date=1341114399]<br>
So by your reasoning scientists should not be paid as much as a miner because they do not physically use their bodies as much as miners do?<br>
[/quote]<br>
M1lkman’s reasoning. If hard work should pay off, then it should be like that.</p>
<p>But it doesn’t do that, you can work as much as you want, but you would never be as rich as the capitalists. Since there is a limited amount of people can be capitalists, then it would always be someone with little economic power and people with waste amount of economic power, In US this have lead to the abolishment of the democracy. (If they ever had one)</p>
<p>The media and those who advertise, is those who decide the elections. They decide what message your hear and what to see, and they decide how to report the news stories. Take the health care reform. 95% said it was unconstitutional in a Fox News poll, and 90% said it was constitutional in a more liberal audience. It is a bad sign when the News corporations reject the reality and substitute it with their own mindset. Because something is wrong when your interpretation of the constitution is depended of your “ideology”.<br>
(The exact numbers isn’t as important, and might be slightly incorrect)</p>
<p>Your ability to lobbying in US is too small to have any effect. If you are rich you could buy some politicians if you want. It doesn’t matter who you vote for when both candidates are bought by the same people. This does not only apply to the political world. As neither the politicians nor the people is controlling the economy. Americans are letting a small non-elected elite control the most important in their country.</p>
<p>Or is it OK in a society that someone has more power than other, based on luck, exploiting and inheritance?[/quote]</p>
<p>I think you are twisting my words. You said I said </p><blockquote>hard work should pay off</blockquote>. Hard work DOES payoff in today’s capitalistic society. You make it seem as though it doesn’t.
<p>The problem is everyone wants to be a millionaire but nobody wants to work to become a millionaire. The people in poverty EXPECT the government to come through with welfare, food stamps, etc. The government should provide the minimum to stay alive but then people think, “Oh, look at this person who has millions of dollars. Why can’t I be that rich? It isn’t fair!”. Then people think they are entitled to get a television set, cable, internet, and a cell phone. The rich are getting richer and the poor are getting richer too. The people who are homeless CHOSE to be homeless. I have asked a group of homeless people why they are homeless and most of them said they didn’t think they needed to pay taxes so the best way of avoiding taxes is to be homeless. They think the rich should pay the taxes for them. I then asked if they were happy being homeless. Most said yes, they have the money from pan handling to buy a case of beer every night, a group of people they can call a family, and no government breathing down their neck. Do you think these people deserve that kind of lifestyle? They are living like reckless teenagers. They don’t work hard but they feel they are entitled to everything everyone else is getting.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/53</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 12:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-53</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="51" data-topic="447153">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ytuio9`:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>So by your reasoning scientists should not be paid as much as a miner because they do not physically use their bodies as much as miners do?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>M1lkman’s reasoning. If hard work should pay off, then it should be like that.</p>
<p>But it doesn’t do that, you can work as much as you want, but you would never be as rich as the capitalists. Since there is a limited amount of people can be capitalists, then it would always be someone with little economic power and people with waste amount of economic power, In US this have lead to the abolishment of the democracy. (If they ever had one)</p>
<p>The media and those who advertise, is those who decide the elections. They decide what message your hear and what to see, and they decide how to report the news stories. Take the health care reform. 95% said it was unconstitutional in a Fox News poll, and 90% said it was constitutional in a more liberal audience. It is a bad sign when the News corporations reject the reality and substitute it with their own mindset. Because something is wrong when your interpretation of the constitution is depended of your “ideology”.<br>
(The exact numbers isn’t as important, and might be slightly incorrect)</p>
<p>Your ability to lobbying in US is too small to have any effect. If you are rich you could buy some politicians if you want. It doesn’t matter who you vote for when both candidates are bought by the same people. This does not only apply to the political world. As neither the politicians nor the people is controlling the economy. Americans are letting a small non-elected elite control the most important in their country.</p>
<p>Or is it OK in a society that someone has more power than other, based on luck, exploiting and inheritance?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 10:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So by your reasoning scientists should not be paid as much as a miner because they do not physically use their bodies as much as miners do?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 03:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>By my model you would get money by studying, as that is also a part of your tasks to be a manager or any other job requiring education. With such a system, long education wouldn’t be an argument anymore, as you got money for it. Electing the leadership would do away with all the bad things, as the selection of management would be as much racist/sexist as the workers. Nobody would work under bad leadership, so you would make sure that people elected the right man/woman.</p>
<p>So you could choose, do you want a job where you don’t need to use to much of your body and earn less, or would you get higher wages and really do a hard job.</p>
<p>You said hard work should pay off, and my model would make sure that happened. Capitalism doesn’t make that happen, as the way to get rich there is to exploit you workers, not hard work. (Left-wingers define “exploit” a bit different than others in this context).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 21:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:46, topic:447153”][quote author=m1lkman link=topic=550051.msg4034467#msg4034467 date=1341079436]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>You’re clearly fucking retarded. People are poor because the rich people have society built where the rich people stay rich, the middle class do all the work, and the poor people stay poor. The rockerfeller family has enough money to feed, shelter, and cloth the whole world. Greedy fucking bastards.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This pisses me off. People bitch and moan because they would rather receive a handout than work hard. That is the cancer that is killing society. Not greed or wealth but the idea of entitlements.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Good that we agree, we should abolish inheritance and gifts above a certain value. Lets us give higher wages to people who work hard, like miners. And give lower wages to those who only tell other people what to do. I think your idea works perfectly to a certain degree.</p>
<p>Wage = Hours * Hard Work Index * CONSTANT.<br>
Hard Work index for average job is at 100, and then modify it by how much harder your job (By a percentage) is compared to the average.<br>
The constant is the same for everyone, and is modified when you want to modify the wage level. And yes, abolish all gambling, as that has nothing to do with hard work. (Gabling like in betting on the Stock Exchange)</p>
<p>I’m not sure how smart this is, but this is how it should be according to your hard work mindset.[/quote]</p>
<p>No. The money is in managing. The way I view it: Everyone can be a miner; not everyone can manage a group of people. Hence the manager earns more money. The manager (normally) has more experience mining and was indeed a miner. Managers normally have gone to school or have shown exceptional work ethic - hence why they have been promoted among the other miners. I say normally so often because there are some who shouldn’t be in management and are only there because of nepotism, racism, or sexism. &lt;— Those should be abolished first.</p>
<p>There is money in hard labor jobs. Plumbers, one who goes to houses and fixes peoples’ plumbing, make more money than a help desk assistant, one who answers questions and fixes peoples computer from the office.</p>
<p>I’m not sure I agree with the abolishment of inheritance (Parent to child). I could be persuaded :P.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 21:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No, what’s killing society is greed, corruption, and ignorance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 20:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:46, topic:447153”][quote author=m1lkman link=topic=550051.msg4034467#msg4034467 date=1341079436]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>You’re clearly fucking retarded. People are poor because the rich people have society built where the rich people stay rich, the middle class do all the work, and the poor people stay poor. The rockerfeller family has enough money to feed, shelter, and cloth the whole world. Greedy fucking bastards.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This pisses me off. People bitch and moan because they would rather receive a handout than work hard. That is the cancer that is killing society. Not greed or wealth but the idea of entitlements.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Lets us give higher wages to people who work hard, like miners. And give lower wages to those who only tell other people what to do.[/quote]</p>
<p>No, that is stupid. Those people (Managers usually) do a lot more then just that. I don’t know any job that ONLY tells other people what to do. Oh, and lets just give miners, who most of the time haven’t gone/finished college or even high school a pay raise.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 18:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“m1lkman, post:45, topic:447153”][quote author=Clawz fury link=topic=550051.msg4033912#msg4033912 date=1341020945]<br>
You’re clearly fucking retarded. People are poor because the rich people have society built where the rich people stay rich, the middle class do all the work, and the poor people stay poor. The rockerfeller family has enough money to feed, shelter, and cloth the whole world. Greedy fucking bastards.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>This pisses me off. People bitch and moan because they would rather receive a handout than work hard. That is the cancer that is killing society. Not greed or wealth but the idea of entitlements.[/quote]<br>
Good that we agree, we should abolish inheritance and gifts above a certain value. Lets us give higher wages to people who work hard, like miners. And give lower wages to those who only tell other people what to do. I think your idea works perfectly to a certain degree.</p>
<p>Wage = Hours * Hard Work Index * CONSTANT.<br>
Hard Work index for average job is at 100, and then modify it by how much harder your job (By a percentage) is compared to the average.<br>
The constant is the same for everyone, and is modified when you want to modify the wage level. And yes, abolish all gambling, as that has nothing to do with hard work. (Gabling like in betting on the Stock Exchange)</p>
<p>I’m not sure how smart this is, but this is how it should be according to your hard work mindset.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 18:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="41" data-topic="447153">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Clawz fury:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re clearly fucking retarded. People are poor because the rich people have society built where the rich people stay rich, the middle class do all the work, and the poor people stay poor. The rockerfeller family has enough money to feed, shelter, and cloth the whole world. Greedy fucking bastards.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This pisses me off. People bitch and moan because they would rather receive a handout than work hard. That is the cancer that is killing society. Not greed or wealth but the idea of entitlements.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 18:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Unleashed <span class="bbcode-s">Revolution</span>: We can’t go against the system alone, we need to inform people. The other problem is that people seems to accept the system, as long as it isn’t too bad. It wasn’t before the food crisis in France and Russian Empire that the people turned against the state.</p>
<p>Again forget US and Europe, our system is causing problems in the rest of the world. US wouldn’t go into Iraq if they weren’t capitalistic bastards. We wouldn’t have 9 million  people dying of food if we had a non egoistic system. Over 1 billion people would be hungry if we didn’t exploit the 3. world. In many places it is more  profitable to grow stuff for the third world, than it is to produce food for the population.</p>
<p>The buttrape of Libya was also all about the oil, I don’t have specific numbers on it, but the Norwegian bombing of Libya was profitable. Capitalism KILLS. So tell me, how can people in Africa and the Middle east go against our system? If they do, they get a visit from a US drone.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 09:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Acorn1 Acorn_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/acorn1">@Acorn1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>amen nigga.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 03:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unleashed_Revolution Unleashed Revolution]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unleashed_revolution">@Unleashed_Revolution</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Clawz fury, post:41, topic:447153”][quote author=Unleashed Revolution link=topic=550051.msg4033471#msg4033471 date=1340987867]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>MistaBigBoss: The poor people cares. Forget about us, if you can write on this forum you are among the most privileged on this earth. Think about the people doing close to slave labour, people who cannot afford food, and those who suffers because of US/NATO’s imperialist wars.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then make something out of your situation? I’m sorry that you might be piss poor because of your parent’s inability to do whatever. Your trying to blame the rich because of <span class="bbcode-b">your</span> issues, not theirs. Why would they honestly care? What would you want to define society? Everyone is not needed for a society to work. That should be obvious to see with how things have and always ran. Money will always be the thing that defines every aspect of your life. If you don’t have it? <span class="bbcode-i">Okay, do something about it.</span> It isn’t like you are in a trapped situation where there is no possibilities.  People are born with a lot more then you? Okay, so it’s cool to put all our burdens on them because they certainty had a choice in that?</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>what else would define the world except money? intelligence? herp that wouldn’t last long</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<ol>
<li>Remove “Revolution” from your username.</li>
<li>When you realize that everyone is as important for the society to work, you would see that the discrimination must stop. We need to find other things to do than feeding of others misfortune and exploit people. We should all be well of because we are all humans contributing to the society. Why should some people have power just because they were lucky and/or inherited a lot of money?<br>
[/quote]You’re a communist. If it were up to you, no one would have freedom and everyone would be controlled by the government. I don’t like that idea.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Communism was actually supposed to be a world of perfection, so I dont see your point here</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lets try and be serious. The idea of communism ever being ‘perfect’ is slim to none.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You’re clearly fucking retarded. People are poor because the rich people have society built where the rich people stay rich, the middle class do all the work, and the poor people stay poor. The rockerfeller family has enough money to feed, shelter, and cloth the whole world. Greedy fucking bastards.[/quote]<br>
Again, money defines every aspect of your life. Don’t like it? Do something about it. Why should they go out of their way to support some stranger like you or me? Do you give random hand outs to homeless people?  Probably not. If you don’t like how the system is setup then go against it. A poor person can inevitably become rich through hard work, just like a rich person can become poor by shitty choices. Your just like the many other people who blame the ‘bastards’ simply because they have it better. Be realistic instead of bitching and moaning about how fucked you think everything is.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 02:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Clawz_fury lare69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/clawz_fury">@Clawz_fury</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Unleashed Revolution, post:31, topic:447153”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=550051.msg4033417#msg4033417 date=1340983518]<br>
MistaBigBoss: The poor people cares. Forget about us, if you can write on this forum you are among the most privileged on this earth. Think about the people doing close to slave labour, people who cannot afford food, and those who suffers because of US/NATO’s imperialist wars.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Then make something out of your situation? I’m sorry that you might be piss poor because of your parent’s inability to do whatever. Your trying to blame the rich because of <span class="bbcode-b">your</span> issues, not theirs. Why would they honestly care? What would you want to define society? Everyone is not needed for a society to work. That should be obvious to see with how things have and always ran. Money will always be the thing that defines every aspect of your life. If you don’t have it? <span class="bbcode-i">Okay, do something about it.</span> It isn’t like you are in a trapped situation where there is no possibilities.  People are born with a lot more then you? Okay, so it’s cool to put all our burdens on them because they certainty had a choice in that?</p>
<p>[quote author=cLassic link=topic=550051.msg4033387#msg4033387 date=1340981630]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>what else would define the world except money? intelligence? herp that wouldn’t last long</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<ol>
<li>Remove “Revolution” from your username.</li>
<li>When you realize that everyone is as important for the society to work, you would see that the discrimination must stop. We need to find other things to do than feeding of others misfortune and exploit people. We should all be well of because we are all humans contributing to the society. Why should some people have power just because they were lucky and/or inherited a lot of money?<br>
[/quote]You’re a communist. If it were up to you, no one would have freedom and everyone would be controlled by the government. I don’t like that idea.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Communism was actually supposed to be a world of perfection, so I dont see your point here</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lets try and be serious. The idea of communism ever being ‘perfect’ is slim to none.[/quote]</p>
<p>You’re clearly fucking retarded. People are poor because the rich people have society built where the rich people stay rich, the middle class do all the work, and the poor people stay poor. The rockerfeller family has enough money to feed, shelter, and cloth the whole world. Greedy fucking bastards.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 01:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Acorn1 Acorn_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/acorn1">@Acorn1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“m1lkman, post:39, topic:447153”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=550051.msg4033670#msg4033670 date=1341000797]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>One does not need money to have a good education. Let me rephrase. One does not need to come from money to have a good education. There are plenty of stories of people who worked their ass off to get into college. People who aren’t content with being at the bottom. People determined to get more out of life. Don’t tell me that you need to be rich to get into a good school.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do not care for your “one in a million” stories.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Except it isn’t “one in a million”. I’m not talking about rags to riches; I’m talking about the people whom have worked to create a comfortable lifestyle for their family. Their are millions of stories of people whom have moved from the slums to the suburbs. Have you heard of the Great Depression? Do you know how many people refused to quit when the going got tough?[/quote]<br>
^Exactly.<br>
I understand exactly what you’re trying to say bowser but it’s just not the case usually.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/40</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 20:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Bowser jr, post:38, topic:447153”][quote author=m1lkman link=topic=550051.msg4033662#msg4033662 date=1341000480]<br>
One does not need money to have a good education. Let me rephrase. One does not need to come from money to have a good education. There are plenty of stories of people who worked their ass off to get into college. People who aren’t content with being at the bottom. People determined to get more out of life. Don’t tell me that you need to be rich to get into a good school.<br>
[/quote]<br>
I do not care for your “one in a million” stories.[/quote]</p>
<p>Except it isn’t “one in a million”. I’m not talking about rags to riches; I’m talking about the people whom have worked to create a comfortable lifestyle for their family. Their are millions of stories of people whom have moved from the slums to the suburbs. Have you heard of the Great Depression? Do you know how many people refused to quit when the going got tough?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/39</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 20:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="36" data-topic="447153">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>One does not need money to have a good education. Let me rephrase. One does not need to come from money to have a good education. There are plenty of stories of people who worked their ass off to get into college. People who aren’t content with being at the bottom. People determined to get more out of life. Don’t tell me that you need to be rich to get into a good school.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do not care for your “one in a million” stories. I didn’t say you needed to be rich, just that you needed money. The American dream is just a tool to make people think they all can be rich and well off.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/38</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 20:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n10si_t n10si t]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n10si_t">@n10si_t</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>didnt read, but</p>
<p>hurr durr i live in middle class america with virtually no worries as a teenager but society is bad :((((</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/37</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 20:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>One does not need money to have a good education. Let me rephrase. One does not need to come from money to have a good education. There are plenty of stories of people who worked their ass off to get into college. People who aren’t content with being at the bottom. People determined to get more out of life. Don’t tell me that you need to be rich to get into a good school.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/36</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 20:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Unleashed Revolution, post:31, topic:447153”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=550051.msg4033417#msg4033417 date=1340983518]<br>
MistaBigBoss: The poor people cares. Forget about us, if you can write on this forum you are among the most privileged on this earth. Think about the people doing close to slave labour, people who cannot afford food, and those who suffers because of US/NATO’s imperialist wars.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Then make something out of your situation? I’m sorry that you might be piss poor because of your parent’s inability to do whatever. You’re trying to blame the rich because of <span class="bbcode-b">your</span> issues, not theirs. Why would they honestly care? What would you want to define society? Everyone is not needed for a society to work. That should be obvious to see with how things have and always ran. Money will always be the thing that defines every aspect of your life. If you don’t have it? <span class="bbcode-i">Okay, do something about it.</span> It isn’t like you are in a trapped situation where there is no possibilities.  People are born with a lot more then you? Okay, so it’s cool to put all our burdens on them because they certainty had a choice in that?[/quote]<br>
Forget about us I said. I’m starting at a good education after this summer and will earn above average when I’m finished. So this is not my rage against society.</p>
<p>In many places your freedom is decided by your economy. Want to have a good education, and you need money. Want to be healthy and you need money. Despite what Mitt Romney want you to believe, not everyone can be in the top 1%.</p>
<p>The beginner salary I can expect is $74000, and that will increase in five years when I’m finished. So just to make this clear, I’m not suffering economical.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/35</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 18:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“the elve age, post:32, topic:447153”][quote author=Unleashed Revolution link=topic=550051.msg4033471#msg4033471 date=1340987867]<br>
Money will always be the thing that defines every aspect of your life.<br>
[/quote]Keep believing that and see how far you make it.[/quote]<br>
He is correct to an extent, money is a currency correct? Currency is tradable value, so if you have lots of value that people want you can exchange it for what you want and so forth.If you have not much/no currency don’t expect a good standard of living.<br>
^Bad explanation as usual but it gets the point across I think.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 17:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unleashed_Revolution Unleashed Revolution]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unleashed_revolution">@Unleashed_Revolution</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“the elve age, post:32, topic:447153”][quote author=Unleashed Revolution link=topic=550051.msg4033471#msg4033471 date=1340987867]<br>
Money will always be the thing that defines every aspect of your life.<br>
[/quote]Keep believing that and see how far you make it.[/quote]<br>
I don’t have to believe in it to know it is partially true. What else defines your life? Family? What helps the family to make it properly work? Money. What makes your life reasonably well? Money. What defines the pentacle of your success?</p>
<p>There is more and more to this. You could probably throw up a case of a social work saving five kids, but again, money will always play a part in that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 16:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Society</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Unleashed Revolution, post:31, topic:447153”]Money will always be the thing that defines every aspect of your life.[/quote]Keep believing that and see how far you make it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 16:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-447153-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/society/447153.rss">Society</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
