<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help With New Server-Connecting</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-server-connecting/439313</link>
    <description>Hello Moparscape, I&#39;ve been working on servers for a good two years now. I took breakk recently for a good five months because I got back into playing other people&#39;s RSPS&#39;. Recently, I&#39;ve been trying to make a new server and I&#39;ve been having a problem. I got a new laptop for Christmas because my old computer with all my server stuff on it broke. So, I&#39;ve been trying to make a new server and this is what happens when I try to connect. I&#39;ve done some coding, such as adding some things to the source already so I&#39;d be pretty sad if I fu--ed up the source somehow. I&#39;m running windows 7, home edition, dual core i7 processors, and 8gb of RAM. I know that won&#39;t help but it&#39;s just so you get an idea of what I&#39;m using. Here&#39;s the problem: I am trying to connect to the server with a webclient maker and it&#39;s not working. It&#39;s saying the server is offline. Here&#39;s what I did: I downloaded the port-forward tool from portforward.com and portforwared, I set an exception for 43594 in my firewall, and I ran the server. (Run.bat) Everytime I try to connect to it, it says offline. HELP ME!!!!

Thanks in advance, Chris.

PS: If problem is succefully fixed and I&#39;m working good, there might be a reward :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 19:04:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-server-connecting/439313.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help With New Server-Connecting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cia_nick cia nick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cia_nick">@cia_nick</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Disable windows 7 fire wall or try a different source that’s %100 guaranteed to work if you did everything you said…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-server-connecting/439313/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-server-connecting/439313/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 19:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439313-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-server-connecting/439313.rss">Help With New Server-Connecting</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help With New Server-Connecting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@iDoSkillzzz iDoSkillzzz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/idoskillzzz">@iDoSkillzzz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello Moparscape, I’ve been working on servers for a good two years now. I took breakk recently for a good five months because I got back into playing other people’s RSPS’. Recently, I’ve been trying to make a new server and I’ve been having a problem. I got a new laptop for Christmas because my old computer with all my server stuff on it broke. So, I’ve been trying to make a new server and this is what happens when I try to connect. I’ve done some coding, such as adding some things to the source already so I’d be pretty sad if I fu–ed up the source somehow. I’m running windows 7, home edition, dual core i7 processors, and 8gb of RAM. I know that won’t help but it’s just so you get an idea of what I’m using. Here’s the problem: I am trying to connect to the server with a webclient maker and it’s not working. It’s saying the server is offline. Here’s what I did: I downloaded the port-forward tool from <a href="http://portforward.com" rel="nofollow noopener">portforward.com</a> and portforwared, I set an exception for 43594 in my firewall, and I ran the server. (Run.bat) Everytime I try to connect to it, it says offline. HELP ME!!!</p>
<p>Thanks in advance, Chris.</p>
<p>PS: If problem is succefully fixed and I’m working good, there might be a reward <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-server-connecting/439313/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-server-connecting/439313/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 18:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439313-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-new-server-connecting/439313.rss">Help With New Server-Connecting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
