<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Snippets board</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/snippets-board/444787</link>
    <description>[b]What I [i]think[/i] should be added to the forum:[/b] I think we should add a snippets child board under the board Server Tutorials!

[b]Why:[/b] I think we should get this because for instance if a person want to learn how to do a certain thing, they dont want to search through every page of the snippets thread?! its barely recongnized. They also dont get much feedback on what they can do to make the snippet better. 
[b]reason 2:[/b] This would make the moderators job easier because I have seen countless reports on people saying [i]This is a snippet, not a tutorial.[/i] Which means more reports in modCP and then more work for a mod. 
[b]Reason 3:[/b]The last reason why is because the snippets/tutorials would be easier and quicker to navigate through. Snippets purpose are for bits of code to be added into our RSPS. We do not need a tutorial explaining most of the time. IF the author feels like explaining all the code and teaching our members. Then by all means post it in the tutorials section. Not all of us need tutorials.

That is why I feel we need a snippets board. Hope this gets reviewed and considered! Thank you for reading!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 12:42:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/snippets-board/444787.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Snippets board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m just going to move this topic to the resolved section. The reason being is that this has already been suggested by another member and is currently under discussion. I hope you understand.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/snippets-board/444787/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/snippets-board/444787/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 12:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444787-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/snippets-board/444787.rss">Snippets board</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Snippets board</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kronixz kronikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kronixz">@kronixz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">What I <span class="bbcode-i">think</span> should be added to the forum:</span> I think we should add a snippets child board under the board Server Tutorials!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Why:</span> I think we should get this because for instance if a person want to learn how to do a certain thing, they dont want to search through every page of the snippets thread?! its barely recongnized. They also dont get much feedback on what they can do to make the snippet better.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">reason 2:</span> This would make the moderators job easier because I have seen countless reports on people saying <span class="bbcode-i">This is a snippet, not a tutorial.</span> Which means more reports in modCP and then more work for a mod.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Reason 3:</span>The last reason why is because the snippets/tutorials would be easier and quicker to navigate through. Snippets purpose are for bits of code to be added into our RSPS. We do not need a tutorial explaining most of the time. IF the author feels like explaining all the code and teaching our members. Then by all means post it in the tutorials section. Not all of us need tutorials.</p>
<p>That is why I feel we need a snippets board. Hope this gets reviewed and considered! Thank you for reading!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/snippets-board/444787/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/snippets-board/444787/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 02:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444787-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/snippets-board/444787.rss">Snippets board</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
