<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Spout discussion!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/spout-discussion/445264</link>
    <description>Hey guys,

So, does anyone else use Spout? Plugin or server?

If you&#39;re now just like o.O, Spout is a plugin/server which bridges the gap between client and server. It works alongside the Spoutcraft client which is a legal client launcher*, and allows things such as custom blocks and extra GUI.
As an example, check out the plugins &quot;MoreMaterials&quot; Which adds extra blocks in packs, which can be made by anyone (I made some packs which add staves and runes for a magic plugin), or &quot;mmoCore&quot; which adds GUI elements. I did not write either of these, although I&#39;ve done a lot of extra stuff for mmoCore (8 addons for the Info section)

Go check out their site, www.spout.org - If you get the client and want to see it in action, feel free to drop into my server as a greylister. You can find the IP via my site, as I&#39;m not sure if I can directly advertise here or not so just playing it safe.


*Sorry, that means anyone with cracked minecraft can&#39;t use it. Just man up and buy the game anyway, there are hundreds of more interesting, better servers if you do.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 18:26:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/spout-discussion/445264.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Spout discussion!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flenix1 Flenix1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flenix1">@Flenix1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,</p>
<p>So, does anyone else use Spout? Plugin or server?</p>
<p>If you’re now just like o.O, Spout is a plugin/server which bridges the gap between client and server. It works alongside the Spoutcraft client which is a legal client launcher*, and allows things such as custom blocks and extra GUI.<br>
As an example, check out the plugins “MoreMaterials” Which adds extra blocks in packs, which can be made by anyone (I made some packs which add staves and runes for a magic plugin), or “mmoCore” which adds GUI elements. I did not write either of these, although I’ve done a lot of extra stuff for mmoCore (8 addons for the Info section)</p>
<p>Go check out their site, <a href="http://www.spout.org" rel="nofollow noopener">www.spout.org</a> - If you get the client and want to see it in action, feel free to drop into my server as a greylister. You can find the IP via my site, as I’m not sure if I can directly advertise here or not so just playing it safe.</p>
<p>*Sorry, that means anyone with cracked minecraft can’t use it. Just man up and buy the game anyway, there are hundreds of more interesting, better servers if you do.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/spout-discussion/445264/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/spout-discussion/445264/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 18:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-445264-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/spout-discussion/445264.rss">Spout discussion!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
