<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What method of MySQL mirroring should I use for this?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-method-of-mysql-mirroring-should-i-use-for-this/344254</link>
    <description>I&#39;m running an web application hosting service (basically hosting forums for free), and I have two remote servers available. The code for the application is stored on both servers and isn&#39;t a problem, but I&#39;m wondering how to deal with the databases.

When someone goes onto a site *.example-host.com, they are sent to one of the two servers and both must be capable of loading the forums from a database. The database must also have write access, for when new members register or post topics etc.

The main requirement is speed, but uptime is also important (if a server goes out, the site should still work).

I have a few options, but I&#39;m inexperienced and not sure which to go with:

1) [PHP] Split the forum records 50:50 between the two servers. If a server does not have the record for a forum requested, it can request it from the other by remote MySQL and load it. This idea sounded okay, until I realised that 50% of the time, users would be waiting significantly longer for pages to load. I also realised that if one of the servers went down, half the forums would be inaccessible and registrations would have to be disabled.

2) [MySQL] Dual master replication. This would attempt to mirror the two databases and sounds perfect, but I&#39;ve heard that it can be very problematic. I don&#39;t know how fast this is.

3) [MySQL] Use a standard replication, distribute read only queries on both nodes and read/write queries to the master. This sounds like a good option, but again, I&#39;m not sure on speed. I also don&#39;t know what would happen if the master server went down.

If you have any other suggestions, please post them :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 07:53:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-method-of-mysql-mirroring-should-i-use-for-this/344254.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What method of MySQL mirroring should I use for this?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m running an web application hosting service (basically hosting forums for free), and I have two remote servers available. The code for the application is stored on both servers and isn’t a problem, but I’m wondering how to deal with the databases.</p>
<p>When someone goes onto a site *.example-host.com, they are sent to one of the two servers and both must be capable of loading the forums from a database. The database must also have write access, for when new members register or post topics etc.</p>
<p>The main requirement is speed, but uptime is also important (if a server goes out, the site should still work).</p>
<p>I have a few options, but I’m inexperienced and not sure which to go with:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>[PHP] Split the forum records 50:50 between the two servers. If a server does not have the record for a forum requested, it can request it from the other by remote MySQL and load it. This idea sounded okay, until I realised that 50% of the time, users would be waiting significantly longer for pages to load. I also realised that if one of the servers went down, half the forums would be inaccessible and registrations would have to be disabled.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>[MySQL] Dual master replication. This would attempt to mirror the two databases and sounds perfect, but I’ve heard that it can be very problematic. I don’t know how fast this is.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>[MySQL] Use a standard replication, distribute read only queries on both nodes and read/write queries to the master. This sounds like a good option, but again, I’m not sure on speed. I also don’t know what would happen if the master server went down.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>If you have any other suggestions, please post them <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-method-of-mysql-mirroring-should-i-use-for-this/344254/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-method-of-mysql-mirroring-should-i-use-for-this/344254/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 07:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-344254-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-method-of-mysql-mirroring-should-i-use-for-this/344254.rss">What method of MySQL mirroring should I use for this?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
