<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need Music Tab and Cache Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-music-tab-and-cache-help/448316</link>
    <description>Hey guys,

First of all, my client (delta, I think 377 but not sure) is not loading the sprites and whatnot located within the cache folder.  All it does is bring up the original sprites (like the kind in the Moparscape Client) even though it compiles fine and I can login without errors, etc.  On this gameframe, there is no music tab (or music sprite, even though there is one in the client&#39;s cache which isn&#39;t being loaded).  Can someone either help me diagnose why the client is not utilizing its cache or help me add the missing music tab?  Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 01:06:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-music-tab-and-cache-help/448316.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need Music Tab and Cache Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dragon99999 Dragon99999]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragon99999">@Dragon99999</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,</p>
<p>First of all, my client (delta, I think 377 but not sure) is not loading the sprites and whatnot located within the cache folder.  All it does is bring up the original sprites (like the kind in the Moparscape Client) even though it compiles fine and I can login without errors, etc.  On this gameframe, there is no music tab (or music sprite, even though there is one in the client’s cache which isn’t being loaded).  Can someone either help me diagnose why the client is not utilizing its cache or help me add the missing music tab?  Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-music-tab-and-cache-help/448316/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-music-tab-and-cache-help/448316/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 01:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-448316-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-music-tab-and-cache-help/448316.rss">Need Music Tab and Cache Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
