<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Interface drawing (Ubuntu)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-interface-drawing-ubuntu/443847</link>
    <description>Alright, while recently switching over to Ubuntu I find that this one PI client doesn&#39;t want to draw the interfaces, the inventory stones, or the crowns... All my sprites are packed into the cache, so I&#39;m assuming its not unpacking correctly, I get a null pointer on start up, but no details of were it comes from. I&#39;ve tracked it down to the StreamLoader class, I think it isn&#39;t unpacking their.. I don&#39;t know if I&#39;m right.. I&#39;ve tried running in Wine, Eclipse, and just with the jar.. Nothing works.. Anyone know the issue?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 08:50:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-interface-drawing-ubuntu/443847.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Interface drawing (Ubuntu)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, while recently switching over to Ubuntu I find that this one PI client doesn’t want to draw the interfaces, the inventory stones, or the crowns… All my sprites are packed into the cache, so I’m assuming its not unpacking correctly, I get a null pointer on start up, but no details of were it comes from. I’ve tracked it down to the StreamLoader class, I think it isn’t unpacking their… I don’t know if I’m right… I’ve tried running in Wine, Eclipse, and just with the jar… Nothing works… Anyone know the issue?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-interface-drawing-ubuntu/443847/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-interface-drawing-ubuntu/443847/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 08:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-443847-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-interface-drawing-ubuntu/443847.rss">[PI] Interface drawing (Ubuntu)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
