<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>xHTML Tags, and xHTML/CSS Integration</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xhtml-tags-and-xhtml-css-integration/65048</link>
    <description>Hey there... this is a new tutorial of mine that I just made. It isn&#39;t going to be very well formatted like my past few tutorials were because I don&#39;t have too much time to make it, but I just wanted to do something..

PLEASE NOTE: This guide will not help you if you are not willing to learn. It gives you a few line of code, but it most likely won&#39;t help you unless you read the whole guide and try to understand what everything does. Just using the exact code that I give you without adding to it and changing it will not give you a good website. You need to use your brain and expand on what I tell you.


So.. first, in order use you xHTML and CSS together, you first need to create two new files. Name one &quot;index.php&quot; and the other &quot;css.css&quot; (or something along those lines... the index page needs to be the same though).

Now, open the index.php file and build your basic xHTML layout. If you don&#39;t know how to do this, please see my other topic by clicking [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,55911.0.html]here[/url].

Now you should have something that looks like this (not exactly, but close):
[code]&lt;html&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
&lt;title&gt;&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;
&lt;body&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;[/code]

Now, after the title tags, but before you close your head tag, add this:
[code]&lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot; href=&quot;css.css&quot; /&gt;[/code]

What this does, is tell your index.php file to work with your css file.

Now that they know how to work together, you need to know how to make them actually do something.

The point of the CSS is to reduce the amount of code that you have in each file on your site. So basically, if you delete your CSS, your site should be white with black text and loose almost all sense of formatting.

So... the first thing that you need to do is get your coloring all sorted out... so... pick what you want your text color to be and your background color to be and put them into the following code, which you should then insert into your CSS file:
[code]body {
background: #000000;
color: #FFFFFF;
}[/code]
The numbers after the &quot;background&quot; text are the color of the background, and the numbers after the &quot;color&quot; text is the color that the text will be on your website.

Once that is all sorted out, the formatting and content is pretty much up to you. The big thing that you need to know though is how divs work... it is quite easy though.

First, pick a name for your div. Let&#39;s say you want it to be for where your banner will go, so we will name it &quot;banner&quot;.

Now, we insert it into the CSS:
[code]#banner {
background: #000000; url(&#39;http://www.yourimageurlhere.com&#39;) no-repeat;
color: #FFFFFF;
width: 600px;
height: 110px;
text-align: center;
}[/code]
Everything in there is pretty self-explanitory. Just edit it so that it fits with your new site. Also, if your CSS doesn&#39;t work at some point, make sure that you didn&#39;t forget to put a &quot;;&quot; at the end of each line.

Now, we need to put it into your code. The style won&#39;t do anything if it isn&#39;t actually in the index file...

So... put this into your index between the two &#39;body&#39; tags:
[code]&lt;div id=&quot;banner&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;[/code]

Now, your banner should be in your site!

The final thing that I will be telling you is that with divs, you can also style it without using the CSS. Just input this code into the index between the &#39;body&#39; tags:
[code]&lt;div style=&quot;background: #123456; color: #123456; border: 1px solid #123456;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;[/code]
As you can hopefully see, I basically just took out the id bit and put the style there instead. I don&#39;t recommend this method, but it is there if you need it.

Hopefully your learned something from this guide. It seems simple, but if you actually use it to learn, you should be able to create a descent website from using your new skills.

-Alexia</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 22:36:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xhtml-tags-and-xhtml-css-integration/65048.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>xHTML Tags, and xHTML/CSS Integration</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@alexia alexia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/alexia">@alexia</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey there… this is a new tutorial of mine that I just made. It isn’t going to be very well formatted like my past few tutorials were because I don’t have too much time to make it, but I just wanted to do something…</p>
<p>PLEASE NOTE: This guide will not help you if you are not willing to learn. It gives you a few line of code, but it most likely won’t help you unless you read the whole guide and try to understand what everything does. Just using the exact code that I give you without adding to it and changing it will not give you a good website. You need to use your brain and expand on what I tell you.</p>
<p>So… first, in order use you xHTML and CSS together, you first need to create two new files. Name one “index.php” and the other “css.css” (or something along those lines… the index page needs to be the same though).</p>
<p>Now, open the index.php file and build your basic xHTML layout. If you don’t know how to do this, please see my other topic by clicking <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,55911.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>Now you should have something that looks like this (not exactly, but close):</p>
<p>[code]</p>





[/code]
<p>Now, after the title tags, but before you close your head tag, add this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">&lt;link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="css.css" /&gt;</code></pre>
<p>What this does, is tell your index.php file to work with your css file.</p>
<p>Now that they know how to work together, you need to know how to make them actually do something.</p>
<p>The point of the CSS is to reduce the amount of code that you have in each file on your site. So basically, if you delete your CSS, your site should be white with black text and loose almost all sense of formatting.</p>
<p>So… the first thing that you need to do is get your coloring all sorted out… so… pick what you want your text color to be and your background color to be and put them into the following code, which you should then insert into your CSS file:</p>
<p><code>body {
background: #000000;
color: #FFFFFF;
}</code><br>
The numbers after the “background” text are the color of the background, and the numbers after the “color” text is the color that the text will be on your website.</p>
<p>Once that is all sorted out, the formatting and content is pretty much up to you. The big thing that you need to know though is how divs work… it is quite easy though.</p>
<p>First, pick a name for your div. Let’s say you want it to be for where your banner will go, so we will name it “banner”.</p>
<p>Now, we insert it into the CSS:</p>
<p><code>#banner {
background: #000000; url('http://www.yourimageurlhere.com') no-repeat;
color: #FFFFFF;
width: 600px;
height: 110px;
text-align: center;
}</code><br>
Everything in there is pretty self-explanitory. Just edit it so that it fits with your new site. Also, if your CSS doesn’t work at some point, make sure that you didn’t forget to put a “;” at the end of each line.</p>
<p>Now, we need to put it into your code. The style won’t do anything if it isn’t actually in the index file…</p>
<p>So… put this into your index between the two ‘body’ tags:</p>
<p>[code]</p><div>
</div>[/code]
<p>Now, your banner should be in your site!</p>
<p>The final thing that I will be telling you is that with divs, you can also style it without using the CSS. Just input this code into the index between the ‘body’ tags:</p>
<p>[code]</p><div>
</div>[/code]
As you can hopefully see, I basically just took out the id bit and put the style there instead. I don't recommend this method, but it is there if you need it.
<p>Hopefully your learned something from this guide. It seems simple, but if you actually use it to learn, you should be able to create a descent website from using your new skills.</p>
<p>-Alexia</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xhtml-tags-and-xhtml-css-integration/65048/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xhtml-tags-and-xhtml-css-integration/65048/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 22:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-65048-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/xhtml-tags-and-xhtml-css-integration/65048.rss">xHTML Tags, and xHTML/CSS Integration</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
