<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Oz the Great and Powerful</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oz-the-great-and-powerful/533515</link>
    <description>Ahh James Franco, the man who is always starts off a man whore in every movie. But forget about that, thats not what we&#39;re here to discuss. The movie Oz the Great and Powerful is a backtrack from the 1939 film The Wizard of Oz. If you don&#39;t really understand the concept of the wizard of oz in the original movie you&#39;re probably going to have a hard time taking in or even understanding the fact that the wizard of oz is not actually, a wizard... It&#39;s funny because whilst watching the original movie as a child I held on to the concept that oz was actually a magical wizard and I never really thought about it before watching this movie, though it seems after watching this movie it cleared up literally everything. I understood the concept of oz being a brain wizard rather than some magical wizard which in my opinion is actually a well thought out plan for a 1930s movie even though they didn&#39;t go into much depth and it probably wasn&#39;t even a concept purposely planned. Even today when they put together the pieces to make this movie it all just seemed so fluent, I loved it.

I couldn&#39;t help but notice how smoking hot Mila Kunis was at the start of the movie, dayum she was working it all the way up to the magic fruit in which you&#39;ll understand when you watch the movie. Same with Rachel Weisz who I did not recognize at first because I&#39;m used to seeing her on an altar about to be sacrificed to a mummy.

Another thing I loved was the humor, though some parts were extremely cliche it did have some funny munchkins. You can never go wrong with munchkins, they are always funny especially when you picture Marlon Wayans&#39;s face is on all of them.

The only thing I disliked was the fact that nothing was said about Dory, and after seeing this movie you kind of want the Wizard of Oz film to have never existed because you want a complete remake with only James Franco as the hero. By you I mean I, its the sort of movie I get mixed feelings for and I want more.

So anyway I&#39;m looking forward to a sequel that will probably happen in 20 years from now with a completely different cast with a completely different man whore, looking forward to it! Other than that I would give this movie a rating of 7.5 tabbies out of 10.

*note to self, find a real way to rate these movies instead of making up a random number*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 12:50:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oz-the-great-and-powerful/533515.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Oz the Great and Powerful</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ahh James Franco, the man who is always starts off a man whore in every movie. But forget about that, thats not what we’re here to discuss. The movie Oz the Great and Powerful is a backtrack from the 1939 film The Wizard of Oz. If you don’t really understand the concept of the wizard of oz in the original movie you’re probably going to have a hard time taking in or even understanding the fact that the wizard of oz is not actually, a wizard… It’s funny because whilst watching the original movie as a child I held on to the concept that oz was actually a magical wizard and I never really thought about it before watching this movie, though it seems after watching this movie it cleared up literally everything. I understood the concept of oz being a brain wizard rather than some magical wizard which in my opinion is actually a well thought out plan for a 1930s movie even though they didn’t go into much depth and it probably wasn’t even a concept purposely planned. Even today when they put together the pieces to make this movie it all just seemed so fluent, I loved it.</p>
<p>I couldn’t help but notice how smoking hot Mila Kunis was at the start of the movie, dayum she was working it all the way up to the magic fruit in which you’ll understand when you watch the movie. Same with Rachel Weisz who I did not recognize at first because I’m used to seeing her on an altar about to be sacrificed to a mummy.</p>
<p>Another thing I loved was the humor, though some parts were extremely cliche it did have some funny munchkins. You can never go wrong with munchkins, they are always funny especially when you picture Marlon Wayans’s face is on all of them.</p>
<p>The only thing I disliked was the fact that nothing was said about Dory, and after seeing this movie you kind of want the Wizard of Oz film to have never existed because you want a complete remake with only James Franco as the hero. By you I mean I, its the sort of movie I get mixed feelings for and I want more.</p>
<p>So anyway I’m looking forward to a sequel that will probably happen in 20 years from now with a completely different cast with a completely different man whore, looking forward to it! Other than that I would give this movie a rating of 7.5 tabbies out of 10.</p>
<p><em>note to self, find a real way to rate these movies instead of making up a random number</em></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oz-the-great-and-powerful/533515/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oz-the-great-and-powerful/533515/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 12:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533515-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/oz-the-great-and-powerful/533515.rss">Oz the Great and Powerful</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
