<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sponsor</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sponsor/363729</link>
    <description>Topic was locked, not sure why.. no one posted why.

&#39;@ bidding, &quot;1       3lou 55       Grinderscape       $455 USD       October 09, 2010, 11:00:12 PM       $0 USD &quot;

You see how someone is able to bid 12 second after bidding ended.. crap like this shouldn&#39;t be able to be done. I might of paid for the last 3 month for my bids, but might not this month =[.&#39;

Not trying to cry but it&#39;ll be nice if we could bid legibility.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:33:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sponsor/363729.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sponsor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I responded to you via PM, but I’ll post it here as well:</p>
<p>It was legitimate, and no one cheated.  I’ll see if I can explain it to you real quick.  This is how the page calculates if bidding is enabled up towards the top of the page:</p>
<p><code>$curr_time = time();
$bidding = ($curr_time &gt; $time_begin) &amp;&amp; ($curr_time &lt; $time_end);</code></p>
<p>if $bidding is false, no one can bid and no bids are accepted.  I check it on submit as well, so it’s not like you can just keep the page open either.  So, since $bidding was true, that means he got past this check in time.  Now the page does some processing, validating the bid, up until the bid is updated in the MySQL database.  Now, when I go to update the bid, instead of using the value in $curr_time, like perhaps I should, I insert the value from a new call of time(), which may be quite a bit later depending on how busy the server is.  That is why the value in the database is after the time he actually hit the submit button.  Does that make sense to you?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sponsor/363729/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sponsor/363729/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363729-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sponsor/363729.rss">Sponsor</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sponsor</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wtf_is_life wtf is life]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wtf_is_life">@wtf_is_life</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Topic was locked, not sure why… no one posted why.</p>
<p>'@ bidding, "1       3lou 55       Grinderscape       $455 USD       October 09, 2010, 11:00:12 PM       $0 USD "</p>
<p>You see how someone is able to bid 12 second after bidding ended… crap like this shouldn’t be able to be done. I might of paid for the last 3 month for my bids, but might not this month =[.’</p>
<p>Not trying to cry but it’ll be nice if we could bid legibility.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sponsor/363729/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sponsor/363729/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-363729-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sponsor/363729.rss">Sponsor</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
