<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Adding defence and Prayer</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-defence-and-prayer/165391</link>
    <description>Mkay here they are...

I need help making..

Prayer work, say you turn on Melee protect and the npcs will only hit 0 on you. I need help making it drain too. My prayer is completely defective. :( Also i&#39;v looked through topics and only one on rune-server has been posted and its no help.

Examples:
Turning on a str pray and its like I&#39;m super potting, just doesn&#39;t show up on your stats.
Turning on Melee Pro and getting hit less/not at all by npcs.

Making defense work correctly is the most important. I asked PaliDino but iether he wants to keep secret or he has no time to explain, but I need defense to correctly work. Say i&#39;m wearing full bandos.. From then on I&#39;ll get hit high 60% less than when I have no armor.

If you can help me with these two things my email is
John_95_07@hotmail.com

These is my only two big problems atm.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 05:08:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-defence-and-prayer/165391.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Adding defence and Prayer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_J_O_H_N [-J O H N-]]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_j_o_h_n">@_J_O_H_N</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Mkay here they are…</p>
<p>I need help making…</p>
<p>Prayer work, say you turn on Melee protect and the npcs will only hit 0 on you. I need help making it drain too. My prayer is completely defective. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> Also i’v looked through topics and only one on rune-server has been posted and its no help.</p>
<p>Examples:<br>
Turning on a str pray and its like I’m super potting, just doesn’t show up on your stats.<br>
Turning on Melee Pro and getting hit less/not at all by npcs.</p>
<p>Making defense work correctly is the most important. I asked PaliDino but iether he wants to keep secret or he has no time to explain, but I need defense to correctly work. Say i’m wearing full bandos… From then on I’ll get hit high 60% less than when I have no armor.</p>
<p>If you can help me with these two things my email is<br>
<a href="mailto:John_95_07@hotmail.com">John_95_07@hotmail.com</a></p>
<p>These is my only two big problems atm.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-defence-and-prayer/165391/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-defence-and-prayer/165391/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 05:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-165391-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-defence-and-prayer/165391.rss">Adding defence and Prayer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
