<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Funny Letter</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773</link>
    <description>Some chick wrote a letter to her ex explaining what happened the night they broke up.  Then he wrote back.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Brad,
It would be difficult for me to be any more miserable right now,
I feel like the worst person ever. First, let me start by saying
that I am truly truly sorry, and I hate myself for hurting you. Of all the people in the whole entire world, you were honestly the last person that I would ever want to wrong in any way. There is no excuse at all for anything that happened, so I won&#39;t even try other than to say all of us had WAY too much to drink, and I did a stupid thing. I can handle you being pissed at me, I absolutely deserve it, I can even handle the ugly words that were exchanged between us, what I can&#39;t handle is thinking that you see me as a different person. It is weird, I feel like I just went through a horrible break up or something. The world looked funny yesterday, I couldn&#39;t crack a smile if you paid me, there are songs I can&#39;t listen to, and I just ! feel beyond crushed. I don&#39;t know if you meant everything you said to me, and I am hoping that you didn&#39;t. I know that I was wrong on many levels, but I am also hoping that this is something that we can deal with. I know it sounds totally crazy and stupid, but you have come to play such a significant role in my life, I can&#39;t imagine my days without you. It is totally strange and weird to say that, and you could say that my behavior didn&#39;t reflect that, and you would be correct. I hate feeling like you hate me, and I hate feeling like all of your friends think I am a terrible person, because I am not. I know there is nothing I can say or do to take back what happened, but I just want you to know that fighting with you was just about the worst thing I could have ever imagined. It was right up there with one of the ugliest nights of my life, and I would give anything in the world to rewind and fix it. I am not sure if you will respond to this, part of me thinks that you won&#39;t. If not today, then maybe some other time. Also, thanks for getting my stuff together, although I think my sunglasses are still at your house, if you could keep your eyes peeled for them that would be great. I can&#39;t even focus or work today, I can&#39;t eat, I seriously feel like it was an ugly break up, and I am hoping against hopes that it was not that and you are not done with me. Please don&#39;t cut me off, I really don&#39;t think I can handle that. I am so sorry.

Elizabeth




Dear Elizabeth,

Thank you for your concern. I&#39;ll be sure to file it away under &quot;L&quot; for &quot;Long-winded diatribes from drunken whores I couldn&#39;t care less about&quot;. You did a stupid thing huh? No...doing long division and forgetting to carry the one is &quot;a stupid thing&quot;; Mixing in a red
sock with a load of whites is &quot;a stupid thing&quot;; Blowing some guy in a bathroom for 45 minutes while I sit at the bar wondering if you&#39;re taking so long because you ate too much bran that morning isn&#39;t as much a &quot;Stupid thing&quot; as it is grounds for permanent removal from my social calendar. To be honest, I&#39;m not sure if it was more amusing that you went and degraded yourself in a public toilet not once but twice in a 2 hour span, or that you seemed to think that by saying &quot;Well, I didn&#39;t Fuck him&quot; somehow gave you a clean slate. So forgive me if I couldn&#39;t care less if the world &quot;looked funny&quot; to you yesterday. Since your world revolves around blow dryers, golden retrievers, Prada Bags and Jelly Beans, I&#39;m sure it must have been
most unsettling to actually have to consider someone else&#39;s feelings for 24 hours straight. The good news for you is that my friends don&#39;t think you&#39;re a terrible person, they just think you&#39;re the average run of the mill cum-guzzling blond who commands about as much
respect as your average child porn collector. I could be wrong but, it&#39;s pretty hard to respect some B&amp;T chick who comes out to spend the night at my place even though she&#39;s seeing someone else in New jersey and winds up tongue-bathing the taint of anyone who decides 30 minutes of droning commentary on Colin Farrell&#39;s new haircut is worth putting up with for a hand job in the men&#39;s room. The good thing about being a guy is that when I eventually bump into the young lad who finger-blasted you on top of a towel dispenser last saturday, we&#39;ll have a shot and laugh our heads off about the time it happened. By the way, for the amount of time you claim to spend in spin class you really must be doing something wrong to sport the thunder thighs you do. Watching you parade around my bedroom in a thong was a
little like watching sea lions mate. Thought you might like to know.

PS.

I BCC&#39;d about 100 people on this email.

Talk to you never,
Brad&lt;/blockquote&gt;

http://www.pocketfives.com/poker-forums/13/holy-sheet-Funny-1338907/p/1338907
Some of the replies are funnier than the letters themselves.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 20:03:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Funny Letter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>probably fake</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 20:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253773-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss">Funny Letter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Funny Letter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThatOneServer Mike_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thatoneserver">@ThatOneServer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>comments arent that funny… maybe this one.</p>
<blockquote>After reading Brad's response I did a chair spin and a double fist pump!!!!
<p>LMFAO</p>
<p>Yogi</p>
</blockquote>
<p>that shits hilarious though</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253773-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss">Funny Letter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Funny Letter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_itman |-|itman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_itman">@_itman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol’d</p>
<p>Lmfao dude wow.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 19:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253773-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss">Funny Letter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Funny Letter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Oh wait, I’m so drunk. Let’s give someone a blowjob!</p>
<p>Drunks don’t blow others, other then to impress. She is an attention whore.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 19:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253773-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss">Funny Letter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Funny Letter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m.dog311 m.dog311]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m.dog311">@m.dog311</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ya, he handled it pretty well though <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 18:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253773-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss">Funny Letter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Funny Letter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Made me lol. Proud to be a man!</p>
<p>Sucks that people like her actually exist though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 18:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253773-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss">Funny Letter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Funny Letter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@maniown maniown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maniown">@maniown</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>By the way, for the amount of time you claim to spend in spin class you really must be doing something wrong to sport the thunder thighs you do. Watching you parade around my bedroom in a thong was a<br>
little like watching sea lions mate. Thought you might like to know.</p>
<p>Made me lol irl so hard</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 18:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253773-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss">Funny Letter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Funny Letter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_bank the bank]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_bank">@the_bank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol, “The good thing about being a guy is that when I eventually bump into the young lad who finger-blasted you on top of a towel dispenser last saturday, we’ll have a shot and laugh our heads off about the time it happened.”</p>
<p>It’s so true.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 14:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253773-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss">Funny Letter</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Funny Letter</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m.dog311 m.dog311]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m.dog311">@m.dog311</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Some chick wrote a letter to her ex explaining what happened the night they broke up.  Then he wrote back.</p>
<blockquote>Brad,
It would be difficult for me to be any more miserable right now,
I feel like the worst person ever. First, let me start by saying
that I am truly truly sorry, and I hate myself for hurting you. Of all the people in the whole entire world, you were honestly the last person that I would ever want to wrong in any way. There is no excuse at all for anything that happened, so I won't even try other than to say all of us had WAY too much to drink, and I did a stupid thing. I can handle you being pissed at me, I absolutely deserve it, I can even handle the ugly words that were exchanged between us, what I can't handle is thinking that you see me as a different person. It is weird, I feel like I just went through a horrible break up or something. The world looked funny yesterday, I couldn't crack a smile if you paid me, there are songs I can't listen to, and I just ! feel beyond crushed. I don't know if you meant everything you said to me, and I am hoping that you didn't. I know that I was wrong on many levels, but I am also hoping that this is something that we can deal with. I know it sounds totally crazy and stupid, but you have come to play such a significant role in my life, I can't imagine my days without you. It is totally strange and weird to say that, and you could say that my behavior didn't reflect that, and you would be correct. I hate feeling like you hate me, and I hate feeling like all of your friends think I am a terrible person, because I am not. I know there is nothing I can say or do to take back what happened, but I just want you to know that fighting with you was just about the worst thing I could have ever imagined. It was right up there with one of the ugliest nights of my life, and I would give anything in the world to rewind and fix it. I am not sure if you will respond to this, part of me thinks that you won't. If not today, then maybe some other time. Also, thanks for getting my stuff together, although I think my sunglasses are still at your house, if you could keep your eyes peeled for them that would be great. I can't even focus or work today, I can't eat, I seriously feel like it was an ugly break up, and I am hoping against hopes that it was not that and you are not done with me. Please don't cut me off, I really don't think I can handle that. I am so sorry.
<p>Elizabeth</p>
<p>Dear Elizabeth,</p>
<p>Thank you for your concern. I’ll be sure to file it away under “L” for “Long-winded diatribes from drunken whores I couldn’t care less about”. You did a stupid thing huh? No…doing long division and forgetting to carry the one is “a stupid thing”; Mixing in a red<br>
sock with a load of whites is “a stupid thing”; Blowing some guy in a bathroom for 45 minutes while I sit at the bar wondering if you’re taking so long because you ate too much bran that morning isn’t as much a “Stupid thing” as it is grounds for permanent removal from my social calendar. To be honest, I’m not sure if it was more amusing that you went and degraded yourself in a public toilet not once but twice in a 2 hour span, or that you seemed to think that by saying “Well, I didn’t Fuck him” somehow gave you a clean slate. So forgive me if I couldn’t care less if the world “looked funny” to you yesterday. Since your world revolves around blow dryers, golden retrievers, Prada Bags and Jelly Beans, I’m sure it must have been<br>
most unsettling to actually have to consider someone else’s feelings for 24 hours straight. The good news for you is that my friends don’t think you’re a terrible person, they just think you’re the average run of the mill cum-guzzling blond who commands about as much<br>
respect as your average child porn collector. I could be wrong but, it’s pretty hard to respect some B&amp;T chick who comes out to spend the night at my place even though she’s seeing someone else in New jersey and winds up tongue-bathing the taint of anyone who decides 30 minutes of droning commentary on Colin Farrell’s new haircut is worth putting up with for a hand job in the men’s room. The good thing about being a guy is that when I eventually bump into the young lad who finger-blasted you on top of a towel dispenser last saturday, we’ll have a shot and laugh our heads off about the time it happened. By the way, for the amount of time you claim to spend in spin class you really must be doing something wrong to sport the thunder thighs you do. Watching you parade around my bedroom in a thong was a<br>
little like watching sea lions mate. Thought you might like to know.</p>
<p>PS.</p>
<p>I BCC’d about 100 people on this email.</p>
<p>Talk to you never,<br>
Brad</p>
</blockquote>
<p><a href="http://www.pocketfives.com/poker-forums/13/holy-sheet-Funny-1338907/p/1338907" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.pocketfives.com/poker-forums/13/holy-sheet-Funny-1338907/p/1338907</a><br>
Some of the replies are funnier than the letters themselves.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 13:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-253773-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/funny-letter/253773.rss">Funny Letter</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
