<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Item given once</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-given-once/171321</link>
    <description>I&#39;m trying to create a sort of hidden finds system into my server such as if a player finds one of my hidden npcs or an object, when they click it, they get a prize of an item or money, now i have everything worked out apart from how i can store the information that says the player either has or hasn&#39;t already collected the prize, otherwise they could just click away merrily and get as much of the prize as they want. I was thinking about adding something to their character files or moreinfo files but I&#39;m not going to try unless i get some advice first on how i could do it because iv never changed how the stored information works so id probably screw it up, anybody know how i can do this? thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2008 09:07:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-given-once/171321.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Item given once</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_qwertyuiop_xx xx qwertyuiop xx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_qwertyuiop_xx">@xx_qwertyuiop_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There’s no other way than storing the information somewhere.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-given-once/171321/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-given-once/171321/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2008 09:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-171321-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-given-once/171321.rss">Item given once</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Item given once</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@webbsta webbsta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/webbsta">@webbsta</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m trying to create a sort of hidden finds system into my server such as if a player finds one of my hidden npcs or an object, when they click it, they get a prize of an item or money, now i have everything worked out apart from how i can store the information that says the player either has or hasn’t already collected the prize, otherwise they could just click away merrily and get as much of the prize as they want. I was thinking about adding something to their character files or moreinfo files but I’m not going to try unless i get some advice first on how i could do it because iv never changed how the stored information works so id probably screw it up, anybody know how i can do this? thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-given-once/171321/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-given-once/171321/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2008 07:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-171321-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/item-given-once/171321.rss">Item given once</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
