<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889</link>
    <description>Hello, and here is my guide to level to 1 to level 99.  Keep in mind that you will probably require a lot of patience to achieve this. Here&#39;s a few things that you can do to keep you preoccupied while you fish.  If you own a laptop, sit down on the couch start fishing and watch a little T.V.
Listen to music, watch Youtube videos, etc.  But remember every so often to check if the spot has change or if your inventory is full.  First of, buy a small net and start fishing to level 5 and get a fishing rod and some bait, continue to fish till level 20, to fly fish.  Once you&#39;re at that level, sell all of the fish you have received and buy about 5k+ feathers and a fly fishing rod.  Fish all the way to level 45 and start doing lobsters.  This step is going to take a while.  Fish all the way to level 65 fishing. Now here is the part you can go two different ways, harpooning or fly fishing.  Yes, you&#39;re all probably thinking, &quot;Fly fishing, wtf?&quot; Well it is no mistake.  Fly fishing is the one of the fastest ways to level fishing at higher levels because you get a full inventory so quickly.  But this method in my opinion is the most boring, so if you little patience you will hate this method.  Here is the swordfishing method.  First go to Fist of Guthix and get enough tokens so that you can get the swordfish gloves.  These are very important.  They raise the Exp from swordfish from 100 to 200.  A very big difference in fishing.  Once you have those keep fishing until level 68 then enter the fishing guild.  Fish their from now on.  Fish to level 76.  You can now do Sharks, but keep in the mind, this the slowest fish to catch, but if you want to make more money while leveling do this.  If you do not care about the money, you can do three methods.  Fly fishing, Lobsters or Swordfishing.  At level 76 you will probably be getting about 2-3 lobsters every single dip.  Fast and little bit of profit.  While swordfishing, you are probably bound to get more swordfish than usual, which means more exp.  Choose any of those three ways to get to level 99 then (Good luck from there on). Some alternatives, that might be useful is to do the stealing creation minigame to get one of the harpoons, which will raise the exp you receive by 100. Congratulations! If you have reached the end of this guide, you are probably at 99 fishing. By now you probably have a couple million in GP.  Thank you for reading my guide and if you have any questions or comments please post them, I don&#39;t bite.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 00:25:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@J_G_I_L_L J G I L L]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/j_g_i_l_l">@J_G_I_L_L</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Greg the Xeno, post:5, topic:278889”]Most people who open this thread are gonna skip the WOT and read the replies. Paragraphs, Please?</p>
<p>Omg, I did just that.[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 00:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278889-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss">Best way to level to 99 fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Vengeance _Vengeance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_vengeance">@_Vengeance</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>RSBot…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 06:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278889-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss">Best way to level to 99 fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eczema3 eczema3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eczema3">@eczema3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tl;dr,</p>
<p>flyfish in shilo.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2009 12:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278889-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss">Best way to level to 99 fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fellixombc fellixombc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fellixombc">@fellixombc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“guitars595, post:1, topic:278889”]Hello, and here is my guide to level to 1 to level 99.  Keep in mind that you will probably require a lot of patience to achieve this. Here’s a few things that you can do to keep you preoccupied while you fish.  If you own a laptop, sit down on the couch start fishing and watch a little T.V.</p>
<p>Listen to music, watch Youtube videos, etc.  But remember every so often to check if the spot has change or if your inventory is full.  First of, buy a small net and start fishing to level 5 and get a fishing rod and some bait, continue to fish till level 20, to fly fish.  Once you’re at that level, sell all of the fish you have received and buy about 5k+ feathers and a fly fishing rod.  Fish all the way to level 45 and start doing lobsters.  This step is going to take a while.  Fish all the way to level 65 fishing.</p>
<p>Now here is the part you can go two different ways, harpooning or fly fishing.  Yes, you’re all probably thinking, “Fly fishing, wtf?” Well it is no mistake.  Fly fishing is the one of the fastest ways to level fishing at higher levels because you get a full inventory so quickly.  But this method in my opinion is the most boring, so if you little patience you will hate this method.  Here is the swordfishing method.  First go to Fist of Guthix and get enough tokens so that you can get the swordfish gloves.  These are very important.  They raise the Exp from swordfish from 100 to 200.  A very big difference in fishing.</p>
<p>Once you have those keep fishing until level 68 then enter the fishing guild.  Fish their from now on.  Fish to level 76.  You can now do Sharks, but keep in the mind, this the slowest fish to catch, but if you want to make more money while leveling do this.  If you do not care about the money, you can do three methods.  Fly fishing, Lobsters or Swordfishing.  At level 76 you will probably be getting about 2-3 lobsters every single dip.  Fast and little bit of profit.  While swordfishing, you are probably bound to get more swordfish than usual, which means more exp.  Choose any of those three ways to get to level 99 then (Good luck from there on). Some alternatives, that might be useful is to do the stealing creation minigame to get one of the harpoons, which will raise the exp you receive by 100. Congratulations! If you have reached the end of this guide, you are probably at 99 fishing.</p>
<p>By now you probably have a couple million in GP.  Thank you for reading my guide and if you have any questions or comments please post them, I don’t bite.[/quote]</p>
<p>Separated it a bit, but honestly, just bot, while watching T.V. So when a random comes, just stop the script or pause it, then just do the random yourself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2009 23:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278889-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss">Best way to level to 99 fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greg_the_Xeno Greg the Xeno]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greg_the_xeno">@Greg_the_Xeno</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Most people who open this thread are gonna skip the WOT and read the replies. Paragraphs, Please?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 15:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278889-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss">Best way to level to 99 fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@atrox atrox_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/atrox">@atrox</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tl;dr</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 14:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278889-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss">Best way to level to 99 fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@slayer215 slayer215]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slayer215">@slayer215</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i dont see “shilo village” anywhere in that</p>
<p>or any paragraphs</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 05:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278889-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss">Best way to level to 99 fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thebeanie TheBeanie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thebeanie">@Thebeanie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No paragraphs?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 23:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278889-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss">Best way to level to 99 fishing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Best way to level to 99 fishing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@guitars595 guitars595]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/guitars595">@guitars595</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, and here is my guide to level to 1 to level 99.  Keep in mind that you will probably require a lot of patience to achieve this. Here’s a few things that you can do to keep you preoccupied while you fish.  If you own a laptop, sit down on the couch start fishing and watch a little T.V.<br>
Listen to music, watch Youtube videos, etc.  But remember every so often to check if the spot has change or if your inventory is full.  First of, buy a small net and start fishing to level 5 and get a fishing rod and some bait, continue to fish till level 20, to fly fish.  Once you’re at that level, sell all of the fish you have received and buy about 5k+ feathers and a fly fishing rod.  Fish all the way to level 45 and start doing lobsters.  This step is going to take a while.  Fish all the way to level 65 fishing. Now here is the part you can go two different ways, harpooning or fly fishing.  Yes, you’re all probably thinking, “Fly fishing, wtf?” Well it is no mistake.  Fly fishing is the one of the fastest ways to level fishing at higher levels because you get a full inventory so quickly.  But this method in my opinion is the most boring, so if you little patience you will hate this method.  Here is the swordfishing method.  First go to Fist of Guthix and get enough tokens so that you can get the swordfish gloves.  These are very important.  They raise the Exp from swordfish from 100 to 200.  A very big difference in fishing.  Once you have those keep fishing until level 68 then enter the fishing guild.  Fish their from now on.  Fish to level 76.  You can now do Sharks, but keep in the mind, this the slowest fish to catch, but if you want to make more money while leveling do this.  If you do not care about the money, you can do three methods.  Fly fishing, Lobsters or Swordfishing.  At level 76 you will probably be getting about 2-3 lobsters every single dip.  Fast and little bit of profit.  While swordfishing, you are probably bound to get more swordfish than usual, which means more exp.  Choose any of those three ways to get to level 99 then (Good luck from there on). Some alternatives, that might be useful is to do the stealing creation minigame to get one of the harpoons, which will raise the exp you receive by 100. Congratulations! If you have reached the end of this guide, you are probably at 99 fishing. By now you probably have a couple million in GP.  Thank you for reading my guide and if you have any questions or comments please post them, I don’t bite.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 18:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-278889-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/best-way-to-level-to-99-fishing/278889.rss">Best way to level to 99 fishing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
