<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Project] WarcraftReviews</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-warcraftreviews/433568</link>
    <description>So I&#39;m starting a new website called WarcraftReviews.  Its goal is not just to give a listing of servers sorted by votes, but by reviews and ratings, which you probably figured out by now why I made a topic about sorting with the Bayesian Estimate.  As a whole it is incomplete, but has the basics and things needed to have its sole purpose functional.  A lot of things will be added, and another goal of it is to have a place for the whole WoW Private Server Community, socializing about events, servers, WoW, etc.

I know the design nor optimization isn&#39;t the best, but I would like for you to browse the site and its features for me and find any flaws, tips, comments, advice, whatever.  I still have a lot of things to learn, but making a website of this purpose is something I really want to do.

edit:  make a topic asking members to test site... don&#39;t even give link. the fuck: http://warcraftreviews.net/
just a note, there&#39;s already one server that register from asking admins of servers to join.  you can test out the reviews on that server to maybe make them feel special.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 02:16:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-warcraftreviews/433568.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Project] WarcraftReviews</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@DEFET DEFET]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/defet">@DEFET</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I’m starting a new website called WarcraftReviews.  Its goal is not just to give a listing of servers sorted by votes, but by reviews and ratings, which you probably figured out by now why I made a topic about sorting with the Bayesian Estimate.  As a whole it is incomplete, but has the basics and things needed to have its sole purpose functional.  A lot of things will be added, and another goal of it is to have a place for the whole WoW Private Server Community, socializing about events, servers, WoW, etc.</p>
<p>I know the design nor optimization isn’t the best, but I would like for you to browse the site and its features for me and find any flaws, tips, comments, advice, whatever.  I still have a lot of things to learn, but making a website of this purpose is something I really want to do.</p>
<p>edit:  make a topic asking members to test site… don’t even give link. the fuck: <a href="http://warcraftreviews.net/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://warcraftreviews.net/</a><br>
just a note, there’s already one server that register from asking admins of servers to join.  you can test out the reviews on that server to maybe make them feel special.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-warcraftreviews/433568/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-warcraftreviews/433568/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 02:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-433568-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-warcraftreviews/433568.rss">[Project] WarcraftReviews</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
