<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ringtone Help Needed</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ringtone-help-needed/102159</link>
    <description>I&#39;m helping a friend get free ringtones because we can&#39;t find any ICP ringtones online. Anyways, I downloaded software that will convert sections of an mp3 to a .amr, and then another program that will upload the file to a mobile friendly website so that my friend can download it to his phone, and set it as his ringtone. We downloaded it fine but we couldn&#39;t set it as a ringtone. The phone says it is not allowed. After research we found that his model phone, the SGH-D807, can only have .DS, and .DM ringtones. We searched google, and cnet for a converter but we can&#39;t find anything having to do with a file exetension .dm, let alone a converter. If anyone has had this problem before, and can help us, it would be greatly appreciated.

Thanks,

Buzzy</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 May 2007 13:05:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ringtone-help-needed/102159.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ringtone Help Needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Buzzy Buzzy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/buzzy">@Buzzy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m helping a friend get free ringtones because we can’t find any ICP ringtones online. Anyways, I downloaded software that will convert sections of an mp3 to a .amr, and then another program that will upload the file to a mobile friendly website so that my friend can download it to his phone, and set it as his ringtone. We downloaded it fine but we couldn’t set it as a ringtone. The phone says it is not allowed. After research we found that his model phone, the SGH-D807, can only have .DS, and .DM ringtones. We searched google, and cnet for a converter but we can’t find anything having to do with a file exetension .dm, let alone a converter. If anyone has had this problem before, and can help us, it would be greatly appreciated.</p>
<p>Thanks,</p>
<p>Buzzy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ringtone-help-needed/102159/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ringtone-help-needed/102159/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2007 13:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-102159-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ringtone-help-needed/102159.rss">Ringtone Help Needed</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
