<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What do you think?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380</link>
    <description>[size=17pt]All the information here is from my own opinion and not facts. Secondly, This is not for a RSPS, it is just in theory. [/size]
   Hey guys, my name is David Pow, to give a little history on myself. I am currently in school and I can not work on my server as much as I want to. I program/work/do everything on ProjectBluelight. I do have to say, I am not a very good programer. Personally, I love video games, but to be honest i&#39;m a noob at everything I play. One day I decided &quot;hey screw you guys, I am going to make my own damn game.&quot; After about three months now I am here. Now to anyone who actually read my little history, I thank you.
   
   Now To the point, I&#39;ve been taking some time away from the computer and of course I still can&#39;t stop thinking of new idea&#39;s. I have looked far down into things. I have looked at every aspect that I can think of. I have been asking, and thinking to myself, &quot;what do I want to see in a game?&quot;  I came to a conclusion &quot;I want to be special, I want to mean something to the game, I want to make a difference, I want a Goal, I want Power&quot;  Now that is what an average person wants to be inside a RPG. What I personally think people want to see from MMO&#39;s; is that a person wants to be recognized by someone else, to have a friend, to interact, to socialize. 

   With taking and using each one of these personal aspects of RPG&#39;s and MMO&#39;s. I have started to come up with a game that is created to suck the player in. I have thought of a system that helps the player set goals and look forward to what they can accomplish. And yet at the same time lets them feel as if they by themselves hold a position of power among the game. I have also rounded it off, so that a player can also feel the pride between him and his &#39;team&#39; (faction, what ever you want to call it) A Great way to get a player to stick to a game, Which JAGEX has done pretty well in, is the leveling system.(is used in almost every game) The leveling system is all based on experience points, widely known as exp... It has a way of just pulling the user in, and progressing him through the game. It is what a lot of big time games use such as - Dungeons and Dragons online, Runescape, Pokemon, etc... But i have configured and even better system similar to an Activity base-Free-Form Base. I have come up with a sturdy game method that I have never seen before. I have not yet completed it fully, so i will not &#39;give away&#39; my idea just yet. In this I hope that I will get great feedback on this. Please tell me what You think of this subject and my theories on RPG&#39;s and MMO&#39;s. 
  
    Guys please do not forget that I come up with most my these ideas myself, So i really posted this to see what you guys think of my work in theory. I would love to be proved wrong or even given a better answer for it will only help me make a better idea for future gaming.

[size=18pt]Please contact me if u have any questions or you just want to hear more about it, or even discuss it with me.[/size]
                   [size=24pt]Contacts -[/size]
[size=14pt]SKYPE - Godofvictory, but my display name is GoV
Chatango - Godofvictory
Email - Projectbluelight@live.com[/size]
[size=18pt] [EDIT][/size] 
I don&#39;t think you guys understood my post... I posted this in theory to state my own opinion on Level-based Games. I did say that I have an idea, but I have not revealed it yet. I am still working on it that is why. Also for the reasons of people stealing this idea. Back to the point though, [size=14pt]I MADE THIS POST SO THAT I COULD SEE YOUR GUY&#39;S THOUGHTS ON LEVEL BASE GAMES, RPG&#39;s, MMO&#39;s, And MMORPG&#39;s. [/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 19:59:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Valthin Valthin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/valthin">@Valthin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cane : Exactly it is the processes like that, that make a player feel as if he is in control, building his addiction to the game<br>
Liquid Magic: I am not looking for idea’s I already have them all… I am looking for a team to share them with. How about u look at my next post and you will see what I mean, it will be made clearer.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 19:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@error.login cane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/error.login">@error.login</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Or your player should alter the game on the path he chooses, I like these games. They make things interesting and everyone’s game will be different. That will attract people and keep them playing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 17:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Liquid_Magic Liquid Magic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/liquid_magic">@Liquid_Magic</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You have all of these amazing ideas, yet you go to moparscape for ideas.  Why don’t you stop planning ahead before you actually do anything?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 17:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@eyeownyew Eyeownyew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eyeownyew">@eyeownyew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lin’s post just gave me an idea.</p>
<p>Try to make an RPG that requires constant attention whilst online.<br>
(I’ve seen that before. I play one currently. Pretty addicting.)</p>
<p>It’s hard for me to get off the game at 2AM. It has no leveling, if you added that and your other ‘amazing ideas’, the game could be very successful.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 16:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Valthin Valthin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/valthin">@Valthin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im not trying to build my rep if thats what u think, and i haven’t stated the great idea yet… I don’t want to spoil my surprise. I am sorry if i did not make that clear, also this post was only for me stating what people want to see from RPG’s and MMO’s that is it. So if you would like to ‘hear’ this ‘great idea’ I would be glad to explain it to you, but i believe this is my fault. For I didn’t make the post clear enough.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 07:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Taking 3 months off and coming here trying to build your way up isn’t going to help at all.</p>
<p>Here’s my opinion on your idea: No. RPGs can’t be unique and they’ll always be the boring sit-and-watch. The goals are always the same: do this so you can do this later then sit and watch some more. Honestly I don’t see anything in your ‘great idea’ that isn’t the base of every other RPG out there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 07:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Valthin Valthin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/valthin">@Valthin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well you see i didn’t put it there because I’m not programming anything, everything I have is in theory. Im just looking for someone to talk to about my ideas mold them shape them to the best then in about a year I plan on creating the mechanic. All I am really looking for is a team to test out my theories.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 04:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck. This should go in general programming, however.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 04:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ix_Soulcist_xI Soulcist]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ix_soulcist_xi">@Ix_Soulcist_xI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>To be honest, I don’t know if the development will last that long and I don’t think it will be a finished project. Nevertheless, I will put some faith into this development and hope that it goes well.</p>
<p>You should focus on what the member’s like which you seem to be doing or plan on doing, so at the moment, I have no advice.</p>
<p>Good luck.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 04:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What do you think?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Valthin Valthin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/valthin">@Valthin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=17pt]All the information here is from my own opinion and not facts. Secondly, This is not for a RSPS, it is just in theory. [/size]<br>
Hey guys, my name is David Pow, to give a little history on myself. I am currently in school and I can not work on my server as much as I want to. I program/work/do everything on ProjectBluelight. I do have to say, I am not a very good programer. Personally, I love video games, but to be honest i’m a noob at everything I play. One day I decided “hey screw you guys, I am going to make my own damn game.” After about three months now I am here. Now to anyone who actually read my little history, I thank you.</p>
<p>Now To the point, I’ve been taking some time away from the computer and of course I still can’t stop thinking of new idea’s. I have looked far down into things. I have looked at every aspect that I can think of. I have been asking, and thinking to myself, “what do I want to see in a game?”  I came to a conclusion “I want to be special, I want to mean something to the game, I want to make a difference, I want a Goal, I want Power”  Now that is what an average person wants to be inside a RPG. What I personally think people want to see from MMO’s; is that a person wants to be recognized by someone else, to have a friend, to interact, to socialize.</p>
<p>With taking and using each one of these personal aspects of RPG’s and MMO’s. I have started to come up with a game that is created to suck the player in. I have thought of a system that helps the player set goals and look forward to what they can accomplish. And yet at the same time lets them feel as if they by themselves hold a position of power among the game. I have also rounded it off, so that a player can also feel the pride between him and his ‘team’ (faction, what ever you want to call it) A Great way to get a player to stick to a game, Which JAGEX has done pretty well in, is the leveling system.(is used in almost every game) The leveling system is all based on experience points, widely known as exp… It has a way of just pulling the user in, and progressing him through the game. It is what a lot of big time games use such as - Dungeons and Dragons online, Runescape, Pokemon, etc… But i have configured and even better system similar to an Activity base-Free-Form Base. I have come up with a sturdy game method that I have never seen before. I have not yet completed it fully, so i will not ‘give away’ my idea just yet. In this I hope that I will get great feedback on this. Please tell me what You think of this subject and my theories on RPG’s and MMO’s.</p>
<pre><code>Guys please do not forget that I come up with most my these ideas myself, So i really posted this to see what you guys think of my work in theory. I would love to be proved wrong or even given a better answer for it will only help me make a better idea for future gaming.
</code></pre>
<p>[size=18pt]Please contact me if u have any questions or you just want to hear more about it, or even discuss it with me.[/size]<br>
[size=24pt]Contacts -[/size]<br>
[size=14pt]SKYPE - Godofvictory, but my display name is GoV<br>
Chatango - Godofvictory<br>
Email - <a href="mailto:Projectbluelight@live.com">Projectbluelight@live.com</a>[/size]<br>
[size=18pt] [EDIT][/size]<br>
I don’t think you guys understood my post… I posted this in theory to state my own opinion on Level-based Games. I did say that I have an idea, but I have not revealed it yet. I am still working on it that is why. Also for the reasons of people stealing this idea. Back to the point though, [size=14pt]I MADE THIS POST SO THAT I COULD SEE YOUR GUY’S THOUGHTS ON LEVEL BASE GAMES, RPG’s, MMO’s, And MMORPG’s. [/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 04:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-378380-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-do-you-think/378380.rss">What do you think?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
