<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Half fixed</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/half-fixed/389810</link>
    <description>[s]Why does it say my server is offline when people connect using the webclient? It does this at random times, online for some people, offline for others, I can log in using the webclient, nobody else can, yesterday they were able to, and one time only 32 bit users were able to log in. What the fuck, am I getting ddosed? I also can&#39;t connect to a lot of RSPS websites, those big private servers, and RL has been down for me for the past few days, but I can go on all the other websites. This isn&#39;t just for one of my household PCs, it&#39;s for all of them. Do I request an IP change? Am I getting ddosed? What&#39;s going on :x[/s]

Well, I had to update my no-ip IP. Was pending deletion &gt;.&gt;
Still can&#39;t figure out why sometimes people can&#39;t connect...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 20:18:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/half-fixed/389810.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Half fixed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-s">Why does it say my server is offline when people connect using the webclient? It does this at random times, online for some people, offline for others, I can log in using the webclient, nobody else can, yesterday they were able to, and one time only 32 bit users were able to log in. What the fuck, am I getting ddosed? I also can’t connect to a lot of RSPS websites, those big private servers, and RL has been down for me for the past few days, but I can go on all the other websites. This isn’t just for one of my household PCs, it’s for all of them. Do I request an IP change? Am I getting ddosed? What’s going on :x</span></p>
<p>Well, I had to update my no-ip IP. Was pending deletion &gt;.&gt;<br>
Still can’t figure out why sometimes people can’t connect…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/half-fixed/389810/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/half-fixed/389810/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 20:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-389810-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/half-fixed/389810.rss">Half fixed</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
