<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071</link>
    <description>From http://www.instructables.com
[b][size=10pt]Intro How to make a blowgun and various ammo[/size][/b]
Of all the things I have ever made, this is one of my favorites. Its an extremely simple and effective design and suprisingly powerful.
I include directions to make 3 different types of ammo for it. Regular pointy ammo, exploding ammo, and high voltage ammo. My favorite is probably the high voltage ammo, it packs quite a dangerous punch. 
As always this project is dangerous, and I think it goes without saying &quot;dont shoot at people, unless its self-defence, then certainly by all means go ahead and shoot at people.&quot;
[size=10pt][b]Step 1 The gun[/b][/size]
Not really much to make. 
Just a simple 5/8&quot; wide 4&#39; long piece of copper or brass tubing. When you buy it make sure there are no kinks or bends in it or else it looses its accuracy.

You can vary the length of the tube to suite your needs / lung capacity. A longer tube will have a greater accuracy and will add speed to the projectile, but you will need the lung capacity to be able to forcefully blow a projectile from it, and a longer pipe is harder to carry around. I settled on 4&#39; because it felt like a good length.
I also spray painted it black for looks.

If you want to be able to carry it over your shoulder you can attatch a shoulder strap. I used an old guitar strap and taped it to each end, but dont put it all the way to the end on the side you are going to blow from.
[img]http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FBM/BH80/FBMBH80JKGEPUCI0TT.medium.jpg[/img]

[size=10pt][b]Step 2 Pointy ammo[/b][/size]
Parts:

1. Box of nails, the sharper the better, I used 8D finish 2-1/2&quot; they do not have large heads on them.
2. Ball of yarn
3. Scissors
4. Tape

Process:

These are the easiest type of ammo to make. Simply cut small strips of yarn (or cut 1 long strip and fold it) and tape it to the back of the nail. Make sure that the tape has a good grip on both the yarn and the nail, so it wont fall off when fired. There needs to be enough yarn so that it will block all the air behind the nail when it is in the gun, but not enough so that it causes excess drag when it is fired. Just experiment until you get the perfect amount of yarn to use.
[img]http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FWF/OXQI/FWFOXQIJ0YEPUCI0WR.medium.jpg[/img]

[size=10pt][b]Step 3 Explody ammo[/b][/size]
Thats right EXPLODY!!

Parts:

1. Drinking straws
2. Strike anywhere matches
3. Flash powder(Bottom of post)
4. Yarn

Process:

Cut the drinking straw to slightly shorter then 2 match lengths. Stick as many pieces of yarn into one end of the straw as possible. The yarn will not only act to to help accelerate the straw, but will also act as a plug preventing the flash powder and match from falling out, so make sure there is plenty of yarn. Insert one match into the other end of the straw, so that the head is facing the open end. Fill the straw with flash powder until the head is reached, but not submerged. 
(Warning: Do this step roughly and youll be missing fingers, make sure to avoid excess jolts on the match heads. A good idea is to go outside and play with the strike anywhere matches, if you are unaware of their sensitivity, thats right play with matches to be safe. Try striking them on different surfaces until they ignite, notice the different amounts of force required to ignite heads with larger white tips, as you will see they are not overly sensitive. In fact they are almost not sensitive enough to make this work, but still better safe then sorry.)
Insert the other match, with the head facing in, so that the 2 match heads are in contact. Pour in slightly more flash powder to cover the 2 heads, if you want you can even fill up the rest of the straw with flash powder for a larger boom (Legal note: I almost forgot, dont use more then 50 miligrams its illegal. Even less then 50 is probably illegal depending on what state you are in. If 50 miligrams isnt enough to fill the straw, you can always mix 50 miligrams with gunpowder as filler, it should still have a nice report to it.)
With both matches in the straw, stuff around the matchstick with tissues or something so the powder does not leak when the straw is horozintal. Just dont stuff it so tight that it prevents the match stick from moving.
[img]http://static2.instructables.com/pub/F89/UKR2/F89UKR2COTEPUCI13J.medium.jpg[/img]

[b][size=10pt]Step 4 Zappy ammo[/size][/b]
High voltage ammo has never been so simple and fun. 

Parts:

1. Photoflash capacitor. The most important thing about it is that it is small enough to fit in the tube. I forget what type of disposable camera I harvested the one I am using from. So the only thing I can suggest is just to test out a range of capacitors, and when you find one that fits perfectly see if the maker sells them in bulk.
2. Disposable camera with exposed charge leads.
3. 2 metal pins
4. Soldering iron and solder

Process:

Solder the 2 pins onto the leads from the capacitor. Put some electrical tape around the base to provent accidental bridging. Because the capacitor is already wide enough to block most of the air behind it, just put a small piece of electrical tape on the back, this not only traps extra air, but prevents you from being shocked if you accidentally breath in, although if you are dumb enough to breathe in you deserve to be shocked. 
Now you may be asking yourself &quot;isnt putting a high voltage capacitor inside a metal tube, and then inserting that tube in my mouth extremely dangerous?&quot; The answer is yes. However to minimize the chance that the leads will be bridged when the capacitor is flying through the tube, place a piece of electrical tape over the needles and bend it down both sides, so it completely coveres all parts of the needle. Push the 2 points just slightly through the tip of the electrical tape. You may not even need to push them through depending on how hard you can blow. The safest thing to do would to be to have the tips of the pins covered, and then driven through the tape and into the target by the force of the impact.
[img]http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FO5/1WY7/FO51WY7IA1EPUCI17L.medium.jpg[/img]

[size=10pt][b]Step 5 Firing[/b][/size]
Use a pencil to push the projectile into the blowgun. 

For pointy ammo: Not much to it, just raise the gun to your mouth, aim it at the target, and give a strong steady blow until the ammo leaves the barrel.

For the explody ammo: Needs an extremely powerful blow to get it to ignite the matches, also needs a pretty solid target. I am currently working on a system that uses those &quot;party-snaps&quot; to ignite a powder, they seem to have a closer sensitivity to what would be the ideal for this project. They are simply tiny rocks coated with silver fulminate, Ill update if I can get a working dart made using them.

For the zappy ammo: Charge the capacitor just before you insert it in the tube. You can charge it by touching the leads to the 2 fingers on a tazer glove, or the charging contacts from a disposable camera. It is a good idea to wear rubber gloves when handling the capacitor to prevent getting shocked. Insert the capacitor into the tube and give a good strong blow. When the it hits the target, as long as it is not an insulator, all the voltage will be dumped into it.
[img]http://static2.instructables.com/pub/F1A/SRCT/F1ASRCTJM9EPUCI290.medium.jpg[/img]

[size=10pt][b]How to make flash powder[/b][/size]
Flash powder is the universal composition for almost all pyrotechnic reports. Bottle rockets, thunderbombs, m-80&#39;s, shells, everything. If it is not enclosed in a container then a bright flash along with a lot of smoke will be produced as shown in the picture. If it is enclosed in a container, even the smallest ammounts will produce a loud report and a violent explosion. 
If you are going to use this to make fireworks please note that fireworks must be legal in your state, you might need some sort of license, and that you can use no more then 50 miligrams per firecracker ANYWHERE no exceptions. Any firework that contains more then 50 miligrams is illegal in every state.
Flash powder was originally used for producing light for cameras about 100 years ago. You have probably seen something to this extent where a photographer holds a wooden handle with a flat platform on top, says look at the birdy, and poof he ignites the flash powder.
There are many different formulas for flash powder, I will explain the simplest one with the easiest chemicals to get your hands on.
[size=10pt][b]Step 1 Chemicals[/b][/size]
The simplest formula for flash powder has only 2 components.

400-600 mesh aluminum powder. The mesh refers to the size of the particles in the powder, it may also be refered to by its actual particle size in microns. For micron size the smaller the number the smaller the particle, for mesh size the higher the number the smaller the particle. A general rule of thumb - the smaller the particle the better. Can be bought on e-bay.

Potassium perchlorate - it is the oxidizer in the reaction. It is getting harder and harder to come by, the CPSC is trying to outlaw many different chemicals, and potassium perchlorate is high on their priority list. As of this writing it can still be bought on unitednuclear.com.
[img]http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FTN/4K1Z/FTN4K1Z4BDEPUCHXG9.medium.jpg[/img]

[size=10pt][b]Step 2 Mix[/b][/size]
Always mix chemicals by their weight. The ratio for the flash powder formula is:

Aluminum powder 30%
Potassium perchlorate 70%

Before you start measuring out the chemicals, it is good practice to neutralize your environment by spraying some anti-static spray around where you will be working. It can be made easily by mixing 1 part fabric softener to 9 parts water and putting it in a spray bottle.

Using the ratio, measure out how much aluminum powder you will use and put it in a plastic ziplock bag (spray the bag with anti-static also) Then measure out how much potassium perchlorate you will use and put it in the bag. Seal the bag and gently shake it around until the chemicals are evenly mixed.

Once the flash powder is mixed do not seal it in any form of container, this will lessen the risk of an accidental explosion.
Do not store the flash powder only make what you are going to use.
[img]http://static2.instructables.com/pub/F9A/K2C0/F9AK2C0AA1EPUCHXJL.medium.jpg[/img]

[b][size=10pt]Step 3 Use[/size][/b]
Place a small amount of flash powder on the ground outside. Make sure the area is clear of any thing that can catch on fire, or any loose objects.
Insert a 10 in. long fuse into the pile.
Light and stand back. When the fuse ignites the flash powder a bright flash and pfft sound will be given off.
A large cloud of smoke will also be produced.

I know its hypocriticla for me to say this but: Please be satisfied with that and do not make fireworks. 

Odds are I know a lot more about fireworks then you, so I have the experience to do these things safely, no matter how dangerous I make it seem in videos or photos. I know exact burning rates of all the fuse I use, proper amount&#39;s of powder to use, and proper containers to use, etc. So please dont try to make fireworks unless you know what you are doing.
[img]http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FB8/AK9L/FB8AK9L37FEPUCHXLD.medium.jpg[/img]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 07:50:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cow821 cow821]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cow821">@cow821</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“goatee, post:9, topic:35071”]Cow how old are you and where do you live (country not street :P)[/quote]12 U.S. No Im not a weapons freak.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 07:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="6" data-topic="35071">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_2.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Cow, shit don’t tell people on here how to make flash powder… people will have lost fingers by tommorow.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If people <em>really</em> wanted to know, they’d find out on their own. Be it <a href="http://www.wikipedia.org" rel="nofollow noopener">www.wikipedia.org</a>, an actual encyclopedia with the compound, or just by asking someone else.<br>
It isn’t hard to find stuff like that on the web - Most things on wiki list chemical compounds, even for stuff like the V and G series nerve gases and so on.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 05:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cow how old are you and where do you live (country not street :P)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 04:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xxlegitxx xxlegitxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxlegitxx">@xxlegitxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="6" data-topic="35071">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/mopman/40/33_2.png" class="avatar"> Mopman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Cow, shit don’t tell people on here how to make flash powder… people will have lost fingers by tommorow.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Good.  Then they won’t spam.  Unless they learn how to type with their toes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 03:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@YourDistracted YourDistracted]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yourdistracted">@YourDistracted</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol i been making flash powder with chemicals stolen from school since year 7.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 02:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Cow, shit don’t tell people on here how to make flash powder… people will have lost fingers by tommorow.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 19:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bloodrayne bloodrayne]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bloodrayne">@bloodrayne</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol I guess its cool, but I just wouldn’t try the nails…lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 17:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@YourDistracted YourDistracted]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yourdistracted">@YourDistracted</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Did i mention i love you cow821?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 14:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cow821 cow821]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cow821">@cow821</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well what if I want to hurt someone? Just kidding I thought it was awsome and made them all myself they work very well. I shot the pencil one at my friend it cut him…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 06:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bloodrayne bloodrayne]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bloodrayne">@bloodrayne</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice. I think that would actually hurt people though… I mean with nails? This is useless unless you want to kill someone <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 06:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cow821 cow821]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cow821">@cow821</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>From <a href="http://www.instructables.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.instructables.com</a><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">[size=10pt]Intro How to make a blowgun and various ammo[/size]</span><br>
Of all the things I have ever made, this is one of my favorites. Its an extremely simple and effective design and suprisingly powerful.<br>
I include directions to make 3 different types of ammo for it. Regular pointy ammo, exploding ammo, and high voltage ammo. My favorite is probably the high voltage ammo, it packs quite a dangerous punch.<br>
As always this project is dangerous, and I think it goes without saying “dont shoot at people, unless its self-defence, then certainly by all means go ahead and shoot at people.”<br>
[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Step 1 The gun</span>[/size]<br>
Not really much to make.<br>
Just a simple 5/8" wide 4’ long piece of copper or brass tubing. When you buy it make sure there are no kinks or bends in it or else it looses its accuracy.</p>
<p>You can vary the length of the tube to suite your needs / lung capacity. A longer tube will have a greater accuracy and will add speed to the projectile, but you will need the lung capacity to be able to forcefully blow a projectile from it, and a longer pipe is harder to carry around. I settled on 4’ because it felt like a good length.<br>
I also spray painted it black for looks.</p>
<p>If you want to be able to carry it over your shoulder you can attatch a shoulder strap. I used an old guitar strap and taped it to each end, but dont put it all the way to the end on the side you are going to blow from.<br>
<img src="http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FBM/BH80/FBMBH80JKGEPUCI0TT.medium.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Step 2 Pointy ammo</span>[/size]<br>
Parts:</p>
<ol>
<li>Box of nails, the sharper the better, I used 8D finish 2-1/2" they do not have large heads on them.</li>
<li>Ball of yarn</li>
<li>Scissors</li>
<li>Tape</li>
</ol>
<p>Process:</p>
<p>These are the easiest type of ammo to make. Simply cut small strips of yarn (or cut 1 long strip and fold it) and tape it to the back of the nail. Make sure that the tape has a good grip on both the yarn and the nail, so it wont fall off when fired. There needs to be enough yarn so that it will block all the air behind the nail when it is in the gun, but not enough so that it causes excess drag when it is fired. Just experiment until you get the perfect amount of yarn to use.<br>
<img src="http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FWF/OXQI/FWFOXQIJ0YEPUCI0WR.medium.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Step 3 Explody ammo</span>[/size]<br>
Thats right EXPLODY!!</p>
<p>Parts:</p>
<ol>
<li>Drinking straws</li>
<li>Strike anywhere matches</li>
<li>Flash powder(Bottom of post)</li>
<li>Yarn</li>
</ol>
<p>Process:</p>
<p>Cut the drinking straw to slightly shorter then 2 match lengths. Stick as many pieces of yarn into one end of the straw as possible. The yarn will not only act to to help accelerate the straw, but will also act as a plug preventing the flash powder and match from falling out, so make sure there is plenty of yarn. Insert one match into the other end of the straw, so that the head is facing the open end. Fill the straw with flash powder until the head is reached, but not submerged.<br>
(Warning: Do this step roughly and youll be missing fingers, make sure to avoid excess jolts on the match heads. A good idea is to go outside and play with the strike anywhere matches, if you are unaware of their sensitivity, thats right play with matches to be safe. Try striking them on different surfaces until they ignite, notice the different amounts of force required to ignite heads with larger white tips, as you will see they are not overly sensitive. In fact they are almost not sensitive enough to make this work, but still better safe then sorry.)<br>
Insert the other match, with the head facing in, so that the 2 match heads are in contact. Pour in slightly more flash powder to cover the 2 heads, if you want you can even fill up the rest of the straw with flash powder for a larger boom (Legal note: I almost forgot, dont use more then 50 miligrams its illegal. Even less then 50 is probably illegal depending on what state you are in. If 50 miligrams isnt enough to fill the straw, you can always mix 50 miligrams with gunpowder as filler, it should still have a nice report to it.)<br>
With both matches in the straw, stuff around the matchstick with tissues or something so the powder does not leak when the straw is horozintal. Just dont stuff it so tight that it prevents the match stick from moving.<br>
<img src="http://static2.instructables.com/pub/F89/UKR2/F89UKR2COTEPUCI13J.medium.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=10pt]Step 4 Zappy ammo[/size]</span><br>
High voltage ammo has never been so simple and fun.</p>
<p>Parts:</p>
<ol>
<li>Photoflash capacitor. The most important thing about it is that it is small enough to fit in the tube. I forget what type of disposable camera I harvested the one I am using from. So the only thing I can suggest is just to test out a range of capacitors, and when you find one that fits perfectly see if the maker sells them in bulk.</li>
<li>Disposable camera with exposed charge leads.</li>
<li>2 metal pins</li>
<li>Soldering iron and solder</li>
</ol>
<p>Process:</p>
<p>Solder the 2 pins onto the leads from the capacitor. Put some electrical tape around the base to provent accidental bridging. Because the capacitor is already wide enough to block most of the air behind it, just put a small piece of electrical tape on the back, this not only traps extra air, but prevents you from being shocked if you accidentally breath in, although if you are dumb enough to breathe in you deserve to be shocked.<br>
Now you may be asking yourself “isnt putting a high voltage capacitor inside a metal tube, and then inserting that tube in my mouth extremely dangerous?” The answer is yes. However to minimize the chance that the leads will be bridged when the capacitor is flying through the tube, place a piece of electrical tape over the needles and bend it down both sides, so it completely coveres all parts of the needle. Push the 2 points just slightly through the tip of the electrical tape. You may not even need to push them through depending on how hard you can blow. The safest thing to do would to be to have the tips of the pins covered, and then driven through the tape and into the target by the force of the impact.<br>
<img src="http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FO5/1WY7/FO51WY7IA1EPUCI17L.medium.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Step 5 Firing</span>[/size]<br>
Use a pencil to push the projectile into the blowgun.</p>
<p>For pointy ammo: Not much to it, just raise the gun to your mouth, aim it at the target, and give a strong steady blow until the ammo leaves the barrel.</p>
<p>For the explody ammo: Needs an extremely powerful blow to get it to ignite the matches, also needs a pretty solid target. I am currently working on a system that uses those “party-snaps” to ignite a powder, they seem to have a closer sensitivity to what would be the ideal for this project. They are simply tiny rocks coated with silver fulminate, Ill update if I can get a working dart made using them.</p>
<p>For the zappy ammo: Charge the capacitor just before you insert it in the tube. You can charge it by touching the leads to the 2 fingers on a tazer glove, or the charging contacts from a disposable camera. It is a good idea to wear rubber gloves when handling the capacitor to prevent getting shocked. Insert the capacitor into the tube and give a good strong blow. When the it hits the target, as long as it is not an insulator, all the voltage will be dumped into it.<br>
<img src="http://static2.instructables.com/pub/F1A/SRCT/F1ASRCTJM9EPUCI290.medium.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">How to make flash powder</span>[/size]<br>
Flash powder is the universal composition for almost all pyrotechnic reports. Bottle rockets, thunderbombs, m-80’s, shells, everything. If it is not enclosed in a container then a bright flash along with a lot of smoke will be produced as shown in the picture. If it is enclosed in a container, even the smallest ammounts will produce a loud report and a violent explosion.<br>
If you are going to use this to make fireworks please note that fireworks must be legal in your state, you might need some sort of license, and that you can use no more then 50 miligrams per firecracker ANYWHERE no exceptions. Any firework that contains more then 50 miligrams is illegal in every state.<br>
Flash powder was originally used for producing light for cameras about 100 years ago. You have probably seen something to this extent where a photographer holds a wooden handle with a flat platform on top, says look at the birdy, and poof he ignites the flash powder.<br>
There are many different formulas for flash powder, I will explain the simplest one with the easiest chemicals to get your hands on.<br>
[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Step 1 Chemicals</span>[/size]<br>
The simplest formula for flash powder has only 2 components.</p>
<p>400-600 mesh aluminum powder. The mesh refers to the size of the particles in the powder, it may also be refered to by its actual particle size in microns. For micron size the smaller the number the smaller the particle, for mesh size the higher the number the smaller the particle. A general rule of thumb - the smaller the particle the better. Can be bought on e-bay.</p>
<p>Potassium perchlorate - it is the oxidizer in the reaction. It is getting harder and harder to come by, the CPSC is trying to outlaw many different chemicals, and potassium perchlorate is high on their priority list. As of this writing it can still be bought on <a href="http://unitednuclear.com" rel="nofollow noopener">unitednuclear.com</a>.<br>
<img src="http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FTN/4K1Z/FTN4K1Z4BDEPUCHXG9.medium.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Step 2 Mix</span>[/size]<br>
Always mix chemicals by their weight. The ratio for the flash powder formula is:</p>
<p>Aluminum powder 30%<br>
Potassium perchlorate 70%</p>
<p>Before you start measuring out the chemicals, it is good practice to neutralize your environment by spraying some anti-static spray around where you will be working. It can be made easily by mixing 1 part fabric softener to 9 parts water and putting it in a spray bottle.</p>
<p>Using the ratio, measure out how much aluminum powder you will use and put it in a plastic ziplock bag (spray the bag with anti-static also) Then measure out how much potassium perchlorate you will use and put it in the bag. Seal the bag and gently shake it around until the chemicals are evenly mixed.</p>
<p>Once the flash powder is mixed do not seal it in any form of container, this will lessen the risk of an accidental explosion.<br>
Do not store the flash powder only make what you are going to use.<br>
<img src="http://static2.instructables.com/pub/F9A/K2C0/F9AK2C0AA1EPUCHXJL.medium.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">[size=10pt]Step 3 Use[/size]</span><br>
Place a small amount of flash powder on the ground outside. Make sure the area is clear of any thing that can catch on fire, or any loose objects.<br>
Insert a 10 in. long fuse into the pile.<br>
Light and stand back. When the fuse ignites the flash powder a bright flash and pfft sound will be given off.<br>
A large cloud of smoke will also be produced.</p>
<p>I know its hypocriticla for me to say this but: Please be satisfied with that and do not make fireworks.</p>
<p>Odds are I know a lot more about fireworks then you, so I have the experience to do these things safely, no matter how dangerous I make it seem in videos or photos. I know exact burning rates of all the fuse I use, proper amount’s of powder to use, and proper containers to use, etc. So please dont try to make fireworks unless you know what you are doing.<br>
<img src="http://static2.instructables.com/pub/FB8/AK9L/FB8AK9L37FEPUCHXLD.medium.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 06:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35071-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/making-a-blow-gun-with-diffrent-ammo-very-detailed-d/35071.rss">Making a blow gun with diffrent ammo(Very detailed) :D</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
