<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A game you should NOT play. EVER!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-game-you-should-not-play-ever/524014</link>
    <description>DARK by Kalypso

Before telling why, I just have to say: NEVER play this game, unless you get paid a hell of a load of cash!
I played the first map and was like &quot;Hmm.. Might be a good game.&quot; Have I ever been this wrong!?
About 12 hours of gameplay and the counter is at less than FOUR = most of the time you spend in it goes to repeating stuff that happened a hundred times before.

Dark. Better name would be Dork, reflecting to the brain dead F&#39;ers that created this garbage.
Story: Linear and stupid. The end was clear to me before playing 30 minutes.
Main character: Looks like a jockey from Left 4 Dead and is blind and does everything others say.
Main character voice acting: They change the voice actor of this Eric guy all the time! Why the F couldn&#39;t they just have this Max Payne (The first) narrator at all times!? The voices don&#39;t feel the same at all! Like &quot;Who is talking? Oh, it&#39;s Eric&#39;s fifth voice actor!&quot;
Controls: Can they be called that seriously? Trying to use the &quot;teleport&quot; while crouching in cover is simply impossible if you try to teleport forward. No jumping?!
Physics: None.
Skills: These could&#39;ve been very, VERY interesting, but no! There are eight &quot;vampire skills&quot; but only using one of them was best suitable in my thoughts as there is no fast or clear switching method between them. Press number 7 to use the healing was the only of those shortcuts I remember. The teleport kill might&#39;ve been number 4. There are more skills than just these eight, like the health increase. However the passive skills section had only one skill worth caring of: Blood meter increase.
Graphics: They did a good job with the lights and graphics were overall &quot;okay&quot;. They used same textures however every-F&#39;ing-where!
Overall gameplay: The beginning was promising but the deeper I got into this game, the more I hated it!

My rating: 0.5/10 - I would&#39;ve rather spent this time piercing my penis with needles. The half point comes from the Max Payne narrator and the design of the &quot;homies club&quot;. The posters around the club were also successful.

(Just in case you wonder why I wrote this: I don&#39;t want to see a game like this anymore. EVER!)

EDIT: I forgot to tell you Eric is no vampire at all, he&#39;s a weakling that has some odd powers. In hand to hand combat Eric sucks nuts. Also: Why doesn&#39;t he use guns?! Seriously he&#39;d have hard to get rid of all of the ammo he&#39;d found on his enemies bodies!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 10:17:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-game-you-should-not-play-ever/524014.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A game you should NOT play. EVER!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ArmorCroc ArmorCroc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/armorcroc">@ArmorCroc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>DARK by Kalypso</p>
<p>Before telling why, I just have to say: NEVER play this game, unless you get paid a hell of a load of cash!<br>
I played the first map and was like “Hmm… Might be a good game.” Have I ever been this wrong!?<br>
About 12 hours of gameplay and the counter is at less than FOUR = most of the time you spend in it goes to repeating stuff that happened a hundred times before.</p>
<p>Dark. Better name would be Dork, reflecting to the brain dead F’ers that created this garbage.<br>
Story: Linear and stupid. The end was clear to me before playing 30 minutes.<br>
Main character: Looks like a jockey from Left 4 Dead and is blind and does everything others say.<br>
Main character voice acting: They change the voice actor of this Eric guy all the time! Why the F couldn’t they just have this Max Payne (The first) narrator at all times!? The voices don’t feel the same at all! Like “Who is talking? Oh, it’s Eric’s fifth voice actor!”<br>
Controls: Can they be called that seriously? Trying to use the “teleport” while crouching in cover is simply impossible if you try to teleport forward. No jumping?!<br>
Physics: None.<br>
Skills: These could’ve been very, VERY interesting, but no! There are eight “vampire skills” but only using one of them was best suitable in my thoughts as there is no fast or clear switching method between them. Press number 7 to use the healing was the only of those shortcuts I remember. The teleport kill might’ve been number 4. There are more skills than just these eight, like the health increase. However the passive skills section had only one skill worth caring of: Blood meter increase.<br>
Graphics: They did a good job with the lights and graphics were overall “okay”. They used same textures however every-F’ing-where!<br>
Overall gameplay: The beginning was promising but the deeper I got into this game, the more I hated it!</p>
<p>My rating: 0.5/10 - I would’ve rather spent this time piercing my penis with needles. The half point comes from the Max Payne narrator and the design of the “homies club”. The posters around the club were also successful.</p>
<p>(Just in case you wonder why I wrote this: I don’t want to see a game like this anymore. EVER!)</p>
<p>EDIT: I forgot to tell you Eric is no vampire at all, he’s a weakling that has some odd powers. In hand to hand combat Eric sucks nuts. Also: Why doesn’t he use guns?! Seriously he’d have hard to get rid of all of the ammo he’d found on his enemies bodies!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-game-you-should-not-play-ever/524014/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-game-you-should-not-play-ever/524014/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 10:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-524014-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-game-you-should-not-play-ever/524014.rss">A game you should NOT play. EVER!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
