<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>AlienSitter Beta</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aliensitter-beta/13710</link>
    <description>Crashe here, as you already saw. Well, this is my second submission to moparisthebest.com. My first submission, a simple slots game, got lost on the host&#39;s servers and didn&#39;t get played. Well, I&#39;m baaack.

You can get it here: [url=http://www.file.sc/ba2cbf/AS_Beta.zip]http://www.file.sc/ba2cbf/AS_Beta.zip[/url]

The read-me is in the folder, just unzip and play away. Lets hope the upload host is reliable.

In a sentence, this game is an Alien-Babysitter. In more than a sentence...

You get to have and name your very own alien. I&#39;m in the very early development stages, so there&#39;s not much to do yet. Later it will include face, color, and facial hair selection, as well as gender.

Tell me what you think! Hope you enjoy!

**EDIT** Please, ignore the unnamed groupbox (i.e. &quot;Groupbox2&quot;). That was one mistake that slipped through before I uploaded the file. I also noticed that when I ran the application on another computer, the text size and font were different. Please adjust the playing screen to accomodate the text sizes, if they change. If you would, please report back any problems you may encounter so that I can fix them.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 09:40:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aliensitter-beta/13710.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>AlienSitter Beta</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@crashe crashe]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/crashe">@crashe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Crashe here, as you already saw. Well, this is my second submission to <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a>. My first submission, a simple slots game, got lost on the host’s servers and didn’t get played. Well, I’m baaack.</p>
<p>You can get it here: <a href="http://www.file.sc/ba2cbf/AS_Beta.zip" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.file.sc/ba2cbf/AS_Beta.zip</a></p>
<p>The read-me is in the folder, just unzip and play away. Lets hope the upload host is reliable.</p>
<p>In a sentence, this game is an Alien-Babysitter. In more than a sentence…</p>
<p>You get to have and name your very own alien. I’m in the very early development stages, so there’s not much to do yet. Later it will include face, color, and facial hair selection, as well as gender.</p>
<p>Tell me what you think! Hope you enjoy!</p>
<p><strong>EDIT</strong> Please, ignore the unnamed groupbox (i.e. “Groupbox2”). That was one mistake that slipped through before I uploaded the file. I also noticed that when I ran the application on another computer, the text size and font were different. Please adjust the playing screen to accomodate the text sizes, if they change. If you would, please report back any problems you may encounter so that I can fix them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aliensitter-beta/13710/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aliensitter-beta/13710/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 09:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13710-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/aliensitter-beta/13710.rss">AlienSitter Beta</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
