<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Fight Caves - Make it start without relogging</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fight-caves-make-it-start-without-relogging/434806</link>
    <description>Hello, before I start asking for this help, I want you to understand I am new to this. I am trying to learn to code servers and I&#39;m stuck on this. Please don&#39;t flame, just help. And if you can&#39;t, don&#39;t bother posting.

Well, as you can read from the title, I need help with fight caves. I&#39;m using Exion&#39;s base and you need to log out in order for fight caves to start. I have looked for fixes on google but all I find is fixes that require the Cycle-based Task Manager by Graham. I&#39;ve tried to follow and understand his tutorial but I seem to be getting stuck. Can you possibly spoon feed me how to add the cycle-based task manager or come up with a fix that does not require it.

Thank-you for your time :)

-(newfag) RegalX</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 20:15:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fight-caves-make-it-start-without-relogging/434806.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Fight Caves - Make it start without relogging</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RegalX RegalX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/regalx">@RegalX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, before I start asking for this help, I want you to understand I am new to this. I am trying to learn to code servers and I’m stuck on this. Please don’t flame, just help. And if you can’t, don’t bother posting.</p>
<p>Well, as you can read from the title, I need help with fight caves. I’m using Exion’s base and you need to log out in order for fight caves to start. I have looked for fixes on google but all I find is fixes that require the Cycle-based Task Manager by Graham. I’ve tried to follow and understand his tutorial but I seem to be getting stuck. Can you possibly spoon feed me how to add the cycle-based task manager or come up with a fix that does not require it.</p>
<p>Thank-you for your time <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>-(newfag) RegalX</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fight-caves-make-it-start-without-relogging/434806/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fight-caves-make-it-start-without-relogging/434806/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 20:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-434806-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fight-caves-make-it-start-without-relogging/434806.rss">[PI] Fight Caves - Make it start without relogging</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
