<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mopar Upgrade?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-upgrade/49090</link>
    <description>Well I was just wondering about the graphics of the oh great Mopar. This experience of feeling like a hacker can only go but so far? The graphics of Mopar are very out of date. Look at the regular Runescape graphics nowadays. The Lesser Demons in Runescape look like detailed apes, but the Mopar Lesser Demons look like sticks with Highheels on. This question comes to mind when you think... How long are the graphics going to stay this way? I do understand it is not completely easy to do this, I also understand and appretiate Mr.Mopar. I am only trying to heighten the gaming experience with a question. Not when? IF! Please share your knowledge.
 
P.S. Dont be a flaming baby because I bring this up! You dont have to read it! 

                                                                                                               Thankyou, Xx Black xX :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 06:08:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-upgrade/49090.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mopar Upgrade?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Xx_Black_xX Xx Black xX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_black_xx">@Xx_Black_xX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well I was just wondering about the graphics of the oh great Mopar. This experience of feeling like a hacker can only go but so far? The graphics of Mopar are very out of date. Look at the regular Runescape graphics nowadays. The Lesser Demons in Runescape look like detailed apes, but the Mopar Lesser Demons look like sticks with Highheels on. This question comes to mind when you think… How long are the graphics going to stay this way? I do understand it is not completely easy to do this, I also understand and appretiate Mr.Mopar. I am only trying to heighten the gaming experience with a question. Not when? IF! Please share your knowledge.</p>
<p>P.S. Dont be a flaming baby because I bring this up! You dont have to read it!</p>
<pre><code>                                                                                                           Thankyou, Xx Black xX :)</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-upgrade/49090/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-upgrade/49090/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 06:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-49090-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mopar-upgrade/49090.rss">Mopar Upgrade?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
