<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Confused!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/191301</link>
    <description>Ok so today i decided to make a part of the dual arena safe and it worked!! so i thought hell ill do the same to capes too so people cant attk people buying capes...  So i put the code in, and it made the dual arena where u stake not work... meaning u couldnt attack anyone.. so i deleted the capes one and its fixed but the capes is wild again... What did i do wrong?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 21, 2008, 03:23:57 AM[/size][hr]lemme explain this lil better....  I made the cords for the dual arena not in the arena but where the alter is and bank...  I made that area safe...  So i did the same to the capes area, and that made the capes area safe..  But the arena where people fite is safe as well.. so i had to delete the capes cords.  now u can attack in the arena but the u can also attack in the capes are (where u buy skill capes)  should i just move the capes somewhere else or does someone have a solution&gt;?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 17:18:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/191301.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Confused!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@x0_0wn x0 0wn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x0_0wn">@x0_0wn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You’ve mucked up your coords.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/191301/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/191301/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 17:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-191301-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/191301.rss">Confused!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Confused!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bhpkyeah satesql]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bhpkyeah">@bhpkyeah</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok so today i decided to make a part of the dual arena safe and it worked!! so i thought hell ill do the same to capes too so people cant attk people buying capes…  So i put the code in, and it made the dual arena where u stake not work… meaning u couldnt attack anyone… so i deleted the capes one and its fixed but the capes is wild again… What did i do wrong?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: March 21, 2008, 03:23:57 AM[/size][hr]lemme explain this lil better…  I made the cords for the dual arena not in the arena but where the alter is and bank…  I made that area safe…  So i did the same to the capes area, and that made the capes area safe…  But the arena where people fite is safe as well… so i had to delete the capes cords.  now u can attack in the arena but the u can also attack in the capes are (where u buy skill capes)  should i just move the capes somewhere else or does someone have a solution&gt;?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/191301/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/191301/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 13:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-191301-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/191301.rss">Confused!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
