<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Confused</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/459211</link>
    <description>Been working on a project for about 2 and a half months, and decided to host it off my computer for a few days so my friends can find bugs.  I came home from work today and tried logging in, and it wouldn&#39;t let me login on my personal client. my friends cannot connect either tho when I released it to them I had 13 of them online for like 5 hours before I went to bed. I checked my portforwarding, restarted server and then restarted my computer, and I still haven&#39;t found out why the hell it&#39;s not letting anyone login? All it says on login attempt is &quot;error connecting to server&quot; Can someone add me on skype, I have a microphone and I can screenshare my problem and explain to the best of my knowledge whats happening. 

                                      Skype name Nick.Cholka</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 01:24:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/459211.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Confused</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sounds like you have a deadlocking issue.</p>
<p><a href="http://run-server.org/runescape-development/google/snippets/290951-pi-deadlock-issue-fix.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://run-server.org/runescape-development/google/snippets/290951-pi-deadlock-issue-fix.html</a><br>
(Add an ‘e’ to the end of ‘run’)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/459211/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/459211/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 01:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459211-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/459211.rss">Confused</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Confused</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@youngnino youngnino]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/youngnino">@youngnino</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Been working on a project for about 2 and a half months, and decided to host it off my computer for a few days so my friends can find bugs.  I came home from work today and tried logging in, and it wouldn’t let me login on my personal client. my friends cannot connect either tho when I released it to them I had 13 of them online for like 5 hours before I went to bed. I checked my portforwarding, restarted server and then restarted my computer, and I still haven’t found out why the hell it’s not letting anyone login? All it says on login attempt is “error connecting to server” Can someone add me on skype, I have a microphone and I can screenshare my problem and explain to the best of my knowledge whats happening.</p>
<pre><code>                                  Skype name Nick.Cholka</code></pre>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/459211/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/459211/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 01:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-459211-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/confused/459211.rss">Confused</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
