<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>508 Server NPC, Item, etc. Files</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-npc-item-etc-files/243723</link>
    <description>Hey everyone!

I joined this forum a while ago, but I never even posted anything... :) I wanna get back into some RS private server stuff, but it&#39;s been a while since I used some of the old servers, and it seems that things have changed with the 508 servers.

First off, I&#39;m wondering if anyone has any kind of documentation for Palidino76&#39;s files in the data folder. I&#39;m also wondering if dialogue and shops are possible in 508, because I see no files that have to do with those.

Second, I&#39;m wondering what I have to call/instance to create new objects, NPCs, etc in the source code itself.


Thanks! :D[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 14, 2008, 08:56:53 pm[/size][hr]-Bump-

Anyone?

I looked at the source and figured out how to spawn NPCs.

However, I can&#39;t seem to figure out how to make item drops, or modify the location of certain objects, or add shops and dialogue.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 14, 2008, 08:58:11 pm[/size][hr]I think I edited my post instead of bumping the thread, lol.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 14, 2008, 09:48:30 pm[/size][hr]Hm, I think there isn&#39;t any dialogue stuff in 508...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 20:39:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-npc-item-etc-files/243723.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>508 Server NPC, Item, etc. Files</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xyzz123 xyzz123]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xyzz123">@xyzz123</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey everyone!</p>
<p>I joined this forum a while ago, but I never even posted anything… <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> I wanna get back into some RS private server stuff, but it’s been a while since I used some of the old servers, and it seems that things have changed with the 508 servers.</p>
<p>First off, I’m wondering if anyone has any kind of documentation for Palidino76’s files in the data folder. I’m also wondering if dialogue and shops are possible in 508, because I see no files that have to do with those.</p>
<p>Second, I’m wondering what I have to call/instance to create new objects, NPCs, etc in the source code itself.</p>
<p>Thanks! :D[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 14, 2008, 08:56:53 pm[/size][hr]-Bump-</p>
<p>Anyone?</p>
<p>I looked at the source and figured out how to spawn NPCs.</p>
<p>However, I can’t seem to figure out how to make item drops, or modify the location of certain objects, or add shops and dialogue.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 14, 2008, 08:58:11 pm[/size][hr]I think I edited my post instead of bumping the thread, lol.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: November 14, 2008, 09:48:30 pm[/size][hr]Hm, I think there isn’t any dialogue stuff in 508…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-npc-item-etc-files/243723/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-npc-item-etc-files/243723/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 20:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-243723-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-server-npc-item-etc-files/243723.rss">508 Server NPC, Item, etc. Files</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
