<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>~~Silver Age Roleplay Server (1.1)~~</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silver-age-roleplay-server-1-1/437813</link>
    <description>[IMG]http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/SilverAge.png[/img]

Website: Silverage.enjin.com

Have you ever been on a minecraft &quot;roleplay&quot; server, and then realized that it was nothing more than World of Warcraft in Minecraft, with the word Roleplay in the title? This is not the case for Silver Age. On this server, we encourage the interaction and stories of real roleplaying, and discourage pvp, spawnkilling, and many other things that many &quot;roleplay&quot; servers seem to have. If you have been searching for a roleplay server where you can really roleplay your character in a world built by us, then you have come to the right place. You will not be subject to the pre-made story of the server. Our lore has many different directions it can take, and what direction it takes is reliant on you, the player.

Announcements:
(1) You need spout to join this server!

Lore

Pre-History
Many, many thousands of years ago, there was nothing but magical essence floating within the Deep. Whenever one essence collided with another, a new object was formed, but these objects were small and useless. There was one being: Xaeos. He watched this happen for Eons, in pain. He was not the god who created the essences and so he could not touch them. Just wait for them to collide. One day, by chance, the essence of nature collided with the essence of life and born from it, were the Lymerians. They were mystical creatures who were slightly humanoid, but also spirit-like too. They were the first creations, but did not have a place to call home, or a place that they could root themselves to, and so Xaeos created the first land, and planted a sapling upon the ground and then said, “Protect this sapling with your life, for your life shall depend upon this sapling.” The Lymerians never left the sapling, and over time, more essences collided to form creatures, such as Humans and Rinese. The Lymerians developed tools and weapons to help defend the sapling from attacks from other creatures. For the next three thousand years, this is what happened, with each race advancing their technology and forming tribes, constantly battling each other. Over these thousands of years, the tree grew until it was miles tall and it’s roots extended down into the nether. The second oldest race, the Stonefaces, or “Rinese” in the Lymerias language, lived around the mountains. They were vaguely humanoid, but had grey, clay-colored faces and their skin had a rock-like hardness to it. They made great miners and blacksmiths. The two races lived in solitude for the entire Growth Age, or the first three thousand years of the of Agazatra.

2123 B.C - 0 A.C:
The first 2123 years of recorded time was called the Advancement Age. It was the age in which the Rinese and the Lymerians first made contact as the world’s most advanced races, as well as when the Yarlak race and the Carmakan race entered Agazatra. In 2123 B.C (B.C = Before Conquer), the Lymerians began to record time based on the movement of the sun and the planets in the Deep. hundreds of years later, the Rinese came into contact with the Lymerians. They both impressed each other with their various creations: The Rinese catapult and the Islari magic. The Rinese and Lymerian sremained allies until the Yarlaks entered northern Agazatra. The Yarlaks were a humanoid race with large beards and who preferred battle-axes and maces to the common Rinese sword. The Yarlaks were a more or less nomadic race who used brute force and fire to pillage and destroy various scattered towns. Soon, they had carved out a spot for themselves in Agazatra, and they, the Lymerians, and the Rinese were the only ones left. In about 200 B.C, the last race to enter Agazatra, the Cherzian people, arrived in the central plains from across the Great Sea. They were the only out of the four present races who had mastered the art of Sea Travel. They also did not hunt for their food, they used advanced Agriculture, unlike the cooking skills of the Rinese, the hunting skills of the Yarlaks, and the harvesting of fruit from trees that the Lymerians practiced. They tried to communicate with the Lymerians and learn their magical ways. They explained how they came from the deserts of the far west, and used sandstone from the beach to build a new city on the coast, called Cherzia. Over time, the Islari and the Cherzians became allies. When the Cherzians began conquest of Agazatra in 40 B.C, they promised the Islari that they would protect the Tree of Life, and in return, the Islari taught them magic and willingly let them extend their borders around their land. The Cherzian Empire had been born.

Conquest (40 B.C- 0 A.C)
The Empire knew that it’s biggest enemy were the Rinese. They were quick and intelligent warriors, and had skin made of some type of thin stone - a sword would not do as much to them as they would a different race. Because of this, they decided to conquer the Yarlak first. They did not have to however, because the Yarlak were already enemies of the Rinese. They willingly joined the empire, and fought against the Rinese. From 36 B.C - 3 B.C, the two empires were locked in a state of stalemate, until the Rinese led a sneak attack on Cherzia . They blew the walls up with a material known as TnT. They had just invented it and tested it on Cherzia. They razed the city, and nearly destroyed the heart of the Empire, but then they retreated. One year later, Cherzia was being rebuilt and the Emperor had ceased attacks of the Rinese empire for the time being. He requested a talk with the leader of the Rinese, and asked him why he had stopped attacking Cherzia. The leader of Rina responded, saying that he only wanted to do as much damage to the Cherzians as the Cherzians had done to them. After that, realizing that fighting for this long was pointless because neither of them would win, the Rinese joined the empire because it was in their best interest to bond with the rest of Agazatra and defend themselves from threats elsewhere. The Cherzian Empire became officially complete in 0 A.C, and has been peacefully thriving for seventy years. Each race but the Islari have their own city and the Islari live in the College of Cil’Adil, or near the Tree of Life itself.

(Recently: 0 A.C. - 70 A.C.)

The age beginning at the end of the conquering has been called the Silver Age. The Emperor is Emperor Eliri Romanus IV. The empire is in a peaceful state. Emperor Eliri has passed a number of acts to prevent citizens from making new cities or factions within the empire, but allows the creation of small guilds. As time goes on, there have been reports of necromancers raising portals to an alternate dimension. The Emperor&#39;s current goal is to put a stop to this, but as chaotic as things get, the daily life of the citizens goes on.

Gods

- Xaeos: The God of All and the Lord of Fate-
Xaranor: The King of Gods, and the God of time and intelligence-
Aquarius: The God of the Ocean and Sleep-
Zilanth: The God of the Nether, Fire, and Magic-
Fyrendyr: The God of Weapons, Armor, and the Forge-
Mayaja: The God of Wisdom and Love

Races

The Cherzian

The Cherzians are the bulk of the Empire. They migrated to Agazatra from over the desert, displayed in their unique architectural style that mixes bricks with sandstone. About 40% of the population of the empire is Cherzian. They usually have a range of fair to tan skin, but they have all ranges. They are known for their farming skills, having invented it. Their home city is New Cherzia, but they can be found in all of the cities. They are known to be adept archers, farmers, and swordsmen, but are especially known to be stealthy and agile warriors.Average Life Span: 87 Years Old
Leader: Emperor Tilius Eliri IV
City: New Cherzia (The Capital of the Empire)Cannot be: Redstone Engineer

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

The Rinese

The Rinese are the second oldest race, living on a secluded island that is connected to the mainland by a bridge. They are known for their redstone capabilities, as well as their close friendship with the Islari. They have greyish, clay-like skin, and are known to be taller than the average Carmakan, their height averaging about 5&#39;9. They are mostly found in their home city, as well as Cherzia.During the great conquering, they were the hardest enemies, destroying parts of Cherzia with their redstone weapons. They are known to be great engineers, miners, and blacksmiths.Average Life Span: 123 Years Old
Representative: Aero Bohr
City: Ionia
Cannot Be: Mages

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

The Yarlak

The Yarlak are a warlike race who live in the north. They were the second race to join the Empire. They are known for their smiths and swordsman. They are about tied with the Rinese in terms of population. They are very similar to the Carmakan, possibly stemming from the same race originally and then splitting apart. They are polar opposites of the Islari, but maintain a general friendship with them after they joined the empire. They are known to be great swordsmen, blacksmiths, and lumberjacks.Average Life Span: 87 Years Old
Representative: Throren
City: Borikheim
Cannot Be: Cleric, Redstone Engineer

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

The Lymerians

The Lymerians are a nymph-like race who are the oldest race, as well as the longest lived race. They have no city, but many build their own houses in the large forest that surrounds the College of Cil&#39;Adil, and the Tree of Life, Cil&#39;Adil. They are classical magicians and clerics, not being able to be swordsmen, The leader of the College of Cil&#39;Adil is is a Lymerian and the oldest man in the world. His name Val&#39;um. They do not have a city and so are found in all cities, but mostly New Cherzia or a house in the wilderness. They are known to be great magi, clerics, and engineers.
Average Life Span: 1010 Years Old
Representative: Val&#39;um
City: None
Cannot Be: Swordsmen
Miner


~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Classes

[IMG]http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/RedstoneApprentice.png[/img]

NOTE: Those who apply for redstone engineer cannot already know redstone in their applications. They have to go to the College of Cil&#39;Adil IN GAME, and attend Val&#39;um&#39;s classes.

[IMG]http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/MageClass.png[/img]

NOTE: Those who apply for mage cannot already know magic in their applications. They have to go to the College of Cil&#39;Adil IN GAME, and attend Val&#39;um&#39;s classes.

[IMG]http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/ClericClass.png[/img]

NOTE: Those who apply for cleric cannot already know magic in their applications, nor can they know how to make potions. They have to go to the College of Cil&#39;Adil IN GAME, and attend Val&#39;um&#39;s classes. Also, for now, clerics can only use healing spells. When the nether is released in the first expansion, they will be able to go into the nether and collect their ingredients for potions. Whatever ingredients they can obtain now, they can use.

[IMG]http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/BlacksmithClass.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/FarmerClass.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/MinerClass.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/SwordsmenClass.png[/img]

[IMG]http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/WoodsmanClass.png[/img]

Rules:
No PvP without RP. You are allowed to attack someone who has a death bounty on his/her head, or if you have a real RP reason to kill them. You are not allowed to make a quick descicion to kill someone because they have armor you want. You are allowed to attempt to rob someone, but you must roleplay it out, by demanding what you want, and then watching how the victim responds.
Executions:
If you do something very bad (e.g. Murder, Creation of a city, Assaulting the emperor), you will have a large bounty put on your head, and you will be exiled from all cities. If a guard finds you, he has permission to kill you and once he has killed you, you will be added to the character execution list. We will have execution events every now and then, and your character will be executed (if you’re not online, then you will need to get a new character), but it is advised to be online when the event is happening. Once your character is executed, you can start a new character with a new starterkit and everything.

No metagaming
No powergaming
No griefing at all unless you are breaking into a wanted man&#39;s house, or it is supported by the law
No swearing (As far I as I know, kids play on this server as well, so if you character has something bad to say, use *swears*).
Do not do anything that might disrupt roleplay. I am pretty sure that the whitelist process filters out anybody who might do this but this is a strict rule, and you will be banned for breaking it. I am aiming to host a serious roleplay server.
The staff and I reserve the right to ban someone for the breaking of any of these rules on the first offense. We do, however, accept ban disputes, so if you feel that you have been banned wrongly, you can pm me telling me your username, why you were banned, and why you think that you should be unbanned.
Join Us!
To join us, you can go to the website (click the picture at the top of the post), read all of the rules, and then post the whitelist application in the appropriate forum.


StaffAdmins

:- Gamer9726 (Emperor Tilius Romanus Eliri IV)
- Elbowgrease (Aero_Bohr, Representative of the Rinese)
- Devilmonkey6 (Val&#39;um, Representative of the Islari)
- Karnoshan (Throren, Representative of the Yarlak)

Moderators-

- Apple_Calister
- Futurii
- Marcellan
- Darkside_97
- Goudkindin
- Open Spot
- Open Spot
- Open Spot

No new players can ask for moderator, and if you ask for it, you will never get it. If there is a spot open and I see that you are helpful, responsible, and a good roleplayer, I will notify you and ask you to be a moderator.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 16:49:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silver-age-roleplay-server-1-1/437813.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>~~Silver Age Roleplay Server (1.1)~~</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gamer9726 gamer9726]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gamer9726">@gamer9726</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/SilverAge.png" title="SilverAge.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/SilverAge.png" alt width="690" height="130"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">SilverAge.png</span><span class="informations">865×164</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Website: <a href="http://Silverage.enjin.com" rel="nofollow noopener">Silverage.enjin.com</a></p>
<p>Have you ever been on a minecraft “roleplay” server, and then realized that it was nothing more than World of Warcraft in Minecraft, with the word Roleplay in the title? This is not the case for Silver Age. On this server, we encourage the interaction and stories of real roleplaying, and discourage pvp, spawnkilling, and many other things that many “roleplay” servers seem to have. If you have been searching for a roleplay server where you can really roleplay your character in a world built by us, then you have come to the right place. You will not be subject to the pre-made story of the server. Our lore has many different directions it can take, and what direction it takes is reliant on you, the player.</p>
<p>Announcements:<br>
(1) You need spout to join this server!</p>
<p>Lore</p>
<p>Pre-History<br>
Many, many thousands of years ago, there was nothing but magical essence floating within the Deep. Whenever one essence collided with another, a new object was formed, but these objects were small and useless. There was one being: Xaeos. He watched this happen for Eons, in pain. He was not the god who created the essences and so he could not touch them. Just wait for them to collide. One day, by chance, the essence of nature collided with the essence of life and born from it, were the Lymerians. They were mystical creatures who were slightly humanoid, but also spirit-like too. They were the first creations, but did not have a place to call home, or a place that they could root themselves to, and so Xaeos created the first land, and planted a sapling upon the ground and then said, “Protect this sapling with your life, for your life shall depend upon this sapling.” The Lymerians never left the sapling, and over time, more essences collided to form creatures, such as Humans and Rinese. The Lymerians developed tools and weapons to help defend the sapling from attacks from other creatures. For the next three thousand years, this is what happened, with each race advancing their technology and forming tribes, constantly battling each other. Over these thousands of years, the tree grew until it was miles tall and it’s roots extended down into the nether. The second oldest race, the Stonefaces, or “Rinese” in the Lymerias language, lived around the mountains. They were vaguely humanoid, but had grey, clay-colored faces and their skin had a rock-like hardness to it. They made great miners and blacksmiths. The two races lived in solitude for the entire Growth Age, or the first three thousand years of the of Agazatra.</p>
<p>2123 B.C - 0 A.C:<br>
The first 2123 years of recorded time was called the Advancement Age. It was the age in which the Rinese and the Lymerians first made contact as the world’s most advanced races, as well as when the Yarlak race and the Carmakan race entered Agazatra. In 2123 B.C (B.C = Before Conquer), the Lymerians began to record time based on the movement of the sun and the planets in the Deep. hundreds of years later, the Rinese came into contact with the Lymerians. They both impressed each other with their various creations: The Rinese catapult and the Islari magic. The Rinese and Lymerian sremained allies until the Yarlaks entered northern Agazatra. The Yarlaks were a humanoid race with large beards and who preferred battle-axes and maces to the common Rinese sword. The Yarlaks were a more or less nomadic race who used brute force and fire to pillage and destroy various scattered towns. Soon, they had carved out a spot for themselves in Agazatra, and they, the Lymerians, and the Rinese were the only ones left. In about 200 B.C, the last race to enter Agazatra, the Cherzian people, arrived in the central plains from across the Great Sea. They were the only out of the four present races who had mastered the art of Sea Travel. They also did not hunt for their food, they used advanced Agriculture, unlike the cooking skills of the Rinese, the hunting skills of the Yarlaks, and the harvesting of fruit from trees that the Lymerians practiced. They tried to communicate with the Lymerians and learn their magical ways. They explained how they came from the deserts of the far west, and used sandstone from the beach to build a new city on the coast, called Cherzia. Over time, the Islari and the Cherzians became allies. When the Cherzians began conquest of Agazatra in 40 B.C, they promised the Islari that they would protect the Tree of Life, and in return, the Islari taught them magic and willingly let them extend their borders around their land. The Cherzian Empire had been born.</p>
<p>Conquest (40 B.C- 0 A.C)<br>
The Empire knew that it’s biggest enemy were the Rinese. They were quick and intelligent warriors, and had skin made of some type of thin stone - a sword would not do as much to them as they would a different race. Because of this, they decided to conquer the Yarlak first. They did not have to however, because the Yarlak were already enemies of the Rinese. They willingly joined the empire, and fought against the Rinese. From 36 B.C - 3 B.C, the two empires were locked in a state of stalemate, until the Rinese led a sneak attack on Cherzia . They blew the walls up with a material known as TnT. They had just invented it and tested it on Cherzia. They razed the city, and nearly destroyed the heart of the Empire, but then they retreated. One year later, Cherzia was being rebuilt and the Emperor had ceased attacks of the Rinese empire for the time being. He requested a talk with the leader of the Rinese, and asked him why he had stopped attacking Cherzia. The leader of Rina responded, saying that he only wanted to do as much damage to the Cherzians as the Cherzians had done to them. After that, realizing that fighting for this long was pointless because neither of them would win, the Rinese joined the empire because it was in their best interest to bond with the rest of Agazatra and defend themselves from threats elsewhere. The Cherzian Empire became officially complete in 0 A.C, and has been peacefully thriving for seventy years. Each race but the Islari have their own city and the Islari live in the College of Cil’Adil, or near the Tree of Life itself.</p>
<p>(Recently: 0 A.C. - 70 A.C.)</p>
<p>The age beginning at the end of the conquering has been called the Silver Age. The Emperor is Emperor Eliri Romanus IV. The empire is in a peaceful state. Emperor Eliri has passed a number of acts to prevent citizens from making new cities or factions within the empire, but allows the creation of small guilds. As time goes on, there have been reports of necromancers raising portals to an alternate dimension. The Emperor’s current goal is to put a stop to this, but as chaotic as things get, the daily life of the citizens goes on.</p>
<p>Gods</p>
<ul>
<li>Xaeos: The God of All and the Lord of Fate-<br>
Xaranor: The King of Gods, and the God of time and intelligence-<br>
Aquarius: The God of the Ocean and Sleep-<br>
Zilanth: The God of the Nether, Fire, and Magic-<br>
Fyrendyr: The God of Weapons, Armor, and the Forge-<br>
Mayaja: The God of Wisdom and Love</li>
</ul>
<p>Races</p>
<p>The Cherzian</p>
<p>The Cherzians are the bulk of the Empire. They migrated to Agazatra from over the desert, displayed in their unique architectural style that mixes bricks with sandstone. About 40% of the population of the empire is Cherzian. They usually have a range of fair to tan skin, but they have all ranges. They are known for their farming skills, having invented it. Their home city is New Cherzia, but they can be found in all of the cities. They are known to be adept archers, farmers, and swordsmen, but are especially known to be stealthy and agile warriors.Average Life Span: 87 Years Old<br>
Leader: Emperor Tilius Eliri IV<br>
City: New Cherzia (The Capital of the Empire)Cannot be: Redstone Engineer</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">
The Rinese

The Rinese are the second oldest race, living on a secluded island that is connected to the mainland by a bridge. They are known for their redstone capabilities, as well as their close friendship with the Islari. They have greyish, clay-like skin, and are known to be taller than the average Carmakan, their height averaging about 5'9. They are mostly found in their home city, as well as Cherzia.During the great conquering, they were the hardest enemies, destroying parts of Cherzia with their redstone weapons. They are known to be great engineers, miners, and blacksmiths.Average Life Span: 123 Years Old
Representative: Aero Bohr
City: Ionia
Cannot Be: Mages

</code></pre>
<p>The Yarlak</p>
<p>The Yarlak are a warlike race who live in the north. They were the second race to join the Empire. They are known for their smiths and swordsman. They are about tied with the Rinese in terms of population. They are very similar to the Carmakan, possibly stemming from the same race originally and then splitting apart. They are polar opposites of the Islari, but maintain a general friendship with them after they joined the empire. They are known to be great swordsmen, blacksmiths, and lumberjacks.Average Life Span: 87 Years Old<br>
Representative: Throren<br>
City: Borikheim<br>
Cannot Be: Cleric, Redstone Engineer</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">
The Lymerians

The Lymerians are a nymph-like race who are the oldest race, as well as the longest lived race. They have no city, but many build their own houses in the large forest that surrounds the College of Cil'Adil, and the Tree of Life, Cil'Adil. They are classical magicians and clerics, not being able to be swordsmen, The leader of the College of Cil'Adil is is a Lymerian and the oldest man in the world. His name Val'um. They do not have a city and so are found in all cities, but mostly New Cherzia or a house in the wilderness. They are known to be great magi, clerics, and engineers.
Average Life Span: 1010 Years Old
Representative: Val'um
City: None
Cannot Be: Swordsmen
Miner


</code></pre>
<p>Classes</p>
<p><img src="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/RedstoneApprentice.png" alt width="624" height="159"></p>
<p>NOTE: Those who apply for redstone engineer cannot already know redstone in their applications. They have to go to the College of Cil’Adil IN GAME, and attend Val’um’s classes.</p>
<p><img src="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/MageClass.png" alt width="624" height="159"></p>
<p>NOTE: Those who apply for mage cannot already know magic in their applications. They have to go to the College of Cil’Adil IN GAME, and attend Val’um’s classes.</p>
<p><img src="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/ClericClass.png" alt width="624" height="159"></p>
<p>NOTE: Those who apply for cleric cannot already know magic in their applications, nor can they know how to make potions. They have to go to the College of Cil’Adil IN GAME, and attend Val’um’s classes. Also, for now, clerics can only use healing spells. When the nether is released in the first expansion, they will be able to go into the nether and collect their ingredients for potions. Whatever ingredients they can obtain now, they can use.</p>
<p><img src="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/BlacksmithClass.png" alt width="624" height="159"></p>
<p><img src="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/FarmerClass.png" alt width="624" height="159"></p>
<p><img src="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/MinerClass.png" alt width="624" height="159"></p>
<p><img src="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/SwordsmenClass.png" alt width="624" height="159"></p>
<p><img src="http://i1200.photobucket.com/albums/bb331/turtwig26/WoodsmanClass.png" alt width="624" height="159"></p>
<p>Rules:<br>
No PvP without RP. You are allowed to attack someone who has a death bounty on his/her head, or if you have a real RP reason to kill them. You are not allowed to make a quick descicion to kill someone because they have armor you want. You are allowed to attempt to rob someone, but you must roleplay it out, by demanding what you want, and then watching how the victim responds.<br>
Executions:<br>
If you do something very bad (e.g. Murder, Creation of a city, Assaulting the emperor), you will have a large bounty put on your head, and you will be exiled from all cities. If a guard finds you, he has permission to kill you and once he has killed you, you will be added to the character execution list. We will have execution events every now and then, and your character will be executed (if you’re not online, then you will need to get a new character), but it is advised to be online when the event is happening. Once your character is executed, you can start a new character with a new starterkit and everything.</p>
<p>No metagaming<br>
No powergaming<br>
No griefing at all unless you are breaking into a wanted man’s house, or it is supported by the law<br>
No swearing (As far I as I know, kids play on this server as well, so if you character has something bad to say, use <em>swears</em>).<br>
Do not do anything that might disrupt roleplay. I am pretty sure that the whitelist process filters out anybody who might do this but this is a strict rule, and you will be banned for breaking it. I am aiming to host a serious roleplay server.<br>
The staff and I reserve the right to ban someone for the breaking of any of these rules on the first offense. We do, however, accept ban disputes, so if you feel that you have been banned wrongly, you can pm me telling me your username, why you were banned, and why you think that you should be unbanned.<br>
Join Us!<br>
To join us, you can go to the website (click the picture at the top of the post), read all of the rules, and then post the whitelist application in the appropriate forum.</p>
<p>StaffAdmins</p>
<p>:- Gamer9726 (Emperor Tilius Romanus Eliri IV)</p>
<ul>
<li>Elbowgrease (Aero_Bohr, Representative of the Rinese)</li>
<li>Devilmonkey6 (Val’um, Representative of the Islari)</li>
<li>Karnoshan (Throren, Representative of the Yarlak)</li>
</ul>
<p>Moderators-</p>
<ul>
<li>Apple_Calister</li>
<li>Futurii</li>
<li>Marcellan</li>
<li>Darkside_97</li>
<li>Goudkindin</li>
<li>Open Spot</li>
<li>Open Spot</li>
<li>Open Spot</li>
</ul>
<p>No new players can ask for moderator, and if you ask for it, you will never get it. If there is a spot open and I see that you are helpful, responsible, and a good roleplayer, I will notify you and ask you to be a moderator.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silver-age-roleplay-server-1-1/437813/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silver-age-roleplay-server-1-1/437813/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 16:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437813-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/silver-age-roleplay-server-1-1/437813.rss">~~Silver Age Roleplay Server (1.1)~~</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
