<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Emailing Jagex</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emailing-jagex/454871</link>
    <description>So, I was on vacation a few weeks back and I haven&#39;t actively played RuneScape in a few months. I usually don&#39;t check the email that is registered to my RuneScape account but as I didn&#39;t really have anything else to do while at this hotel due to its poor internet speed, I decided to check all my emails. I found out that my account got recovered a month prior. Reading the emails that Jagex had send, I found out the person had changed my display name multiple times, and had tried changing the registered email of the account to another. I promptly emailed Jagex&#39;s account help and received the automatic message stating that they&#39;d get back to you in two weeks. It&#39;s been nearly two months now. Has anyone else had problems with this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 23:29:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emailing-jagex/454871.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Emailing Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have actually. It took about a month and they then replied. If you want it to go a little faster go to the support forums on the runescape forums and talk there on one of the pinned topics.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emailing-jagex/454871/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emailing-jagex/454871/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 23:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454871-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emailing-jagex/454871.rss">Emailing Jagex</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Emailing Jagex</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Null_Amount N_A]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/null_amount">@Null_Amount</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So, I was on vacation a few weeks back and I haven’t actively played RuneScape in a few months. I usually don’t check the email that is registered to my RuneScape account but as I didn’t really have anything else to do while at this hotel due to its poor internet speed, I decided to check all my emails. I found out that my account got recovered a month prior. Reading the emails that Jagex had send, I found out the person had changed my display name multiple times, and had tried changing the registered email of the account to another. I promptly emailed Jagex’s account help and received the automatic message stating that they’d get back to you in two weeks. It’s been nearly two months now. Has anyone else had problems with this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emailing-jagex/454871/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emailing-jagex/454871/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 22:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-454871-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/emailing-jagex/454871.rss">Emailing Jagex</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
