<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Simple Color Clicking Script help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-color-clicking-script-help/359246</link>
    <description>Howdy,

I&#39;ve been looking up and down the internet for a simple script that clicks a certain color every time it pops up, but I simply cannot find it. I&#39;ve tried adjusting different color clicking scripts, but these either refuse to click at all or just make my mouse go completely crazy. So I was hoping someone here could write me up a very small and simple script.

Basicly, what I&#39;m looking for is a color clicker for a small facebook app, the app plays a trailer and during this trailer a white text shows up randomly across the screen, if you click this you get points, the faster you click, the more points. The text itself is white, the same color as most of the facebook-page, so most scripts I have found just start spamming away at the edge of the actual trailer window. So I&#39;d either have to input the coords of the corner of the box, or I could just resize the window far enough so it only shows the trailer (dunno if this will work though).

Any help you could give me is much appreciated.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 16:19:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-color-clicking-script-help/359246.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Simple Color Clicking Script help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Galeck Galeck]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/galeck">@Galeck</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Howdy,</p>
<p>I’ve been looking up and down the internet for a simple script that clicks a certain color every time it pops up, but I simply cannot find it. I’ve tried adjusting different color clicking scripts, but these either refuse to click at all or just make my mouse go completely crazy. So I was hoping someone here could write me up a very small and simple script.</p>
<p>Basicly, what I’m looking for is a color clicker for a small facebook app, the app plays a trailer and during this trailer a white text shows up randomly across the screen, if you click this you get points, the faster you click, the more points. The text itself is white, the same color as most of the facebook-page, so most scripts I have found just start spamming away at the edge of the actual trailer window. So I’d either have to input the coords of the corner of the box, or I could just resize the window far enough so it only shows the trailer (dunno if this will work though).</p>
<p>Any help you could give me is much appreciated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-color-clicking-script-help/359246/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-color-clicking-script-help/359246/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 16:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-359246-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-color-clicking-script-help/359246.rss">Simple Color Clicking Script help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
