<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[QUESTION] How to retrieve lost data due to reformatting?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-how-to-retrieve-lost-data-due-to-reformatting/172909</link>
    <description>Does anyone know of any programs or ways how to retrieve lost data, which are due to reformatting of the computer?

I just recently (today) got a virus, even though I have all kinds of up-to-date protection. This virus didn&#39;t take long from when I obtained it, until my computer couldn&#39;t even be rebooted. So, the only choice I had to do was to reformat my computer, and therefore lose around 14 days of programming on my recent project. I did back it up around 14 days ago (30/12-2007), so I didn&#39;t lose it all, but still very much (about half of what I had done).

So, my question is, as stated earlier... Do you know about any program or ways how to retrieve lost data, on a reformatted HDD?

EDIT:
I might have fixed it... I used File Scavenger to retrieve them, and as far as I know, they are all retrieved. The only thing I need to redo is to re-save them once again, as they cannot be compiled (it seems). I can look at them, the text is all fine, but still something won&#39;t let them be compiled (some encryption or something).</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 09:33:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-how-to-retrieve-lost-data-due-to-reformatting/172909.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[QUESTION] How to retrieve lost data due to reformatting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@killer_jcd killer jcd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/killer_jcd">@killer_jcd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>there is a way. I would need to ask my parents they have done this for me a few times. But ill get right back to you, there is a way. But I also believe that you have needed to reformat it a specific way to save all saved data. so yea. ill get right back to you and before I do try, <a href="http://www.google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.google.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-how-to-retrieve-lost-data-due-to-reformatting/172909/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-how-to-retrieve-lost-data-due-to-reformatting/172909/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 09:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-172909-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-how-to-retrieve-lost-data-due-to-reformatting/172909.rss">[QUESTION] How to retrieve lost data due to reformatting?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[QUESTION] How to retrieve lost data due to reformatting?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Does anyone know of any programs or ways how to retrieve lost data, which are due to reformatting of the computer?</p>
<p>I just recently (today) got a virus, even though I have all kinds of up-to-date protection. This virus didn’t take long from when I obtained it, until my computer couldn’t even be rebooted. So, the only choice I had to do was to reformat my computer, and therefore lose around 14 days of programming on my recent project. I did back it up around 14 days ago (30/12-2007), so I didn’t lose it all, but still very much (about half of what I had done).</p>
<p>So, my question is, as stated earlier… Do you know about any program or ways how to retrieve lost data, on a reformatted HDD?</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
I might have fixed it… I used File Scavenger to retrieve them, and as far as I know, they are all retrieved. The only thing I need to redo is to re-save them once again, as they cannot be compiled (it seems). I can look at them, the text is all fine, but still something won’t let them be compiled (some encryption or something).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-how-to-retrieve-lost-data-due-to-reformatting/172909/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-how-to-retrieve-lost-data-due-to-reformatting/172909/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 06:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-172909-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/question-how-to-retrieve-lost-data-due-to-reformatting/172909.rss">[QUESTION] How to retrieve lost data due to reformatting?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
