<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ipad 5</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ipad-5/533845</link>
    <description>With the (hopeful) release annoucement coming on the Apple media event on the 15th the date for the Ipad 5 draws nearer and nearer. I debated with myself several times over which tablet to get and referenced back to the other topic I had about tablets several times.

I know now I will be purchasing the new Ipad 5 when it comes out. I&#39;d love to get feedback on what everyone&#39;s thoughts are going to be on the tablet/who else is going to purchase it/ and etc.

This topic is for discussion on the development, rumors, official release information which it comes available, how we believe ( and later how it performs )  it will perform and etc.

For now I will be citing this article: 

http://www.ubergizmo.com/2013/10/ipad-5-release-date-news-and-rumored-specs/

I am really liking the idea of the touch fingerprint sensor that may come with the ipad 5. I&#39;m fairly certain it will be in it cause well if it came with a phone then surely they would do the same with a tablet. (considering more apps are available then)

I do kind of have to agree that the same chipset may be used for the cpu. I never had issues with lag on the ipad 4 I fooled around with at a friends house but it would be nice to see continued upgrades to this.

My only real concern is that with the apple ceo guy whatever his name dead Apple does seem to be falling little by little once more. I just hope the ipad 5 isn&#39;t a huge disappointment.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 13:27:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ipad-5/533845.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ipad 5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>With the (hopeful) release annoucement coming on the Apple media event on the 15th the date for the Ipad 5 draws nearer and nearer. I debated with myself several times over which tablet to get and referenced back to the other topic I had about tablets several times.</p>
<p>I know now I will be purchasing the new Ipad 5 when it comes out. I’d love to get feedback on what everyone’s thoughts are going to be on the tablet/who else is going to purchase it/ and etc.</p>
<p>This topic is for discussion on the development, rumors, official release information which it comes available, how we believe ( and later how it performs )  it will perform and etc.</p>
<p>For now I will be citing this article:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.ubergizmo.com/2013/10/ipad-5-release-date-news-and-rumored-specs/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.ubergizmo.com/2013/10/ipad-5-release-date-news-and-rumored-specs/</a></p>
<p>I am really liking the idea of the touch fingerprint sensor that may come with the ipad 5. I’m fairly certain it will be in it cause well if it came with a phone then surely they would do the same with a tablet. (considering more apps are available then)</p>
<p>I do kind of have to agree that the same chipset may be used for the cpu. I never had issues with lag on the ipad 4 I fooled around with at a friends house but it would be nice to see continued upgrades to this.</p>
<p>My only real concern is that with the apple ceo guy whatever his name dead Apple does seem to be falling little by little once more. I just hope the ipad 5 isn’t a huge disappointment.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ipad-5/533845/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ipad-5/533845/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 13:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-533845-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ipad-5/533845.rss">Ipad 5</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
