<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>GETTING COMPILE&amp;&quot;RUN&quot; to Work!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-compile-run-to-work/415343</link>
    <description>hey guys, i got a new computer and my &quot;java&quot; is on my desk top! i downloaded a server to mess with because i haven&#39;t coded for a long time and want to make a 100% new server. I need help getting the Run and Compile to work.. sounds easy? but For some reason it defiantly will not work no mater what i try, this is 1 thing im not a expert in... please comment on what i may need to do? or give me a link! PS-- When i try the compiler it says i do not have JDK-- and i do!

We can also just team viewer it or something--PM Me or  Email Me at 
Kingprodigy@hotmail.com</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 00:07:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-compile-run-to-work/415343.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>GETTING COMPILE&amp;&quot;RUN&quot; to Work!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@king_prodigy king prodigy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/king_prodigy">@king_prodigy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hey guys, i got a new computer and my “java” is on my desk top! i downloaded a server to mess with because i haven’t coded for a long time and want to make a 100% new server. I need help getting the Run and Compile to work… sounds easy? but For some reason it defiantly will not work no mater what i try, this is 1 thing im not a expert in… please comment on what i may need to do? or give me a link! PS-- When i try the compiler it says i do not have JDK-- and i do!</p>
<p>We can also just team viewer it or something–PM Me or  Email Me at<br>
<a href="mailto:Kingprodigy@hotmail.com">Kingprodigy@hotmail.com</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-compile-run-to-work/415343/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-compile-run-to-work/415343/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 00:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-415343-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-compile-run-to-work/415343.rss">GETTING COMPILE&amp;&quot;RUN&quot; to Work!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
