<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Marijuana :o</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663</link>
    <description>Okay, Believe it or not, i smoke it, well i use to anyways with my brothers... and about a week and a half ago i smoked like 4 hits from a bowl and the bad part is i forgot about my probation, i have a probation meeting tomorrow and i was wondering if i took only 4 hits, if it should be out by now, it&#39;s been about 2 weeks so yeah, just wondering.

If you smoke or have ever smoked reply with this :D

Do you smoke :

Whats The Best You&#39;ve smoked:

How long have you been smoking:

What kind of high are you (funny, lazy, etc) :

Have you ever smoked with a parent:

lol, dont flame :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 04:52:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Canuowneazy calls lil wayne and eminem idiots.</p>
<p>Lil wayne runs his own record company, Young money. His total networth is $75 million dollars.</p>
<p>Eminem runs shady records, and his networth is $110 million (in 2006)</p>
<p>Both are <span class="bbcode-b">successful business men</span> that now have all the money they could dream of. They played the system and got rich as fuck and will enjoy the rest of their lives very much.</p>
<p>Canuowneazy, what have you accomplished?</p>
<p>If you’re stupid enough to think that people only smoke pot to “be like lil wayne and eminem” then your probably a lot more stupid then both lil wayne and eminem… Typical arrogant/angsty teenager…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/94</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 04:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-94</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Project Epic, post:7, topic:377766”][quote author=Canownueazy link=topic=473554.msg3480400#msg3480400 date=1296072084]<br>
I find it lolworthy at the amount of adults on this site</p>
<p>Oh and any kind of drug like this is for retards</p>
<p>Science doesn’t prove anything I prove everything</p>
<p>Anybody who does this idiocy wants to be just like morons Lil Wayne and Eminem who are both idiots and have no use to society other than infect kid’s minds to do idiot stuff like this and be disrespectful to others and always have their way.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>&lt;3 your wisdom baffles me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> i totally agree bro.[/quote]<br>
Some of the greatest musicians, writers, artists etc of all time created their work under the influence of cannabis. Food for thought.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/93</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 04:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-93</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="90" data-topic="377663">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/jc22493/40/5_1887921562df0dabfae55079ddabeb03.png" class="avatar"> Jc22493:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/jme">@jme</a>: I think it goes both ways. I can’t prove that marijuana is addictive, but the users of marijuana who argue that it is not addictive cannot prove that either, so this debate will always be at a stalemate. Furthermore, research in this area is informational, but only to a certain extent. Some research states that it is not addictive, while others state that it is addictive, such as the first link that came up on Google when I searched “Is marijuana addictive?”… Of course I’m being a bit biased by using sources that support my side, but isn’t that what everyone else is doing?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve dealt with real addictions. Coffee, tobacco, cocaine almost… Marijuana isn’t a real addiction.</p>
<p>I hope we can both agree on something though. Marijuana is not a physical addiction. It’s addictive in the way that games like minecraft are. Because if something is enjoyable, we as humans we will want to repeat it. But that’s as far as it goes.</p>
<p>But when you quit, there’s no withdrawels. For example I had a lung infection not long ago, so I quit smoking weed for a few days. That was simple. But do you think I could stop smoking cigarettes during those days? no.</p>
<p>I never smoke pot until late at night (anymore), I don’t like it in the day time as it makes you sleepy afterwards. I don’t experience cravings or withdrawels during the day either, as a real drug addiction would.</p>
<p>The reasons drugs like nicotine are addictive, is because it increases your brains natural “pleasure” chemical, dopamine. Your body adapts to this increased dopamine by reducing the available dopamine receptors. Therefore when you haven’t had a nicotine fix in a while, you have less dopamine then normal. Leaving you feeling like shit. The only way to replenish this dopamine is to get nicotine (or stop nicotine entirely for a few days to a few weeks)</p>
<p>The reason marijuana can be considered addictive, is because it’s fun. Not because of any physical effect on your body or brain. Hence being called “habit-forming”</p>
<p>Basically it boils down to self control. Wake up in the morning and… you have weed, you have nothing important to do, and if you smoke the weed you will feel great and have a better day. It’s hard to say no to this! But again, thats a mind over matter thing. Agreed?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/92</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 04:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-92</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Kane † Kane †]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_kane">@_Kane</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Saphire`, post:88, topic:377663”][quote author=† Kane † link=topic=473554.msg3481292#msg3481292 date=1296161474]<br>
Another thing about how weed is bad is it can often lead people to try more dangerous drugs. Like they could say something like, “Oh this isn’t so bad, I’m gonna go try meth and see what it feels like.”</p>
<p>And don’t be the smartass to comment saying “I don’t do that!” because it’s not like everyone who smokes weed is gonna end up doing meth or crack or something.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>First: We have been talking about that for a number of posts.</p>
<p>Secondly: I respect my drugs, I do take more things than marijuana but not on a daily basis. I only take certain drugs basing    on what I feel like emotionally and physically, I chose to do that anyway and i didn’t start off on cannabis, I started on cocaine and then learned to respect it.[/quote]</p>
<p>Oh sorry. Haven’t really had time to read all the replies.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/91</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 23:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-91</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“k0 twin, post:60, topic:377663”][quote author=Jc22493 link=topic=473554.msg3479744#msg3479744 date=1296005933]<br>
<span class="mention">@k0</span> twin:</p>
<p>There is absolutely no proof that the drug is not addictive; you cannot imply that just because “everyone out there” believes that. You also cannot state that it isn’t addictive when a small percentage of the population of marijuana users is in fact psychologically dependent on the drug.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Habit forming is not the same as addictive. Everything we do is habit forming. Absolutely no basis for making it illegal. Until there is proof that it is addictive I will assume it is not addictive. I can easily stop smoking for months with it having no effect on me.[/quote]<br>
Likewise. “Until there is proof that it is not addictive, I will assume it is addictive.” It can go both ways. I’m not blaming you for believing any specific thing, for I may be wrong, but basing our information off skewed textbooks and other “reliable” resources isn’t enough to prove anything, especially when talking about an issue this controversial. As for “I can stop anytime and it will have no effect on me,” of course all users are going to defend themselves with that argument, but I can swear on my grandparents’ lives that you would long for it if you lacked it.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/jme">@jme</a>: I think it goes both ways. I can’t prove that marijuana is addictive, but the users of marijuana who argue that it is not addictive cannot prove that either, so this debate will always be at a stalemate. Furthermore, research in this area is informational, but only to a certain extent. Some research states that it is not addictive, while others state that it is addictive, such as the first link that came up on Google when I searched “Is marijuana addictive?”… Of course I’m being a bit biased by using sources that support my side, but isn’t that what everyone else is doing?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/90</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 21:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-90</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@abatssk8ter abatssk8ter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/abatssk8ter">@abatssk8ter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Gateway thing is bullshit, it’s about will power and self control. It’s like saying you can never eat chocolate,  or any sweets your whole life because it would be a “gateway food” and it could lead you to eat bad foods to make you fat.</p>
<p>Bullllllllssshhhhhiiiiiiittttttttttttttt</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/89</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 21:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-89</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saphire1 Saphire`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saphire1">@Saphire1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote="† Kane †, post:87, topic:377663"]Another thing about how weed is bad is it can often lead people to try more dangerous drugs. Like they could say something like, “Oh this isn’t so bad, I’m gonna go try meth and see what it feels like.”</p>
<p>And don’t be the smartass to comment saying “I don’t do that!” because it’s not like everyone who smokes weed is gonna end up doing meth or crack or something.[/quote]</p>
<p>First: We have been talking about that for a number of posts.</p>
<p>Secondly: I respect my drugs, I do take more things than marijuana but not on a daily basis. I only take certain drugs basing    on what I feel like emotionally and physically, I chose to do that anyway and i didn’t start off on cannabis, I started on cocaine and then learned to respect it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/88</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 21:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-88</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Kane † Kane †]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_kane">@_Kane</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Another thing about how weed is bad is it can often lead people to try more dangerous drugs. Like they could say something like, “Oh this isn’t so bad, I’m gonna go try meth and see what it feels like.”</p>
<p>And don’t be the smartass to comment saying “I don’t do that!” because it’s not like everyone who smokes weed is gonna end up doing meth or crack or something.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/87</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-87</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saphire1 Saphire`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saphire1">@Saphire1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>With your gateway theory, I grow my own smoke. Therefore have no reason to involve marijuana as a gateway drug.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/86</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 11:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-86</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“k0 twin, post:84, topic:377663”][quote author=Cole1497 link=topic=473554.msg3480906#msg3480906 date=1296105317]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Some of this shit is ignorant as fuck, any smoke you put into your lungs is bad for you whether it’s cancerous or not.<br>
You can ingest marijuana anyway you want but when you take it orally theirs little to no harm to your body.<br>
And saying marijuana is not addictive is like saying food isn’t addictive.<br>
Nobodies ever died from marijuana anyways.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>True, they die from the drugs they want to try after marijuana enters their life. Although that’s not an actual statistic, more like an educated assumption.</p>
<p>[/quote]<br>
I would definitely agree with you that there is a gateway effect. Like 100%. But marijuana is not a “gateway drug”. There’s no chemical in the plant that makes you want to try harder drugs. The gateway effects comes with the blending of the drug markets. Because it’s illegal you have to get your weed from a dealer, and most dealers who deal weed also deal harder drugs. So when someones buying there weed the dealer might say “Hey, wanna try something a little stronger?”. There’s your gateway effect.</p>
<p>You become exposed to harder drugs because marijuana has been grouped in with them. It’s not the actual using of marijuana.[/quote]</p>
<p>Besides this,</p>
<p>1.(marijuana as a gateway to other drugs) “Analysis of the demographic and social characteristics of a large sample of applicants seeking approval to use marijuana medically in California supports an interpretation of long term non problematic use by many who had first tried it as adolescents, and then either continued to use it or later resumed its use as adults. In general, they have used it at modest levels and in consistent patterns which anecdotally-often assisted their educational achievement, employment performance, and establishment of a more stable life-style. These data suggest that rather than acting as a gateway to other drugs, (which many had also tried), cannabis has been exerting a beneficial influence on most.”</p>
<p>Source: Thomas J O’Connell and Ché B Bou-Matar, “Long term marijuana users seeking medical cannabis in California (2001–2007): demographics, social characteristics, patterns of cannabis and other drug use of 4117 applicants,” Harm Reduction Journal, (November 2007).<br>
<a href="http://www.harmreductionjournal.com/content/pdf/1477-7517-4-16.pdf" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://www.harmreductionjournal.com/content/pdf/1477-7517-4-16.pdf</a></p>
<p>but: check out this page too. <a href="http://www.erowid.org/plants/cannabis/cannabis_myth13.shtml">http://www.erowid.org/plants/cannabis/cannabis_myth13.shtml</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/85</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 05:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-85</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Cole1497, post:83, topic:377663”][quote author=abatssk8ter link=topic=473554.msg3480904#msg3480904 date=1296105025]<br>
Some of this shit is ignorant as fuck, any smoke you put into your lungs is bad for you whether it’s cancerous or not.<br>
You can ingest marijuana anyway you want but when you take it orally theirs little to no harm to your body.<br>
And saying marijuana is not addictive is like saying food isn’t addictive.<br>
Nobodies ever died from marijuana anyways.<br>
[/quote]<br>
True, they die from the drugs they want to try after marijuana enters their life. Although that’s not an actual statistic, more like an educated assumption.[/quote]<br>
I would definitely agree with you that there is a gateway effect. Like 100%. But marijuana is not a “gateway drug”. There’s no chemical in the plant that makes you want to try harder drugs. The gateway effects comes with the blending of the drug markets. Because it’s illegal you have to get your weed from a dealer, and most dealers who deal weed also deal harder drugs. So when someones buying their weed the dealer might say “Hey, wanna try something a little stronger?”. There’s your gateway effect.</p>
<p>You become exposed to harder drugs because marijuana has been grouped in with them. It’s not the actual using of marijuana.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/84</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 05:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-84</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cole1497 Cole1497]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cole1497">@Cole1497</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“abatssk8ter, post:82, topic:377663”]Some of this shit is ignorant as fuck, any smoke you put into your lungs is bad for you whether it’s cancerous or not.<br>
You can ingest marijuana anyway you want but when you take it orally theirs little to no harm to your body.<br>
And saying marijuana is not addictive is like saying food isn’t addictive.<br>
Nobodies ever died from marijuana anyways.[/quote]<br>
True, they die from the drugs they want to try after marijuana enters their life. Although that’s not an actual statistic, more like an educated assumption.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/83</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 05:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-83</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@abatssk8ter abatssk8ter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/abatssk8ter">@abatssk8ter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Some of this shit is ignorant as fuck, any smoke you put into your lungs is bad for you whether it’s cancerous or not.<br>
You can ingest marijuana anyway you want but when you take it orally theirs little to no harm to your body.<br>
And saying marijuana is not addictive is like saying food isn’t addictive.<br>
Nobodies ever died from marijuana anyways.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/82</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 05:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-82</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote="`Alec, post:73, topic:377663"]Wait, let me get this right. You tell jc22493 that he can’t just make statements without proof, yet you do the same exact thing numerous times?? A lot of people can take me seriously actually, I don’t know how you couldn’t.</p>
<p>It is addictive, if it wasn’t addictive you wouldn’t have been doing it for the past 6 years. You then go on to say that you know others who have smoked marijuana for 20 years, how does that not strike you as addictive?</p>
<p>Yeah, how many of these studies were for altered marijuana (whatever the fuck you call it)? I bet none of them were, the marijuana that you and others smoke is not the same as the marijuana that Americans smoked in the 70’s.</p>
<p>It’s definitely not common ignorance, if you want to keep doing drugs like you have for the past 6 years I can’t stop you. If you like paying however much you pay for drugs I cannot stop you. You’re simply killing yourself, not me, I honestly don’t care.</p>
<p>I never said that I supported cigarettes being legal, if I had it my way they wouldn’t be. However:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The main threat with marijuana is the obvious health risks. Marijuana affects multiple parts of the body negatively, including <span class="bbcode-b">(but not limited to) the lungs, brain, eyes, and genitals</span>. The drug contains <span class="bbcode-b">twice the carcinogens</span> of government-sanctioned <span class="bbcode-b">tobacco</span> products and actively attacks the immune system of the lungs, leading to a near-cubing of the likelihood for <span class="bbcode-b">lung cancer </span>in the user. It also induces severe hallucinations and<span class="bbcode-b"> slows down brain waves</span>, leading to severe <span class="bbcode-b">mental retardation in mild cases, and Asperger’s Syndrome in extreme cases</span>. It severely hampers the users ability to drive, read, or recognize an incoming train. Lastly, it is confirmed in all reported cases to result in complete infertility and a decreased sex drive, which may be the only positive side effect of the drug. Worse, many of these effects can be passed onto nearby users through secondhand smoke.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Myth: Marijuana is completely non-addictive.</p>
<p>Fact: Marijuana is not only 1000 times more physically addictive than heroin, but the side effects of the drug often lead to a state of poor decision-making, where a second “joint” seems like a good idea to improve the high from the drug. Due to the long-lasting effects of this mental impairment, it can be said that marijuana gets you hooked from the first use.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Again, continue thinking whatever you want about marijuana, it’s your life.</p>
<p><span class="mention">@responses</span> to my metaphor:</p>
<p>Whoever said that you would be “severing many arteries” is very misguided, you would definitely live unless you lost too much blood.</p>
<p>Yeah, I’ll still stand by what I said, just because you won’t be killed by marijuana, you will be severed for life (this is similar to loosing multiple limbs)…[/quote]</p>
<p>hahahaha those quotes are from uncyclopedia. You’re basing your information on an article written for <span class="bbcode-b">comedy</span> purposes. It’s satire.<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/uncyclopedia/images/6/64/Favicon.ico/revision/latest?cb=20111002012029" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="http://uncyclopedia.wikia.com/wiki/Marijuana" target="_blank">Uncyclopedia</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:636/470;"><img src="https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/uncyclopedia/images/5/5a/Stoner%27s_House.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20090805033937" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="http://uncyclopedia.wikia.com/wiki/Marijuana" target="_blank">Marijuana</a></h3>

<p>The hard street drug Marijuana is a rising and popular gateway drug, known for its ease to obtain, its catastrophic effects, and its uninformed proponents. The most common form of consumption, the joint involves taking the marijuana plant, rolling it...</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Don’t be such a fool.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/81</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 04:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-81</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k0_twin k0 twin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k0_twin">@k0_twin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="73" data-topic="377663">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 `Alec:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You then go on to say that you know others who have smoked marijuana for 20 years, how does that not strike you as addictive?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’ve been eating pizza for the last 18 years. I must be addicted.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="73" data-topic="377663">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 `Alec:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah, how many of these studies were for altered marijuana (whatever the fuck you call it)? I bet none of them were, the marijuana that you and others smoke is not the same as the marijuana that Americans smoked in the 70’s.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There’s good weed, and there’s bad weed. This is always how it’s been. Sure we may have gotten better in the growing process over the years with the increase in technology, but why the fuck does it matter if it’s not the same as it was a few decades ago. Just because the potency went up doesn’t mean it went up enough to become dangerous.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="73" data-topic="377663">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 `Alec:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You’re simply killing yourself, not me, I honestly don’t care.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Already answered this, marijuana will not kill you. Another example of the common ignorance. It’s good you have an opinion, but base it on <span class="bbcode-b">fact</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/80</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 01:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-80</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Kane † Kane †]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_kane">@_Kane</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Eminem doesn’t rap about drugs and all that…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/79</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-79</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saphire1 Saphire`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saphire1">@Saphire1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Canownueazy, post:76, topic:377663”]I find it lolworthy at the amount of adults on this site</p>
<p>Oh and any kind of drug like this is for retards</p>
<p>Science doesn’t prove anything I prove everything</p>
<p>Anybody who does this idiocy wants to be just like morons Lil Wayne and Eminem who are both idiots and have no use to society other than infect kid’s minds to do idiot stuff like this and be disrespectful to others and always have their way.[/quote]</p>
<p>Your saying that eminem and lil wayne makes me smoke weed? No, I listen to soft rock.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/78</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 22:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-78</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JuniorCautionz JuniorCautionz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/juniorcautionz">@JuniorCautionz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ive Smoked…</p>
<p>Lemon Haze<br>
Ak<br>
Thai (Sum Thing Like That)<br>
Cheese</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/77</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 20:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-77</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Canownueazy Canownueazy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/canownueazy">@Canownueazy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I find it lolworthy at the amount of adults on this site</p>
<p>Oh and any kind of drug like this is for retards</p>
<p>Science doesn’t prove anything I prove everything</p>
<p>Anybody who does this idiocy wants to be just like morons Lil Wayne and Eminem who are both idiots and have no use to society other than infect kid’s minds to do idiot stuff like this and be disrespectful to others and always have their way.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/76</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 20:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-76</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saphire1 Saphire`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saphire1">@Saphire1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alec, your entitled to your own opinion and i respect that, although i must point out that marijuana is not addictive in any way shape or form. When i first started smoking herb I continued to do it everyday for two years and when i first got with my partner she asked me to stop when she got pregnant. So I did for a number of months but started back up out of freewil, my partner smokes it also and she agrees totally to what I’m saying<br>
here.</p>
<p>EDIT: I forgot to mention, if my partner didn’t lose the baby I wouldn’t be smoking it now, although she is pregnant again I still smoke, but not around her and when my baby is born. He/she will never be around me when i decide to spark up a spliff.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/75</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 19:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-75</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I didn’t tell jc to post proof. I said you can’t just say “prove its not”</p>
<p>thats like saying <span class="bbcode-s">god</span> the flying spaghetti monster exists, prove he doesn’t. It doesnt work that way. I believe I posted proof and sources, but you edited them from your quote.</p>
<p>Don’t know where you got your info, but it doesnt cite it’s sources and it contradicts all credible scientific/medical studies. I’ve got to go to work now, so we shall explain more detailed, when I get home in 9.5 hours <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/74</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 18:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-74</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jme, post:72, topic:377663”]What a joke. How could anyone take you seriously?</p>
<p>Well first, it’s not addictive.</p>
<p>and second, it doesn’t kill brain cells. Or not anymore then breathing oxygen does.</p>
<p>Alright, you win this one. Smoking anything can be bad. But compare it to tobacco. The dried marijuana buds contain 33% of the tar that tobacco has. Compare someone then who smokes once every few weeks, to someone who smokes 25 cigarettes or more a day. Also, 90% of tobacco related cancer is not caused by carcinogens. It’s caused by radioactive chemical, Radium 226. Which is then broken down in your body to polonium 210 and lead 210. Marijuana does not contain these.</p>
<p>On top of that, some interesting studies are showing that THC kills aging or mutating cells, potentially preventing cancer or slowing it down. It’s also been shown to reduce tumours.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Also, being ‘sheltered’ has nothing to do with your opinion on illegal drugs, this is actually called having <span class="bbcode-b">common sense</span>. As far as I am concerned, I am the healthy one while you are not. If you don’t care about your future or your mental health, go ahead and do drugs.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s not common sense. That’s common ignorance. I’m not healthy? I specifically remember the doctor telling me I’m a “very healthy young man”, when I got my blood test recently. I’m also sharp, witty, intelligent, and perform well socially. And I havent even used marijuana responsibly like I try to preach others to do. I’ve smoked multiple times a day for the past 6 years. I know lawyers and teachers that have been doing the same for over 20 years. Again, not trying to convince anyone to start smoking. I’m trying to make people sensible about it.[/quote]</p>
<p>Wait, let me get this right. You tell jc22493 that he can’t just make statements without proof, yet you do the same exact thing numerous times?? A lot of people can take me seriously actually, I don’t know how you couldn’t.</p>
<p>It is addictive, if it wasn’t addictive you wouldn’t have been doing it for the past 6 years. You then go on to say that you know others who have smoked marijuana for 20 years, how does that not strike you as addictive?</p>
<p>Yeah, how many of these studies were for altered marijuana (whatever the fuck you call it)? I bet none of them were, the marijuana that you and others smoke is not the same as the marijuana that Americans smoked in the 70’s.</p>
<p>It’s definitely not common ignorance, if you want to keep doing drugs like you have for the past 6 years I can’t stop you. If you like paying however much you pay for drugs I cannot stop you. You’re simply killing yourself, not me, I honestly don’t care.</p>
<p>I never said that I supported cigarettes being legal, if I had it my way they wouldn’t be. However:</p>
<blockquote>The main threat with marijuana is the obvious health risks. Marijuana affects multiple parts of the body negatively, including [b](but not limited to) the lungs, brain, eyes, and genitals[/b]. The drug contains [b]twice the carcinogens[/b] of government-sanctioned [b]tobacco[/b] products and actively attacks the immune system of the lungs, leading to a near-cubing of the likelihood for [b]lung cancer [/b]in the user. It also induces severe hallucinations and[b] slows down brain waves[/b], leading to severe [b]mental retardation in mild cases, and Asperger's Syndrome in extreme cases[/b]. It severely hampers the users ability to drive, read, or recognize an incoming train. Lastly, it is confirmed in all reported cases to result in complete infertility and a decreased sex drive, which may be the only positive side effect of the drug. Worse, many of these effects can be passed onto nearby users through secondhand smoke.</blockquote>
<blockquote>Myth: Marijuana is completely non-addictive.
<p>Fact: Marijuana is not only 1000 times more physically addictive than heroin, but the side effects of the drug often lead to a state of poor decision-making, where a second “joint” seems like a good idea to improve the high from the drug. Due to the long-lasting effects of this mental impairment, it can be said that marijuana gets you hooked from the first use.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Again, continue thinking whatever you want about marijuana, it’s your life.</p>
<p><span class="mention">@responses</span> to my metaphor:</p>
<p>Whoever said that you would be “severing many arteries” is very misguided, you would definitely live unless you lost too much blood.</p>
<p>Yeah, I’ll still stand by what I said, just because you won’t be killed by marijuana, you will be severed for life (this is similar to loosing multiple limbs)…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/73</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 18:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-73</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="57" data-topic="377663">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 `Alec:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Anyone here that does drugs will just use the defense “you’re so wrong and misguided you haven’t even done drugs!!11” or “yeah, well there’s no downside so why not!@!”. Marijuana is bad, <span class="bbcode-b">just because it doesn’t kill you doesn’t mean it’s good for you</span>… Honestly, that’s like saying “yeah dude, hacking off your own arms and legs is extremely safe because it most likely will not kill you!!!”.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What a joke. How could anyone take you seriously?</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="57" data-topic="377663">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 `Alec:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>However, most people addicted to drugs like marijuana will think that there is nothing wrong with them because it only affects their thoughts for a little bit (this is ridiculous because they are killing off brain cells).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well first, it’s not addictive.</p>
<blockquote>Myth: Marijuana is Highly Addictive. Long term marijuana users experience physical dependence and withdrawal, and often need professional drug treatment to break their marijuana habits.
<p>Fact: Most people who smoke marijuana smoke it only occasionally. A small minority of Americans - less than 1 percent - smoke marijuana on a daily basis. An even smaller minority develop a dependence on marijuana. Some people who smoke marijuana heavily and frequently stop without difficulty. Others seek help from drug treatment professionals. Marijuana does not cause physical dependence. If people experience withdrawal symptoms at all, they are remarkably mild.</p>
<p>•United States. Dept. of Health and Human Services. DASIS Report Series, Differences in Marijuana Admissions Based on Source of Referral. 2002. June 24 2005.<br>
•Johnson, L.D., et al. “National Survey Results on Drug Use from the Monitoring the Future Study, 1975-1994, Volume II: College Students and Young Adults.” Rockville, MD: U.S. Department of Health and Human Services, 1996.<br>
•Kandel, D.B., et al. “Prevalence and demographic correlates of symptoms of dependence on cigarettes, alcohol, marijuana and cocaine in the U.S. population.” Drug and Alcohol Dependence 44 (1997):11-29.<br>
•Stephens, R.S., et al. “Adult marijuana users seeking treatment.” Journal of Consulting and Clinical Psychology 61 (1993): 1100-1104.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>and second, it doesn’t kill brain cells. Or not anymore then breathing oxygen does.</p>
<blockquote>Myth: Marijuana Kills Brain Cells. Used over time, marijuana permanently alters brain structure and function, causing memory loss, cognitive impairment, personality deterioration, and reduced productivity.
<p>Fact: None of the medical tests currently used to detect brain damage in humans have found harm from marijuana, even from long term high-dose use. An early study reported brain damage in rhesus monkeys after six months exposure to high concentrations of marijuana smoke. In a recent, more carefully conducted study, researchers found no evidence of brain abnormality in monkeys that were forced to inhale the equivalent of four to five marijuana cigarettes every day for a year. The claim that marijuana kills brain cells is based on a speculative report dating back a quarter of a century that has never been supported by any scientific study.</p>
<p>•Heath, R.G., et al. “Cannabis Sativa: Effects on Brain Function and Ultrastructure in Rhesus Monkeys.” Biological Psychiatry 15 (1980): 657-690.<br>
•Ali, S.F., et al. “Chronic Marijuana Smoke Exposure in the Rhesus Monkey IV: Neurochemical Effects and Comparison to Acute and Chronic Exposure to Delta-9-Tetrahydrocannabinol (THC) in Rats.” Pharmacology Biochemistry and Behavior 40 (1991): 677-82.</p>
</blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="57" data-topic="377663">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 `Alec:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s not even the ‘getting high’ part that is bad (as far as I know), you are inhaling toxins into your lungs, and giving your brain harmful chemicals.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Alright, you win this one. Smoking anything can be bad. But compare it to tobacco. The dried marijuana buds contain 33% of the tar that tobacco has. Compare someone then who smokes once every few weeks, to someone who smokes 25 cigarettes or more a day. Also, 90% of tobacco related cancer is not caused by carcinogens. It’s caused by radioactive chemical, Radium 226. Which is then broken down in your body to polonium 210 and lead 210. Marijuana does not contain these.</p>
<p>It’s not even close to as bad a tobacco. Why should tobacco be legal and socially acceptable?</p>
<blockquote>Fact: Moderate smoking of marijuana appears to pose minimal danger to the lungs. Like tobacco smoke, marijuana smoke contains a number of irritants and carcinogens. But marijuana users typically smoke much less often than tobacco smokers, and over time, inhale much less smoke. As a result, the risk of serious lung damage should be lower in marijuana smokers. There have been no reports of lung cancer related solely to marijuana, and in a large study presented to the American Thoracic Society in 2006, even heavy users of smoked marijuana were found not to have any increased risk of lung cancer. Unlike heavy tobacco smokers, heavy marijuana smokers exhibit no obstruction of the lung's small airway. That indicates that people will not develop emphysema from smoking marijuana.
<p>•Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse. “Legalization: Panacea or Pandora’s Box.” New York. (1995): 36.<br>
•Turner, Carlton E. The Marijuana Controversy. Rockville: American Council for Drug Education, 1981.<br>
•Nahas, Gabriel G. and Nicholas A. Pace. Letter. “Marijuana as Chemotherapy Aid Poses Hazards.” New York Times 4 December 1993: A20.<br>
•Inaba, Darryl S. and William E. Cohen. Uppers, Downers, All-Arounders: Physical and Mental Effects of Psychoactive Drugs. 2nd ed. Ashland: CNS Productions, 1995. 174.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>On top of that, some interesting studies are showing that THC kills aging or mutating cells, potentially preventing cancer or slowing it down. It’s also been shown to reduce tumours.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="57" data-topic="377663">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 `Alec:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Also, being ‘sheltered’ has nothing to do with your opinion on illegal drugs, this is actually called having <span class="bbcode-b">common sense</span>. As far as I am concerned, I am the healthy one while you are not. If you don’t care about your future or your mental health, go ahead and do drugs.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s not common sense. That’s common ignorance. I’m not healthy? I specifically remember the doctor telling me I’m a “very healthy young man”, when I got my blood test recently. I’m also sharp, witty, intelligent, and perform well socially. And I havent even used marijuana responsibly like I try to preach others to do. I’ve smoked multiple times a day for the past 6 years. I know lawyers and teachers that have been doing the same for over 20 years. Again, not trying to convince anyone to start smoking. I’m trying to make people sensible about it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/72</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 18:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-72</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="70" data-topic="377663">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Saphire`:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Relating to the topic, not hacking arms and legs off.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and I was relating to Alec’s post, hence the quote<br>
Sorry, should have made it clearer</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/71</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 14:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-71</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Marijuana :o</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Saphire1 Saphire`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/saphire1">@Saphire1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Relating to the topic, not hacking arms and legs off.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663/70</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 14:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-377663-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/marijuana-o/377663.rss">Marijuana :o</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
