<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Error Connecting Whilst Loading Client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-whilst-loading-client/399522</link>
    <description>When I&#39;m trying to run the client that I am co - owner on - it just says &quot;error connecting, please report.&quot; He showed me a video, and sent me screenshots proving it works for him and 2 other people that play. I also can run other clients, for instance my server, - the client and all. I have the client, and i have the orginal cache, named erasedpkz, and the custom one, prodsempirecache, so they&#39;re both extracted in my C drive, and they aren&#39;t conflicting because I tried removing one or the other from there, and putting back after trying to run again, and it still doesn&#39;t work.

Apologies if this sounds confusing, but please help me. I have JDK, and yea like I said, I can run any other client. 

P.S. Yes it does open, but then gives me the error, or opens a black screen that says, error while running prodsempire blablabla, try these steps to fix this, like it does for the mopar webclient. but this is a download client.

Yep, help me.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 16:53:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-whilst-loading-client/399522.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Error Connecting Whilst Loading Client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@obabygirl obabygirl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/obabygirl">@obabygirl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When I’m trying to run the client that I am co - owner on - it just says “error connecting, please report.” He showed me a video, and sent me screenshots proving it works for him and 2 other people that play. I also can run other clients, for instance my server, - the client and all. I have the client, and i have the orginal cache, named erasedpkz, and the custom one, prodsempirecache, so they’re both extracted in my C drive, and they aren’t conflicting because I tried removing one or the other from there, and putting back after trying to run again, and it still doesn’t work.</p>
<p>Apologies if this sounds confusing, but please help me. I have JDK, and yea like I said, I can run any other client.</p>
<p>P.S. Yes it does open, but then gives me the error, or opens a black screen that says, error while running prodsempire blablabla, try these steps to fix this, like it does for the mopar webclient. but this is a download client.</p>
<p>Yep, help me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-whilst-loading-client/399522/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-whilst-loading-client/399522/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 16:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399522-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-whilst-loading-client/399522.rss">Error Connecting Whilst Loading Client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
