<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My essay for school</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333</link>
    <description>[center]Online Schooling[/center]

	Do you want your kids to be staring at a computer all day? Wouldn’t you rather see your kids get a better social life? The department of education is considering making all schooling done on a computer. The department should choose not to make schooling online.
	
            It would be very unhealthy to sit and stare at the computer all through your school day. One superior reason is that looking at a screen will end up hurting your vision in the long run. About.com says “Workers who spend many hours using computers should make sure they have regular eye examinations, which can help detect early signs of glaucoma”. This is telling you that gazing into a computer monitor can give you glaucoma, a eye disease dealing with high fluid pressure in the eye. Also staring at the computer will kill brain cells, and losing enough brain cells could turn out very bad. The biggest reason that has to do with learning on the computer is that being on the computer and not in the classroom situation would affect your learning. This is because you would not be able to ask your peers or your teacher about something you are having trouble with. One last reason that working on the computer could be unhealthy is that you won’t be active and you could become overweight.

	Another big reason that the online schooling would not be a good thing is that there would be no social environment to be in. First of all school is where you make a majority of your friends and without it you wouldn’t be socially active. On the note of making most of your friends at school PBS.org says “Educators[…] acknowledge that making friends is one of the most valuable things children do as they learn and grow”. The second way that this would be unhealthy for your social life is that if you were to be on the computer for 6 hours a day for school then you would want to stay on the computer and be on it for a longer period of time. The last reason I have for being antisocial is that if a problem occurs there would be no one to talk to, or to get help from.

	The last main reason that there shouldn’t be online school it could be troublesome financially. First of all some families have more that one student in school and maybe they would only have one computer to do it on. How would both kids be able to go to school? The only option would be that the family would be obligated to buy another computer, which could be financially burdening to some families. Also would it be free to take the classes or would the students have to pay a fee to take it on the internt? These are all questions that are unanswered and unknown. If the school district has to pay for it, it could cost taxpayers more money, which could also be bothersome. The next reason is that not everyone has the Internet yet and might have to go to the library every time they want to use it. Johnnie L. Roberts says “As of December, more than half of U.S. homes were wired with the high-speed pipeline to the Net”(42). High speed internet however would be essential to be taking online schools or else it would take even longer and turn into more unhealthy time.

	The other side of this choice is to have online schooling. One argument they might have is that there won’t be a need of transportation because the schooling would be done at home not at a school building. This might be true but the transportation for schools right now is figured out and there is no problem with it. Another argument that they might have is that the student could have more choices for classes because there won’t need to be teachers for each class. This could be beneficial but without a teacher it could be hard to learn anything. The last big reason that they might have is that it could fit someone’s schedule better. This could be true but it could also mean that kids could go on the computer late at night and not get enough sleep to be in a healthy learning environment.

	All in all online schooling is unhealthy, unsocial, and to financial burdening. The bottom line is that having online schools could cause big problems. All you need to help is a pencil or a pen and a piece of paper, just write a simple letter the department of education saying your view on the topic of online schools. 


[b]if you have any mistakes or things i can improve on that would be great, i need a good grade[/b] :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2007 13:05:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My essay for school</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pk3r_Dale Pk3r Dale]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk3r_dale">@Pk3r_Dale</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i think that is a really good essay i agree with it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2007 13:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35333-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333.rss">My essay for school</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My essay for school</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Only thing a PC can harm unless you launch a nuke using a radio transmition from it is your eyes, then again, there’s that freak expensive laser eyesight curing thing…I didn’t read the whole thing, but from what I did read I can say plain schooling is better, as it plays a huge role in the social lives of people. I must agree thogh that online schooling is much faster and more flexible,as said y 13om13e12.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2007 07:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35333-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333.rss">My essay for school</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My essay for school</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kazza kazza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kazza">@kazza</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol this section is so random <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> i got a 10 page essay to do so your lucky lol but its good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2007 23:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35333-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333.rss">My essay for school</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My essay for school</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@13om13e12 13om13e12]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/13om13e12">@13om13e12</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ya but the personal attribute you talked about depends on the person.  Ive tried computer schooling also.  i liked the flexibility and how fast i could go, but the assignments were very boring and no personal interaction.  But like i said it depends on the person.  And my initial critisism was for the structure, not so much the info.  But ya you should always make sure your evidence is on the source, and make sure the sources are reliable.  But still a good essay</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2006 23:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35333-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333.rss">My essay for school</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My essay for school</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@premier premier]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/premier">@premier</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>alright thanks, i just could think of more things that side of it, i would like online schools too</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35333-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333.rss">My essay for school</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My essay for school</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BobDole81 BobDole81]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobdole81">@BobDole81</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well I disagree with the essay entirely <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:">  I actually attend a public cyber charter school and don’t feel any such concerns.  I do spend a fair bit on the computer each day, but I must say that I believe I’d spend just as much time even if I didn’t attend.  But I don’t see how staring at the computer kills brain cells to be honest…</p>
<p>Furthermore, there are many programs offered, not all of which depend on being at the computer all day.  For example, the Calvert curriculum is done entirely offline with the exception of tutoring, testing, etc.  Granted, there are virtual classes where one attends classes in an online setting, but that takes place for limited periods of time.  In addition, if one ever needed help, there are always tutoring sessions available, and you are free to email or call teachers for individual subjects.  In regards to socialization, cyber schools in general should host social events for students…if not, it’s up to the families themselves to incorporate it.  In my case, I take advantage of the early college program, so I actually go into a local college (3 times a week at the moment)…I wouldn’t say I miss out on such social interaction.</p>
<p>Finally, cyber schools typically provide each student with their own computer and offer reimbursement for internet…as long as its a public school, you have to really as you’re paying school taxes…Overall, I see cyber schools as offering more flexibility and opportunities, not problems.</p>
<p>But that’s just my opinion - I’m not asking you to change your essay <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:">  Your essay sounds good overall, but I think you should remove statements such as “the next reason” and “another argument” just so that it flows more nicely.  But I think the content is good.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 10:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35333-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333.rss">My essay for school</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My essay for school</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@13om13e12 13om13e12]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/13om13e12">@13om13e12</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>overall the essay is nice.  My only critizism is in the intro.  only attention getters and then your thesis. you should try to build up to the thesis with backround or basic info on the topic.  also instead of randomly choosing which topic of evidence you use first try to make some order, such as chronological or maybe order of importance ( order of importance would be good for this)  thats just my constructive critizism but you would probably get an “A” without changing it anyway.  GOOD JOB <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 10:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35333-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333.rss">My essay for school</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My essay for school</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@premier premier]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/premier">@premier</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Online Schooling[/center]</p>
<pre><code>Do you want your kids to be staring at a computer all day? Wouldn’t you rather see your kids get a better social life? The department of education is considering making all schooling done on a computer. The department should choose not to make schooling online.

        It would be very unhealthy to sit and stare at the computer all through your school day. One superior reason is that looking at a screen will end up hurting your vision in the long run. About.com says “Workers who spend many hours using computers should make sure they have regular eye examinations, which can help detect early signs of glaucoma”. This is telling you that gazing into a computer monitor can give you glaucoma, a eye disease dealing with high fluid pressure in the eye. Also staring at the computer will kill brain cells, and losing enough brain cells could turn out very bad. The biggest reason that has to do with learning on the computer is that being on the computer and not in the classroom situation would affect your learning. This is because you would not be able to ask your peers or your teacher about something you are having trouble with. One last reason that working on the computer could be unhealthy is that you won’t be active and you could become overweight.

Another big reason that the online schooling would not be a good thing is that there would be no social environment to be in. First of all school is where you make a majority of your friends and without it you wouldn’t be socially active. On the note of making most of your friends at school PBS.org says “Educators[…] acknowledge that making friends is one of the most valuable things children do as they learn and grow”. The second way that this would be unhealthy for your social life is that if you were to be on the computer for 6 hours a day for school then you would want to stay on the computer and be on it for a longer period of time. The last reason I have for being antisocial is that if a problem occurs there would be no one to talk to, or to get help from.

The last main reason that there shouldn’t be online school it could be troublesome financially. First of all some families have more that one student in school and maybe they would only have one computer to do it on. How would both kids be able to go to school? The only option would be that the family would be obligated to buy another computer, which could be financially burdening to some families. Also would it be free to take the classes or would the students have to pay a fee to take it on the internt? These are all questions that are unanswered and unknown. If the school district has to pay for it, it could cost taxpayers more money, which could also be bothersome. The next reason is that not everyone has the Internet yet and might have to go to the library every time they want to use it. Johnnie L. Roberts says “As of December, more than half of U.S. homes were wired with the high-speed pipeline to the Net”(42). High speed internet however would be essential to be taking online schools or else it would take even longer and turn into more unhealthy time.

The other side of this choice is to have online schooling. One argument they might have is that there won’t be a need of transportation because the schooling would be done at home not at a school building. This might be true but the transportation for schools right now is figured out and there is no problem with it. Another argument that they might have is that the student could have more choices for classes because there won’t need to be teachers for each class. This could be beneficial but without a teacher it could be hard to learn anything. The last big reason that they might have is that it could fit someone’s schedule better. This could be true but it could also mean that kids could go on the computer late at night and not get enough sleep to be in a healthy learning environment.

All in all online schooling is unhealthy, unsocial, and to financial burdening. The bottom line is that having online schools could cause big problems. All you need to help is a pencil or a pen and a piece of paper, just write a simple letter the department of education saying your view on the topic of online schools. 
</code></pre>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">if you have any mistakes or things i can improve on that would be great, i need a good grade</span> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 06:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-35333-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-essay-for-school/35333.rss">My essay for school</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
