<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>About the forum</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-forum/434031</link>
    <description>One thing I&#39;ve seen on and on is other members being rude to someone who asks a question on here.  In almost every thread here there is at least one person who will respond to a question rudely but doesn&#39;t even answer the question, they are just making the other person feel like they are idiots.  If someone asks a question just answer back politely and don&#39;t say something that will be rude.  Even if you say you were being sarcastic, sarcasm isn&#39;t very easy to really tell on the internet.  Sure some people you can joke around with once you get to know their personality more and more, but in general I just see a bunch of comments almost attacking another person due to something they asked that they just may not have known.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 16:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-forum/434031.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>About the forum</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@si_force Si Force]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/si_force">@si_force</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, if spam/flame is happening in those threads, all we can ask you to do is report them and we’ll take appropriate action. Giving new members/members with questions a hard time is against our rules and we won’t tolerate it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-forum/434031/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-forum/434031/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 16:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-434031-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-forum/434031.rss">About the forum</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>About the forum</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathwilldie0 deathwilldie0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathwilldie0">@deathwilldie0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>One thing I’ve seen on and on is other members being rude to someone who asks a question on here.  In almost every thread here there is at least one person who will respond to a question rudely but doesn’t even answer the question, they are just making the other person feel like they are idiots.  If someone asks a question just answer back politely and don’t say something that will be rude.  Even if you say you were being sarcastic, sarcasm isn’t very easy to really tell on the internet.  Sure some people you can joke around with once you get to know their personality more and more, but in general I just see a bunch of comments almost attacking another person due to something they asked that they just may not have known.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-forum/434031/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-forum/434031/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-434031-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/about-the-forum/434031.rss">About the forum</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
