<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Being aware of your incapabilities</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/being-aware-of-your-incapabilities/228001</link>
    <description>I think about this every time the situation happens. I&#39;ll give an example to start this off.

say your sister does something stupid and then when you tell her shes going to get yelled at for it, she would say something like &quot;I&#39;m not getting in trouble because i didn&#39;t know any better.&quot;

That makes no sense at all because if she is aware that she doesn&#39;t know any better then she obviously wouldn&#39;t have done it. Fact is, you cant [i]know[/i] that you don&#39;t know any better.

Still thats an example of a younger group. How about raising the age a bit. Say someone with an addiction to a drug. Any drug, no matter. Say they tell you that they can&#39;t stop, because they aren&#39;t in control, or they don&#39;t have the ability to stop. This is almost the same concept. If you have the ability to buy the addiction and use it.. and If you are aware of your addiction, don&#39;t you have the same will power to stop that you have to continue? Whats so hard about realizing and putting it into effect. 

I really haven&#39;t understood why people do this. If you are aware that you are unable to comprehend things, yet you are doing it in the process that you tell anyone whats wrong. can&#39;t you figure out and stop doing the wrong thing? It&#39;s almost like right and wrong have become completely oblivious to their thoughts.

Anyone have an example or person story like this post about it, I&#39;m interested in your opinion. Also, what are your views on this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 01:09:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/being-aware-of-your-incapabilities/228001.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Being aware of your incapabilities</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Reaper_X The Reaper X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_reaper_x">@The_Reaper_X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think about this every time the situation happens. I’ll give an example to start this off.</p>
<p>say your sister does something stupid and then when you tell her shes going to get yelled at for it, she would say something like “I’m not getting in trouble because i didn’t know any better.”</p>
<p>That makes no sense at all because if she is aware that she doesn’t know any better then she obviously wouldn’t have done it. Fact is, you cant <span class="bbcode-i">know</span> that you don’t know any better.</p>
<p>Still thats an example of a younger group. How about raising the age a bit. Say someone with an addiction to a drug. Any drug, no matter. Say they tell you that they can’t stop, because they aren’t in control, or they don’t have the ability to stop. This is almost the same concept. If you have the ability to buy the addiction and use it… and If you are aware of your addiction, don’t you have the same will power to stop that you have to continue? Whats so hard about realizing and putting it into effect.</p>
<p>I really haven’t understood why people do this. If you are aware that you are unable to comprehend things, yet you are doing it in the process that you tell anyone whats wrong. can’t you figure out and stop doing the wrong thing? It’s almost like right and wrong have become completely oblivious to their thoughts.</p>
<p>Anyone have an example or person story like this post about it, I’m interested in your opinion. Also, what are your views on this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/being-aware-of-your-incapabilities/228001/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/being-aware-of-your-incapabilities/228001/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 01:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-228001-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/being-aware-of-your-incapabilities/228001.rss">Being aware of your incapabilities</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
