<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Clean simple client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-simple-client/379804</link>
    <description>I don&#39;t know if this is the right section, so sorry if its not. I am looking for a clean simple client.. all the ones I find have interfaces and yadda yadda.. i just want to make a clean webclient that my clan mates can connect to my server and play. So far I have been failing at getting any webclients to work correctly. I enjoy the RSCemulation kind but that you have to download to play, which is fine in that context.

Anyone have suggestions of a client?  I am running.. i think a 508 ExRendum private server source.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 14:06:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-simple-client/379804.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Clean simple client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@knivesrun knivesrun]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/knivesrun">@knivesrun</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t know if this is the right section, so sorry if its not. I am looking for a clean simple client… all the ones I find have interfaces and yadda yadda… i just want to make a clean webclient that my clan mates can connect to my server and play. So far I have been failing at getting any webclients to work correctly. I enjoy the RSCemulation kind but that you have to download to play, which is fine in that context.</p>
<p>Anyone have suggestions of a client?  I am running… i think a 508 ExRendum private server source.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-simple-client/379804/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-simple-client/379804/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 14:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-379804-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clean-simple-client/379804.rss">Clean simple client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
