<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RSPS Programmers/Coders Needed</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-programmers-coders-needed/534583</link>
    <description>This has been a long coming idea of mine for quite some time now, but up until recently I did not have the means to set it into motion. After a few months, I&#39;ve acquired the correct resources to make this happen; now I just need a team.

I have been wanting to start a successful RSPS. I played around with some 317&#39;s back a few years ago and really enjoyed creating an environment where players could relax and enjoy a game. What I am asking of the moparscape community is it to start from a clean base, whatever source and generation we choose and make it as successful to RS as possible. I have the knowledge to add small snippets and tutorials, but never really got good at it. My skills lie more in the hardware and software spectrum of computers. 

[b]What I am offering:[/b]
I will handle all hosting related manners. I will be running the server testing from my own computer until the time for public release when I will buy a top of the range VPS.
I have business class internet with reliable, consistent 76\19 speed. I will handle the upkeep, my partners would be responsible for weekly updates if possible. 
I am familiar with registering domains. I will need some help with building a website as well as forums for the game. In this area, I would like a developer who is capable of linking the forum user database with the users from the server. 
I do have an allowed budget for this product, and I do have income.
When the server gains popularity, I will split the profits fairly. I am not looking for a get cash quick scheme, I am genuinely looking to start a successful community. You will also all receive Admin permissions on server and forums. 

I will be available to my team almost 24/7 and will distribute my mobile number to them after things have been finalized.

I am in full time employment. I do not have time to learn how to develop a server, and am just looking for a team to handle server and client side of things. An example would be to implement a webclient. 

If you have the skills for the job, but don&#39;t like the terms, contact me anyway. It can&#39;t hurt to talk and see if we can work something out. 

Aside from experience, the only trait I&#39;m looking for is maturity, and possibly age. 

Please contact me via Skype: King.Lxa

Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:34:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-programmers-coders-needed/534583.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RSPS Programmers/Coders Needed</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LumbysChild LumbysChild]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lumbyschild">@LumbysChild</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This has been a long coming idea of mine for quite some time now, but up until recently I did not have the means to set it into motion. After a few months, I’ve acquired the correct resources to make this happen; now I just need a team.</p>
<p>I have been wanting to start a successful RSPS. I played around with some 317’s back a few years ago and really enjoyed creating an environment where players could relax and enjoy a game. What I am asking of the moparscape community is it to start from a clean base, whatever source and generation we choose and make it as successful to RS as possible. I have the knowledge to add small snippets and tutorials, but never really got good at it. My skills lie more in the hardware and software spectrum of computers.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What I am offering:</span><br>
I will handle all hosting related manners. I will be running the server testing from my own computer until the time for public release when I will buy a top of the range VPS.<br>
I have business class internet with reliable, consistent 76\19 speed. I will handle the upkeep, my partners would be responsible for weekly updates if possible.<br>
I am familiar with registering domains. I will need some help with building a website as well as forums for the game. In this area, I would like a developer who is capable of linking the forum user database with the users from the server.<br>
I do have an allowed budget for this product, and I do have income.<br>
When the server gains popularity, I will split the profits fairly. I am not looking for a get cash quick scheme, I am genuinely looking to start a successful community. You will also all receive Admin permissions on server and forums.</p>
<p>I will be available to my team almost 24/7 and will distribute my mobile number to them after things have been finalized.</p>
<p>I am in full time employment. I do not have time to learn how to develop a server, and am just looking for a team to handle server and client side of things. An example would be to implement a webclient.</p>
<p>If you have the skills for the job, but don’t like the terms, contact me anyway. It can’t hurt to talk and see if we can work something out.</p>
<p>Aside from experience, the only trait I’m looking for is maturity, and possibly age.</p>
<p>Please contact me via Skype: King.Lxa</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-programmers-coders-needed/534583/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-programmers-coders-needed/534583/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534583-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rsps-programmers-coders-needed/534583.rss">RSPS Programmers/Coders Needed</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
