<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>*~*~*~*~*~error connecting to server~*~*~*~*~*</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/372903</link>
    <description>Hey, every time I try to play a server it always says error connecting to server. You may just say &quot;the server is down&quot; but this happens when i know my friend is on the server when i get a message saying error connecting to server. This has been happening for a long long long long time and i can only play servers when i go to a friends house. lol. This problem has been happening after i tried to make my own server. I do not wanna make my own server now. I just want this problem fixed so i can play any server i want. If anyone could help that would be great and very much appreciated.
Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 02:54:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/372903.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>*~*~*~*~*~error connecting to server~*~*~*~*~*</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@banana_panda banana panda]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/banana_panda">@banana_panda</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, every time I try to play a server it always says error connecting to server. You may just say “the server is down” but this happens when i know my friend is on the server when i get a message saying error connecting to server. This has been happening for a long long long long time and i can only play servers when i go to a friends house. lol. This problem has been happening after i tried to make my own server. I do not wanna make my own server now. I just want this problem fixed so i can play any server i want. If anyone could help that would be great and very much appreciated.<br>
Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/372903/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/372903/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 02:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-372903-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/372903.rss">*~*~*~*~*~error connecting to server~*~*~*~*~*</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
