<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Error connecting to server?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/384843</link>
    <description>I have downloaded a server and i change the server ip to my ipv4 address in &quot;client.java&quot; First I tried this in my naptop and it works, i can log in in my both my pc and naptop at the same time. But after i sent the client to my friends, they cannot log in, it said &quot;error connecting to the server, why ?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 16:55:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/384843.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Error connecting to server?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_kush †kush†]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_kush">@_kush</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You have to PortFoward, also, your ipv4 address is your network address, not your internet protocal, (ip). I suggest going for you to do this :</p>
<p>1.) Go to <a href="http://www.no-ip.org" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.no-ip.org</a><br>
2.) Register…<br>
3.) Go to “Add Hosts”<br>
4.) Set up a ip name with your ip in it and if you want you can try to get it the name of your server, (eg: <a href="http://moparscape.no-ip.org" rel="nofollow noopener">moparscape.no-ip.org</a>.)</p>
<p><img src="http://i54.tinypic.com/339kq3k.jpg" alt width="140" height="120"> Just an example of how it should look.</p>
<p>5.) And then download the no-ip.DUC.</p>
<p>Run the no-ip.DUC, and login with the e-mail you used to register. Now re-start the server, (just x it out and run it) and then BAM. People should be able too connect to your server… if this doesn’t work, then you may need to PortFoward, which isn’t really that big of a deal. So, I’ll just post early on how to PortFoward.</p>
<p>When you portfoward, this is the part where you will need your ipv4 address, (ex: 192.168.1.108).</p>
<p>It’s not hard to portfoward depending on the router you use. Just type in 192.168.1.1 (or whatever your network ip address is, not your ipv4.) And then it might ask you for Login Details.</p>
<p>If you know the information, fill it in. If not, then it may still be the default password and admin. Chances are 70/30% that it’s the default.</p>
<p>User: admin<br>
Password: admin or password</p>
<p>After that, proceed to the Gaming part of your router, mine says Applications and Games, it should list a couple of boxes for you to fill in, I can’t post a screenshot of this because my dad get’s paranoid about me hosting on the router cuz he uses the same one… but this is how the information should look</p>
<p>|Name                         |Protocol                | Ports     | Ports    | IP Address            |<br>
RSPS\rsps                    |TCP                      | 43594   | 43594   | (your ipv4 address)</p>
<p>If that was a bad layout for simple text… I’ll try to help you out, but reply if you need any more help… but after your done portfowarding, save the changes, and proceed restart your server again. Now, try to get your friends to connect to you, and if they still can’t, just post in here if theres still a problem, also, don’t forget to give them a new client with your no-ip address in it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/384843/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/384843/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 16:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384843-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/384843.rss">Error connecting to server?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Error connecting to server?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathnote777 deathnote777]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathnote777">@deathnote777</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have downloaded a server and i change the server ip to my ipv4 address in “client.java” First I tried this in my naptop and it works, i can log in in my both my pc and naptop at the same time. But after i sent the client to my friends, they cannot log in, it said "error connecting to the server, why ?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/384843/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/384843/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 15:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-384843-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-connecting-to-server/384843.rss">Error connecting to server?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
