<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Advise..?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167</link>
    <description>I need some advice on my project. I am finally coming up to the landscape part of the things and it&#39;s extremely crucial that nobody knows the map. Since it&#39;s completely custom I want players to have that &#39;fresh&#39; adventure feel that we all had when we played RSC for the first time. I would also like the point out that there will be 3 different team &#39;bases&#39; which other teams will invade. With that being said here are my concerns. 

-I don&#39;t want anyone to know the map.
-I don&#39;t want other teams to have an advantage when it comes to invading (until they learn them on their own)

Now obviously I will change the way the landscape is packaged to keep people from using landscape editors to view things. Hopefully people with knowledge of these things will respect the project and just let it play out but that won&#39;t happen.

What do you guys suggest?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 23:18:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Advise..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“imthenull, post:7, topic:519167”]You could make minor edits to the landscape every week or so, with things such as natural disasters.</p>
<p>I think river/lava overflows would be an awesome thing to randomly add/remove on a weekly basis.[/quote]</p>
<p>That thing I posted in the show off thread relating to changing textures is related to this project. If a certain god is dominating a region it will relate to that god (lava = zamorak, water = sara, grass = guthix) I have not implemented anything relating to the changing of landscapes but it’s a possible idea that I might be interested in exploring.</p>
<p>The map for my project is very small, homelands will be about 4 sectors and the mainland will be about the size of the f2p landscape without the wild. With it being so small I don’t want people to take advantage of it and I want things to constantly change keeping the players on their feet. Like a massive meteor took out a city and next thing you know it’s a training ground for precious rocks/fish… that would be epic.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="6" data-topic="519167">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/codeforfame/40/3743_1.png" class="avatar"> CodeForFame:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>But like I said, designing a map that requires it to be a secret is just a bad idea.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yes, it’s not suppose to be a top notch secret but I want players to have that adventure feel. I won’t be providing a map on the website for people to view. I would like for ‘teams’ to work together to draw their own conclusion, working together to make their own maps with pictures or drawings. If a team is able to explore the map first then they get the advantage because they have awareness of treasures/npcs/training locations.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="519167">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 object:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Edit: It’s by 99% certainty <em>not</em> possible to guarantee that noone can reverse anything related to this problem. It might, however, become much harder.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>There are a few people in the scene who will be able to figure it out. I know if I just change the file extension from .rscd to .gtfo 90% of people won’t be able to open it with a landscape editor (especially if I even change the landscape package completely that gets rid of anyone with a landscape editor.</p>
<p>Now I am interested in sending landscape files from the server -&gt; client. This would be extremely beneficial especially if the landscape was changed in real time but that sounds extreme! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 23:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519167-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss">Advise..?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Advise..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RSCShadow RSCShadow]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rscshadow">@RSCShadow</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“imthenull, post:7, topic:519167”]You could make minor edits to the landscape every week or so[/quote]You said that already.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 22:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519167-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss">Advise..?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Advise..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imthenull imthenull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imthenull">@imthenull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You could make minor edits to the landscape every week or so, with things such as natural disasters.</p>
<p>I think river/lava overflows would be an awesome thing to randomly add/remove on a weekly basis.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 20:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519167-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss">Advise..?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Advise..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you only send them the landscapes they need, as they need them, then they can’t discover parts of the map they haven’t seen.</p>
<p>Though, as soon as a single person sees it once, it’s no longer a secret, seeing they can share it outside the game. They could do something as simple as taking a screenshot.</p>
<p>But like I said, designing a map that requires it to be a secret is just a bad idea.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 19:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519167-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss">Advise..?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Advise..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Protosstribe object]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/protosstribe">@Protosstribe</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>One way is to send the files to the client on every first login (and subsequently every time the map changes on the server-side). By every first login I am referring to the first login since the client program was started.</p>
<p>Every time the files are sent, they should be encrypted. The key to decrypt them should be different every time.</p>
<p>Instead of just sending the files encrypted, would be to send a unique class able to decrypt said files together with the files. This way it would be harder to decompile the class performing the decryption. If someone do decompile it, it is of no use, simply because the next class will be totally different.</p>
<p>Edit: It’s by 99% certainty <em>not</em> possible to guarantee that noone can reverse anything related to this problem. It might, however, become much harder.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 07:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519167-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss">Advise..?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Advise..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Each sector having a unique key would be nice but it does suck because eventually the entire thing will be explored or a map will be made by players on their teams for new players.</p>
<p>I want players to be able to change their homelands at free will. I have object registration complete so they can act as ‘builders’ but the actual landscape to change will require an update. Hmm. Still debating if team bases/homelands should have the ability to extend their landscape, I just don’t know. This is getting difficult.</p>
<p>Any other cheap ideas I could possibly do besides changing the way the landscape is packaged? The only worry I have here is that someone who knows a thing or two about the rsc client to leak a public map. I want it to be fun for the players to explorer and draw their own conclusions. I just don’t see it happening though <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> sigh.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 04:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519167-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss">Advise..?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Advise..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imthenull imthenull]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imthenull">@imthenull</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You could randomly generate a fresh map every couple of weeks or so. That would be really cool.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 03:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519167-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss">Advise..?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Advise..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CodeForFame CodeForFame]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/codeforfame">@CodeForFame</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You need to have keys to decrypt each sector. When a player is allowed to see it, send them the key.</p>
<p>What stops people from making accounts on each team and making a map like that?</p>
<p>Also, designing a map around obscurity is a bad idea… People will eventually explore the whole thing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 01:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519167-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss">Advise..?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Advise..?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rodgerwilco Rodgerwilco]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rodgerwilco">@Rodgerwilco</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I need some advice on my project. I am finally coming up to the landscape part of the things and it’s extremely crucial that nobody knows the map. Since it’s completely custom I want players to have that ‘fresh’ adventure feel that we all had when we played RSC for the first time. I would also like the point out that there will be 3 different team ‘bases’ which other teams will invade. With that being said here are my concerns.</p>
<p>-I don’t want anyone to know the map.<br>
-I don’t want other teams to have an advantage when it comes to invading (until they learn them on their own)</p>
<p>Now obviously I will change the way the landscape is packaged to keep people from using landscape editors to view things. Hopefully people with knowledge of these things will respect the project and just let it play out but that won’t happen.</p>
<p>What do you guys suggest?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 00:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-519167-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/advise/519167.rss">Advise..?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
