<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hosting off DSL?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-off-dsl/284172</link>
    <description>ok so i have a friend and i was helping him set up his own server that he can play at his own leisure... i host my servers off utorrent so when i set up his server i used that.... i did everything, had his no-ip running, set his variables etc... then i tried logging on using the silab client with the simple allstar source... and t wouldnt log in.... then he says &quot;when i tried it off internet running on wireless it logged in&quot; he explained how his internet is DSL modem thingy... any ideas how he runs off this ??? is it a different port to 43594 or summut?

thanks in advance... djmorgan92</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 15:14:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-off-dsl/284172.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hosting off DSL?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@djmorgan92 djmorgan92]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/djmorgan92">@djmorgan92</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok so i have a friend and i was helping him set up his own server that he can play at his own leisure… i host my servers off utorrent so when i set up his server i used that… i did everything, had his no-ip running, set his variables etc… then i tried logging on using the silab client with the simple allstar source… and t wouldnt log in… then he says “when i tried it off internet running on wireless it logged in” he explained how his internet is DSL modem thingy… any ideas how he runs off this ??? is it a different port to 43594 or summut?</p>
<p>thanks in advance… djmorgan92</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-off-dsl/284172/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-off-dsl/284172/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 15:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-284172-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hosting-off-dsl/284172.rss">Hosting off DSL?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
