<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>CSS Nilla clan Logo/Spray (whichever you prefer to call it)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/css-nilla-clan-logo-spray-whichever-you-prefer-to-call-it/314763</link>
    <description>Hey guys, ive been attempting to make a logo/spray for my nilla clan for CSS. I found out that im absolutely useless with photoshop.
Im here because i require aid of some professionals/people who are alot better than me.

My clan name is immortaL.sa

Basically the theme im looking for is things that represnt immortality but still relate to things to do with counterstrike such as bullet holes and blood. For the main image I would like maybe a devil. Kind of that like devil jin from tekken...maybe with bullet holes in the chest area with small amounts of light shining through and a slight drip of blood.. Maybe even just the upper body and then wings and head with bullet holes in the wings with light shining through?

For colour of background im looking it to be transparent as im going to a LAN contest with my team and im going to be printing it on T-shirts to make us stand out. For inner colour im looking for darker colours such as Black/Purple (not to much purple) in a gradient effect in like &quot; explosive&quot;  bubble

Im not exactly sure how i would describe the texture maybe metallic i guess. 

For the text I would like &quot;immortaL.sa as it is there. For colour maybe something that contrasts with darker colours such as &quot;dark&quot; shade of white..? Big enough to read but not to much to take over the main image of immortality from the devil/demon image. Maybe above the left wing of the demon / devil? for font maybe something like a bundle of hay with like a thread kind of effect to it.

If you cant get it how I would like it please show me what you have and ill do my best effort to make it easier or less confusing.
If you have any questions on extra things or something to do with this please let me know

Sorry about my not very descriptive words. If you would like me to explain something better or something just let me know ill do my best. I havent got a very large vocabulary.

EDIT:
For the size of it im thinking something like 600x480? if thats not a good size for you or you want to make it a little smaller or bigger go for it. Whatever is easier for you


Thanks to anyone who can help! :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 06:20:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/css-nilla-clan-logo-spray-whichever-you-prefer-to-call-it/314763.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>CSS Nilla clan Logo/Spray (whichever you prefer to call it)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@M4G3OWNS M4G3OWNS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m4g3owns">@M4G3OWNS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys, ive been attempting to make a logo/spray for my nilla clan for CSS. I found out that im absolutely useless with photoshop.<br>
Im here because i require aid of some professionals/people who are alot better than me.</p>
<p>My clan name is immortaL.sa</p>
<p>Basically the theme im looking for is things that represnt immortality but still relate to things to do with counterstrike such as bullet holes and blood. For the main image I would like maybe a devil. Kind of that like devil jin from tekken…maybe with bullet holes in the chest area with small amounts of light shining through and a slight drip of blood… Maybe even just the upper body and then wings and head with bullet holes in the wings with light shining through?</p>
<p>For colour of background im looking it to be transparent as im going to a LAN contest with my team and im going to be printing it on T-shirts to make us stand out. For inner colour im looking for darker colours such as Black/Purple (not to much purple) in a gradient effect in like " explosive"  bubble</p>
<p>Im not exactly sure how i would describe the texture maybe metallic i guess.</p>
<p>For the text I would like "immortaL.sa as it is there. For colour maybe something that contrasts with darker colours such as “dark” shade of white…? Big enough to read but not to much to take over the main image of immortality from the devil/demon image. Maybe above the left wing of the demon / devil? for font maybe something like a bundle of hay with like a thread kind of effect to it.</p>
<p>If you cant get it how I would like it please show me what you have and ill do my best effort to make it easier or less confusing.<br>
If you have any questions on extra things or something to do with this please let me know</p>
<p>Sorry about my not very descriptive words. If you would like me to explain something better or something just let me know ill do my best. I havent got a very large vocabulary.</p>
<p>EDIT:<br>
For the size of it im thinking something like 600x480? if thats not a good size for you or you want to make it a little smaller or bigger go for it. Whatever is easier for you</p>
<p>Thanks to anyone who can help! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/css-nilla-clan-logo-spray-whichever-you-prefer-to-call-it/314763/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/css-nilla-clan-logo-spray-whichever-you-prefer-to-call-it/314763/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 06:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-314763-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/css-nilla-clan-logo-spray-whichever-you-prefer-to-call-it/314763.rss">CSS Nilla clan Logo/Spray (whichever you prefer to call it)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
