<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Player Update packet</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/player-update-packet/179592</link>
    <description>I have been fooling around with the old 317 client (mopar&#39;s refactor) and, mainly speaking, my few hours dealing with the player update packet have only been half successful. I should have mostly completed updating when it comes to walking as well as other player updating. However, the actual player update block is the part I am having troubles with. I looked at the client and saw that a 0 tells the client to not update that player, but I did that and it still continued to update. In actuality, it is trying to do the chat update (so it throws an ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException in the stream class). Even if I don&#39;t write the byte, it still does that. Has anyone else had these problems with that pesky packet as well?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 20:18:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Inside Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/player-update-packet/179592.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Player Update packet</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cheese_Police c|p]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheese_police">@Cheese_Police</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>moparisthebest also failed to refactor the stream class correctly, like writeByte is writeWordBigEndian (what the fuck?).</p>
<p>Could be that you are mixing up your packet structure.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/player-update-packet/179592/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/player-update-packet/179592/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 20:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-179592-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/player-update-packet/179592.rss">Player Update packet</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Player Update packet</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have been fooling around with the old 317 client (mopar’s refactor) and, mainly speaking, my few hours dealing with the player update packet have only been half successful. I should have mostly completed updating when it comes to walking as well as other player updating. However, the actual player update block is the part I am having troubles with. I looked at the client and saw that a 0 tells the client to not update that player, but I did that and it still continued to update. In actuality, it is trying to do the chat update (so it throws an ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException in the stream class). Even if I don’t write the byte, it still does that. Has anyone else had these problems with that pesky packet as well?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/player-update-packet/179592/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/player-update-packet/179592/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 04:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-179592-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/player-update-packet/179592.rss">Player Update packet</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
