<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Private server? D:</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-d/273337</link>
    <description>how do i get my private server to work i have my source, portforwarded, haave duc have an ip and everything it lets me log into 127.0.0.1 but not my ip and it lets me register but i have to wait all night with it running, and still doesnt even put it on the list and noones able to join me what am i missing for people to join?? i check marked my ip for it to work but noone can join please help i know theres other tutorials, but i dont understand what i did wrong i just need help with the step that so people can come in is it enviromental variables? if so, i kinda had problems with that, where do i put the codes on the top, or the bottom? i put classpath and path on the bottom both capitals on the path and classpath? where do in put them on the top place? and delete them on the bottom? i mean, idk what i did wrong on the bottom theres a PATHEXT though... but on the top theres only TEMP and TMP please help thanks ill be willing to give you admin on my server</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 12:57:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-d/273337.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Private server? D:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@twins twins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/twins">@twins</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>so you make a Path… Reread the tut… make sure you really understand it and there are not words there that you do not know.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-d/273337/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-d/273337/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 12:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-273337-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-d/273337.rss">Private server? D:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Private server? D:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@im_0nlyy im 0nlyy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/im_0nlyy">@im_0nlyy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>how do i get my private server to work i have my source, portforwarded, haave duc have an ip and everything it lets me log into 127.0.0.1 but not my ip and it lets me register but i have to wait all night with it running, and still doesnt even put it on the list and noones able to join me what am i missing for people to join?? i check marked my ip for it to work but noone can join please help i know theres other tutorials, but i dont understand what i did wrong i just need help with the step that so people can come in is it enviromental variables? if so, i kinda had problems with that, where do i put the codes on the top, or the bottom? i put classpath and path on the bottom both capitals on the path and classpath? where do in put them on the top place? and delete them on the bottom? i mean, idk what i did wrong on the bottom theres a PATHEXT though… but on the top theres only TEMP and TMP please help thanks ill be willing to give you admin on my server</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-d/273337/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-d/273337/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 12:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-273337-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/private-server-d/273337.rss">Private server? D:</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
