<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Adding &quot;Silab Items&quot;</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-silab-items/313022</link>
    <description>Hey, now then, I have a 317 client but want to add the &quot;Silab items&quot; to it. Cache update right? Skillcapes, Godswords etc. 

So I was wondering if anyone would be so nice as to explain how I go about adding the new cache etc. to my 317. My server is apparently already compatible, but there&#39;s obviously something wrong because when I spawn above 9,000, it&#39;s seeds, nulls and dwarf heads. 

I know this is a common problem but I don&#39;t know what&#39;s behind it all. 

I&#39;m a beginner.

I&#39;m willing to learn,  so give me the best information you got please and that will do fine. Even a link to a tutorial would be good.

Cheers.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 00:51:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-silab-items/313022.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Adding &quot;Silab Items&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lust.BS Lust.BS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lust.bs">@Lust.BS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey, now then, I have a 317 client but want to add the “Silab items” to it. Cache update right? Skillcapes, Godswords etc.</p>
<p>So I was wondering if anyone would be so nice as to explain how I go about adding the new cache etc. to my 317. My server is apparently already compatible, but there’s obviously something wrong because when I spawn above 9,000, it’s seeds, nulls and dwarf heads.</p>
<p>I know this is a common problem but I don’t know what’s behind it all.</p>
<p>I’m a beginner.</p>
<p>I’m willing to learn,  so give me the best information you got please and that will do fine. Even a link to a tutorial would be good.</p>
<p>Cheers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-silab-items/313022/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-silab-items/313022/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 00:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-313022-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/adding-silab-items/313022.rss">Adding &quot;Silab Items&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
