<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help With Server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622</link>
    <description>Table of Contents
First Post

    * 1. Useful Downloads
    * 2. Frequently Asked Questions
    * 3. MoparScape FAQ&#39;s
    * 4. Continuation of MoparScape FAQ&#39;s.
    * 5. Private Server Creation FAQ&#39;s
    * 6. Reminder and ending message




Top • Bottom •  Contents

Useful Downloads
In this part of the thread, there will be downloads of JDK, WinRar, etc. This will prevent topics regarding downloads.
JDK
Hamachi
WinRar
Moparscape 3.2 w/Aryan Client
Project 16 server base
Cheezscape server base
Testscape server base
MoparScape Download List
MoparScape Downloads Section
Compiler v 1.9 - Mod Taharok
Although, I advise you all to run a virus scan after you download something. For more information, click here.

Top • Bottom •  Contents

Frequently Asked Questions
I would request that NO-ONE post questions here, this is for you to look here an get the answer to your question without posting. This is NOT under any circumstances meant to be a help thread, do not turn it into one.

First, before you post anywhere on MoparScape, you need to read the Moparisthebest / MoparScape rules found here.

Legend
Q = Question
A = Answer

Top • Bottom •  Contents

MoparScape FAQ&#39;s

Q: How do I take a screen shot and post it on a thread here in MoparScape?

A: At the top of your keyboard, you will see a button that says &quot;Print Screen&quot;. When you hit this button, it will take a screen shot of the screen you are currently viewing. Then open up &quot;Microsoft Paint&quot; and paste it there. You will have the screen you took a screen shot of pasted on the paint window. Save it and go to an image hosting site. (www.photobucket.com etc.) Upload your pictures there and copy the img code and post it on a thread. You will see the image that you took a screen shot of.


Q: I can&#39;t log-in to any sever. I know the server is up, what is wrong?

A: This problem can be caused by not having the latest Java. Click here for a direct link to the download.


Q: Why can&#39;t I log-in to a server, I always get &quot;Error connecting to server must be down&quot; what&#39;s wrong?

A: If you can log-in to some servers then there is a 99%  chance that the other server is either Hamachi and you are trying to connect to it or it is just down. If you can&#39;t join any server, then you should re-download JDK 6u1 if you do not have it. Download it here. Also, you may want to re-download the MoparScape client after your JDK download is finished. Download the MoparScape client here.


Q: When I try to use the MoparScape client or web client, I get a red &quot;x&quot; in the corner. What&#39;s wrong?



A: This problem is usually caused by not having the latest Java. For a direct link to download JDK 6.0, click here.


Q: How do I join a server?

A: To join a private server, you need to go to &quot;File&quot; in either your MoparScape client or web client and click &quot;New Port&quot;.



Enter the port of the server (usually 43594, 5555) and click &quot;ok&quot;.



Click &quot;File&quot; once more and click &quot;New Server&quot;.



Enter the IP-Address of the server (e.g. Testscape.no-ip.org) and click &quot;ok&quot;.



Make up a user name and password and log-in!




Q: What are some commands for MoparScape?

A: Some useful commands for MoparScape are listed below:

::item
This command to spawn any item , if you type in the correct item id . For example, ::item 1233 1 spawns one Black Dagger (p) . To spawn more than one , you must make sure you ave the noted version of the item . To spawn more than one Black Dagger (p) the command is : ::item 1234 100 . This will spawn you 100 noted Black Dagger (p) &#39;s .

::pickup
This command is to spawn money or an item . You can use the above command for an item , in which the same rules apply . They are explained above . To spawn money , you can type in :pickup 0995 10000 . This spawns you 10000 gold .

::emote
If you type in ::emote 1 this will do the first emote on your emote list . You can type in the numbers all the way up to 22 .

::goup
If you type this in , your character will move up one space .

::godown
If you type this in , your character will move down one space .

::mypos 2
If you type this in , it will display to you your X coordinate as well as your Y coordinate .

::pass
If you type in ::pass swordfish , it will change your password to swordfish . You can make your password anything you want .

::clientdrop
Disconnects you quickly.

::lag
Lags your client.

::fpson
Turns of frames per second.

::fpsoff
Turns the above off.

::coordson
Shows your current world position.

::coordsoff
Turns the above off.

::noclip
Allows you to walk through walls.

Q: How do I advertise my server?

A: This can be done 1 way. Firstly, you may enter it on the new server status page. To do this, scroll to the bottom of the list and select the option to enter your own server. Then enter in the Server Name, port, IP-Address. To enter a Hamachi server, scroll down and click to enter your Hamachi server. Fill out the required information. Also, your server must be Online at the time otherwise you will get a message saying your server is off line.


Q: What are all the options of the bars and stuff at the top?

A: There are several options. First off, please look at the picture I have posted.


Home

When this option is clicked, it will direct you to the MoparScape Home/Index. A link is pasted below.
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php

Help

In Help, you will learn the abilities of the SMF forum. At the top you will see the options &quot;Introduction • Registering • Logging In • Profile • Posting • Personal Message • Searching&quot;. If you follow this until the end, you will have learned what all the abilities of the SMF forum are. This can be very helpful and I suggest you read them as it will make a better person in MoparScape. A link to &quot;Help&quot; is pasted below.
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=help

Search

In Search, you have the ability to type in a few words which can be: a topic title, key words in a topic title. This is very helpful when searching for a tutorial and even for a certain topic. This is usually a faster method than looking through the pages of the tutorials section. A link to &quot;Search&quot; is pasted below.
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=search

Profile

In Profile, you have the options to change your password, post a signature, e-mails and much much more! A link to &quot;Profile&quot; is pasted below.
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=profile

My Messages

In My Messages, you have the option to send Personal Messages to other members. This is also your inbox, in which Personal Messages will be placed when there is one sent to you. A link to &quot;My Messages&quot; is pasted below.
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=mymessages

Calendar

In Calendar, you have the option to view the calendar of the year as well as birthdays. A link to &quot;Calendar&quot; is pasted below.
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=calendar

Members

In Members, you have the option to search for other members and view their names, e-mails (as long as they aren&#39;t hidden), their last posts, their post count, their current rep and even their signature. A link to &quot;Members&quot; is pasted below.
http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php?action=members

Logout

When you click Logout, you will be logged out of your account.
 
These are the options on the options bar of SMF.

At the very top, you will see a little welcome message like &quot;Welcome [yournamehere]&quot;. Thanks to Moparisthebest for making us feel welcome. Wink

Above the option bar, you will see a few other phrases such as: &quot;Show unread posts since last visit&quot;. If this option is clicked, you will be veiwing the topics that haven&#39;t been viewed since your last visit.

Below it, you will see the option &quot;Show new replies to your posts&quot;. If this option is clicked, you will be viewing topics that you have posted in, in which others have posted after you. This is helpful when helping someone with a problem, when they reply, you will see it here.

Below that, you will see the option &quot;Total time logged in:&quot;. Beside this, you will see the amount of time that you have been logged into your account.

Q: What do all the things at the top do when you are posting, like the menu of the text box?

A:


Subject
Beside this option, you will see a text box. Within this, you can type in the subject of your topic. It can be a problem, a tutorial or anything related to MoparScape that is not an advertisement of a server. Please make sure that the topic title is not flamming anyone or swearing. Remember grammer and spelling is a must.

Message icon
This function allows you to choose the icon which will appear beside the subject of your post. It can be a or or any of the available icons.


When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear that is &quot;[b ][ /b]&quot;. In between the brackets &quot;]&quot; and &quot;[&quot; you can type the words that you wish to be placed in bold text. This can be useful when trying to catch peoples eye. Please do not abuse it.


When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear that is &quot;[i ][ /i]&quot;. In between the brackets &quot;]&quot; and &quot;[&quot; you can type the words that you wish to be placed in italic (slanted) text. This can be useful when making a topic look neat and organized.


When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear that is &quot;[u ][ /u]&quot;. In between the brackets &quot;]&quot; and &quot;[&quot; you can type the words that you wish to have underlined. This can be useful when organizing a topic and using correct grammer.


When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear that is &quot;[s ][ /s]&quot;. In between the brackets &quot;]&quot; and &quot;[&quot; you can type the words that you wish to have a strike through. This can be used for crossing out questions that have been answered if you have several.


When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear the is &quot;[shadow=red,left ][ /shadow]&quot;. In between the brackets &quot;]&quot; and &quot;[&quot; you can type the words that you wish to be colored and shadowed. You can switch the color by changing the code from &quot;red&quot; to another color. This can be used for making things look fancy. Please do not abuse this.


Top • Bottom • Contents[/list</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 10:13:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help With Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SilentCJ SilentCJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silentcj">@SilentCJ</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="307622">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 `Aaron:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>We don’t post topics more than once if they have been locked already.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 10:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-307622-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622.rss">Help With Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help With Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Telenim Telenim]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/telenim">@Telenim</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You’re stupid and this it not yours.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 06:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-307622-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622.rss">Help With Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help With Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n33bz0rpl0x `Aaron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n33bz0rpl0x">@n33bz0rpl0x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>We don’t post topics more than once if they have been locked already.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 06:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-307622-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622.rss">Help With Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help With Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@WestSideMass WestSideMass]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/westsidemass">@WestSideMass</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Pretty sure this ones getting locked too.<br>
Just because you double post basically the same thing doesn’t mean It won’t get locked the second time.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 20:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-307622-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622.rss">Help With Server</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Help With Server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Table of Contents<br>
First Post</p>
<pre><code>* 1. Useful Downloads
* 2. Frequently Asked Questions
* 3. MoparScape FAQ's
* 4. Continuation of MoparScape FAQ's.
* 5. Private Server Creation FAQ's
* 6. Reminder and ending message
</code></pre>
<p>Top • Bottom •  Contents</p>
<p>Useful Downloads<br>
In this part of the thread, there will be downloads of JDK, WinRar, etc. This will prevent topics regarding downloads.<br>
JDK<br>
Hamachi<br>
WinRar<br>
Moparscape 3.2 w/Aryan Client<br>
Project 16 server base<br>
Cheezscape server base<br>
Testscape server base<br>
MoparScape Download List<br>
MoparScape Downloads Section<br>
Compiler v 1.9 - Mod Taharok<br>
Although, I advise you all to run a virus scan after you download something. For more information, click here.</p>
<p>Top • Bottom •  Contents</p>
<p>Frequently Asked Questions<br>
I would request that NO-ONE post questions here, this is for you to look here an get the answer to your question without posting. This is NOT under any circumstances meant to be a help thread, do not turn it into one.</p>
<p>First, before you post anywhere on MoparScape, you need to read the Moparisthebest / MoparScape rules found here.</p>
<p>Legend<br>
Q = Question<br>
A = Answer</p>
<p>Top • Bottom •  Contents</p>
<p>MoparScape FAQ’s</p>
<p>Q: How do I take a screen shot and post it on a thread here in MoparScape?</p>
<p>A: At the top of your keyboard, you will see a button that says “Print Screen”. When you hit this button, it will take a screen shot of the screen you are currently viewing. Then open up “Microsoft Paint” and paste it there. You will have the screen you took a screen shot of pasted on the paint window. Save it and go to an image hosting site. (<a href="http://www.photobucket.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.photobucket.com</a> etc.) Upload your pictures there and copy the img code and post it on a thread. You will see the image that you took a screen shot of.</p>
<p>Q: I can’t log-in to any sever. I know the server is up, what is wrong?</p>
<p>A: This problem can be caused by not having the latest Java. Click here for a direct link to the download.</p>
<p>Q: Why can’t I log-in to a server, I always get “Error connecting to server must be down” what’s wrong?</p>
<p>A: If you can log-in to some servers then there is a 99%  chance that the other server is either Hamachi and you are trying to connect to it or it is just down. If you can’t join any server, then you should re-download JDK 6u1 if you do not have it. Download it here. Also, you may want to re-download the MoparScape client after your JDK download is finished. Download the MoparScape client here.</p>
<p>Q: When I try to use the MoparScape client or web client, I get a red “x” in the corner. What’s wrong?</p>
<p>A: This problem is usually caused by not having the latest Java. For a direct link to download JDK 6.0, click here.</p>
<p>Q: How do I join a server?</p>
<p>A: To join a private server, you need to go to “File” in either your MoparScape client or web client and click “New Port”.</p>
<p>Enter the port of the server (usually 43594, 5555) and click “ok”.</p>
<p>Click “File” once more and click “New Server”.</p>
<p>Enter the IP-Address of the server (e.g. <a href="http://Testscape.no-ip.org" rel="nofollow noopener">Testscape.no-ip.org</a>) and click “ok”.</p>
<p>Make up a user name and password and log-in!</p>
<p>Q: What are some commands for MoparScape?</p>
<p>A: Some useful commands for MoparScape are listed below:</p>
<p>::item<br>
This command to spawn any item , if you type in the correct item id . For example, ::item 1233 1 spawns one Black Dagger § . To spawn more than one , you must make sure you ave the noted version of the item . To spawn more than one Black Dagger § the command is : ::item 1234 100 . This will spawn you 100 noted Black Dagger § 's .</p>
<p>::pickup<br>
This command is to spawn money or an item . You can use the above command for an item , in which the same rules apply . They are explained above . To spawn money , you can type in :pickup 0995 10000 . This spawns you 10000 gold .</p>
<p>::emote<br>
If you type in ::emote 1 this will do the first emote on your emote list . You can type in the numbers all the way up to 22 .</p>
<p>::goup<br>
If you type this in , your character will move up one space .</p>
<p>::godown<br>
If you type this in , your character will move down one space .</p>
<p>::mypos 2<br>
If you type this in , it will display to you your X coordinate as well as your Y coordinate .</p>
<p>::pass<br>
If you type in ::pass swordfish , it will change your password to swordfish . You can make your password anything you want .</p>
<p>::clientdrop<br>
Disconnects you quickly.</p>
<p>::lag<br>
Lags your client.</p>
<p>::fpson<br>
Turns of frames per second.</p>
<p>::fpsoff<br>
Turns the above off.</p>
<p>::coordson<br>
Shows your current world position.</p>
<p>::coordsoff<br>
Turns the above off.</p>
<p>::noclip<br>
Allows you to walk through walls.</p>
<p>Q: How do I advertise my server?</p>
<p>A: This can be done 1 way. Firstly, you may enter it on the new server status page. To do this, scroll to the bottom of the list and select the option to enter your own server. Then enter in the Server Name, port, IP-Address. To enter a Hamachi server, scroll down and click to enter your Hamachi server. Fill out the required information. Also, your server must be Online at the time otherwise you will get a message saying your server is off line.</p>
<p>Q: What are all the options of the bars and stuff at the top?</p>
<p>A: There are several options. First off, please look at the picture I have posted.</p>
<p>Home</p>
<p>When this option is clicked, it will direct you to the MoparScape Home/Index. A link is pasted below.<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Help</p>
<p>In Help, you will learn the abilities of the SMF forum. At the top you will see the options “Introduction • Registering • Logging In • Profile • Posting • Personal Message • Searching”. If you follow this until the end, you will have learned what all the abilities of the SMF forum are. This can be very helpful and I suggest you read them as it will make a better person in MoparScape. A link to “Help” is pasted below.<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=help" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=help" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Search</p>
<p>In Search, you have the ability to type in a few words which can be: a topic title, key words in a topic title. This is very helpful when searching for a tutorial and even for a certain topic. This is usually a faster method than looking through the pages of the tutorials section. A link to “Search” is pasted below.<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=search" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=search" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Profile</p>
<p>In Profile, you have the options to change your password, post a signature, e-mails and much much more! A link to “Profile” is pasted below.<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=profile" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=profile" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>My Messages</p>
<p>In My Messages, you have the option to send Personal Messages to other members. This is also your inbox, in which Personal Messages will be placed when there is one sent to you. A link to “My Messages” is pasted below.<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=mymessages" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=mymessages" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Calendar</p>
<p>In Calendar, you have the option to view the calendar of the year as well as birthdays. A link to “Calendar” is pasted below.<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=calendar" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=calendar" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Members</p>
<p>In Members, you have the option to search for other members and view their names, e-mails (as long as they aren’t hidden), their last posts, their post count, their current rep and even their signature. A link to “Members” is pasted below.<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=members" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/4/41fecb6185fddc2758aeba68c3f8c9c78e26e4ff.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="500" height="500">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/?action=members" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Logout</p>
<p>When you click Logout, you will be logged out of your account.</p>
<p>These are the options on the options bar of SMF.</p>
<p>At the very top, you will see a little welcome message like “Welcome [yournamehere]”. Thanks to Moparisthebest for making us feel welcome. Wink</p>
<p>Above the option bar, you will see a few other phrases such as: “Show unread posts since last visit”. If this option is clicked, you will be veiwing the topics that haven’t been viewed since your last visit.</p>
<p>Below it, you will see the option “Show new replies to your posts”. If this option is clicked, you will be viewing topics that you have posted in, in which others have posted after you. This is helpful when helping someone with a problem, when they reply, you will see it here.</p>
<p>Below that, you will see the option “Total time logged in:”. Beside this, you will see the amount of time that you have been logged into your account.</p>
<p>Q: What do all the things at the top do when you are posting, like the menu of the text box?</p>
<p>A:</p>
<p>Subject<br>
Beside this option, you will see a text box. Within this, you can type in the subject of your topic. It can be a problem, a tutorial or anything related to MoparScape that is not an advertisement of a server. Please make sure that the topic title is not flamming anyone or swearing. Remember grammer and spelling is a must.</p>
<p>Message icon<br>
This function allows you to choose the icon which will appear beside the subject of your post. It can be a or or any of the available icons.</p>
<p>When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear that is “[b ][ /b]”. In between the brackets “]” and “[” you can type the words that you wish to be placed in bold text. This can be useful when trying to catch peoples eye. Please do not abuse it.</p>
<p>When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear that is “[i ][ /i]”. In between the brackets “]” and “[” you can type the words that you wish to be placed in italic (slanted) text. This can be useful when making a topic look neat and organized.</p>
<p>When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear that is “[u ][ /u]”. In between the brackets “]” and “[” you can type the words that you wish to have underlined. This can be useful when organizing a topic and using correct grammer.</p>
<p>When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear that is “[s ][ /s]”. In between the brackets “]” and “[” you can type the words that you wish to have a strike through. This can be used for crossing out questions that have been answered if you have several.</p>
<p>When this option is clicked, you will see a code appear the is “[shadow=red,left ][ /shadow]”. In between the brackets “]” and “[” you can type the words that you wish to be colored and shadowed. You can switch the color by changing the code from “red” to another color. This can be used for making things look fancy. Please do not abuse this.</p>
<p>Top • Bottom • Contents[/list</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 20:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-307622-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-server/307622.rss">Help With Server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
