<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204</link>
    <description>[B]Features:[/B]
Chops and Banks Yews in EdgeVille.
Chops and Banks Yews in Catherby.
Chops and Banks the Magic Tree&#39;s &amp; Magic/Yew from the Tree Patch by The Tree Gnome Stronghold Bank.
Supports up to 100 players.
Supports All Axes.
Supports S.M.A.R.T.
Saves Progress Reports.
Supports Latest SCAR &amp; SRL.
Solves All Currently Solvable Randoms.
Detects and Avoids Ents.
Intelligent AntiBan.
Comprehensive &amp; Accurate Progress Reports.
Options for almost every scenario.
Working Bird Nest Finder!!
The only Working Strange Plant Finder &amp; Picker!
Drops Low Value Items from Random Events.
Uses Genie Lamps on any Skill of your Choosing.

[B]
This has been tested and works using SCAR 3.15b
This has been tested and works using SRL 20[/B]



This Script Was Formerly the Popular [I][B]Simple Yew Cutter &amp; Banker[/B][/I] it has outgrown the simple in it&#39;s title and will soon support numerous other locations and tree types including Banking Magic Trees hence the Ultra.

Please take a little bit of time and read through the options within the script before starting it. It should be fairly easy for most to read and understand.

Wherever possible I have used existing SRL functions to maintain future compatibility.

Any Positive or Helpful Comments, Advise or Requests Please Let me know..

If you have any problems please ensure you have followed the instructions correctly and read through the posts before posting your problem. Also post as many details as possible concerning the nature of your problem.


[B]Instructions:[/B]
Make sure that Windows is set to [B]32bit[/B] colour depth.
Unless you use the S.M.A.R.T version make sure that Runescape runs in [B]Low Detail[/B].
Add Your details to the player form.
Set Your Players Locations (locations in script at top) which are:

[B]CY[/B] - If you type CY you place your player in Catherby bank for chopping yews (Members)

[B]E[/B] - If you type E you place your player in Edgevile bank for chopping yews

[B]SM[/B] - If you type SM you place you player in Tree Gnome Stronghold bank for cutting magic trees (Members)                   

Stand Anywhere in Edgeville Bank, the Tree Gnome Stronghold Bank or the Catherby Bank.
Make sure you have any axe, anywhere in your backpack or hand.
Start Script.
[B]Enjoy!![/B]

[B]oh. and by the way this script does have a stats in it 
but the stats script doesnt seem to work so scar will open a page but if it comes up with something like &quot;sorry this service is unavalible at the moment&quot; then dont worry i am trying to fix it[/B]


[CODE]

******************************* Version History *******************************
V1.71 Made new procedure for the catherby bank and it now saves proggys.
V1.7  Updated for SRL4 revision 19 and Shuttleu has taken over the script.
V1.63 Fixed problem with not finding the rock color.
V1.62 Fixed issue where script would bank axe if it was in the players inventory.
      Changed FindBirdsNest to use old FindObj and Work all the time again.
V1.61 Updated for SRL4 revision 15
      Fixed a small AntiBan bug whic could cause a player to wander off randomly.
      Improved all Gnome Stronghold Routines.
      Improved walking routines in catherby.
      Improved Shop Finding in Catherby.
      Added a Shop Autocolour failsafe in Catherby.
      Improved Edgeville timings, should now be even more efficient.
V1.60 Quick fix for a bug within my new StrangeplantFinder which caused it not to work. Now Works.
V1.59 Fixed an error whilst chopping Catherby Yews which could cause player to get lost.
      Fixed an error where player would not return to catherby bank when certain shop colours were set.
      Small improvement to Tree Symbol AutoColouring.
      Created new function to find two seperate points within a defined distance from each other.
      Made major changes to StrangePlantFinder routine, nearly ready for full public release.
      Made a small change to Catherby routine to stop occasional erroneous MM click.
      Changed tree symbol detection in stronghold to autocolour routine used in catherby.
      Gnome Stronghold Magic Tree Cutiing now looks for Magic Tree Spot before Farming Tree Spot.
      Created a Bank symbol Autocolour Routine for when FindSymbol Fails, means less logging out on busy worlds.
      Changed starting GameTab order.
      Added individual per player report to end of final report.
      Improved Catherby Banking Procedure.
      Improved Edgeville return to Bank routine.
      Improved ability to find Bank Symbol in edgeville even in a very busy bank.
      Improved Tree symbol acuracy in Edgeville.
      Improved CutTillDown procedure for speed, tree detection, mouse tracking &amp; antiban.
      Improved return to bank procedure in Magic Trees in Gnome Stronghold.
      Improved ability to find gnome banker in Gnome Stronghold Bank.
      Modified position correction in gnome stronghold mage cutting routine to stop it gettin lost.
      Made small change to CutTillDown procedure to reduce mouse movement whilst chopping.
V1.58 Fully Implimented and tested Catherby Yews option.
      Made small changes to CutTillDown to stay focused on active tree.
      Improved walk to yews and back in Catherby area.
      Lots of tweaking to find tree colour by symbol or dtm for Catherby.
      Re-wrote &amp; simplified bank area detection in Catherby.
      Improved opening bank procedure for Catherby.
V1.57 Optimised CutTillDown Routine.
      Fixed rare error in CutTillDown which could cause player to lose location after a random.
      Found and Fixed a possible cause of lag in CutDownEdYew procedure.
      Added a timer to CutDownEdYew to change trees if player was waiting too long.
      Improved GetIconColours to SetRun after a logout/in and ensure that a tree colour was found.
      Improved MyInPin to cope with additional potential for incorrect entry.
V1.56 Slight tweak of CheckForAllRandoms to remove surplus debug messages.
      hopefully fixed lag.
      Stopped GetIconColours being called every trip in EdgeVille.
V1.55 Improved stronghold cutting to chop mages first if any exist.
      Improved time to first cut at gnome stronghold.
      Removed an earlier temporary bodge as it was no longer needed.
      Improved stair finding routine.
      Added check to make sure player has the required level to chop magic logs if in stronghold.
      Added a couple of small check in preparation for 2 new areas.
V1.54 Increased chance of AntiBan running whilst waiting for Magic Trees to grow back.
      Improved mage cutting procedure and made it universal so it can be used in other areas.
      Replaced old CutTillDown procedure with the new improved version version.
      Reduced erroneous messages in debug window.
      Added a Random Members/Non Members World Chooser function.
      Improved chances of finding gnome banker.
      Improved banking procedure and added a check to ensure correct pin was entered.
      Made function MoveToStM more robust.
      Fixed an issue with antiban that could cause Randoms Checking to result in &quot;No GameTab&quot; Error.
      Tracked down and corrected error which could result in double reports.
      Improved Capt Arnav check and logout.
V1.53 Integrated New Area: The Magic Tree/Farming Tree Patch in the Tree Gnome Stronghold Area.
      Integrated beta version of Negaals FindTree function.
      Added Magic Tree Capability to Negaals FindTree Function.
      Fixed Negaals Tree Finder to world with SRL rev 14.
      Changed orientation when chopping south yew as some randoms could be hidden behind tree.
      Added Players Location.
      Created new functions: CoordsToDegrees(x, y) &amp; MakeCompassCoords(x, y) to automatically position a targert north of the player.
      Changed procedure names &amp; main program structure to incorporate additional locations.
      Updated reports to incorporate magic logs &amp; locations.
      Updated SRL Reporting to record all Magic Logs as well as Yews.
      Created new routine to LogOut player if encountering Capt Arnav who now appears occasionally when chopping in Tree Patch.
      Created new routine Detect and click continue for Nature Spirit Message that appears occasionally when chopping near Tree Patch.
      added quick temp Bodge to allow yews to be cut in Tree Patch.
V1.52 Fixed bug in Strange Plant Finder which could cause it to wait indefinitely.
V1.51 Implimented possible fix for Lag some people experienced when chopping.
      Automatically sets brightness.
V1.50 Major Update hundreds of minor changes
      Name Change to Ultra Chop n Bank in preparation for future additions.
      Now Supports Multiple Players.
      Created new procedure MyRandomPlayerNext as SRL version was not working for me.
      Created new function NoMorePlayers returns false when all players are finished.
      Re-Written Reports to cope with individual Players.
      Created a new Final Report.
      Added Debug Option true/false.
      Changed all commenting to follows SRL Style.
      Added more items to unwanted items list.
      Updated Birds Nest(Egg) DTM so that it will detect all types.
      Fixed memory allocation problem with Strange Plant Finder.
      Fixed odd mouse behaviour and loop that happened if plant took too long to die.
      Improved Strange Plant Finder behaviour after picking.
      Improved Banking Routine.
      Improved Custom Run Away Routine.
V1.12 beta Added Variable TypeOfAxe to the FindTheAxe. Returns the Type of Axe that is being used.
      Made some small changes in readiness for the switchover to a Multi-Player Script.
      Implemented new quick check function as a failsafe to check axe is present while chopping.
      Added a check to make sure a valid world is selected for S.M.A.R.T.
      Improved Strange Plant Finder and now also detects if plant is after other player.
      Reduced amount of times DropUnwanted is called. Now only calls it when needed.
      Improved CustomRunAway procedure. Now even more robust.
      Improved GoToBank procedure. Now even more robust.
V1.11 beta Fixed my previous FindFight Fix. Fighting Randoms should be detected for everyone now.
      Major overhall of my FindTheAxe function turning it into a completely self contain function.
      Added Woodcutting/Attack Level checking &amp; handling to FindTheAxe function.
      Added option to FindTheAxe to set axe position.
      Added a variable to FindTheAxe to determine axe location.
      Updated MyFindBirdsNest to return the GameTab position to where it was at before it was called.
V1.10 beta Added support for SMART
      added more unwanted items to DropUnwanted array
      Changed CustomRunAway to shorter WaitTime &amp; to just run to bank as RandomDetection is now better.
      Replaced custom CountItemDtm with offical SRL function: CountItemsDtm
      Tweaked my Bird Nest Finder to improve the guarantee that last text is changed to avoid a loop.
      Temp Fix to correct FindFight problem created by the SRL 12 &amp; 13 update
      Dramatically reduced CPU overheads by removing all redundant Randoms checks.
V1.09 Fixed a conflict in StrangePlantFinder that caused an access violation (Cleared DTM and then Counted DTM)
V1.08 beta Added a Strange Plant Finder (Very Beta but works, needs refining in a major way)
      Tweaked AntiBan to start less often to improve speed of cutting
      Improved Reporting system and now Digit Groups all number to make them easy to read.
V1.07 beta Added a procedure to wait and try again when a &quot;not LoggedIn&quot; event is detected
      Now saves and Displays a Screenshot for when &quot;Not LoggedIn&quot; event is detected to help debug
      Added Woodcutting Level, XP &amp; Script Version to reporting
V1.06 beta Added Custom Procedure to Find Birds Nests when dropped from tree. (beta)
      Record failed attempts to find Birds Nest.
      added procedure to drop low value items from Random events
      improved random detection.
V1.05 beta Fixed Minor Reorting issue for RandomItemsBanked
      Lots of small improvements.
      Last Version Posted in First Scripts, If you want further versions become a Junior Member.
V1.04 beta Updated to work with SRL 11
      increased speed of cutting.
V1.03 beta Fixed the intermittent FindTalk Random bug.
      Improved CustomRunAway procedure.
      Integrated SRL Stats.
      Minor bug fixes and optimisations.
V1.02 beta Fixed a few bugs introduced when I cleaned up the script for release.
      Improved Item Count Function &amp; Fixed intermitent problems with it.
      Created Custom Runaway From Fight Routine just for Edgeville Yew Area. (beta)
V1.01 beta Minor Tweaks to a few Coordinates &amp; small counting fix.
V1.00 beta First public beta release
*******************************************************************************[/CODE]

[B]If you like and use this script then don&#39;t forget to Rep++ me (for updating the script) and.....[/B]
[B]RATE THIS THREAD!! [/B][B]*****[/B] [B]5 Stars!![/B]

you can download the script form here [URL=http://&quot;http://www.shuttleu.net/UltraCutnBank.scar&quot;]Ultra Cut n Bank[/URL]
i would have just uploaded it here but the forum wont let me because the file size is too big because it is over 3000 lines long


~shut</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 23:23:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@script_owned script_owned]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/script_owned">@script_owned</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This script is almost a year old so it is probably out-dated use one on the newer scripts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 23:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@satanatas satanatas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/satanatas">@satanatas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>im new to this… when i click on the link to download this script, it takes me to <a href="http://found-not-help.com" rel="nofollow noopener">found-not-help.com</a> because it copied the link as “http://%22http//www.shuttleu.net/UltraCutnBank.scar%22”    can you pleeeasee help me out?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 19:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@omegaxx omegaxx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omegaxx">@omegaxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i Love this thank youuu =]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 23:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@superwauwie superwauwie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/superwauwie">@superwauwie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes it can,<br>
You only have to change (if he use BMP) the BMP’s and replace them with the willow one.<br>
(I can’t see how his script looks like, because of the broking link.)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 16:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andy89898 Andy89898]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andy89898">@Andy89898</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>can you do it with willows?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 18:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wasted202 wasted202]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wasted202">@wasted202</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i agree with the fu, they didnt put your name on the left of every post for no reason…<br>
[center]<img src="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnwarn.gif" alt width="" height=""> Useless gravedig.[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 07:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IP-Drowner IP-Drowner]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ip-drowner">@IP-Drowner</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“shuttleu, post:4, topic:224204”][quote author=IP-Drowner link=topic=294515.msg2368632#msg2368632 date=1218090747]<br>
Did you get permission to upgrade it from U L T R A Shuttleu?<br>
[/quote]U L T R A didn’t make this script</p>
<p>~shut[/quote]<br>
:o I thought he did because of the name <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>[quote=“the fu superior, post:6, topic:224204”][quote author=shuttleu link=topic=294515.msg2368870#msg2368870 date=1218117645]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Did you get permission to upgrade it from U L T R A Shuttleu?<br>
[/quote]U L T R A didn’t make this script</p>
<p>~shut</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Stop doing this<br>
“~shut”<br>
we know who the fuck you are.</p>
<p>~asshole[/quote]<br>
WTF is wrong with doing that? Got a problem with name signatures?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 05:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whothe0 the fu superior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whothe0">@whothe0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“shuttleu, post:4, topic:224204”][quote author=IP-Drowner link=topic=294515.msg2368632#msg2368632 date=1218090747]<br>
Did you get permission to upgrade it from U L T R A Shuttleu?<br>
[/quote]U L T R A didn’t make this script</p>
<p>~shut[/quote]</p>
<p>Stop doing this<br>
“~shut”<br>
we know who the fuck you are.</p>
<p>~asshole</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@LikeLightning LikeLightning]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/likelightning">@LikeLightning</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>o.o, your link is not working to the download / script page.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 12:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shuttleu shuttleu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shuttleu">@shuttleu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“IP-Drowner, post:3, topic:224204”]Did you get permission to upgrade it from U L T R A Shuttleu?[/quote]U L T R A didn’t make this script</p>
<p>~shut</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 14:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IP-Drowner IP-Drowner]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ip-drowner">@IP-Drowner</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Did you get permission to upgrade it from U L T R A Shuttleu?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 06:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n33bz0rpl0x `Aaron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n33bz0rpl0x">@n33bz0rpl0x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="1" data-topic="224204">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/shuttleu/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> shuttleu:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you like and use this script then don’t forget to Rep++ me (for updating the script) and…</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 01:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Ultra Cut n Bank</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@shuttleu shuttleu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shuttleu">@shuttleu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Features:</span><br>
Chops and Banks Yews in EdgeVille.<br>
Chops and Banks Yews in Catherby.<br>
Chops and Banks the Magic Tree’s &amp; Magic/Yew from the Tree Patch by The Tree Gnome Stronghold Bank.<br>
Supports up to 100 players.<br>
Supports All Axes.<br>
Supports S.M.A.R.T.<br>
Saves Progress Reports.<br>
Supports Latest SCAR &amp; SRL.<br>
Solves All Currently Solvable Randoms.<br>
Detects and Avoids Ents.<br>
Intelligent AntiBan.<br>
Comprehensive &amp; Accurate Progress Reports.<br>
Options for almost every scenario.<br>
Working Bird Nest Finder!!<br>
The only Working Strange Plant Finder &amp; Picker!<br>
Drops Low Value Items from Random Events.<br>
Uses Genie Lamps on any Skill of your Choosing.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
This has been tested and works using SCAR 3.15b<br>
This has been tested and works using SRL 20</span></p>
<p>This Script Was Formerly the Popular <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Simple Yew Cutter &amp; Banker</span></span> it has outgrown the simple in it’s title and will soon support numerous other locations and tree types including Banking Magic Trees hence the Ultra.</p>
<p>Please take a little bit of time and read through the options within the script before starting it. It should be fairly easy for most to read and understand.</p>
<p>Wherever possible I have used existing SRL functions to maintain future compatibility.</p>
<p>Any Positive or Helpful Comments, Advise or Requests Please Let me know…</p>
<p>If you have any problems please ensure you have followed the instructions correctly and read through the posts before posting your problem. Also post as many details as possible concerning the nature of your problem.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Instructions:</span><br>
Make sure that Windows is set to <span class="bbcode-b">32bit</span> colour depth.<br>
Unless you use the S.M.A.R.T version make sure that Runescape runs in <span class="bbcode-b">Low Detail</span>.<br>
Add Your details to the player form.<br>
Set Your Players Locations (locations in script at top) which are:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">CY</span> - If you type CY you place your player in Catherby bank for chopping yews (Members)</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">E</span> - If you type E you place your player in Edgevile bank for chopping yews</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">SM</span> - If you type SM you place you player in Tree Gnome Stronghold bank for cutting magic trees (Members)</p>
<p>Stand Anywhere in Edgeville Bank, the Tree Gnome Stronghold Bank or the Catherby Bank.<br>
Make sure you have any axe, anywhere in your backpack or hand.<br>
Start Script.<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Enjoy!!</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">oh. and by the way this script does have a stats in it<br>
but the stats script doesnt seem to work so scar will open a page but if it comes up with something like “sorry this service is unavalible at the moment” then dont worry i am trying to fix it</span></p>
<p>[CODE]</p>
<p>******************************* Version History *******************************<br>
V1.71 Made new procedure for the catherby bank and it now saves proggys.<br>
V1.7  Updated for SRL4 revision 19 and Shuttleu has taken over the script.<br>
V1.63 Fixed problem with not finding the rock color.<br>
V1.62 Fixed issue where script would bank axe if it was in the players inventory.<br>
Changed FindBirdsNest to use old FindObj and Work all the time again.<br>
V1.61 Updated for SRL4 revision 15<br>
Fixed a small AntiBan bug whic could cause a player to wander off randomly.<br>
Improved all Gnome Stronghold Routines.<br>
Improved walking routines in catherby.<br>
Improved Shop Finding in Catherby.<br>
Added a Shop Autocolour failsafe in Catherby.<br>
Improved Edgeville timings, should now be even more efficient.<br>
V1.60 Quick fix for a bug within my new StrangeplantFinder which caused it not to work. Now Works.<br>
V1.59 Fixed an error whilst chopping Catherby Yews which could cause player to get lost.<br>
Fixed an error where player would not return to catherby bank when certain shop colours were set.<br>
Small improvement to Tree Symbol AutoColouring.<br>
Created new function to find two seperate points within a defined distance from each other.<br>
Made major changes to StrangePlantFinder routine, nearly ready for full public release.<br>
Made a small change to Catherby routine to stop occasional erroneous MM click.<br>
Changed tree symbol detection in stronghold to autocolour routine used in catherby.<br>
Gnome Stronghold Magic Tree Cutiing now looks for Magic Tree Spot before Farming Tree Spot.<br>
Created a Bank symbol Autocolour Routine for when FindSymbol Fails, means less logging out on busy worlds.<br>
Changed starting GameTab order.<br>
Added individual per player report to end of final report.<br>
Improved Catherby Banking Procedure.<br>
Improved Edgeville return to Bank routine.<br>
Improved ability to find Bank Symbol in edgeville even in a very busy bank.<br>
Improved Tree symbol acuracy in Edgeville.<br>
Improved CutTillDown procedure for speed, tree detection, mouse tracking &amp; antiban.<br>
Improved return to bank procedure in Magic Trees in Gnome Stronghold.<br>
Improved ability to find gnome banker in Gnome Stronghold Bank.<br>
Modified position correction in gnome stronghold mage cutting routine to stop it gettin lost.<br>
Made small change to CutTillDown procedure to reduce mouse movement whilst chopping.<br>
V1.58 Fully Implimented and tested Catherby Yews option.<br>
Made small changes to CutTillDown to stay focused on active tree.<br>
Improved walk to yews and back in Catherby area.<br>
Lots of tweaking to find tree colour by symbol or dtm for Catherby.<br>
Re-wrote &amp; simplified bank area detection in Catherby.<br>
Improved opening bank procedure for Catherby.<br>
V1.57 Optimised CutTillDown Routine.<br>
Fixed rare error in CutTillDown which could cause player to lose location after a random.<br>
Found and Fixed a possible cause of lag in CutDownEdYew procedure.<br>
Added a timer to CutDownEdYew to change trees if player was waiting too long.<br>
Improved GetIconColours to SetRun after a logout/in and ensure that a tree colour was found.<br>
Improved MyInPin to cope with additional potential for incorrect entry.<br>
V1.56 Slight tweak of CheckForAllRandoms to remove surplus debug messages.<br>
hopefully fixed lag.<br>
Stopped GetIconColours being called every trip in EdgeVille.<br>
V1.55 Improved stronghold cutting to chop mages first if any exist.<br>
Improved time to first cut at gnome stronghold.<br>
Removed an earlier temporary bodge as it was no longer needed.<br>
Improved stair finding routine.<br>
Added check to make sure player has the required level to chop magic logs if in stronghold.<br>
Added a couple of small check in preparation for 2 new areas.<br>
V1.54 Increased chance of AntiBan running whilst waiting for Magic Trees to grow back.<br>
Improved mage cutting procedure and made it universal so it can be used in other areas.<br>
Replaced old CutTillDown procedure with the new improved version version.<br>
Reduced erroneous messages in debug window.<br>
Added a Random Members/Non Members World Chooser function.<br>
Improved chances of finding gnome banker.<br>
Improved banking procedure and added a check to ensure correct pin was entered.<br>
Made function MoveToStM more robust.<br>
Fixed an issue with antiban that could cause Randoms Checking to result in “No GameTab” Error.<br>
Tracked down and corrected error which could result in double reports.<br>
Improved Capt Arnav check and logout.<br>
V1.53 Integrated New Area: The Magic Tree/Farming Tree Patch in the Tree Gnome Stronghold Area.<br>
Integrated beta version of Negaals FindTree function.<br>
Added Magic Tree Capability to Negaals FindTree Function.<br>
Fixed Negaals Tree Finder to world with SRL rev 14.<br>
Changed orientation when chopping south yew as some randoms could be hidden behind tree.<br>
Added Players Location.<br>
Created new functions: CoordsToDegrees(x, y) &amp; MakeCompassCoords(x, y) to automatically position a targert north of the player.<br>
Changed procedure names &amp; main program structure to incorporate additional locations.<br>
Updated reports to incorporate magic logs &amp; locations.<br>
Updated SRL Reporting to record all Magic Logs as well as Yews.<br>
Created new routine to LogOut player if encountering Capt Arnav who now appears occasionally when chopping in Tree Patch.<br>
Created new routine Detect and click continue for Nature Spirit Message that appears occasionally when chopping near Tree Patch.<br>
added quick temp Bodge to allow yews to be cut in Tree Patch.<br>
V1.52 Fixed bug in Strange Plant Finder which could cause it to wait indefinitely.<br>
V1.51 Implimented possible fix for Lag some people experienced when chopping.<br>
Automatically sets brightness.<br>
V1.50 Major Update hundreds of minor changes<br>
Name Change to Ultra Chop n Bank in preparation for future additions.<br>
Now Supports Multiple Players.<br>
Created new procedure MyRandomPlayerNext as SRL version was not working for me.<br>
Created new function NoMorePlayers returns false when all players are finished.<br>
Re-Written Reports to cope with individual Players.<br>
Created a new Final Report.<br>
Added Debug Option true/false.<br>
Changed all commenting to follows SRL Style.<br>
Added more items to unwanted items list.<br>
Updated Birds Nest(Egg) DTM so that it will detect all types.<br>
Fixed memory allocation problem with Strange Plant Finder.<br>
Fixed odd mouse behaviour and loop that happened if plant took too long to die.<br>
Improved Strange Plant Finder behaviour after picking.<br>
Improved Banking Routine.<br>
Improved Custom Run Away Routine.<br>
V1.12 beta Added Variable TypeOfAxe to the FindTheAxe. Returns the Type of Axe that is being used.<br>
Made some small changes in readiness for the switchover to a Multi-Player Script.<br>
Implemented new quick check function as a failsafe to check axe is present while chopping.<br>
Added a check to make sure a valid world is selected for S.M.A.R.T.<br>
Improved Strange Plant Finder and now also detects if plant is after other player.<br>
Reduced amount of times DropUnwanted is called. Now only calls it when needed.<br>
Improved CustomRunAway procedure. Now even more robust.<br>
Improved GoToBank procedure. Now even more robust.<br>
V1.11 beta Fixed my previous FindFight Fix. Fighting Randoms should be detected for everyone now.<br>
Major overhall of my FindTheAxe function turning it into a completely self contain function.<br>
Added Woodcutting/Attack Level checking &amp; handling to FindTheAxe function.<br>
Added option to FindTheAxe to set axe position.<br>
Added a variable to FindTheAxe to determine axe location.<br>
Updated MyFindBirdsNest to return the GameTab position to where it was at before it was called.<br>
V1.10 beta Added support for SMART<br>
added more unwanted items to DropUnwanted array<br>
Changed CustomRunAway to shorter WaitTime &amp; to just run to bank as RandomDetection is now better.<br>
Replaced custom CountItemDtm with offical SRL function: CountItemsDtm<br>
Tweaked my Bird Nest Finder to improve the guarantee that last text is changed to avoid a loop.<br>
Temp Fix to correct FindFight problem created by the SRL 12 &amp; 13 update<br>
Dramatically reduced CPU overheads by removing all redundant Randoms checks.<br>
V1.09 Fixed a conflict in StrangePlantFinder that caused an access violation (Cleared DTM and then Counted DTM)<br>
V1.08 beta Added a Strange Plant Finder (Very Beta but works, needs refining in a major way)<br>
Tweaked AntiBan to start less often to improve speed of cutting<br>
Improved Reporting system and now Digit Groups all number to make them easy to read.<br>
V1.07 beta Added a procedure to wait and try again when a “not LoggedIn” event is detected<br>
Now saves and Displays a Screenshot for when “Not LoggedIn” event is detected to help debug<br>
Added Woodcutting Level, XP &amp; Script Version to reporting<br>
V1.06 beta Added Custom Procedure to Find Birds Nests when dropped from tree. (beta)<br>
Record failed attempts to find Birds Nest.<br>
added procedure to drop low value items from Random events<br>
improved random detection.<br>
V1.05 beta Fixed Minor Reorting issue for RandomItemsBanked<br>
Lots of small improvements.<br>
Last Version Posted in First Scripts, If you want further versions become a Junior Member.<br>
V1.04 beta Updated to work with SRL 11<br>
increased speed of cutting.<br>
V1.03 beta Fixed the intermittent FindTalk Random bug.<br>
Improved CustomRunAway procedure.<br>
Integrated SRL Stats.<br>
Minor bug fixes and optimisations.<br>
V1.02 beta Fixed a few bugs introduced when I cleaned up the script for release.<br>
Improved Item Count Function &amp; Fixed intermitent problems with it.<br>
Created Custom Runaway From Fight Routine just for Edgeville Yew Area. (beta)<br>
V1.01 beta Minor Tweaks to a few Coordinates &amp; small counting fix.<br>
V1.00 beta First public beta release<br>
*******************************************************************************[/CODE]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">If you like and use this script then don’t forget to Rep++ me (for updating the script) and…</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">RATE THIS THREAD!! </span><span class="bbcode-b">*****</span> <span class="bbcode-b">5 Stars!!</span></p>
<p>you can download the script form here <a data-bbcode="true">Ultra Cut n Bank</a><br>
i would have just uploaded it here but the forum wont let me because the file size is too big because it is over 3000 lines long</p>
<p>~shut</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 23:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-224204-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ultra-cut-n-bank/224204.rss">Ultra Cut n Bank</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
