<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RuneLimited</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521</link>
    <description>[center][SIZE=7][FONT=Impact][COLOR=Blue][I][U]RuneLimited[/U][/I][/COLOR][/FONT][/SIZE][/center]

This is my latest project, RuneLimited. I started a project on it awhile ago and never got around to finishing it. Well the past few weeks I have been working vigorously on it. I haven&#39;t updated the actual server updates recently, but the bug fixes and updates have been updated frequently.

My goal of RuneLimited is to create a server that has a good economy, a good community, and something that provides satisfaction for everybody that plays. I am the creator of this project and the only person involved, I do not wish to form a group project of any sort.

If you want to find some more details about updates, visit the blog for RuneLimited by clicking [url=http://runelimited.blogspot.com/]here[/url]

[b][SIZE=5][COLOR=Blue][u]Features[/u][/COLOR][/size][/b]

[b][COLOR=Blue][U]Shops[/COLOR][/b]
[I]My shop system is what I focused on for a bit, it is what is going to seperate the economy of this server from others. On most servers, you can sell items for the same price you can buy them for. This ruins the economy completely, as the players aren&#39;t encouraged to merchant or sell to other players, so the circulation of coins is ruined.

Well, on RuneLimited, my shop system works similar to RuneScape&#39;s. You can sell an item for less than what you can buy it for. In RuneLimited, if you sell an item, you get 70% of the shop value. Now this only applies to regular items, not rare items like godswords, rare new armour, etcetera. If an item is a rare item, it sells to the shop for 10% of the shop value, which you still receive a fair amount of coins.[/I]

[b][COLOR=Blue][U]Player VS. Player(PKing)[/COLOR][/b]
[I]RuneLimited has the good old PvP that the old RuneScape had, the PKing everybody loved. It has correct multi-combat areas, as well as 100% working 1v1, such as edgeville. The magic on player works, and the spells require ruins, except for teleport spells. If you are in level 20+ wilderness, you cannot teleport, at all. If you ice barrage someone, they are frozen for 20 seconds, that is if the hit is successful.

When you kill someone, all their items except for 3 items [4 if protect items is on] are dropped upon death. If you are killed, it is vice-versa. All prayers work accordingly, with headicons working now. The wilderness levels are 100% like RuneScape, and you can&#39;t attack someone if they aren&#39;t within the range of the levels.[/I]

[b][COLOR=Blue][U]Mini Games[/COLOR][/b]
[I]RuneLimited has several mini games that are fully working. The best one by far is barrows. It has all 6 brothers in their according crypts, which require a spade to get into. Protection prayers work against all of them, and prayer potions are recommended, HIGHLY. When inside crypts and the tunnel, your prayer is drained rapidly, just like in RuneScape. You also receive random chest loots, with the last brother required to kill in the tunnels. The tunnel brother is random.

Jad. The Jad on RuneLimited is not like RuneScape&#39;s. Mine has 8 waves, as I couldn&#39;t be bothered to make all 64 work. Well, don&#39;t think &quot;aww fuck it only has 8 waves its too easy.&quot;. You are wrong. The last 3 stages are extremely challenging, especially defeating Jad. Healers come in and rapidly attack you as well as heal Jad. I find myself struggling to beat my own Jad at times. Also, all NPC&#39;s attack properly, and use the correct graphics and animations. Prayer works perfectly, and is drained rapidly just like RuneScape. When you kill Jad you get a random tokkul reward as well as a fire cape. You MUST kill Jad to wear a fire cape.

Dagannoth caves. The dagannoth caves are located where they are in RuneScape. To get to the dag kings, you must go through the maze like in RuneScape. I didn&#39;t put my all into the caves, so they lack realistic attacks, but they work well. Rewards are like RuneScape.[/I]

[b][COLOR=Blue][U]Items[/COLOR][/b]
[I]The items on the server are actually hard to obtain, instead of typing ::master and ::pickup 1048 1, you actually have to work for items. I have added new items such as godswords, dragon platebody, dragon full helm, and dragon claws. However, these items are hard to obtain, and I am coming up with new ways to obtain rarer items. The circulation of rare items will be kept well under control, as duping is impossible on this server[as far as I know].[/I]

[b][COLOR=Blue][U]Skills[/COLOR][/b]
[I]The skills on RuneLimited will be as close to RuneScape as I can get them, and no tutorials will be used at all. Currently only two skills work perfectly. Woodcutting and firemaking. All skills, except a few, will grant you 3 times the experience you would receive in RuneScape. This way, 99&#39;s are actually challenging, as well as rewarding. ALL skills will be added.[/I]

[b][COLOR=Blue][U]Combat[/COLOR][/b]
[I]You currently get 30xp per hit. I&#39;m thinking of raising it to 40, maybe 45, but no higher. The combat system works very well. Almost all items have correct timers, and almost all items that have special attacks, have 100% special attacks. Like dragon dagger(s), it hits twice perfectly as well as poisons, with the highest poison of 6. Magic works very well and spells require runes, which can be obtained through runecrafting or buying them from players or shops. Prayer also works, with required levels.[/I]

This is all I can think of right now, and I have to go. This post will be updated, and I plan to host the server for people to play. The server is currently undergoing BETA testing, and many bugs have been fixed. There is currently a BETA client out that you can play the server on, [url=http://www.mediafire.com/?qz43tumn1iw][Download Here][/url].


[SIZE=1]NOTE: Pictures are included under the update log.[/SIZE]

[B][U][SIZE=3]Update Log[/SIZE][/U][/B]


[u][b]March 25, 2009[/b][/u]
[i]-New HD models loading[url=http://i44.tinypic.com/330v7k9.jpg][liNK][/url].
-Redid herblore, xp is 5x RuneScape, identifying herbs works, mixing is 100%.
-Woodcutting and firemaking are now 5x RuneScape&#39;s XP.[/i]

[B][U]March 23, 2009[/b]
-Redid NPC dialogue, how it works, and handled it. Uses much less space.
-Fixed a glitch in barrows, tunnel brother would switch sometimes (during same barrows looting).
-Started mining, very basic and poorly done, currently.

[b][u]March 21, 2009[/b]
[i]-Fixed disconnections after 3-5 minutes(Idk what caused tbh rofl).
-Finished barrows. You may talk to someone in Edgeville to teleport there.
-Fixed some monster drops and respawns.[/i]

[b][u]March 17, 2009[/b]
[I]-Fixed magic, it now gives HP xp as well as magic.
-Alching now can use lava staff instead of fire runes.
-Added herblore shop w/ basic herblore herbs.
-Fixed crafting xp, not its not extremely fast.
-Fixed dragonhide requirements, tops need defense and ranged.
-Fixed some shops up, made them more logical.
-Cleaned up commands a bit.
-Added ::premium name and ::regular name for easier editting.
-Fixed some more weapon timers.
-Fixed some chat drawing in the client.[/I]

[b][u]March 16, 2009[/b]
[I]-Added an armour shop up to steel for easier training.
-Fixed a major bug where you&#39;d log in and DC without my client.
-Added 100% premium items. You need premium membership to use them.
-Added 100% premium rank required to use widescreen client.
-Fixed some weapon bugs and timers.
-Released BETA client 2.0[url=http://www.mediafire.com/?qz43tumn1iw][Download Here][/url].[/I]

[b][U]March 11, 2009[/b]
[I]-Worked on clan chat again, tried to get join button working. Failed.
-Cleaned up the process a bit.
-Worked on premium items &amp; benefits.
-Worked on WideScreen[url=http://i42.tinypic.com/209j01u.jpg][liNK][/url]
-Cleaned up some code, made it neater and smaller.[/I]

[b][u]March 5-10, 2009[/b]
[i]-Updates to clan chat have been made. More information on the update blog.
-Clan chat interface almost complete 100%.
-Fixed some monster drops, they were random items.[/i]

[b][u]February 11-20, 2009[/b] - This is one giant update list. Pictures will come later.
[i]-Fixed major lag issues with client on first log-in.
-Added HP orb w/ filling, depleting, and colored text.
-Added Prayer orb w/ filling, depleting, and colored text.
-Add some small things like right-clicking to tabs.
-New equipment interface w/ 100% show equipment interface[URL=http://i42.tinypic.com/2rxtp9e.jpg][liNK][/URL].
-New scrollbars added to every interface.
-Log-in scroll added.
-Reduced size of client.java, model.java, itemdef.java, rsinterface.java, rsapplet.java, and several more files. Dramatically affecting total client size.
-Cooking added, basic with auto-cooking once you start to cook.
-100% dragon dagger special added; hits twice, perfect delays.
-Started smithing bars on anvils.
-Beginning skill guides, need correct interfaces w/ sendFrames/Quests.
-Began working on other skills; e.g. smithing, agility, fletching.
-More to come.[/i]

[b][u]February 8, 2009[/b]
[i]-Dragon claws model and rotations almost perfect.
-Dragon claws pieces added[URL=http://i41.tinypic.com/20u8pab.jpg][liNK][/URL]. There are 2 pieces, left and right, combine them with claw handles to make dragon claws.
-Fixed some bugs with dueling.
-Started to work more on new trade screen.[/i]

[b][u]February 7, 2009[/b]
[i]-Started to complete client.
-Added side-icons to client[icons on tabs].
-Replaced old borders with new ones[like ones around chatbox].
-Loaded new trade interface[not working fully yet].
-Added dragon boots, dragon claws, armadyl godsword.
-Beginning reconstruction of the model class. It will soon load models completely differently and above 22000+.
-Began redoing log-in screen.[/i]

[b][u]February 6, 2009[/b] - BIG update day, several new pictures!
[i]-Fixed up some glitches with NPC dialogue.
-Perfected teleporting with graphics and animations.
-Working wilderness levels with level difference added.
-PvP 1-versus-1 added, target in combat.
-First beta test was held with me, Michael, Hell Mage, Sam, and Lucky Dice.
-Completed destroy item interface.
-Added several items to destroy item interface list.
-Worked on client, near completeion[pictures at bottom].
-Added dragon platebody and shards to client.
-Added full 3 piece smithing for dragon platebody[URL=http://i41.tinypic.com/2mzieki.jpg][liNK][/URL].
-Several bits of code cleaned up.[/i]

[b][u]February 5, 2009[/b]
[i]-Worked on herblore, added level requirements with potion mixing.
-Worked on woodcutting, animations and level requirements added.
-Worked on trading without duping glitches or scamming.
-Perfect trading with real gp conversion(e.g. 2147M coins(2,147,000,000 coins))
-Finished Jad caves, 8 waves, all NPC&#39;s have proper animations and graphics. Defeating Jad gives you a fire cape. Prayer draining in cave is accelerated like RuneScape.[/i]

[b][u]February 4, 2009[/b]
[i]-Started update thread and update log.
-Started working on herblore, will be perfect with 2x RuneScape&#39;s experience.
-Started woodcutting, same as herblore.
-Finished anti-SYI, and anti-multi-login, 1 connection per IP.[/i]


[b][u]Bug Update Log[/u][/b]

[u][b]Initial Bugs[Before/During][/b][/u]
[i]-Random Jad attack on log-in, causing death.
-Disconnections when attacking with certain weapons[specifically bows].
-Very low hits during PvP.
-Random graphics appearing in mid air.
-Animations of weapons glitching or not working.
-Disconnection when clicking too fast during PvP.
-Hitting 4x normal speed upon re-login after disconnection.[/i]

[u][b]Bugs Fixed[During/After BETA][/b][/u]
[i]-Random Jad attack on log-in[[i][b]Fixed 2/27[/b][/i]]. I made it so jad can only attack if you are in the fight caves. Don&#39;t ask why it wasn&#39;t set to this in the beginning. All I had to do was add a couple &quot;&amp;&amp; isInFightCaves()&quot; to a couple things being called in the process().
-Very low hits during PvP[[i][b]Fixed 2/27[/b][/i]]. The hits weren&#39;t high enough for a PvP battle, fixed easily, now hits are random and not always 0&#39;s.
-Hitting 4x normal speed upon re-login[[i][b]Fixed 2/27[/b][/i]]. This was because you would disconnect and the server wouldn&#39;t read animations for your weapon correctly for some strange reason. Problem solved.
-Disconnections when attacking with a bow and no arrows.[b][Fixed 2/28/09][/b][/I]

I am looking into the other glitches, and will try to fix them ASAP. So far the main glitches and bugs have been fixed, such as Jad attacking upon log-in.

Now, I would like to ask you all of something. If you play the BETA and encounter any bugs at all, please post them here with a detailed description of what the bug is, so I can look into fixing it.

[center]__________________[/center]


[u][b][size=3]Pictures[/size][/b][/u]
[SIZE=1]NOTE: Some will be posted as URL&#39;s because of resolution. Also, older pictures will be put into links instead of images.[/SIZE]


[u][B]Bigger pictures[/B][/u]

[URL=http://i42.tinypic.com/2rxtp9e.jpg][i]New show-equipment-stats interface[/i][/URL]

[i][URL=http://i213.photobucket.com/albums/cc167/Galkon/trading1.png]Perfect trading, real RS money colors and k-to-mill gp conversion[CLICK][/URL][/i]

[i][URL=http://i41.tinypic.com/2mzieki.jpg]Perfect dragon platebody with pieces, real 3 piece smithing![CLICK][/URL][/i]

[i][url=http://i40.tinypic.com/drcldt.jpg]New borders[/url][/i]


[u][B]Older images[/B][/u]
[URL=http://img7.imageshack.us/img7/9682/herblore1cw2.png][i]Herblore, mixing without requirements[/i][/URL]

[URL=http://img11.imageshack.us/img11/9433/herblore2po5.png][i]Herblore, mixing with requirements[/i][/URL]

[URL=http://img12.imageshack.us/img12/875/wcing1ll0.png][i]Woodcutting, cutting down a yew tree[/i][/URL]

[URL=http://img5.imageshack.us/img5/1037/antimultilogud5.png][i]Anti-SYI/Anti-Multi-Login, one connection per IP[/i][/URL]

[URL=http://i44.tinypic.com/r7r5nl.jpg][i]Jad, mage attack, prayer protects[/i](more Jad pics to come)[/URL]

[URL=http://i41.tinypic.com/331zo00.jpg][i]Destroy item interface[/i][/URL]

[URL=http://i44.tinypic.com/2rosvmx.jpg][i]Target already in combat[/i][/URL]

[URL=http://i40.tinypic.com/okr7t4.jpg][i]Perfect teleporting[/i][/URL]

[URL=http://i42.tinypic.com/2rxtp9e.jpg][i]New show-equipment-stats interface[/i][/URL]

[url=http://i41.tinypic.com/20u8pab.jpg][i]Dragon claws &amp; pieces[/i][/url]

[url=http://i41.tinypic.com/20u8pab.jpg][i]Dragon claws &amp; pieces[/i][/url]

[url=http://i42.tinypic.com/35lu2vs.jpg][i]Dragon claws &amp; pieces[/i][/url]

[url=http://i42.tinypic.com/dct0u8.jpg][i]Clan Chat 1[/i][/url]

[url=http://i40.tinypic.com/nd270m.jpg][i]Clan Chat 2[/i][/url]

[url=http://i41.tinypic.com/ra1dus.jpg][i]Clan Chat beginning - Credits to Ben/Gnarly for the packets and all that good stuff.[/i][/url]

[url=http://i41.tinypic.com/k486dt.jpg][i]BETA Picture[/i][/url]

[url=http://i39.tinypic.com/2j5its.jpg][i]Perfected Clan Chat[/i][/url]

[url=http://i40.tinypic.com/iyfur6.jpg][i]Clan Chat Interface &amp; Tab[/i][/url]

[url=http://i44.tinypic.com/rr767c.jpg][i]WideScreen Client 1[/i][/url]

[url=http://i42.tinypic.com/209j01u.jpg][I]WideScreen Background[not complete][/I][/url]

[b]Barrows Images[/b]
http://i44.tinypic.com/2rqdllf.jpg
http://i41.tinypic.com/1o84gn.jpg
http://i40.tinypic.com/29vxaqa.jpg
http://i42.tinypic.com/311o115.jpg
http://i39.tinypic.com/14o84kz.jpg
http://i44.tinypic.com/2eautja.jpg
http://i39.tinypic.com/oavuj9.jpg
http://i40.tinypic.com/2yns4lk.jpg
http://i43.tinypic.com/2wm291i.jpg
http://i43.tinypic.com/2vnhqhy.jpg
http://i39.tinypic.com/a3nint.jpg


[b][U]Newest Images[/U][/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 05:44:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Berky-Scape Berky-Scape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/berky-scape">@Berky-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>it looks a very stabile server+ client u gonna release it or not?<br>
Sorry but had no time to read the whole bunch of text :P.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 05:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is INSANE. Great job galkon.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/34</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 05:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zh1 Zh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zh1">@Zh1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Porker? Lol. Pimp3d answer my PMS ON MSN! &gt;.&lt;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/33</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2009 03:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@P_I_M_P_3_D_Tut `Lewk_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/p_i_m_p_3_d_tut">@P_I_M_P_3_D_Tut</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Galkon, You are a porker.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/32</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2009 03:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zh1 Zh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zh1">@Zh1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OMG! That’s very nice! good luck galkon!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/31</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2009 03:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Djayboi6 Dj_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/djayboi6">@Djayboi6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nice job galkon</p>
<p>you should fix something at barrows,in rs when you go down into a tomb you the map is all black and you cant see where you are,you should try and add that</p>
<p>Edit:the minimap sorry didnt point that out</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 22:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moh moh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moh">@moh</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice already saw this on r-server still gl with it! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
Ps. its still amazing how you toke the hd models from 500+? What for suite you used? I only got for 317 servers xd</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/29</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 14:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_ExiledScape `ExiledScape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_exiledscape">@_ExiledScape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/28</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 11:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GalkonsPride GalkonsPride]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/galkonspride">@GalkonsPride</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“benscape, post:25, topic:269521”]I have always respected your work, as you break away from the crowd and do something different. I am liking the look of it so far thought looks neat and tidy, good luck.</p>
<p>BTW: I thought you gave up coding for a while due to real life shit, lol.[/quote]</p>
<p>Took a break.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 07:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cocoa cocoa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cocoa">@cocoa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="23" data-topic="269521">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/galkonspride/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> GalkonsPride:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Finished HD model loading today. Works perfectly, with the exception of gloves and boots. But I can easily fix them.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I was there.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 18:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@benscape benscape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/benscape">@benscape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have always respected your work, as you break away from the crowd and do something different. I am liking the look of it so far thought looks neat and tidy, good luck.</p>
<p>BTW: I thought you gave up coding for a while due to real life shit, lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 15:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krazy_karl krazy karl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krazy_karl">@krazy_karl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice Galkon <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>I swear your awesome at coding <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>Do you think you will ever release?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 13:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GalkonsPride GalkonsPride]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/galkonspride">@GalkonsPride</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Finished HD model loading today. Works perfectly, with the exception of gloves and boots. But I can easily fix them.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 02:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@krazy_karl krazy karl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krazy_karl">@krazy_karl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Awesome mate <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>You should release once finished and see how many downloads you get <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 17:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kihomura Kihomura]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kihomura">@kihomura</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Holy shit Galkon. You’re insane.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/21</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 15:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cmcmvj cmcmvj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cmcmvj">@cmcmvj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-s">beta always off <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></span></p>
<p>nvm:p</p>
<p>btw the equipment interface dont works</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 11:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Khan_ZooZoo Khan_ZooZoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/khan_zoozoo">@Khan_ZooZoo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I downloaded client, its nice <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 16:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Fat Cookies, post:17, topic:269521”]What are you basing this from?<br>
I would advise showing proof that you can advertise all of this.</p>
<p>It will be interesting to see what approach you take to a server.[/quote]<br>
Download his beta client and see.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 18:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What are you basing this from?<br>
I would advise showing proof that you can advertise all of this.</p>
<p>It will be interesting to see what approach you take to a server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 17:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BlazezFire BlazezFire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blazezfire">@BlazezFire</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck Galkon looks awesome so far.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 17:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Gh0st_Jr Gh0st Jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gh0st_jr">@Gh0st_Jr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wuvz it, but then again you knew that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 17:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cmcmvj cmcmvj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cmcmvj">@cmcmvj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>!!@@## &lt;— this says enough lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 19:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moh moh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moh">@moh</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Omg this is like DAMN!your going to release this when u done?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/13</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 19:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I tried it. Looks pretty good so far.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 19:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RuneLimited</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Beast43 Beast43]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/beast43">@Beast43</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Meh 2 pl0xerZ?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 19:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-269521-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/runelimited/269521.rss">RuneLimited</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
