<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SAS: Zombie Assault 3 - Web</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sas-zombie-assault-3-web/522873</link>
    <description>This game has more than one version, I know they have one out for the android, and the iOS. They also have different versions for Ninjakiwi (the site that made the game), and one for kongregate. The one on kongregate receives more attention and more updates.

Recently, in the past ~2 updates they really screwed up the games connection to the servers. They also don&#39;t know how to put a limit on zombies, and there are now more bugs than ever. If you play Purge (which is a game mode where you have to kill the nests to stop zombies from spawning) or Apocalypse (non-stop zombies till you die) after a while the game will start to lag, and will eventually break, because there&#39;s like 800+ zombies on the map. Which is extremely irritating, because that defeats the point of Apocalypse.

However, the game itself is fun (as long as you don&#39;t buy crap with real money). There&#39;s 50 ranks to go through (you can buy straight to rank 40 for like 10-20 bucks), and most unlock something, whether it be a new gun, skill, or enhancement (you can unlock premium options, but you still have to buy them.). At level 40, your health supposedly doubles (I haven&#39;t been able to confirm this), and I&#39;ve seen loads of people with a different character than the normal one.

There&#39;s 3 game modes:
Onslaught: Wave based zombie killing (solo is like 5+ rounds, I believe this is rank based).
Apocalypse: Non-stop zombie killing till you die [Or the game breaks :S]
Purge: Nest based zombie killing, usually there&#39;s 4-5 waves of nests.

The game itself is good, ninjakiwi just needs to fix a couple bugs.

Overall: 7/10.

Oh, I play on Kongregate if anyone wants to hook up on there and give it a go</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 22:58:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sas-zombie-assault-3-web/522873.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SAS: Zombie Assault 3 - Web</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sk8rdude461 sk8rdude461]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sk8rdude461">@sk8rdude461</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This game has more than one version, I know they have one out for the android, and the iOS. They also have different versions for Ninjakiwi (the site that made the game), and one for kongregate. The one on kongregate receives more attention and more updates.</p>
<p>Recently, in the past ~2 updates they really screwed up the games connection to the servers. They also don’t know how to put a limit on zombies, and there are now more bugs than ever. If you play Purge (which is a game mode where you have to kill the nests to stop zombies from spawning) or Apocalypse (non-stop zombies till you die) after a while the game will start to lag, and will eventually break, because there’s like 800+ zombies on the map. Which is extremely irritating, because that defeats the point of Apocalypse.</p>
<p>However, the game itself is fun (as long as you don’t buy crap with real money). There’s 50 ranks to go through (you can buy straight to rank 40 for like 10-20 bucks), and most unlock something, whether it be a new gun, skill, or enhancement (you can unlock premium options, but you still have to buy them.). At level 40, your health supposedly doubles (I haven’t been able to confirm this), and I’ve seen loads of people with a different character than the normal one.</p>
<p>There’s 3 game modes:<br>
Onslaught: Wave based zombie killing (solo is like 5+ rounds, I believe this is rank based).<br>
Apocalypse: Non-stop zombie killing till you die [Or the game breaks :S]<br>
Purge: Nest based zombie killing, usually there’s 4-5 waves of nests.</p>
<p>The game itself is good, ninjakiwi just needs to fix a couple bugs.</p>
<p>Overall: 7/10.</p>
<p>Oh, I play on Kongregate if anyone wants to hook up on there and give it a go</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sas-zombie-assault-3-web/522873/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sas-zombie-assault-3-web/522873/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 22:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-522873-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sas-zombie-assault-3-web/522873.rss">SAS: Zombie Assault 3 - Web</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
