<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[Tut]Threads[Tut]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344</link>
    <description>Threads have been around for some time, but few programmers have actually worked with them. There is even some debate over whether or not the average programmer can use threads effectively. In Java, working with threads can be easy and productive. In fact, threads provide the only way to effectively handle a number of tasks. So it&#39;s important that you become familiar with threads early in your exploration of Java.

Threads are integral to the way Java works. We&#39;ve already seen that an applet&#39;s paint() method isn&#39;t called by the applet itself, but by another thread within the interpreter. At any given time, there may be many such background threads, performing activities in parallel with your application. In fact, it&#39;s easy to get a half dozen or more threads running in an applet without even trying, simply by requesting images, updating the screen, playing audio, and so on. But these things happen behind the scenes; you don&#39;t normally have to worry about them. In this chapter, we&#39;ll talk about writing applications that create and use their own threads explicitly.

[b]Introducing Threads[/b]

Conceptually, a thread is a flow of control within a program. A thread is similar to the more familiar notion of a process, except that multiple threads within the same application share much of the same state--in particular, they run in the same address space. It&#39;s not unlike a golf course, which can be used by many players at the same time. Sharing the same address space means that threads share instance variables, but not local variables, just like players share the golf course, but not personal things like clubs and balls.

Multiple threads in an application have the same problems as the players sharing a golf course: in a word, synchronization. Just as you can&#39;t have two sets of players blindly playing the same green at the same time, you can&#39;t have several threads trying to access the same variables without some kind of coordination. Someone is bound to get hurt. A thread can reserve the right to use an object until it&#39;s finished with its task, just as a golf party gets exclusive rights to the green until it&#39;s done. And a thread that is more important can raise its priority, asserting its right to play through.

The devil is in the details, or course, and those details have historically made threads difficult to use. Java makes creating, controlling, and coordinating threads simple. When creating a new thread is the best way to accomplish some task, it should be as easy as adding a new component to your application.

It is common to stumble over threads when you first look at them, because creating a thread exercises many of your new Java skills all at once. You can avoid confusion by remembering there are always two players involved in running a thread: a Java language object that represents the thread itself and an arbitrary target object that contains the method the thread is to execute. Later, you will see that it is possible to play some sleight of hand and combine these two roles, but that special case just changes the packaging, not the relationship.

[b]The Thread Class and the Runnable Interface[/b]

A new thread is born when we create an instance of the java.lang.Thread class. The Thread object represents a real thread in the Java interpreter and serves as a handle for controlling and synchronizing its execution. With it, we can start the thread, stop the thread, or suspend it temporarily. The constructor for the Thread class accepts information about where the thread should begin its execution. Conceptually, we would like to simply tell it what method to run, but since there are no pointers to methods in Java, we can&#39;t specify one directly. Instead, we have to take a short detour and use the Runnable interface to create an object that contains a &quot;runnable&quot; method.

An object that wants to serve as the target of a Thread can declare that it has an appropriate executable method by implementing the java.lang.Runnable interface. Runnable defines a single, general-purpose method:
[code]public interface Runnable { 
  abstract public void run(); 
} [/code]
Every thread begins its life by executing a [i]run()[/i] method in a particular object. run() is a rather mundane method that can hold an arbitrary body of code. It is public, takes no arguments, has no return value, and is not allowed to throw any exceptions.

Any class can contain an appropriate run() method, simply by declaring that it implements the Runnable interface. An instance of this class is then a runnable object that can serve as the target of a new Thread. In this way, we can effectively run a method in any object we want.

[b]Creating and starting threads[/b]

A newly born Thread remains idle until we give it a figurative slap on the bottom by calling its start() method. The thread then wakes up and proceeds to execute the run() method of its target object. start() can be called only once in the lifetime of a Thread. Once a thread starts, it continues running until the target object&#39;s run() method completes, or we call the thread&#39;s stop() method to kill the thread permanently. A little later, we will look at some other methods you can use to control the thread&#39;s progress while it is running.

Now let&#39;s look at an example. The following class, Animation, implements a run() method to drive its drawing loop:
[code]class Animation implements Runnable { 
   ... 
   public void run() { 
 
       while ( true ) { 
           // Draw Frames 
           ... 
           repaint(); 
       } 
   } 
} [/code]
To use it, we create a Thread object with an instance of Animation as its target object, and invoke its start() method. We can perform these steps explicitly, as in the following:
[code]Animation happy = new Animation(&quot;Mr. Happy&quot;); 
Thread myThread = new Thread( happy ); 
myThread.start(); 
... [/code]
Here we have created an instance of our Animation class and passed it as the argument to the constructor for myThread. When we call the start() method, myThread begins to execute Animation&#39;s run() method. Let the show begin!
[code]class Animation implements Runnable { 
 
    Thread myThread; 
 
    Animation (String name) { 
        myThread = new Thread( this ); 
        myThread.start(); 
    }  
    ... [/code]
In this case, the argument we pass to the Thread constructor is [i]this[/i], the current object instance. We keep the Thread reference in the instance variable myThread, in case we want to stop the show, or exercise some other kind of control.

[b]A natural born thread[/b]

The Runnable interface lets us make an arbitrary object the target of a thread, as we did above. This is the most important, general usage of the Thread class. In most situations where you need to use threads, you&#39;ll create a class that implements the Runnable interface. I&#39;d be remiss, however, if I didn&#39;t show you the other technique for creating a thread. Another design option is to make our target class a subclass of a type that is already runnable. The Thread class itself implements the Runnable interface; it has its own run() method we can override to make it do something useful:
[code]class Animation extends Thread { 
    ... 
         
    public void run() { 
        while (true ) { 
            // Draw Frames 
            ... 
            repaint(); 
        } 
    } 
} [/code]
The skeleton of our Animation class above looks much the same as before, except that our class is now a kind of Thread. To go along with this scheme, the default (empty) constructor of the Thread class makes itself the default target. That is, by default, the Thread executes its own run() method when we call the start() method. Note that our subclass must override the run() method in the Thread class because Thread simply defines an empty run() method.

Now we create an instance of Animation and call its start() method:
[code]Animation bouncy = new Animation(&quot;Bouncy&quot;); 
bouncy.start(); [/code]
Alternatively, we can have the Animation object start itself when it is created, as before:
[code]class Animation extends Thread { 
 
    Animation (String name) { 
        start(); 
    } 
    ... [/code]
Here our Animation object just calls its own start() method when it is created.

Subclassing Thread probably seems like a convenient way to bundle a Thread and its target run() method. However, as always, you should let good object-oriented design dictate how you structure your classes. In most cases, a specific run() method is probably closely related to the functionality of a particular class in your application, so you should implement run() in that class. This technique has the added advantage of allowing run() to access any private variables and methods it might need in the class.

If you subclass Thread to implement a thread, you are saying you need a new type of object that is a kind of Thread. While there is something unnaturally satisfying about making an object primarily concerned with performing a single task (like animation), the actual situations where you&#39;ll want to create a subclass of Thread should be rather rare. If you find you&#39;re subclassing Thread left and right, you may want to examine whether you are falling into the design trap of making objects that are simply glorified functions.

[b]Controlling Threads[/b]

We have seen the start() method used to bring a newly created Thread to life. Three other methods let us control a Thread&#39;s execution: stop(), suspend(), and resume(). None of these methods take any arguments; they all operate on the current thread object. The stop() method complements start(); it destroys the thread. start() and stop() can be called only once in the life of a Thread. By contrast, the suspend() and resume() methods can be used to arbitrarily pause and then restart the execution of a Thread.

Often, for simple tasks, it is easy enough to throw away a thread when we want to stop it and simply create a new one when want to proceed again. suspend() and resume() can be used in situations where the Thread&#39;s setup is very expensive. For example, if creating the thread involves opening a socket and setting up some elaborate communication, it probably makes more sense to use suspend() and resume() with this thread.

Another common need is to put a thread to sleep for some period of time. Thread.sleep() is a static method of the Thread class that causes the currently executing thread to delay for a specified number of milliseconds:
[code]
try { 
    Thread.sleep ( 1000 ); 
}  
catch ( InterruptedException e ) { 
} [/code]
[i]Thread.sleep()[/i] throws an InterruptedException if it is interrupted by another Thread. When a thread is asleep, or otherwise blocked on input of some kind, it doesn&#39;t consume CPU time or compete with other threads for processing.

[b]A Thread&#39;s Life[/b]

A Thread continues to execute until one of the following things happens:

[list]
[li]It returns from its target run() method
[/li][li]It&#39;s interrupted by an uncaught exception

[ul][li]Its stop() method is called[/ul]

So what happens if the run() method for a thread never terminates, and the application that started the thread never calls its stop() method? The answer is that the thread lives on, even after the application that created it has finished. This means we have to be aware of how our threads eventually terminate, or an application can end up leaving orphaned threads that unnecessarily consume resources.

In many cases, what we really want is to create background threads that do simple, periodic tasks in an application. The setDaemon() method can be used to mark a Thread as a daemon thread that should be killed and discarded when no other application threads remain. Normally, the Java interpreter continues to run until all threads have completed. But when daemon threads are the only threads still alive, the interpreter will exit.
Here&#39;s a devilish example of using daemon threads:
[code]
class Devil extends Thread { 
 
    Devil() { 
        setDaemon( true ); 
        start(); 
    } 
         
    public void run() { 
        // Perform evil tasks 
        ... 
    } 
} [/code]
In the above example, the Devil thread sets its daemon status when it is created. If any Devil threads remain when our application is otherwise complete, Java kills them for us. We don&#39;t have to worry about cleaning them up.

Daemon threads are primarily useful in standalone Java applications and in the implementation of the Java system itself, but not in applets. Since an applet runs inside of another Java application, any daemon threads it creates will continue to live until the controlling application exits--probably not the desired effect...
[center][img]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnwarn.gif[/img] Next time you post a tutorial, make it yourself.[/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 11:40:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[Tut]Threads[Tut]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sppt sppt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sppt">@sppt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>To make matters worse, it’s a complete <a href="http://hell.org.ua/Docs/oreilly/java/exp/ch06_01.htm" data-bbcode="true">rip</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 11:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288344-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344.rss">[Tut]Threads[Tut]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Tut]Threads[Tut]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Java_Duke Java Duke]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/java_duke">@Java_Duke</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Cain_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Few programmers have actually worked with them? ARE YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree…<br>
Long tutorial tho, you wasted your time…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 10:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288344-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344.rss">[Tut]Threads[Tut]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Tut]Threads[Tut]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@atrox atrox_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/atrox">@atrox</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>please, stop.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 09:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288344-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344.rss">[Tut]Threads[Tut]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[Tut]Threads[Tut]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MoparUnited MoparUnited]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparunited">@MoparUnited</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Threads have been around for some time, but few programmers have actually worked with them. There is even some debate over whether or not the average programmer can use threads effectively. In Java, working with threads can be easy and productive. In fact, threads provide the only way to effectively handle a number of tasks. So it’s important that you become familiar with threads early in your exploration of Java.</p>
<p>Threads are integral to the way Java works. We’ve already seen that an applet’s paint() method isn’t called by the applet itself, but by another thread within the interpreter. At any given time, there may be many such background threads, performing activities in parallel with your application. In fact, it’s easy to get a half dozen or more threads running in an applet without even trying, simply by requesting images, updating the screen, playing audio, and so on. But these things happen behind the scenes; you don’t normally have to worry about them. In this chapter, we’ll talk about writing applications that create and use their own threads explicitly.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Introducing Threads</span></p>
<p>Conceptually, a thread is a flow of control within a program. A thread is similar to the more familiar notion of a process, except that multiple threads within the same application share much of the same state–in particular, they run in the same address space. It’s not unlike a golf course, which can be used by many players at the same time. Sharing the same address space means that threads share instance variables, but not local variables, just like players share the golf course, but not personal things like clubs and balls.</p>
<p>Multiple threads in an application have the same problems as the players sharing a golf course: in a word, synchronization. Just as you can’t have two sets of players blindly playing the same green at the same time, you can’t have several threads trying to access the same variables without some kind of coordination. Someone is bound to get hurt. A thread can reserve the right to use an object until it’s finished with its task, just as a golf party gets exclusive rights to the green until it’s done. And a thread that is more important can raise its priority, asserting its right to play through.</p>
<p>The devil is in the details, or course, and those details have historically made threads difficult to use. Java makes creating, controlling, and coordinating threads simple. When creating a new thread is the best way to accomplish some task, it should be as easy as adding a new component to your application.</p>
<p>It is common to stumble over threads when you first look at them, because creating a thread exercises many of your new Java skills all at once. You can avoid confusion by remembering there are always two players involved in running a thread: a Java language object that represents the thread itself and an arbitrary target object that contains the method the thread is to execute. Later, you will see that it is possible to play some sleight of hand and combine these two roles, but that special case just changes the packaging, not the relationship.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">The Thread Class and the Runnable Interface</span></p>
<p>A new thread is born when we create an instance of the java.lang.Thread class. The Thread object represents a real thread in the Java interpreter and serves as a handle for controlling and synchronizing its execution. With it, we can start the thread, stop the thread, or suspend it temporarily. The constructor for the Thread class accepts information about where the thread should begin its execution. Conceptually, we would like to simply tell it what method to run, but since there are no pointers to methods in Java, we can’t specify one directly. Instead, we have to take a short detour and use the Runnable interface to create an object that contains a “runnable” method.</p>
<p>An object that wants to serve as the target of a Thread can declare that it has an appropriate executable method by implementing the java.lang.Runnable interface. Runnable defines a single, general-purpose method:</p>
<p><code>public interface Runnable { 
  abstract public void run(); 
} </code><br>
Every thread begins its life by executing a <span class="bbcode-i">run()</span> method in a particular object. run() is a rather mundane method that can hold an arbitrary body of code. It is public, takes no arguments, has no return value, and is not allowed to throw any exceptions.</p>
<p>Any class can contain an appropriate run() method, simply by declaring that it implements the Runnable interface. An instance of this class is then a runnable object that can serve as the target of a new Thread. In this way, we can effectively run a method in any object we want.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Creating and starting threads</span></p>
<p>A newly born Thread remains idle until we give it a figurative slap on the bottom by calling its start() method. The thread then wakes up and proceeds to execute the run() method of its target object. start() can be called only once in the lifetime of a Thread. Once a thread starts, it continues running until the target object’s run() method completes, or we call the thread’s stop() method to kill the thread permanently. A little later, we will look at some other methods you can use to control the thread’s progress while it is running.</p>
<p>Now let’s look at an example. The following class, Animation, implements a run() method to drive its drawing loop:</p>
<p>[code]class Animation implements Runnable {<br>
…<br>
public void run() {</p>
<pre><code>   while ( true ) { 
       // Draw Frames 
       ... 
       repaint(); 
   } 
</code></pre>
<p>}<br>
} [/code]<br>
To use it, we create a Thread object with an instance of Animation as its target object, and invoke its start() method. We can perform these steps explicitly, as in the following:</p>
<p><code>Animation happy = new Animation("Mr. Happy"); 
Thread myThread = new Thread( happy ); 
myThread.start(); 
... </code><br>
Here we have created an instance of our Animation class and passed it as the argument to the constructor for myThread. When we call the start() method, myThread begins to execute Animation’s run() method. Let the show begin!</p>
<p>[code]class Animation implements Runnable {</p>
<pre><code>Thread myThread; 

Animation (String name) { 
    myThread = new Thread( this ); 
    myThread.start(); 
}  
... [/code]
</code></pre>
<p>In this case, the argument we pass to the Thread constructor is <span class="bbcode-i">this</span>, the current object instance. We keep the Thread reference in the instance variable myThread, in case we want to stop the show, or exercise some other kind of control.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">A natural born thread</span></p>
<p>The Runnable interface lets us make an arbitrary object the target of a thread, as we did above. This is the most important, general usage of the Thread class. In most situations where you need to use threads, you’ll create a class that implements the Runnable interface. I’d be remiss, however, if I didn’t show you the other technique for creating a thread. Another design option is to make our target class a subclass of a type that is already runnable. The Thread class itself implements the Runnable interface; it has its own run() method we can override to make it do something useful:</p>
<p>[code]class Animation extends Thread {<br>
…</p>
<pre><code>public void run() { 
    while (true ) { 
        // Draw Frames 
        ... 
        repaint(); 
    } 
} 
</code></pre>
<p>} [/code]<br>
The skeleton of our Animation class above looks much the same as before, except that our class is now a kind of Thread. To go along with this scheme, the default (empty) constructor of the Thread class makes itself the default target. That is, by default, the Thread executes its own run() method when we call the start() method. Note that our subclass must override the run() method in the Thread class because Thread simply defines an empty run() method.</p>
<p>Now we create an instance of Animation and call its start() method:</p>
<p><code>Animation bouncy = new Animation("Bouncy"); 
bouncy.start(); </code><br>
Alternatively, we can have the Animation object start itself when it is created, as before:</p>
<p>[code]class Animation extends Thread {</p>
<pre><code>Animation (String name) { 
    start(); 
} 
... [/code]
</code></pre>
<p>Here our Animation object just calls its own start() method when it is created.</p>
<p>Subclassing Thread probably seems like a convenient way to bundle a Thread and its target run() method. However, as always, you should let good object-oriented design dictate how you structure your classes. In most cases, a specific run() method is probably closely related to the functionality of a particular class in your application, so you should implement run() in that class. This technique has the added advantage of allowing run() to access any private variables and methods it might need in the class.</p>
<p>If you subclass Thread to implement a thread, you are saying you need a new type of object that is a kind of Thread. While there is something unnaturally satisfying about making an object primarily concerned with performing a single task (like animation), the actual situations where you’ll want to create a subclass of Thread should be rather rare. If you find you’re subclassing Thread left and right, you may want to examine whether you are falling into the design trap of making objects that are simply glorified functions.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Controlling Threads</span></p>
<p>We have seen the start() method used to bring a newly created Thread to life. Three other methods let us control a Thread’s execution: stop(), suspend(), and resume(). None of these methods take any arguments; they all operate on the current thread object. The stop() method complements start(); it destroys the thread. start() and stop() can be called only once in the life of a Thread. By contrast, the suspend() and resume() methods can be used to arbitrarily pause and then restart the execution of a Thread.</p>
<p>Often, for simple tasks, it is easy enough to throw away a thread when we want to stop it and simply create a new one when want to proceed again. suspend() and resume() can be used in situations where the Thread’s setup is very expensive. For example, if creating the thread involves opening a socket and setting up some elaborate communication, it probably makes more sense to use suspend() and resume() with this thread.</p>
<p>Another common need is to put a thread to sleep for some period of time. Thread.sleep() is a static method of the Thread class that causes the currently executing thread to delay for a specified number of milliseconds:</p>
<p><code>
try { 
    Thread.sleep ( 1000 ); 
}  
catch ( InterruptedException e ) { 
} </code><br>
<span class="bbcode-i">Thread.sleep()</span> throws an InterruptedException if it is interrupted by another Thread. When a thread is asleep, or otherwise blocked on input of some kind, it doesn’t consume CPU time or compete with other threads for processing.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">A Thread’s Life</span></p>
<p>A Thread continues to execute until one of the following things happens:</p>
<p>[list]<br>
[li]It returns from its target run() method<br>
[/li][li]It’s interrupted by an uncaught exception</p>
<p>[ul][li]Its stop() method is called[/ul]</p>
<p>So what happens if the run() method for a thread never terminates, and the application that started the thread never calls its stop() method? The answer is that the thread lives on, even after the application that created it has finished. This means we have to be aware of how our threads eventually terminate, or an application can end up leaving orphaned threads that unnecessarily consume resources.</p>
<p>In many cases, what we really want is to create background threads that do simple, periodic tasks in an application. The setDaemon() method can be used to mark a Thread as a daemon thread that should be killed and discarded when no other application threads remain. Normally, the Java interpreter continues to run until all threads have completed. But when daemon threads are the only threads still alive, the interpreter will exit.<br>
Here’s a devilish example of using daemon threads:</p>
<p>[code]<br>
class Devil extends Thread {</p>
<pre><code>Devil() { 
    setDaemon( true ); 
    start(); 
} 
     
public void run() { 
    // Perform evil tasks 
    ... 
} 
</code></pre>
<p>} [/code]<br>
In the above example, the Devil thread sets its daemon status when it is created. If any Devil threads remain when our application is otherwise complete, Java kills them for us. We don’t have to worry about cleaning them up.</p>
<p>Daemon threads are primarily useful in standalone Java applications and in the implementation of the Java system itself, but not in applets. Since an applet runs inside of another Java application, any daemon threads it creates will continue to live until the controlling application exits–probably not the desired effect…<br>
[center]<img src="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/Themes/default/images/warnwarn.gif" alt width="" height=""> Next time you post a tutorial, make it yourself.[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 08:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-288344-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/tut-threads-tut/288344.rss">[Tut]Threads[Tut]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
