<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What is this referring to</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-is-this-referring-to/530802</link>
    <description>	public void setLook(int index, int look) {
		this.look[index] = look;
	}

This is a method in the Appearance class in XenoRune 530, however I don&#39;t know what index means. This method is used to set the look of the player.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 02:30:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-is-this-referring-to/530802.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What is this referring to</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ExtremeX-Scape Ryley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extremex-scape">@ExtremeX-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Docent, post:1, topic:530802”]public void setLook(int index, int look) {<br>
this.look[index] = look;<br>
}</p>
<p>This is a method in the Appearance class in XenoRune 530, however I don’t know what index means. This method is used to set the look of the player.[/quote]</p>
<p>“this” is referring to the field “look” that is within that class. The other “look” without the “this” modifier is the parameter. The index is the index within the array which you are setting.</p>
<p>For more information, refer to this post:</p>
<p>[quote=“AtomicInt_, post:8, topic:529813”][quote author=LunarParadise link=topic=648568.msg4361645#msg4361645 date=1378855311]<br>
Hey guys, I took your advice and started learning Java. I made some good improvements, but I have trouble with one thing. I have trouble defining variables.</p>
<p>Here is a very simple piece of code:</p>
<p><code>class variableTest{
public static void main (String[] args) {
int test = 0;
int this = 0;
}</code><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>First of all, Java class names are typed as UpperCamelCase, the first letter of each word should be capitalized.</p>
<p>[tt]int test = 0;[/tt]<br>
This variable is fine, you declared a mutable integer with the value of 0.</p>
<p>[tt]int this = 0;[/tt]<br>
This variable declaration will throw an error because the word “this” is a keyword in Java. I might as well tell you what the keyword does since I brought it up; “this” is a reference to <em>this</em> object, keep in mind every class in Java is an object, any hierarchy of classes will always lead back to the parent of every class, Object. You cannot see the extension when you create a class, but every class is extended by Object, anyway, “this” is a reference to this object, which is this class. Look at this code for example:</p>
<p>[code=java]<br>
public final class ThisKeyword {</p>
<pre><code>private final int x, y;

public ThisKeyword(int x, int y) {
    this.x = x;
    this.y = y;
}
</code></pre>
<p>}[/code]</p>
<p>Do you see how the parameters of the constructor [tt]public ThisKeyword[/tt] have the same exact name as the fields declared before it? Good. Well saying [tt]x = x;[/tt] and [tt]y = y[/tt] would not work, because you would be setting the value of the constructors parameters to themselves, that is why we add the “this” keyword in front of the first call. Make sense?</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Here is mine declaring ints:</p>
<p><code>class declaringTest {
public static void main (String[] args) {
aField = newint[10];
int [] aField = {1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10};
}</code></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Alright, everything is wrong with this code, so let’s start from the beginning;</p>
<p>First of all, in order to create an integer array, we need to add [tt]int[][/tt] before the declaration of the field name.</p>
<p>Now it will look like this<br>
[tt]int[] aField = newint[10];[/tt]</p>
<p>The next thing, keywords “new” and “int” need to be separated because they are two different wrappers.</p>
<p>Now our code will look like this:<br>
[tt]int[] aField = new int[10];[/tt]</p>
<p>There we go. What this does is it creates a new integer array with 9 indices, they are empty, they have no value, and a length of 10, you may ask why only 9 indices, I specified 10? You really get 10 total indices because arrays are 0 based, you start at 0 and work your way up.</p>
<p>0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9</p>
<p>If you were to put something in a index that is greater than 9 or less than 0 you will get an exception because the array does not have room for that index.</p>
<p>On to the next bit of code:<br>
[tt]int [] aField = {1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10};[/tt]</p>
<p>This code is correct, although it does not do the same thing as the first code does, this creates a new integer array, but the indices are not empty, the numbers within the braces are actually the values within the array.</p>
<p>So if you were to print [tt]aField[5][/tt] you would print the value in the fifth index of the array; that value would be 6 because remember, arrays are 0 based.[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-is-this-referring-to/530802/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-is-this-referring-to/530802/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 02:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530802-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-is-this-referring-to/530802.rss">What is this referring to</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What is this referring to</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Docent Limits]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/docent">@Docent</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <pre><code>public void setLook(int index, int look) {
	this.look[index] = look;
}
</code></pre>
<p>This is a method in the Appearance class in XenoRune 530, however I don’t know what index means. This method is used to set the look of the player.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-is-this-referring-to/530802/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-is-this-referring-to/530802/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 02:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-530802-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-is-this-referring-to/530802.rss">What is this referring to</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
