<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How do i portforward?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892</link>
    <description>[b][u][/u][/b]This is very important

How do i portforward My Server so others can get on i Have a tiscali broadband Box.. But i also have hamachi...

I Need Someone to help me do it..

My MSN Is: KraziConway@hotmail.co.uk

Otherwise Just PM me In This</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 00:57:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How do i portforward?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sparkz2k7 sparkz2k7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sparkz2k7">@sparkz2k7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That Website Hey If I Give u remote assistance to my comp can u do it for me?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 00:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-132892-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892.rss">How do i portforward?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do i portforward?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TeleNubby TeleNubby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/telenubby">@TeleNubby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">2. - Port-Forwarding your Router (EXPLAINED)</span></span></span><br>
Ahh… One of the trickiest part to many, and to some very easy. Well whoever you are, this will help you if you’re stuck or just dont know how to do it whatsoever. Alright, we have to start by knowing what you’re router is. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> We can do this one of two ways. And here they are:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">1)</span> <span class="bbcode-i">Ask your parents. They should know this. If they say you dont have a router, then go ahead and skip this part. If they say you so have a router, ask them what company made the router, and what model it is. They should be able to answer this. And also make sure you know where the router is, to double-check on what they have said yourself. If they do not know this, then we’ll have to go try the other way, which may not always work for everybody.</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">2)</span> [i]Ok. Click on Start, then click on Run, and in the run box type <code>cmd</code> This will take you to a black box which is used in creating a server a lot. It’s called the <span class="bbcode-b">Command Prompt</span>. Now, if you cant get to it that way, try Start, then All Programs (or Program Files), then Accessories, and then click on the program named <span class="bbcode-b">Command Prompt</span> Alright. Now that you’re here, right away when it opens up, type in <code>ipconfig</code> You’re Command Prompt should now look something like this:<br>
<img src="http://img178.imageshack.us/img178/5662/servertut3vc3.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
Now look under the <span class="bbcode-b">Ethernet adapter Wireless Network Connection</span> or something similar, and take a look at the <span class="bbcode-b">Default Gateway</span> line. Write this IP down (the one to the right of the Default Gateway text), or remember it. I reccomend writing it down if you’re new to this. Now minimize you’re Command Prompt, and in the Address/URL Bar at the top of your browser (where you type the website like <a href="http://www.site.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.site.com</a> or anything else), and type in that IP that we just talked about it. In my case, it would be <span class="bbcode-b">192.168.1.1</span>. You should see a Username and Password box, and if there is any other info on there it could be useful. For example mine looks like this:<br>
<img src="http://img132.imageshack.us/img132/6111/servertut4fd1.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
And it tells me the Model of my Router: <span class="bbcode-b">WRT54GL</span>, which I can then Google search it and find out what company makes it. If you cannot find anything like this, Google the Default Gateway IP that we looked at earlier. Some routers have like 192.168.2.1 and can then be identified. If not, I say look around in your house and try and find the router.</p>
<p>Ok. Next part of this step. It’s time to login to your router and Port-Forward. Once you have found your Company and Router, visit <a href="http://www.portforward.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.portforward.com</a> and click on the link that says <span class="bbcode-b">Port Forwarding</span> towards the top of the page. Now on the new page find the Company that made your Router or the Brand of it and then click on the name. You should now see a list of programs. Just click on the first one named <span class="bbcode-b">1st SMTP Server</span> and follow every step of it. The static IP Address box, in there type in the IP that was located to the right of the <span class="bbcode-b">IP Address. . . . . </span> line back in the Command Prompt (in IPCONFIG). Now instead of portforwarding the ports for that program (Port 25), portforward the port that your server is going to use. Most servers use the port 43594, so if you want to port-forward that, then go ahead. If the source you’re going to download soon doesn’t, we’ll change it so it does.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 00:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-132892-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892.rss">How do i portforward?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do i portforward?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sparkz2k7 sparkz2k7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sparkz2k7">@sparkz2k7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u"></span></span>This is very important</p>
<p>How do i portforward My Server so others can get on i Have a tiscali broadband Box… But i also have hamachi…</p>
<p>I Need Someone to help me do it…</p>
<p>My MSN Is: <a href="mailto:KraziConway@hotmail.co.uk">KraziConway@hotmail.co.uk</a></p>
<p>Otherwise Just PM me In This</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 00:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-132892-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-i-portforward/132892.rss">How do i portforward?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
