<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Prayer and Magic tab sprites</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/prayer-and-magic-tab-sprites/373618</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve got this issue with my client where the sprites for all prayers and spells (In both prayer books and all 3 spellbooks) where even if you have the level and runes required to use the spell/prayer, the sprite is still faded.
The spells/prayers are usable, but you would have no way of knowing if you we&#39;re able to use them or not without hovering your mouse over them and checking the requirements.
This worked on my old client, but the renaming is different, and I suck at client work anyways, so I wasn&#39;t able to figure it out.

Does anyone know how to fix it?
[s]I believe it&#39;s a Galkon&#39;s Refactored client, but I&#39;m not too sure.
The only thing I can tell you is that the variables in ItemDef seem to match most renamed clients, which wasn&#39;t true for the PI client I used to have.[/s]
Jk, it&#39;s definitely a Galkon&#39;s Refactored client.

Rep for help.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 05:38:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/prayer-and-magic-tab-sprites/373618.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Prayer and Magic tab sprites</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@revengr revengr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/revengr">@revengr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve got this issue with my client where the sprites for all prayers and spells (In both prayer books and all 3 spellbooks) where even if you have the level and runes required to use the spell/prayer, the sprite is still faded.<br>
The spells/prayers are usable, but you would have no way of knowing if you we’re able to use them or not without hovering your mouse over them and checking the requirements.<br>
This worked on my old client, but the renaming is different, and I suck at client work anyways, so I wasn’t able to figure it out.</p>
<p>Does anyone know how to fix it?<br>
<span class="bbcode-s">I believe it’s a Galkon’s Refactored client, but I’m not too sure.<br>
The only thing I can tell you is that the variables in ItemDef seem to match most renamed clients, which wasn’t true for the PI client I used to have.</span><br>
Jk, it’s definitely a Galkon’s Refactored client.</p>
<p>Rep for help.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/prayer-and-magic-tab-sprites/373618/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/prayer-and-magic-tab-sprites/373618/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 05:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-373618-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/prayer-and-magic-tab-sprites/373618.rss">Prayer and Magic tab sprites</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
