<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267</link>
    <description>what this xbox mod will do is
Allow you to play unsigned/backup games
Allow you to use homebrew software such as &quot;Emulators&quot;.
Allow you to run/copy games to the Internal hard-drive.
Allow you to Install a new replacement/larger hard-drive.
Allow you to FTP into your Xbox to load files and edit/delete files.
Reset your Xbox with &quot;IGR&quot; (In Game Reset) button combo.
Allow use of Xbox *&#39;Live&#39; (a script is included to revert to the original dash)
*Limited Use as you&#39;ll need the original game to use the &#39;Live&#39; service
Tools and Items you will require

Memory card (Highly suggest you use the Microsoft Version).
Microsoft Controller or Action Replay/Gameshark with USB Memory card Writer.
Original copy of &#39;James Bond 007: Agent under Fire&#39; (Platinum version may not work).


Get the right Game
I recommend you start with obtaining an original copy of one of 007 Agent Under Fire that will work with the exploits they are:

James Bond 007: Agent under Fire&#39; Platinum versions may not work. I have read that any version with this number 1448517 works this number 1448527 doesn&#39;t work (see photo below).
[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img245.imageshack.us/img245/7029/bondyt0.jpg[/img][/URL]

The Game Save For 007
please download the 007 agent under fire gamesave here. after downloaded copy to your xbox usiong action replay.
Prepare your Xbox
First thing you should do If possible is connect your Xbox to the Internet and update your Dashboard. You can do this simply by choosing the &#39;Live&#39; options and select &#39;Account recovery&#39; this updates your dashboard automatically and once finished will ask you for details of your account to continue, just quit as you&#39;ve accomplished the task of updating the Dashboard. If you actually have a &#39;Live&#39; account you probably don&#39;t need to do anything as your Dashboard will be up to date.

Time to Load our save game
Start the &#39;James Bond 007: Agent Under Fire&#39; Game (the original of course) once in the game and it&#39;s loaded select the option to load a saved game (I have had feedback that on some versions you need to select a level play until the game movies finish then quit the game and then load the saved game) make sure it loads from the hard-drive and if needed delete any existing save games that you may have had before you copy the game save exploit over. The save game should start to load, after a wait of about 10 seconds it should load the UnleashX dash. If this doesn&#39;t work try starting over, there&#39;s a chance your game is newer and patched to fix the exploit hole. You should see the UnleashX dash which looks like the photo below of course if using Krayzie&#39;s installer it will be slightly different.
[URL=http://imageshack.us][IMG]http://img81.imageshack.us/img81/8040/emurj0.jpg[/img][/URL]
From the main menu you should see &#39;Waffle Zone Tool&#39; press &#39;A&#39; to enter this menu and you should now see the options as the above photo. From this menu select &#39;Install UXE Package&#39; and press &#39;A&#39; the script will start copying the needed files. After it is done copying the package, it will boot to Linux and make a backup of your EEPROM. On a 1.6 Xbox, your screen will probably display a corrupt unreadable image, this is fine just ignore it for now and watch for your LED to flash green which means the process is complete. If your not sure just eject your game disk and power off the Xbox after two minutes, this should be more than enough time to create the EEPROM backup.

Power back on and without any game in the DVD-drive your Xbox should boot to the UnleashX screen you saw earlier. The first thing you should do is FTP into your xbox using the IP address shown on your dashboard (user=xbox pass=xbox) . Use a ftp program like flash fxp to ftp if you have any questions about ftping please post it here. Now copy the EEPROM back-up to your PC&#39;s Hard-drive, the back-up will have been made of your original MS Dash, as well as the installed UXE package in E:\Backup\. Your EEPROM will be saved to E:\Backup_linux\, copy these folders and burn them onto a CD to keep them safe. REMEMBER these are the keys to your Xbox, loose them and you won&#39;t be able to recover from a Hard-drive failure or other problem.

Verify that your Xbox will Play an Original game and then try a back-up version, If these test work you have successfully applied the UXE package.

If you would like to install a Larger Hard-drive or simply need to replace the existing Hard-drive due to failure then you need to read this article Here

Using the Xbox &#39;Live&#39;
If you desire to play online you&#39;ll need to make sure you never modify the files located in &#39;E:\Backup\&#39; or &#39;E:\Backup\Modded\&#39; if you do then the included scripts won&#39;t work correctly as the scripts expect the files it needs to be located in these directories.

To reset your Xbox to the Microsoft Dashboard simply choose &#39;Waffle Zone Tools&#39; press &#39;A&#39; to enter this menu and now select &#39;Backup Menu&#39; and press &#39;A&#39; the next item to select is &#39;Restore Unmodded Backup&#39; press &#39;A&#39;, the script will start copying the needed files, after it is done reboot and play the Games you want online (of course you need the Original game).

A possibility exists that Microsoft will eventually implement a check for these type of exploits and when discovered will Ban your Xbox from be able to use the &#39;Live&#39; service.

When you want to revert back to the Softmod you basically repeat the steps to do the exploit the first time with the exception that you should choose &#39;WaffleTools&#39; then &#39;Backup Menu&#39; (NOT Install UXE Package) now here simply choose the option &#39;Restore Modded Backup&#39; this will copy the files needed to revert your box to the UnleashX dash, once complete reboot your Xbox and you should be back to the UnleashX dashboard.

YOU WILL NEED TO FIND YOUR OWN EMULATORS AND GAMES FOR THE XBOX

[b]CREDZ[/b] = http://www.astahost.com/info.php/how-mod-xbox_t13364.html
didnt make this tut myself but i did it to my xbox</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 23:47:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Divine-Devil Divine-Devil]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/divine-devil">@Divine-Devil</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s ok, I seen way better, I know better websites for this kind of stuff.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 23:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78267-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267.rss">MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@liltwixis11 liltwixis11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/liltwixis11">@liltwixis11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>awsome</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 10:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78267-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267.rss">MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RXVL RXVL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rxvl">@RXVL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Use XBMC noobs.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 08:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78267-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267.rss">MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ghostboy195 ghostboy195]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ghostboy195">@ghostboy195</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks anyway though. I told my friend i would mod his xbox if he would buy and AR for himself</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 03:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78267-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267.rss">MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@margera456 margera456]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/margera456">@margera456</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol yeah but i though “hey maybe i should share it with some people from mopar” lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2007 22:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78267-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267.rss">MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ghostboy195 ghostboy195]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ghostboy195">@ghostboy195</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>nice guide, but would have been better if you had made it your self</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2007 17:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78267-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267.rss">MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@margera456 margera456]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/margera456">@margera456</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what this xbox mod will do is<br>
Allow you to play unsigned/backup games<br>
Allow you to use homebrew software such as “Emulators”.<br>
Allow you to run/copy games to the Internal hard-drive.<br>
Allow you to Install a new replacement/larger hard-drive.<br>
Allow you to FTP into your Xbox to load files and edit/delete files.<br>
Reset your Xbox with “IGR” (In Game Reset) button combo.<br>
Allow use of Xbox *‘Live’ (a script is included to revert to the original dash)<br>
*Limited Use as you’ll need the original game to use the ‘Live’ service<br>
Tools and Items you will require</p>
<p>Memory card (Highly suggest you use the Microsoft Version).<br>
Microsoft Controller or Action Replay/Gameshark with USB Memory card Writer.<br>
Original copy of ‘James Bond 007: Agent under Fire’ (Platinum version may not work).</p>
<p>Get the right Game<br>
I recommend you start with obtaining an original copy of one of 007 Agent Under Fire that will work with the exploits they are:</p>
<p>James Bond 007: Agent under Fire’ Platinum versions may not work. I have read that any version with this number 1448517 works this number 1448527 doesn’t work (see photo below).<br>
<a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img245.imageshack.us/img245/7029/bondyt0.jpg" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>The Game Save For 007<br>
please download the 007 agent under fire gamesave here. after downloaded copy to your xbox usiong action replay.<br>
Prepare your Xbox<br>
First thing you should do If possible is connect your Xbox to the Internet and update your Dashboard. You can do this simply by choosing the ‘Live’ options and select ‘Account recovery’ this updates your dashboard automatically and once finished will ask you for details of your account to continue, just quit as you’ve accomplished the task of updating the Dashboard. If you actually have a ‘Live’ account you probably don’t need to do anything as your Dashboard will be up to date.</p>
<p>Time to Load our save game<br>
Start the ‘James Bond 007: Agent Under Fire’ Game (the original of course) once in the game and it’s loaded select the option to load a saved game (I have had feedback that on some versions you need to select a level play until the game movies finish then quit the game and then load the saved game) make sure it loads from the hard-drive and if needed delete any existing save games that you may have had before you copy the game save exploit over. The save game should start to load, after a wait of about 10 seconds it should load the UnleashX dash. If this doesn’t work try starting over, there’s a chance your game is newer and patched to fix the exploit hole. You should see the UnleashX dash which looks like the photo below of course if using Krayzie’s installer it will be slightly different.<br>
<a href="http://imageshack.us" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img81.imageshack.us/img81/8040/emurj0.jpg" alt width="" height=""></a><br>
From the main menu you should see ‘Waffle Zone Tool’ press ‘A’ to enter this menu and you should now see the options as the above photo. From this menu select ‘Install UXE Package’ and press ‘A’ the script will start copying the needed files. After it is done copying the package, it will boot to Linux and make a backup of your EEPROM. On a 1.6 Xbox, your screen will probably display a corrupt unreadable image, this is fine just ignore it for now and watch for your LED to flash green which means the process is complete. If your not sure just eject your game disk and power off the Xbox after two minutes, this should be more than enough time to create the EEPROM backup.</p>
<p>Power back on and without any game in the DVD-drive your Xbox should boot to the UnleashX screen you saw earlier. The first thing you should do is FTP into your xbox using the IP address shown on your dashboard (user=xbox pass=xbox) . Use a ftp program like flash fxp to ftp if you have any questions about ftping please post it here. Now copy the EEPROM back-up to your PC’s Hard-drive, the back-up will have been made of your original MS Dash, as well as the installed UXE package in E:\Backup. Your EEPROM will be saved to E:\Backup_linux, copy these folders and burn them onto a CD to keep them safe. REMEMBER these are the keys to your Xbox, loose them and you won’t be able to recover from a Hard-drive failure or other problem.</p>
<p>Verify that your Xbox will Play an Original game and then try a back-up version, If these test work you have successfully applied the UXE package.</p>
<p>If you would like to install a Larger Hard-drive or simply need to replace the existing Hard-drive due to failure then you need to read this article Here</p>
<p>Using the Xbox ‘Live’<br>
If you desire to play online you’ll need to make sure you never modify the files located in ‘E:\Backup’ or ‘E:\Backup\Modded’ if you do then the included scripts won’t work correctly as the scripts expect the files it needs to be located in these directories.</p>
<p>To reset your Xbox to the Microsoft Dashboard simply choose ‘Waffle Zone Tools’ press ‘A’ to enter this menu and now select ‘Backup Menu’ and press ‘A’ the next item to select is ‘Restore Unmodded Backup’ press ‘A’, the script will start copying the needed files, after it is done reboot and play the Games you want online (of course you need the Original game).</p>
<p>A possibility exists that Microsoft will eventually implement a check for these type of exploits and when discovered will Ban your Xbox from be able to use the ‘Live’ service.</p>
<p>When you want to revert back to the Softmod you basically repeat the steps to do the exploit the first time with the exception that you should choose ‘WaffleTools’ then ‘Backup Menu’ (NOT Install UXE Package) now here simply choose the option ‘Restore Modded Backup’ this will copy the files needed to revert your box to the UnleashX dash, once complete reboot your Xbox and you should be back to the UnleashX dashboard.</p>
<p>YOU WILL NEED TO FIND YOUR OWN EMULATORS AND GAMES FOR THE XBOX</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">CREDZ</span> = <a href="http://www.astahost.com/info.php/how-mod-xbox_t13364.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.astahost.com/info.php/how-mod-xbox_t13364.html</a><br>
didnt make this tut myself but i did it to my xbox</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2007 11:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-78267-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/modding-your-xbox-reply-if-you-like-it/78267.rss">MODDING YOUR XBOX reply if you like it</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
