<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Webclient (I&#39;ve tried and tried and I get same problem)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-ive-tried-and-tried-and-i-get-same-problem/405947</link>
    <description>Hello, I&#39;m not really too concerned about making a web-client right now but I keep trying every now and again with the same results. The following information is what I have already done and I will then explain the error:

I followed Ric&#39;s Webclient Tutorial found [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,336494.0.html]here[/url].

[ul][li]I edited my client.java to have my cache download link and all the methods for that are in there as well.[/li]
[li]I have compiled and Jarred my client with JAR Maker from Ric&#39;s Tutorial.[/li]
[li]I uploaded my webclient page, cache, client.jar, and my certificate all to my web server.[/li][/ul]


When I try to load my client locally it downloads the cache fine, but when I try to run it off my web page on the web server it displays the message: &quot;Downloading Cache&quot; for about 2-3 seconds and then comes up with another message: &quot;Client Updated - Please Reload Client.&quot;

If anyone has any ideas on what might be wrong, please post them here if you might be able to help. Thank you, I really don&#39;t know what is making this act up.

-Ghostly150</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 17:46:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-ive-tried-and-tried-and-i-get-same-problem/405947.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Webclient (I&#39;ve tried and tried and I get same problem)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ghostly150 ghostly150]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ghostly150">@ghostly150</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, I’m not really too concerned about making a web-client right now but I keep trying every now and again with the same results. The following information is what I have already done and I will then explain the error:</p>
<p>I followed Ric’s Webclient Tutorial found <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,336494.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>[ul][li]I edited my client.java to have my cache download link and all the methods for that are in there as well.[/li]<br>
[li]I have compiled and Jarred my client with JAR Maker from Ric’s Tutorial.[/li]<br>
[li]I uploaded my webclient page, cache, client.jar, and my certificate all to my web server.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>When I try to load my client locally it downloads the cache fine, but when I try to run it off my web page on the web server it displays the message: “Downloading Cache” for about 2-3 seconds and then comes up with another message: “Client Updated - Please Reload Client.”</p>
<p>If anyone has any ideas on what might be wrong, please post them here if you might be able to help. Thank you, I really don’t know what is making this act up.</p>
<p>-Ghostly150</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-ive-tried-and-tried-and-i-get-same-problem/405947/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-ive-tried-and-tried-and-i-get-same-problem/405947/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 17:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-405947-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/webclient-ive-tried-and-tried-and-i-get-same-problem/405947.rss">Webclient (I&#39;ve tried and tried and I get same problem)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
