<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Simple question!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-question/487136</link>
    <description>I want to make a private server, but one just for myself. On this server I&#39;d like to add all most of the games features possible. So it would be my own version I could just play alone sorta deal and skill 1 to 99 as slow/fast as I would in regular runescape. I&#39;m a PC technician and I wouldn&#39;t have a problem writing my own scripts and setting it all up. To the point/question, What would I be getting myself into? 
By this i mean has it been done? Is it practical? 
Once I get started, and after I finish, I&#39;ll end up adding my own updates, fixing glitches, general maintenance and  just enjoying my own version of the game. 
I think it would be fun to have all of the game alone do a slayer task and no ones around, it would give me that desolate relaxing feeling. 
I know my questions are not the greatest. I&#39;m just looking for some opinions, facts. 
Please keep your negative comments to yourself by that I don&#39;t mean, for you to not serve me the cold hard truth and give me the facts. I mean don&#39;t tell me why it&#39;s a waste of time and what not. 
That covers it all!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 05:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-question/487136.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Simple question!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowser bowser]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowser">@bowser</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I want to make a private server, but one just for myself. On this server I’d like to add all most of the games features possible. So it would be my own version I could just play alone sorta deal and skill 1 to 99 as slow/fast as I would in regular runescape. I’m a PC technician and I wouldn’t have a problem writing my own scripts and setting it all up. To the point/question, What would I be getting myself into?<br>
By this i mean has it been done? Is it practical?<br>
Once I get started, and after I finish, I’ll end up adding my own updates, fixing glitches, general maintenance and  just enjoying my own version of the game.<br>
I think it would be fun to have all of the game alone do a slayer task and no ones around, it would give me that desolate relaxing feeling.<br>
I know my questions are not the greatest. I’m just looking for some opinions, facts.<br>
Please keep your negative comments to yourself by that I don’t mean, for you to not serve me the cold hard truth and give me the facts. I mean don’t tell me why it’s a waste of time and what not.<br>
That covers it all!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-question/487136/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-question/487136/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 05:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-487136-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/simple-question/487136.rss">Simple question!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
