<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Awesomeness and other 562 clients wont connect</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-awesomeness-and-other-562-clients-wont-connect/465161</link>
    <description>Okay, so here&#39;s the deal.

I&#39;m running 562 servers off of my computer, with no-ip installed and running. I can get the client to connect if I use localhost IP only. When I go to change my IP to the no-ip.org extension, or just using my external ip, the client will not connect. Constantly gets stuck at &quot;Connecting to Update Server&quot; and then gives me an &quot;error_game_js5connect&quot;.

I have tried this on a 317 server as well, with the exact same results. Router/modem through xfinity, and IS port forwarded to 43594 AND 43595 with both TCP/UDP listed. What am I doing wrong? I have searched everywhere for a fix, including here and google. Noone seems to have this fixed, and I never used to have a problem with this a couple of years ago when I used CorruptionX server source/client downloaded from here.

Please help, on a bit of a deadline.

:::EDIT:::

I have teamviewer if that&#39;ll help solve the situation faster. Please lemme know.

:::EDIT:::

If noone wants to help, just delete this topic. I&#39;m actually trying to figure this out, but even with 5 reads, and all the experienced coders out there with more knowledge than myself, I find it pretty sad that my post gets overlooked like I&#39;m just pathetic.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 06:00:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-awesomeness-and-other-562-clients-wont-connect/465161.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Project Awesomeness and other 562 clients wont connect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@phoenixrising phoenixrising]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phoenixrising">@phoenixrising</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, so here’s the deal.</p>
<p>I’m running 562 servers off of my computer, with no-ip installed and running. I can get the client to connect if I use localhost IP only. When I go to change my IP to the <a href="http://no-ip.org" rel="nofollow noopener">no-ip.org</a> extension, or just using my external ip, the client will not connect. Constantly gets stuck at “Connecting to Update Server” and then gives me an “error_game_js5connect”.</p>
<p>I have tried this on a 317 server as well, with the exact same results. Router/modem through xfinity, and IS port forwarded to 43594 AND 43595 with both TCP/UDP listed. What am I doing wrong? I have searched everywhere for a fix, including here and google. Noone seems to have this fixed, and I never used to have a problem with this a couple of years ago when I used CorruptionX server source/client downloaded from here.</p>
<p>Please help, on a bit of a deadline.</p>
<p>:::EDIT:::</p>
<p>I have teamviewer if that’ll help solve the situation faster. Please lemme know.</p>
<p>:::EDIT:::</p>
<p>If noone wants to help, just delete this topic. I’m actually trying to figure this out, but even with 5 reads, and all the experienced coders out there with more knowledge than myself, I find it pretty sad that my post gets overlooked like I’m just pathetic.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-awesomeness-and-other-562-clients-wont-connect/465161/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-awesomeness-and-other-562-clients-wont-connect/465161/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 06:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-465161-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-awesomeness-and-other-562-clients-wont-connect/465161.rss">Project Awesomeness and other 562 clients wont connect</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
