<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Holloween story</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834</link>
    <description>Despite my not so welcome welcome, Holloween is almost here, and I&#39;d like to tell a little stroy :cool:
Please note that there realy were several murders comitted by people bieng hung off the bridge.
ENJOY(not writen by me) :D

http://media.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/images/I44942-2003Oct30L

Boo! It&#39;s the Bunny Man!
30-Year Legend Still Spooks Visitors to Fairfax County Bridge
By Don Oldenburg
Washington Post Staff Writer
Friday, October 31, 2003; Page C01


Angie Proffitt says she&#39;ll never forget her first visit. She was 14 and it was the &#39;70s. Her boyfriend wanted to scare her, and the dark tunnel under a railroad bridge at a dead-end road was the ideal place.

Parked near the bridge, Proffitt recalls she noticed two children at the tunnel opening. She watched them and suddenly, poof! They disappeared, she says.

&quot;I&#39;m saying, &#39;Oh my God!&#39; And seconds later the children were at the back window of the car looking right at me,&quot; she says. &quot;I was hysterical.&quot;

Proffitt heard of Bunny Man Bridge years later and realized that was it. She returned six times. &quot;The bridge is haunted, I do know that,&quot; says Proffitt, who lives in Strasburg, Va., and often visits houses and places said to be haunted. &quot;Those children were victims. They died there.&quot;

The legend of Bunny Man Bridge has evolved in Northern Virginia over the past 30 years the way most scary stories do -- kernels of truth transform frightening rumors into macabre tales where the location&#39;s ripe for fright.

In one version, the Bunny Man story begins in western Fairfax County in 1905, at a mental institution near Clifton, where the bridge was built. The state demolished the asylum and bused convicts to Lorton. Two escaped and hid in the woods.

Residents found carcasses of half-eaten rabbits for weeks. Then one of the inmates was found hanging by a noose from the bridge. The other convict escaped to become the &quot;Bunny Man.&quot;

Then there&#39;s the &#39;70s story about the child, or parent, who dressed up like a bunny, killed his family, then hanged himself from the bridge. Other tales, same period, report a maniac wearing a bunny suit attacking people with a hatchet, and two children killed by a local hermit there, and teens found disemboweled there -- in all, 28 horrible deaths are said to have happened at the bridge!

Anyone who goes to the bridge at midnight on Halloween dies a gruesome death! The story even appeared two years ago on the Fox Family Channel&#39;s &quot;Scariest Places on Earth&quot; show: Want to see the Bunny Man? Stand in the tunnel and repeat &quot;Bunny Man&quot; three times. He&#39;ll appear like Little Bunny Foo Foo on steroids.

The whitewashed Bunny Man Bridge is on Colchester Road outside Clifton. In daylight, it&#39;s a single-lane tunnel, 60 feet long, with strange acoustics. In the blackness of night, it&#39;s a dead end where homes hide behind thick woods, where crickets chirp like racing heartbeats, frogs cry like babies and the stream murmurs. Peaceful as a graveyard.

Steve Sucher of Springfield says it&#39;s creepy. Years ago he would drive by the area going home from work and keep his windows rolled up. &quot;The road is poorly lit, narrow and curvy, which makes one nervous anyhow. But I would get a feeling of dread,&quot; says Sucher, 35, a paranormal research hobbyist who doesn&#39;t buy the Bunny Man story. &quot;I would get weird vibes but I can&#39;t explain why.&quot;

There are reports that Fairfax County police maintain video surveillance of the bridge. A sign used to warn: &quot;Under Surveillance.&quot; Cops are said to pull up soon after visitors arrive. Supposedly, surveillance footage has caught strange phenomena.

Julie Zyvoloski says police showed up in minutes when she visited in March. &quot;The story is believable to a point. Someone escaping. Eating rabbits to survive. Someone hanged,&quot; says Zyvoloski, who grew up in Annandale and lives in Florida. &quot;But I haven&#39;t found any proof of it.&quot;

Neither has Brian Conley. &quot;If you mean, is there any truth to any of the rumors to anybody being murdered, or anything paranormal, I have found no evidence. I believe that to be bogus,&quot; he says.

As the Fairfax County Public Library historian and archivist, Conley has researched the legend&#39;s origins over 11 years, collecting stories and searching through crime reports and newspaper accounts. He found none of the county&#39;s murder cases matched the Bunny Man saga and no murders occurred at the bridge.

In his report, titled &quot;The Bunny Man Unmasked,&quot; he said no insane asylum ever existed in Fairfax County and Lorton Prison was built five years after the convicts were supposedly moved there. Police video surveillance? No power within 600 yards of the bridge.

But Conley did find two stories in The Washington Post from October 1970 that he believes fed the folk tale. &quot;There was on at least two occasions a man in a bunny suit throwing hatchets at people,&quot; he says.

Nobody was killed. Both incidents took place in suburban Virginia. And soon rumors of a killer in bunny clothing spread to Maryland and West Virginia. &quot;It took only a couple weeks before the kids are telling stories,&quot; he says.

Conley speculates the gruesome rumors stuck to the bridge because it was a good place to get frightened. &quot;You could go under that bridge and there was nothing there except a great place to party,&quot; he says. &quot;This is the kind of story that you&#39;d tell if you&#39;re back there partying. In terms of how urban legends get started, this is a real beaut.&quot;

Urban legend expert Jan Harold Brunvand says such monster or maniac stories are common. He mentions the Mothman legend in West Virginia, made into a movie last year, and classic tales such as &quot;The Hook,&quot; &quot;The Killer in the Back Seat&quot; and &quot;The Hairy-Armed Hitchhiker&quot; are widespread.

&quot;Often they are about a deformed and insane person who suffered some kind of electrical, chemical or explosive accident, then retreated to the woods where he terrorizes locals. Like Bunny Man, their primary audience is teenagers,&quot; says Brunvand, author of &quot;The Truth Never Stands in the Way of a Good Story.&quot;

In downtown Clifton, Melissa Bettius, 20, says, &quot;All the high school kids this Halloween are going to Bunny Man Bridge even though you&#39;re not supposed to.&quot;

She works at Noodles &#39;n&#39; Noggins, a shop on Main Street, but the 2003 high school grad says she has been to the bridge often. &quot;It was scary,&quot; she says. &quot;Supposedly on Halloween, somebody in a bunny suit does show up!&quot;

The Haunted Trail at the Park is the Halloween fright hike for trick-or-treaters that has become a tradition. Every year someone creeps around the trail dressed as the Bunny Man.

Tom McNamara, owner of the Clifton General Store, denies it&#39;s him despite what some people say. &quot;No,&quot; he says bluntly.

Anything to the legend?

&quot;Bunk, totally false,&quot; he says.

Tom Peterson&#39;s front yard along Main Street displays a fake cemetery to entertain Halloween ghouls. One headstone reads &quot;Axe Murderer Bunny Man&quot; with the parting words: &quot;I&#39;ll be back!&quot;

Peterson says last year he drove his children, ages 8 and 12, to the bridge, stopped in the tunnel and turned off the car lights. &quot;My kids screamed!&quot; laughs the Robinson High School teacher. &quot;It&#39;s terrifying because of the stories they&#39;ve heard. Every one around here knows about the Bunny Man.&quot;

Officer Courtney Young, spokeswoman for the Fairfax County police, assures that no heinous crimes have happened at the bridge. &quot;We get the usual kind of calls for juvenile trespassing or suspicious vehicles down in that area,&quot; she says.

But Halloweeners deciding to cross that bridge when they get to it tonight will find someone ominous waiting. Fairfax County police this week decided to close down the bridge for Halloween and &quot;run out&quot; all gawkers.

So take Alex Picciano&#39;s word for it. &quot;It was scary but not that scary,&quot; says the Oakton High junior, who went to Bunny Man Bridge the other night with five friends. On the way home, they rented &quot;The Blair Witch Project&quot; and really got scared.

&quot;It would&#39;ve been a lot scarier,&quot; he says, &quot;if we had watched the movie first.&quot;</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 04:46:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Kryptizzler, post:17, topic:20834”][quote author=O M F G link=topic=31660.msg378247#msg378247 date=1162283389]<br>
O M F G<br>
[/quote]Offtopic, but there was a guy on Reinet called OMFG. It stood for Old Men Fucking Grandmas. Nice name ;).[/quote]<br>
Actully it stands for Oh My Fucking God</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 04:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kryptizzler Kryptizzler]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kryptizzler">@Kryptizzler</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“O M F G, post:8, topic:20834”]O M F G[/quote]Offtopic, but there was a guy on Reinet called OMFG. It stood for Old Men Fucking Grandmas. Nice name ;).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 11:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rabcarl rabcarl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rabcarl">@rabcarl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“D27L7T, post:7, topic:20834”]My halloween story.</p>
<p><img src="http://pr0n.encyclopediadramatica.com/images/4/45/Hot_furry.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/quote]</p>
<p>You know you want that. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 10:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>my costume was awsome,yet also thrown together in an hour.<br>
I took a garoyl mask,spraypainted it(while wearin), got a robe-TADA!<br>
lol :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 03:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blacker blacker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blacker">@blacker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes, very scary. I dressed up as something completely and totlly random, thrown together by buying a robe and a random mask ast that Scaty Central tihng at Wal-Mart. Thats even SCARIER.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 07:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice story, but whats the point of it?<br>
P.S. One guy I know dressed up like a princess for halloween…scary…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 07:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wall_of_fir wall of fir]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wall_of_fir">@wall_of_fir</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hmm…how about this:</p>
<p>October 30, 1948:<br>
Malic Orban was walking on his midnight jog when he tripped on something.He looked back, there was nothing there, he was about to get up when he saw a cut up girl in front of him.He was a doctor so he offered to take him to the hospital, or just treat the wounds there.The girl was very apprehensive and BURST into flames he jumped back.Then he woke up…in jail.He called the guard.The guard explained all he knew was that he had raped a girl, when they found the girl she was cut up.Malic was shocked.He hadnt raped that girl, he actually offered to SAVE her!He asked for his one phone call.<br>
The guard said he already used it to dial 1-800-PORN. Malic was terrified, he hadnt done any of this!He immediately hatched a plan.Since his jail clothed were light, he cranked up the thermestat to 120 degrees farenheit.The guard eventually passed out from the heat, and Malic grabbed his coat through one of the bars, and grabbed the keys.<br>
He put on the guards clothes,too.Then something very bizarre happened.<br>
He went outside without being noticed.Then something caught his eye.The girl!He ran up to her and grabbed her by the throat.“WHAT HAVE YOU DONE TO ME!?” The girls face turned green.She had a deeper  voice than him.<br>
She was like “You stupid slut!” and stabbed him, he passed out from lack of blood, and she dragged him to a warehouse on the east side.He woke to a headache and the loud sound of downtown hustling of cars and buses.<br>
He tried to get up but he was tied up, a poof of cloud formed in front of him.The girl, with the knife.<br>
he rembered he stabbed her, but he had no wound.He was very disorientated.The girl walked up to him.<br>
“You dont know me do you?” “No…Should I?”  “Hehe.Good.You see I’m a legend.The split girl.<br>
Two personalities.Two minds.” The girl raised her knife. Malic flinched, yet, he though she would stab him, but she stabbed herself.He KNEW he was gonna be part of SOME kind of ritual.She got some chalk.Drew a circle around him,and  sprinkled blood on him and around him.She started chanting: “Oon Chakka Lakka Lakka, Oon Chakka Lakka Lakka”<br>
Soon he no longer saw her, but he saw himself!He was in the body of the girl! ‘Malic’ bit the ropes and got away.<br>
‘the girl’ was stuck in the body.‘Malic’ changed his name and he’s immortal.He stays around big cities and murders people, and if ‘he’ likes the body, ‘he’ takes it.So ‘he’ can be anyone.watch out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 02:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“rabcarl, post:9, topic:20834”][quote author=O M F G link=topic=31660.msg371586#msg371586 date=1162173946]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Nice story but dotn your mean Halloween instead of Holloween?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lol,forget spellin <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
Coments are more than welcome people!!!I wana know what YOU think bout this!<br>
P.S.<br>
Who hates wnana-be mods on da runescape forums?They always get good threads 2 get locker by startin a flame war! :mad:<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>You actually go on RS forums? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
I LOVE them,I adore them, there’s everything AWSOME on them and I can ALWAYS find the OWNIN thread I’m looking for.[/quote]<br>
AGREED![br][size=1]Posted at: October 30, 2006, 11:14:17 PM[/size][hr]bump…lol[br][size=1]Posted at: October 31, 2006, 05:54:11 AM[/size][hr]Come on ppl, lets not forget to post!Its halloween for cryin out loud and this is a partly true scary<br>
story :mad:<br>
P.S.<br>
I love the halloween update</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 01:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol i live like 20 min away from that bridge; give or take some mins</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 09:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@rabcarl rabcarl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rabcarl">@rabcarl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“O M F G, post:3, topic:20834”][quote author=the fu superior link=topic=31660.msg371576#msg371576 date=1162173880]<br>
Nice story but dotn your mean Halloween instead of Holloween?<br>
[/quote]<br>
lol,forget spellin <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
Coments are more than welcome people!!!I wana know what YOU think bout this!<br>
P.S.<br>
Who hates wnana-be mods on da runescape forums?They always get good threads 2 get locker by startin a flame war! :mad:[/quote]</p>
<p>You actually go on RS forums? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>I hate them, there’s nothing good on them and I can never find the damn thread I’m looking for.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 08:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>O M F G</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 08:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@D27L7T D27L7T]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/d27l7t">@D27L7T</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My halloween story.</p>
<p><img src="http://pr0n.encyclopediadramatica.com/images/4/45/Hot_furry.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 08:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=9" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:">nice story, I doubt the walkin outa the lake :rolleyes:. but the murder might be posible, i’d realy like 2 hear wat u came up with in your research.<br>
The reason I picked the Bunnyman was cuz I live in Fairfax county,VA and I dont like murders,nor hauntings in my area <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"><br>
I’ll go find more stories  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 08:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@blacker blacker]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blacker">@blacker</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol last year I heard about a story called ‘The Jackalyn’ last year, and this is how it goes:</p>
<p>[center]Every year, on Halloween night, 1 minute before midnight <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">IT</span></span> comes. <span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">IT</span></span> is the [glow=black,2,300]Jackalyn[/glow] The Jackalyn is a crazy serial killer who, like I said, comes out of a lake every year on Halloween at 11:59 pm. He has a pumpkin for a head, and carries a knife covered with blood, lake water, and pumpkin seeds  :eek: If anyone is walking by the lake when he comes out (hes only gonna come out of 1 of the lakes in the world, or somethin, lol but then again theres the time zones  :eek:) and stalks that person, a short distance away from the lake, and kills them by surprise. They die so fast that they scream after they die (cause they prepare to scream, then the seocnd they let the air out they die or somethin) beacuse they dont have time before they die. He only stays for 1 minute.<br>
[/center]</p>
<p>Thats all I know, I dont know if its a real urban legend or if he just made it up off the top of his head. Ill do some research just in case.</p>
<p>Whats creepy is that I live right next to a lake, and my birthdays November First, which is the exact time hes ‘supposed’ to go back in.  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>Hope you liked the story. Im sorry, it wasnt a copy paste, but I tried my best at narrating.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 06:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i dont think u normaly cary a gun around with u…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 04:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="20834">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 the fu superior:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Nice story but dotn your mean Halloween instead of Holloween?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lol,forget spellin <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"><br>
Coments are more than welcome people!!!I wana know what YOU think bout this!<br>
P.S.<br>
Who hates wnana-be mods on da runescape forums?They always get good threads 2 get locker by startin a flame war! :mad:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 02:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whothe0 the fu superior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whothe0">@whothe0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice story but dotn your mean Halloween instead of Holloween?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 02:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Holloween story</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@O_M_F_G O M F G]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/o_m_f_g">@O_M_F_G</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Despite my not so welcome welcome, Holloween is almost here, and I’d like to tell a little stroy <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=9" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"><br>
Please note that there realy were several murders comitted by people bieng hung off the bridge.<br>
ENJOY(not writen by me) <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p><a href="http://media.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/images/I44942-2003Oct30L" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://media.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/images/I44942-2003Oct30L</a></p>
<p>Boo! It’s the Bunny Man!<br>
30-Year Legend Still Spooks Visitors to Fairfax County Bridge<br>
By Don Oldenburg<br>
Washington Post Staff Writer<br>
Friday, October 31, 2003; Page C01</p>
<p>Angie Proffitt says she’ll never forget her first visit. She was 14 and it was the '70s. Her boyfriend wanted to scare her, and the dark tunnel under a railroad bridge at a dead-end road was the ideal place.</p>
<p>Parked near the bridge, Proffitt recalls she noticed two children at the tunnel opening. She watched them and suddenly, poof! They disappeared, she says.</p>
<p>“I’m saying, ‘Oh my God!’ And seconds later the children were at the back window of the car looking right at me,” she says. “I was hysterical.”</p>
<p>Proffitt heard of Bunny Man Bridge years later and realized that was it. She returned six times. “The bridge is haunted, I do know that,” says Proffitt, who lives in Strasburg, Va., and often visits houses and places said to be haunted. “Those children were victims. They died there.”</p>
<p>The legend of Bunny Man Bridge has evolved in Northern Virginia over the past 30 years the way most scary stories do – kernels of truth transform frightening rumors into macabre tales where the location’s ripe for fright.</p>
<p>In one version, the Bunny Man story begins in western Fairfax County in 1905, at a mental institution near Clifton, where the bridge was built. The state demolished the asylum and bused convicts to Lorton. Two escaped and hid in the woods.</p>
<p>Residents found carcasses of half-eaten rabbits for weeks. Then one of the inmates was found hanging by a noose from the bridge. The other convict escaped to become the “Bunny Man.”</p>
<p>Then there’s the '70s story about the child, or parent, who dressed up like a bunny, killed his family, then hanged himself from the bridge. Other tales, same period, report a maniac wearing a bunny suit attacking people with a hatchet, and two children killed by a local hermit there, and teens found disemboweled there – in all, 28 horrible deaths are said to have happened at the bridge!</p>
<p>Anyone who goes to the bridge at midnight on Halloween dies a gruesome death! The story even appeared two years ago on the Fox Family Channel’s “Scariest Places on Earth” show: Want to see the Bunny Man? Stand in the tunnel and repeat “Bunny Man” three times. He’ll appear like Little Bunny Foo Foo on steroids.</p>
<p>The whitewashed Bunny Man Bridge is on Colchester Road outside Clifton. In daylight, it’s a single-lane tunnel, 60 feet long, with strange acoustics. In the blackness of night, it’s a dead end where homes hide behind thick woods, where crickets chirp like racing heartbeats, frogs cry like babies and the stream murmurs. Peaceful as a graveyard.</p>
<p>Steve Sucher of Springfield says it’s creepy. Years ago he would drive by the area going home from work and keep his windows rolled up. “The road is poorly lit, narrow and curvy, which makes one nervous anyhow. But I would get a feeling of dread,” says Sucher, 35, a paranormal research hobbyist who doesn’t buy the Bunny Man story. “I would get weird vibes but I can’t explain why.”</p>
<p>There are reports that Fairfax County police maintain video surveillance of the bridge. A sign used to warn: “Under Surveillance.” Cops are said to pull up soon after visitors arrive. Supposedly, surveillance footage has caught strange phenomena.</p>
<p>Julie Zyvoloski says police showed up in minutes when she visited in March. “The story is believable to a point. Someone escaping. Eating rabbits to survive. Someone hanged,” says Zyvoloski, who grew up in Annandale and lives in Florida. “But I haven’t found any proof of it.”</p>
<p>Neither has Brian Conley. “If you mean, is there any truth to any of the rumors to anybody being murdered, or anything paranormal, I have found no evidence. I believe that to be bogus,” he says.</p>
<p>As the Fairfax County Public Library historian and archivist, Conley has researched the legend’s origins over 11 years, collecting stories and searching through crime reports and newspaper accounts. He found none of the county’s murder cases matched the Bunny Man saga and no murders occurred at the bridge.</p>
<p>In his report, titled “The Bunny Man Unmasked,” he said no insane asylum ever existed in Fairfax County and Lorton Prison was built five years after the convicts were supposedly moved there. Police video surveillance? No power within 600 yards of the bridge.</p>
<p>But Conley did find two stories in The Washington Post from October 1970 that he believes fed the folk tale. “There was on at least two occasions a man in a bunny suit throwing hatchets at people,” he says.</p>
<p>Nobody was killed. Both incidents took place in suburban Virginia. And soon rumors of a killer in bunny clothing spread to Maryland and West Virginia. “It took only a couple weeks before the kids are telling stories,” he says.</p>
<p>Conley speculates the gruesome rumors stuck to the bridge because it was a good place to get frightened. “You could go under that bridge and there was nothing there except a great place to party,” he says. “This is the kind of story that you’d tell if you’re back there partying. In terms of how urban legends get started, this is a real beaut.”</p>
<p>Urban legend expert Jan Harold Brunvand says such monster or maniac stories are common. He mentions the Mothman legend in West Virginia, made into a movie last year, and classic tales such as “The Hook,” “The Killer in the Back Seat” and “The Hairy-Armed Hitchhiker” are widespread.</p>
<p>“Often they are about a deformed and insane person who suffered some kind of electrical, chemical or explosive accident, then retreated to the woods where he terrorizes locals. Like Bunny Man, their primary audience is teenagers,” says Brunvand, author of “The Truth Never Stands in the Way of a Good Story.”</p>
<p>In downtown Clifton, Melissa Bettius, 20, says, “All the high school kids this Halloween are going to Bunny Man Bridge even though you’re not supposed to.”</p>
<p>She works at Noodles ‘n’ Noggins, a shop on Main Street, but the 2003 high school grad says she has been to the bridge often. “It was scary,” she says. “Supposedly on Halloween, somebody in a bunny suit does show up!”</p>
<p>The Haunted Trail at the Park is the Halloween fright hike for trick-or-treaters that has become a tradition. Every year someone creeps around the trail dressed as the Bunny Man.</p>
<p>Tom McNamara, owner of the Clifton General Store, denies it’s him despite what some people say. “No,” he says bluntly.</p>
<p>Anything to the legend?</p>
<p>“Bunk, totally false,” he says.</p>
<p>Tom Peterson’s front yard along Main Street displays a fake cemetery to entertain Halloween ghouls. One headstone reads “Axe Murderer Bunny Man” with the parting words: “I’ll be back!”</p>
<p>Peterson says last year he drove his children, ages 8 and 12, to the bridge, stopped in the tunnel and turned off the car lights. “My kids screamed!” laughs the Robinson High School teacher. “It’s terrifying because of the stories they’ve heard. Every one around here knows about the Bunny Man.”</p>
<p>Officer Courtney Young, spokeswoman for the Fairfax County police, assures that no heinous crimes have happened at the bridge. “We get the usual kind of calls for juvenile trespassing or suspicious vehicles down in that area,” she says.</p>
<p>But Halloweeners deciding to cross that bridge when they get to it tonight will find someone ominous waiting. Fairfax County police this week decided to close down the bridge for Halloween and “run out” all gawkers.</p>
<p>So take Alex Picciano’s word for it. “It was scary but not that scary,” says the Oakton High junior, who went to Bunny Man Bridge the other night with five friends. On the way home, they rented “The Blair Witch Project” and really got scared.</p>
<p>“It would’ve been a lot scarier,” he says, “if we had watched the movie first.”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 02:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-20834-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/holloween-story/20834.rss">Holloween story</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
