<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>HDD Missing? EDIT: NEW INFO</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hdd-missing-edit-new-info/399140</link>
    <description>Hello. I posted a few weeks ago about the jetty fail. I didn&#39;t read those answers until now because I forgot I had posted here. Now I need some help.
When this happened I didn&#39;t know that is was gone. Okay... Lets start with the info. This was my dads old computer. It&#39;s a Desktop computer.
He have put some extra things like an extra sata 360GB hard disk. And 2GB Ram and stuff. Now when this error with Jetty happened I just reinstalled
Ubuntu using my &quot;live cd&quot; but i think the first hdd messed up. So now I realise I deleted all the backup files in the newest hdd to install windows vista and ubuntu.
I can&#39;t find the first hard disk I messed up. I have opened the machine and they are both still plugged in. Here is some pictures of the disk manager.

[IMG]http://i621.photobucket.com/albums/tt292/kneistol/screenshot3.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i621.photobucket.com/albums/tt292/kneistol/screenshot2-1.png[/img]
[IMG]http://i621.photobucket.com/albums/tt292/kneistol/screenshot1-2.png[/img]


I have now divided the working harddisk into two pieces. One with vista and one with ubuntu. But I&#39;m missing my old backup harddisk.

If you wonder about the computer and all the things we have put inside it and the specifications or something. just ask. Please i need help.
We have backup of the backup so i have the posibility to reformat it or something like that. Please help me :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 19:42:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hdd-missing-edit-new-info/399140.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>HDD Missing? EDIT: NEW INFO</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kneistol kneistol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kneistol">@kneistol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello. I posted a few weeks ago about the jetty fail. I didn’t read those answers until now because I forgot I had posted here. Now I need some help.<br>
When this happened I didn’t know that is was gone. Okay… Lets start with the info. This was my dads old computer. It’s a Desktop computer.<br>
He have put some extra things like an extra sata 360GB hard disk. And 2GB Ram and stuff. Now when this error with Jetty happened I just reinstalled<br>
Ubuntu using my “live cd” but i think the first hdd messed up. So now I realise I deleted all the backup files in the newest hdd to install windows vista and ubuntu.<br>
I can’t find the first hard disk I messed up. I have opened the machine and they are both still plugged in. Here is some pictures of the disk manager.</p>
<p><img src="http://i621.photobucket.com/albums/tt292/kneistol/screenshot3.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i621.photobucket.com/albums/tt292/kneistol/screenshot2-1.png" alt width="" height=""><br>
<img src="http://i621.photobucket.com/albums/tt292/kneistol/screenshot1-2.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>I have now divided the working harddisk into two pieces. One with vista and one with ubuntu. But I’m missing my old backup harddisk.</p>
<p>If you wonder about the computer and all the things we have put inside it and the specifications or something. just ask. Please i need help.<br>
We have backup of the backup so i have the posibility to reformat it or something like that. Please help me <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hdd-missing-edit-new-info/399140/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hdd-missing-edit-new-info/399140/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 19:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-399140-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hdd-missing-edit-new-info/399140.rss">HDD Missing? EDIT: NEW INFO</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
