<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[317-Delta] Teleport tabs</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-teleport-tabs/542661</link>
    <description>I must be trying to add method&#39;s in the incorrect spot. Here&#39;s the problem. I add method&#39;s into the Wear ID packet (case 41).... Something like this,

[code]if (wearID == 2963) { // Ardougne
blahblahblah(): // MY CODE HERE
}[/code]

OK..... Now, I can get the code to work the way I would like it to, for the teleport tab&#39;s. The only problem is well, it&#39;s a custom item, and when I click the &#39;Break&#39; option to activate the teleport, I equip the item. Obviously I&#39;m not supposed to. I&#39;ve tried to add it in potions.java.... and make the code in the case 41 packet this,

[code]if (wearID == 2963) {
return false;
}[/code]

When I do that, I no longer equip the item, but it can&#39;t read the code anymore because the call isn&#39;t there to recognize the method. I tried adding the call and keeping the return in there, and it won&#39;t recognize the call. How do I fix this?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 22:25:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-teleport-tabs/542661.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[317-Delta] Teleport tabs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MyNameIsDylan MyNameIsDylan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mynameisdylan">@MyNameIsDylan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I must be trying to add method’s in the incorrect spot. Here’s the problem. I add method’s into the Wear ID packet (case 41)… Something like this,</p>
<p><code>if (wearID == 2963) { // Ardougne
blahblahblah(): // MY CODE HERE
}</code></p>
<p>OK… Now, I can get the code to work the way I would like it to, for the teleport tab’s. The only problem is well, it’s a custom item, and when I click the ‘Break’ option to activate the teleport, I equip the item. Obviously I’m not supposed to. I’ve tried to add it in potions.java… and make the code in the case 41 packet this,</p>
<p><code>if (wearID == 2963) {
return false;
}</code></p>
<p>When I do that, I no longer equip the item, but it can’t read the code anymore because the call isn’t there to recognize the method. I tried adding the call and keeping the return in there, and it won’t recognize the call. How do I fix this?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-teleport-tabs/542661/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-teleport-tabs/542661/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 22:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542661-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/317-delta-teleport-tabs/542661.rss">[317-Delta] Teleport tabs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
