<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How do you host?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-you-host/72793</link>
    <description>Well i wanted to know if anyone could tell me how to host a server? Can you tell me or give me a link to a guide? thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 03:49:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-you-host/72793.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How do you host?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@x_spike_x x spike x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x_spike_x">@x_spike_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]This is a short tut i created for hosting:[/center]<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">Procedure</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Hosting on no-ip: </span></p>
<p>No-Ip is what i highly recommend, it’s personalises your server, these are the following steps to hosting on No-Ip:</p>
<p>Go to: <a href="http://www.no-ip.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.no-ip.com</a><br>
And first of all you will need to register, simply click “Sign up now!” Next to the Login section.</p>
<p>Just enter your e-mail address and create a password and fill out that short form. Once you have done that click “i accept.create my account”.</p>
<p>The confirmation email will then have been sent, once you have confirmed your account on your e-mail you can then log in on <a href="http://www.no-ip.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.no-ip.com</a><br>
So then click on “host” in the left hand side navigation bar.</p>
<p>Then you need to create a host name e.g. “pimpscape” then scroll down and click “create host”.</p>
<p>Once you are at this stage you now need to download the no-ip DUC setup.<br>
Simply click “downloads” at the top of the page, then select your format, e.g. windows. Then click download on the next page and save the file.</p>
<p>Once you have downloaded all you need to do is log in the new window using the same details you use on <a href="http://www.no-ip.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.no-ip.com</a></p>
<p>Then once you are logged in you need to check the box next to your host name/ no-ip. e.g. pimpscape.no-ip.info<br>
When you see a smiley face  your up, your ip is forwarded to that ip address and people can connect to your server using that ip address.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Hosting on hamachi: </span></p>
<p>Go to: www.hamachi.cc</p>
<p>This is one is shorter and alot easier, when you are on www.hamachi.cc all you need to do is click “download free” in the left hand side navigation bar.</p>
<p>At this point you do not need to enter your details, just click “go to list of files” (at the bottom).</p>
<p>Then select a format, e.g. windows and under that format click “Download”.<br>
Then save the file and run.</p>
<p>Once you have downloaded hamchi, you need to create a nickname for yourself, e.g. pimp</p>
<p>Then click the “power on button” (bottom left) and then to host your server on hamchi click “join or create host” in the bottom right corner, first button.</p>
<p>Then just enter the name of your server e.g. pimpscape, then a password, other people can now join your network and join you server along this connection.</p>
<h1>=====================================<br>
If you are still having problems, feel free to pm me.</h1>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-you-host/72793/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-you-host/72793/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 03:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72793-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-you-host/72793.rss">How do you host?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How do you host?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fROMOHIO6 fROMOHIO6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fromohio6">@fROMOHIO6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well i wanted to know if anyone could tell me how to host a server? Can you tell me or give me a link to a guide? thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-you-host/72793/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-you-host/72793/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 03:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-72793-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/how-do-you-host/72793.rss">How do you host?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
