<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Distro Watch</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190</link>
    <description>Well, this section doesn&#39;t get alot of stuff other than questions and help topics, I thought we could bring some intelligent discussion to this board since generally only people with a brain will be able to use Linux based operating systems.

I thought we could have our own little distro watch and discussion thread. Spice it up with a bit of a debate, but no ridiculous flame. Should be interesting to see what other people use and why it&#39;s the right thing for them. New users will find it helpful if they&#39;re looking for a new OS and current users will find some hopefully well reviewed alternatives. We&#39;re not looking for HUGE posts, just say what needs to be said. Feel free to link to images of your desktop, but don&#39;t post the full image into this thread, only a link- please.

Personally, I have tried a variety of *unix operating systems. I wanted something simple and is easy to maintain, I wasn&#39;t bothered about too much customization but I wanted it to look just right. I&#39;ve tried all the *ubuntu except the new Gobuntu. I&#39;ve also used openSuse, freeBSD and simplyMepis. I didn&#39;t particularly like any except for Kubuntu. Now, Thug-life pointed me in the direction of Sabayon a little while ago, it&#39;s a very large gentoo based OS that is filled with huge amounts of preloaded software and games. (It comes on a 3.7GB DVD). For me, it was too bloated, I haven&#39;t tried the mini version but I probably will do so soon. The thing about Sabayon was it seemed to concentrated on eyecandy and not enough on functionality. 

I now use Kubuntu on my main computer (with XP as dual boot) and Arch Linux on my old computer. Kubuntu has everything needed for new users to easily understand and for more experienced uses to customize. I Have Arch Linux because there is no fancy easy to use GUIs and everything must be done properly often on the command line - I wanted to try something &quot;real&quot; Linux users use (from Kamu). It&#39;s more difficult and requires experience, but with the help of Mopman, I got it running quite quick and found it to be very slick. I would not however recommend it at all for anyone with less than a few months experience of Linux Operating systems.

*I&#39;ll add more got college now*</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2007 01:05:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Distro Watch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fasga Fasga]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fasga">@Fasga</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have been using Arch Linux full-time for the past two years, and it has worked perfectly for me.  The Arch philosophy follows KISS, but not in the form that it provides easy ways to do everything.  In this sense, KISS more means that it gets rid of all the easy-to-use front-ends.  This essentially makes it easier to get into the actual configuration files and modify things to do exactly what you want them to do.</p>
<p>When you first install Arch Linux, you’ll probably only be confronted with a blank terminal, which allows you to build up your system to be capable of exactly what you want it to do, and nothing more.  This seems to be quite the opposite of Sabayon, which, as you pointed out, installs everything automatically, seemingly bloating your system.  This, in my opinion, speeds up productivity and overall performance.</p>
<p>The Arch package manager, pacman, follows the same philosophy as the rest of the system.  Although there are 3rd party GUI front-ends which a few people prefer to use, pacman itself is a terminal based application.  This contributes to the Arch philosophy that users should have the freedom of choice.  By only providing the very baseline of what you need to install and remove packages easily, it allows you to build up what you really want it to do.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2007 01:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156190-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190.rss">Distro Watch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Distro Watch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Anyway, i have been trying out  ubuntu server edition on my ‘server’, and i must say it is, honestly pretty good especially (like the Desktop edition) good for newer people to linux.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 22:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156190-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190.rss">Distro Watch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Distro Watch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@voiD_dev voiD dev]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/void_dev">@voiD_dev</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ThugLife, post:4, topic:156190”][quote author=voiD dev link=topic=213109.msg1864024#msg1864024 date=1194108819]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Sabayon functions just the same as gentoo, just that Sabayon is for people who like lots of “eye candy”, and tons of programs you don’t need or will ever use pre-installed and configured.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Many distros can just be personalized. Besides who just uses a distro for eye-candy. Pre-installed programs, might be a waste of space. Unless you always use them.</p>
<p>Just my opinion.<br>
[/quote]<br>
The main reason i installed sabayon is because it saved me a whole lot of time, because quite a few of the programs pre-installed i already use.[/quote]<br>
Then it is for you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 05:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156190-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190.rss">Distro Watch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Distro Watch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“voiD dev, post:3, topic:156190”][quote author=ThugLife link=topic=213109.msg1861562#msg1861562 date=1194025925]<br>
Sabayon functions just the same as gentoo, just that Sabayon is for people who like lots of “eye candy”, and tons of programs you don’t need or will ever use pre-installed and configured.</p>
<p>[/quote]<br>
Many distros can just be personalized. Besides who just uses a distro for eye-candy. Pre-installed programs, might be a waste of space. Unless you always use them.</p>
<p>Just my opinion.[/quote]<br>
The main reason i installed sabayon is because it saved me a whole lot of time, because quite a few of the programs pre-installed i already use.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 17:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156190-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190.rss">Distro Watch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Distro Watch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@voiD_dev voiD dev]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/void_dev">@voiD_dev</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="156190">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ThugLife:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sabayon functions just the same as gentoo, just that Sabayon is for people who like lots of “eye candy”, and tons of programs you don’t need or will ever use pre-installed and configured.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Many distros can just be personalized. Besides who just uses a distro for eye-candy. Pre-installed programs, might be a waste of space. Unless you always use them.</p>
<p>Just my opinion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 16:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156190-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190.rss">Distro Watch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Distro Watch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sabayon functions just the same as gentoo, just that Sabayon is for people who like lots of “eye candy”, and tons of programs you don’t need or will ever use pre-installed and configured.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2007 17:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156190-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190.rss">Distro Watch</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Distro Watch</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Greeny Greeny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/greeny">@Greeny</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, this section doesn’t get alot of stuff other than questions and help topics, I thought we could bring some intelligent discussion to this board since generally only people with a brain will be able to use Linux based operating systems.</p>
<p>I thought we could have our own little distro watch and discussion thread. Spice it up with a bit of a debate, but no ridiculous flame. Should be interesting to see what other people use and why it’s the right thing for them. New users will find it helpful if they’re looking for a new OS and current users will find some hopefully well reviewed alternatives. We’re not looking for HUGE posts, just say what needs to be said. Feel free to link to images of your desktop, but don’t post the full image into this thread, only a link- please.</p>
<p>Personally, I have tried a variety of *unix operating systems. I wanted something simple and is easy to maintain, I wasn’t bothered about too much customization but I wanted it to look just right. I’ve tried all the *ubuntu except the new Gobuntu. I’ve also used openSuse, freeBSD and simplyMepis. I didn’t particularly like any except for Kubuntu. Now, Thug-life pointed me in the direction of Sabayon a little while ago, it’s a very large gentoo based OS that is filled with huge amounts of preloaded software and games. (It comes on a 3.7GB DVD). For me, it was too bloated, I haven’t tried the mini version but I probably will do so soon. The thing about Sabayon was it seemed to concentrated on eyecandy and not enough on functionality.</p>
<p>I now use Kubuntu on my main computer (with XP as dual boot) and Arch Linux on my old computer. Kubuntu has everything needed for new users to easily understand and for more experienced uses to customize. I Have Arch Linux because there is no fancy easy to use GUIs and everything must be done properly often on the command line - I wanted to try something “real” Linux users use (from Kamu). It’s more difficult and requires experience, but with the help of Mopman, I got it running quite quick and found it to be very slick. I would not however recommend it at all for anyone with less than a few months experience of Linux Operating systems.</p>
<p><em>I’ll add more got college now</em></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2007 14:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-156190-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/distro-watch/156190.rss">Distro Watch</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
