<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Winamp eggs</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winamp-eggs/13284</link>
    <description>http://www.eeggs.com/tree/555.html

Winamp - Fun with Beats 
[code]Egg 1: With the defualt (Modern) skin chosen stretch the main window until the Beat Analyzer (it says &quot;beat&quot; under it) appears. Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and Click the Center of the beat analyzer. Now put on a song with fast beats and loud bass. (My suggestion would be &quot;Insane in the Brain&quot;) 
Egg 2: Type &quot;nullsoft&quot; in the main window. Since L is a shortcut key to open a file it is neccesary to pres &quot;esc&quot; after both L&#39;s. So you&#39;re really typing 
N-U-L-(esc)-L-(esc)-s-o-f-t. Now put on a song with fast beats and loud bass and enjoy the effect. 
If it doesn&#39;t work for you and you&#39;re interested in what each does: 
Egg 1: Replaces the beat analyzer with 2 llamas that head bang to the beats. 
Egg 2: Changes to opacity of winamp with the beats.[/code]

Winamp - Flashing Winamp 
[code]1. Right click on any audio file 
2. Select open with 
3. Select Winamp 
4. Winamp will open, click play 
5. The Main window flashes to the beat of the music [/code] 

Winamp - Funny messages 
[code]This one is easy. First, make sure you are using the Winamp Modern skin. Next, play a music file in Winamp that makes the &quot;Artist Biography&quot; feature pop up. It is on the very bottom. Now, wait about two or three cycles and a message saying things like &quot;My stepmother was bitten by a llama once&quot; or &quot;Nothing to see here, move along&quot;. See what YOU can find![/code]

Winamp - Funky Llama Background in Credits Screen 
[code]First of all open up Winamp&#39;s &quot;About Winamp&quot; dialogue by clicking right button on the titlebar and clicking &quot;Nullsoft Winamp...&quot; 
Click on the &quot;Credits&quot; tab, see the nice spinning display with a ball floating around the screen, cool eh? Well we can make the walls look funkier too. Hold down CTRL+SHIFT and double click on the animated area with the RIGHT mouse button; 
This display will go full screen with the texture of the ball (the Llama image) and the texture of the wall (gray checkerboard) reversed revealing a quite cool looking display. 
If you repeat the above process while in this full screen view it will revert back to normal windowed display with the textures still changed. 
PS. The display motion is subject to which visualisation you have active, if you have the bar graph style display the rings will mimic each one of the bars, if you have the oscilloscope visualisation active then the light ball will throb in size and brightness in time to the music. [/code] 
[size=38pt][font=Verdana]Enjoy! [/font] [/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 19:29:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winamp-eggs/13284.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Winamp eggs</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@creator_1992 creator_1992]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/creator_1992">@creator_1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://www.eeggs.com/tree/555.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.eeggs.com/tree/555.html</a></p>
<p>Winamp - Fun with Beats</p>
<p><code>Egg 1: With the defualt (Modern) skin chosen stretch the main window until the Beat Analyzer (it says "beat" under it) appears. Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and Click the Center of the beat analyzer. Now put on a song with fast beats and loud bass. (My suggestion would be "Insane in the Brain") 
Egg 2: Type "nullsoft" in the main window. Since L is a shortcut key to open a file it is neccesary to pres "esc" after both L's. So you're really typing 
N-U-L-(esc)-L-(esc)-s-o-f-t. Now put on a song with fast beats and loud bass and enjoy the effect. 
If it doesn't work for you and you're interested in what each does: 
Egg 1: Replaces the beat analyzer with 2 llamas that head bang to the beats. 
Egg 2: Changes to opacity of winamp with the beats.</code></p>
<p>Winamp - Flashing Winamp</p>
<p><code>1. Right click on any audio file 
2. Select open with 
3. Select Winamp 
4. Winamp will open, click play 
5. The Main window flashes to the beat of the music </code></p>
<p>Winamp - Funny messages</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">This one is easy. First, make sure you are using the Winamp Modern skin. Next, play a music file in Winamp that makes the "Artist Biography" feature pop up. It is on the very bottom. Now, wait about two or three cycles and a message saying things like "My stepmother was bitten by a llama once" or "Nothing to see here, move along". See what YOU can find!</code></pre>
<p>Winamp - Funky Llama Background in Credits Screen</p>
<p><code>First of all open up Winamp's "About Winamp" dialogue by clicking right button on the titlebar and clicking "Nullsoft Winamp..." 
Click on the "Credits" tab, see the nice spinning display with a ball floating around the screen, cool eh? Well we can make the walls look funkier too. Hold down CTRL+SHIFT and double click on the animated area with the RIGHT mouse button; 
This display will go full screen with the texture of the ball (the Llama image) and the texture of the wall (gray checkerboard) reversed revealing a quite cool looking display. 
If you repeat the above process while in this full screen view it will revert back to normal windowed display with the textures still changed. 
PS. The display motion is subject to which visualisation you have active, if you have the bar graph style display the rings will mimic each one of the bars, if you have the oscilloscope visualisation active then the light ball will throb in size and brightness in time to the music. </code><br>
[size=38pt][font=Verdana]Enjoy! [/font] [/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winamp-eggs/13284/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winamp-eggs/13284/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 19:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13284-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/winamp-eggs/13284.rss">Winamp eggs</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
