<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Coordinates of objects via client, what&#39;s the method?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coordinates-of-objects-via-client-whats-the-method/331731</link>
    <description>I need the method that contains the x and y coordinates of the objects because I&#39;m trying to make it so when you right click on an object, it shows you the object id and the coordinates of that object. I currently have the object id, but I can&#39;t seem to find what it is that stores the coordinates. I&#39;m not talking about a makeGlobalObject thing. I mean objects in the servers set by default via the client. Like the statue of saradomin in the middle of falador center. I know that&#39;s spawned through the client, but where can I find the coords?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 00:10:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coordinates-of-objects-via-client-whats-the-method/331731.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Coordinates of objects via client, what&#39;s the method?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@runefreak10 runefreak10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/runefreak10">@runefreak10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I need the method that contains the x and y coordinates of the objects because I’m trying to make it so when you right click on an object, it shows you the object id and the coordinates of that object. I currently have the object id, but I can’t seem to find what it is that stores the coordinates. I’m not talking about a makeGlobalObject thing. I mean objects in the servers set by default via the client. Like the statue of saradomin in the middle of falador center. I know that’s spawned through the client, but where can I find the coords?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coordinates-of-objects-via-client-whats-the-method/331731/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coordinates-of-objects-via-client-whats-the-method/331731/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 00:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-331731-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/coordinates-of-objects-via-client-whats-the-method/331731.rss">Coordinates of objects via client, what&#39;s the method?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
