<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>JynxCraft [24/7][Survival] 1.2.5</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jynxcraft-24-7-survival-1-2-5/444853</link>
    <description>
[IMG]http://i229.photobucket.com/albums/ee251/alord123/JynxCraftBannercopy.jpg[/img]

JynxCraft is a survival/build server. We are whitelisted, and for a good reason. Most of the time we are going to be looking for griefers, because we know a lot of you minecraft players love to ruin fun for others *wink wink*.

Most servers these days have so many plugins, and so many game altering mods that it doesn&#39;t even feel like minecraft anymore! The point of this server is to have minecraft be multiplayer, but still feel like minecraft. Build as you would usually, kill monsters as you would usually, except you have a friend or two with you. Just how minecraft multiplayer was intended to be!

We have our own way to deal with players on this server. There is a station in every town that is made that allows players to safely trade without interruptions, or having the other player able to steal from the other.. If you want to decline the trade, you can cancel it and get your items back.

If you want your home regioned, that way we REALLY don&#39;t have to worry about somebody griefing your building, we have world guard so it won&#39;t be any problem ;). 

As you can tell, keeping the game original is VERY important to us! And we believe our server will be entertaining to people because most servers have so many plugins, you don&#39;t even know where to begin.

If you are interested in the server, you can visit our forums at: http://jynxcraft.x10.mx/index.php and get even more details on what we are about.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:57:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jynxcraft-24-7-survival-1-2-5/444853.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>JynxCraft [24/7][Survival] 1.2.5</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jynxcraft jynxcraft]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jynxcraft">@jynxcraft</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://i229.photobucket.com/albums/ee251/alord123/JynxCraftBannercopy.jpg" alt width="468" height="60"></p>
<p>JynxCraft is a survival/build server. We are whitelisted, and for a good reason. Most of the time we are going to be looking for griefers, because we know a lot of you minecraft players love to ruin fun for others <em>wink wink</em>.</p>
<p>Most servers these days have so many plugins, and so many game altering mods that it doesn’t even feel like minecraft anymore! The point of this server is to have minecraft be multiplayer, but still feel like minecraft. Build as you would usually, kill monsters as you would usually, except you have a friend or two with you. Just how minecraft multiplayer was intended to be!</p>
<p>We have our own way to deal with players on this server. There is a station in every town that is made that allows players to safely trade without interruptions, or having the other player able to steal from the other… If you want to decline the trade, you can cancel it and get your items back.</p>
<p>If you want your home regioned, that way we REALLY don’t have to worry about somebody griefing your building, we have world guard so it won’t be any problem ;).</p>
<p>As you can tell, keeping the game original is VERY important to us! And we believe our server will be entertaining to people because most servers have so many plugins, you don’t even know where to begin.</p>
<p>If you are interested in the server, you can visit our forums at: <a href="http://jynxcraft.x10.mx/index.php" rel="nofollow noopener">http://jynxcraft.x10.mx/index.php</a> and get even more details on what we are about.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jynxcraft-24-7-survival-1-2-5/444853/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jynxcraft-24-7-survival-1-2-5/444853/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-444853-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/jynxcraft-24-7-survival-1-2-5/444853.rss">JynxCraft [24/7][Survival] 1.2.5</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
