<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>*new!* moparscape servers not connecting? genius tells you all about it!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-moparscape-servers-not-connecting-genius-tells-you-all-about-it/49701</link>
    <description>[b]Hey, Brian Rivera, I downloaded so many things from MoparScape, and yet, the servers are still offline, or down. Why is that?[/b]
 
 
Firstly, I would like to thank you for your generous capability to e-mail me, as you know, I will always guarrantee perfection to its point!
 
On a computer, files and folders are being shared, when you upload photos on the internet, your computer is relying on some source to maintain that image on the web and not send it by micro-scamming into others&#39; e-mails and spam filters. Therefore, internet servers cannot provide a massive amount of protection due to its capability of providing you with internet. Servers and online registration bases may vary due to your internet and your internet connection, leaving you with unconnected software.
 
MoparScape runs with Java, with Java downloaded, you will have a mass transit of files and folders being stored into your computer, making it more reliable to run Java software. If server status appears to be offline or down, it obviously means your computer program for Java isn&#39;t capable of running any scripts of files, your internet is low on capacity, OR your computer is trying to maintain your photos up on the web from past times uploading and is using up disk space fragments that runs on Java.
 
[b]YOUR SOLUTION: Do whatever it takes to delete any OLD Java software, delete pictures you have on the web, try to get better internet connection, run MoparScape gently and not pouty(aggressively) and most important, &quot;Trust your computer&quot;...give it a NAME![/b]

Guarranteed to work, for any questions, contact me at the forums: [b]brian772cool[/b].

If you have no idea what I just concluded, please contact Moparscape, the MoparScape administrator.
 
 
---Thank you! 
                                              Brian Rivera</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 11:06:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-moparscape-servers-not-connecting-genius-tells-you-all-about-it/49701.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>*new!* moparscape servers not connecting? genius tells you all about it!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@South_Of_Heaven South Of Heaven]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/south_of_heaven">@South_Of_Heaven</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>or maybe your internet is not connected and maybe the servers are just down and it happens all the time. 1 server down an other an’t</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-moparscape-servers-not-connecting-genius-tells-you-all-about-it/49701/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-moparscape-servers-not-connecting-genius-tells-you-all-about-it/49701/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 11:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-49701-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-moparscape-servers-not-connecting-genius-tells-you-all-about-it/49701.rss">*new!* moparscape servers not connecting? genius tells you all about it!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>*new!* moparscape servers not connecting? genius tells you all about it!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@brian772cool brian772cool]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/brian772cool">@brian772cool</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Hey, Brian Rivera, I downloaded so many things from MoparScape, and yet, the servers are still offline, or down. Why is that?</span></p>
<p>Firstly, I would like to thank you for your generous capability to e-mail me, as you know, I will always guarrantee perfection to its point!</p>
<p>On a computer, files and folders are being shared, when you upload photos on the internet, your computer is relying on some source to maintain that image on the web and not send it by micro-scamming into others’ e-mails and spam filters. Therefore, internet servers cannot provide a massive amount of protection due to its capability of providing you with internet. Servers and online registration bases may vary due to your internet and your internet connection, leaving you with unconnected software.</p>
<p>MoparScape runs with Java, with Java downloaded, you will have a mass transit of files and folders being stored into your computer, making it more reliable to run Java software. If server status appears to be offline or down, it obviously means your computer program for Java isn’t capable of running any scripts of files, your internet is low on capacity, OR your computer is trying to maintain your photos up on the web from past times uploading and is using up disk space fragments that runs on Java.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">YOUR SOLUTION: Do whatever it takes to delete any OLD Java software, delete pictures you have on the web, try to get better internet connection, run MoparScape gently and not pouty(aggressively) and most important, “Trust your computer”…give it a NAME!</span></p>
<p>Guarranteed to work, for any questions, contact me at the forums: <span class="bbcode-b">brian772cool</span>.</p>
<p>If you have no idea what I just concluded, please contact Moparscape, the MoparScape administrator.</p>
<p>—Thank you!<br>
Brian Rivera</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-moparscape-servers-not-connecting-genius-tells-you-all-about-it/49701/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-moparscape-servers-not-connecting-genius-tells-you-all-about-it/49701/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2007 20:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-49701-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-moparscape-servers-not-connecting-genius-tells-you-all-about-it/49701.rss">*new!* moparscape servers not connecting? genius tells you all about it!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
