<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Green Mile (film)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677</link>
    <description>Wikipedia
&lt;blockquote&gt;The Green Mile is a story told in flashback by an elderly Paul Edgecomb (Dabbs Greer, later by Tom Hanks in the younger version of the character) in a nursing home who is talking to his friend Elaine about the summer of 1935 when he was a corrections officer in charge of Death Row inmates in Louisiana&#39;s Cold Mountain Penitentiary. His domain was called the &quot;Green Mile&quot; because the condemned prisoners walking to their execution are said to be walking &quot;the last mile&quot;; here, it is a stretch of green linoleum to the electric chair.
One day, a new inmate arrives, John Coffey (Michael Clarke Duncan), a &quot;giant&quot; black man convicted of raping and killing two young white girls. Upon being escorted to his cell, he immediately demonstrates &quot;gentle giant&quot; character traits: keeping to himself, fearing darkness, and being moved to tears on occasion. Soon enough, John reveals extraordinary healing powers by healing Paul&#39;s urinary tract infection and resurrecting a mouse. Later, he would heal the terminally-ill wife of Warden Hal Moores (James Cromwell), who suffered from a large brain tumor. When John is asked to explain his power, he merely says that he &quot;took it back.&quot;
At the same time, Percy Wetmore (Doug Hutchison), a sadistic and unpopular guard, starts work. He &quot;knows people, big people&quot; (he is the nephew of the governor&#39;s wife), in effect preventing Paul or anybody else from doing anything significant to curb his behavior. Percy recognizes that the other officers greatly dislike him and uses that to demand managing the next execution. After that, he promises, he will have himself transferred to an administrative post at Briar Ridge Mental Hospital and Paul will never hear from him again. An agreement is made, but Percy then deliberately sabotages the execution. Instead of wetting the sponge used to conduct electricity, he leaves it dry, causing excruciating pain to Eduard &quot;Del&quot; Delacroix (Michael Jeter).
Shortly before Del&#39;s execution, a violent prisoner named William &quot;Wild Bill&quot; Wharton (Sam Rockwell) arrives, due to be executed for multiple murders committed during a robbery. At one point he seizes John&#39;s arm and John psychically senses that Wharton is the true killer of the two girls, the crime for which John was wrongly convicted and sentenced to death. John &quot;takes back&quot; the sickness in Hal&#39;s wife and regurgitates it into Percy, who then shoots Wharton to death and falls into a permanent catatonic state. Percy is then housed in the Briar Ridge Mental Hospital. In the wake of these events, Paul interrogates John, who says he &quot;punished them bad men&quot; and offers to show Paul what he saw. John takes Paul&#39;s hand stating that he has to give Paul &quot;a part of himself&quot; in order to see and imparts the visions of what he saw, of what really happened to the girls.
Paul asks John what he should do, if he should open the door and let John walk away. John tells him no, he is ready to go because here there is too much pain in the world, which he can feel, and that he is &quot;rightly tired of the pain&quot; and is ready to rest. When John is put in the electric chair, he asks Paul not to put the traditional black hood over his head because he is afraid of the dark. Paul agrees and after Paul shakes his hand, John is executed. As the flashback ends, Paul notes that he requested a transfer to a youth detention center, where he spent the remainder of his career.
In the present, Paul&#39;s friend questions his statement that he had a fully-grown son in 1935. He explains that he was 44 years old at the time of John&#39;s execution and that he is now 108 and still in excellent health. This is apparently a side effect of John giving a &quot;part of himself&quot; to Paul. Mr. Jingles, Del&#39;s mouse resurrected by John, is also still alive — but Paul believes his outliving all of his relatives and friends to be a punishment from God for having John executed. Paul explains he has deep thoughts about how &quot;we each owe a death; there are no exceptions; but, Oh God, sometimes the Green Mile seems so long.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

I kind of shattered a tear drop or six while watching it. Very sad story. Its boring at the start but kicks off when the guys in death row. The movie is actually better than it sounds.

Please no bad comments.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 01:39:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Green Mile (film)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr_Mopar1 Mr Mopar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_mopar1">@Mr_Mopar1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="326677">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/telenim/40/3922_1.png" class="avatar"> Telenim:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>seen</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and[quote=“casey., post:3, topic:326677”]old movie[/quote]<br>
but i liked it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 01:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326677-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677.rss">The Green Mile (film)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Green Mile (film)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="326677">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 `Aaron:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Didn’t like it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 18:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326677-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677.rss">The Green Mile (film)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Green Mile (film)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n33bz0rpl0x `Aaron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n33bz0rpl0x">@n33bz0rpl0x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Didn’t like it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 17:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326677-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677.rss">The Green Mile (film)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Green Mile (film)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@gothic_queen casey.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/gothic_queen">@gothic_queen</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>old movie</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 17:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326677-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677.rss">The Green Mile (film)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Green Mile (film)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Telenim Telenim]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/telenim">@Telenim</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>seen</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 14:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326677-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677.rss">The Green Mile (film)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Green Mile (film)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wikipedia</p>
<blockquote>The Green Mile is a story told in flashback by an elderly Paul Edgecomb (Dabbs Greer, later by Tom Hanks in the younger version of the character) in a nursing home who is talking to his friend Elaine about the summer of 1935 when he was a corrections officer in charge of Death Row inmates in Louisiana's Cold Mountain Penitentiary. His domain was called the "Green Mile" because the condemned prisoners walking to their execution are said to be walking "the last mile"; here, it is a stretch of green linoleum to the electric chair.
One day, a new inmate arrives, John Coffey (Michael Clarke Duncan), a "giant" black man convicted of raping and killing two young white girls. Upon being escorted to his cell, he immediately demonstrates "gentle giant" character traits: keeping to himself, fearing darkness, and being moved to tears on occasion. Soon enough, John reveals extraordinary healing powers by healing Paul's urinary tract infection and resurrecting a mouse. Later, he would heal the terminally-ill wife of Warden Hal Moores (James Cromwell), who suffered from a large brain tumor. When John is asked to explain his power, he merely says that he "took it back."
At the same time, Percy Wetmore (Doug Hutchison), a sadistic and unpopular guard, starts work. He "knows people, big people" (he is the nephew of the governor's wife), in effect preventing Paul or anybody else from doing anything significant to curb his behavior. Percy recognizes that the other officers greatly dislike him and uses that to demand managing the next execution. After that, he promises, he will have himself transferred to an administrative post at Briar Ridge Mental Hospital and Paul will never hear from him again. An agreement is made, but Percy then deliberately sabotages the execution. Instead of wetting the sponge used to conduct electricity, he leaves it dry, causing excruciating pain to Eduard "Del" Delacroix (Michael Jeter).
Shortly before Del's execution, a violent prisoner named William "Wild Bill" Wharton (Sam Rockwell) arrives, due to be executed for multiple murders committed during a robbery. At one point he seizes John's arm and John psychically senses that Wharton is the true killer of the two girls, the crime for which John was wrongly convicted and sentenced to death. John "takes back" the sickness in Hal's wife and regurgitates it into Percy, who then shoots Wharton to death and falls into a permanent catatonic state. Percy is then housed in the Briar Ridge Mental Hospital. In the wake of these events, Paul interrogates John, who says he "punished them bad men" and offers to show Paul what he saw. John takes Paul's hand stating that he has to give Paul "a part of himself" in order to see and imparts the visions of what he saw, of what really happened to the girls.
Paul asks John what he should do, if he should open the door and let John walk away. John tells him no, he is ready to go because here there is too much pain in the world, which he can feel, and that he is "rightly tired of the pain" and is ready to rest. When John is put in the electric chair, he asks Paul not to put the traditional black hood over his head because he is afraid of the dark. Paul agrees and after Paul shakes his hand, John is executed. As the flashback ends, Paul notes that he requested a transfer to a youth detention center, where he spent the remainder of his career.
In the present, Paul's friend questions his statement that he had a fully-grown son in 1935. He explains that he was 44 years old at the time of John's execution and that he is now 108 and still in excellent health. This is apparently a side effect of John giving a "part of himself" to Paul. Mr. Jingles, Del's mouse resurrected by John, is also still alive — but Paul believes his outliving all of his relatives and friends to be a punishment from God for having John executed. Paul explains he has deep thoughts about how "we each owe a death; there are no exceptions; but, Oh God, sometimes the Green Mile seems so long."</blockquote>
<p>I kind of shattered a tear drop or six while watching it. Very sad story. Its boring at the start but kicks off when the guys in death row. The movie is actually better than it sounds.</p>
<p>Please no bad comments.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 14:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-326677-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-green-mile-film/326677.rss">The Green Mile (film)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
