<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>614 Server Help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-server-help/361354</link>
    <description>Okay, so several weeks ago, I downloaded and started coding on a 562 server base (http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,435936.0.html). I think it&#39;s rs2hd. However, I really enjoy the 614 graphics a lot more than the 562 ones, so here&#39;s my question: is it possible to convert a 562 server into a 614 server, and if so, where would I start?

I&#39;m not expecting a full step-by-step tutorial on how to do this. I just want some advice on where I could start. Also, I&#39;m trying my hardest not to have to download an already coded 614 server because the server I&#39;ve been working on has A LOT of custom coding and its structure is very easy to work with.

I know I&#39;ll have to change packet IDs, packet information, etc., etc, but if there is any advice anyone could give me, it&#39;d be awesome  :).

Here&#39;s the 614 client I think I&#39;ll be using if I can successfully do this: http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,453927.0.html</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 22:00:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-server-help/361354.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>614 Server Help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_Realm Project Realm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_realm">@Project_Realm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay, so several weeks ago, I downloaded and started coding on a 562 server base (<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,435936.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,435936.0.html</a>). I think it’s rs2hd. However, I really enjoy the 614 graphics a lot more than the 562 ones, so here’s my question: is it possible to convert a 562 server into a 614 server, and if so, where would I start?</p>
<p>I’m not expecting a full step-by-step tutorial on how to do this. I just want some advice on where I could start. Also, I’m trying my hardest not to have to download an already coded 614 server because the server I’ve been working on has A LOT of custom coding and its structure is very easy to work with.</p>
<p>I know I’ll have to change packet IDs, packet information, etc., etc, but if there is any advice anyone could give me, it’d be awesome  :).</p>
<p>Here’s the 614 client I think I’ll be using if I can successfully do this: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,453927.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,453927.0.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-server-help/361354/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-server-help/361354/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 22:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-361354-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/614-server-help/361354.rss">614 Server Help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
