<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dusting it off</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dusting-it-off/352042</link>
    <description>For the most part, I&#39;ve personally removed a number of locked threads that have served little to no purpose on the forum. I&#39;ve also removed a lot of useless threads that haven&#39;t been locked. And as for active-useless threads, I&#39;ve only locked them to let users know the reason. I will later remove those when I have time.

For the future, the staff encourages everyone to read over the rules of each section. This ESPECIALLY goes for the [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html]Server Tutorials[/url], [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,125.0.html]Server Development[/url], and [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,149.0.html]Development Team[/url] categories. The rules in each of these sections have been ignored tremendously, and I have no doubt that a majority of the users have never even looked at the rules in those sections.

So, enjoy the somewhat cleaned forum. We&#39;ll never completely clean everything, but we always try our best.

- Moparscape Staff</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 22:02:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dusting-it-off/352042.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Dusting it off</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Reaper_X The Reaper X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_reaper_x">@The_Reaper_X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For the most part, I’ve personally removed a number of locked threads that have served little to no purpose on the forum. I’ve also removed a lot of useless threads that haven’t been locked. And as for active-useless threads, I’ve only locked them to let users know the reason. I will later remove those when I have time.</p>
<p>For the future, the staff encourages everyone to read over the rules of each section. This ESPECIALLY goes for the <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,51.0.html" data-bbcode="true">Server Tutorials</a>, <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,125.0.html" data-bbcode="true">Server Development</a>, and <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,149.0.html" data-bbcode="true">Development Team</a> categories. The rules in each of these sections have been ignored tremendously, and I have no doubt that a majority of the users have never even looked at the rules in those sections.</p>
<p>So, enjoy the somewhat cleaned forum. We’ll never completely clean everything, but we always try our best.</p>
<ul>
<li>Moparscape Staff</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dusting-it-off/352042/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dusting-it-off/352042/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 22:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-352042-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/dusting-it-off/352042.rss">Dusting it off</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
