<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>User Submission - Uncalled</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027</link>
    <description>Relaying a private message sent to me by Uncalled, leave feedback and opinions below.
[hr]
Okay, so the first one: Why did I decide to rejoin the forums?

Well, I decided to rejoin these forums for multiple different reasons. I mean, I&#39;ve been with the community for a good amount of time, and I&#39;ve made some great friends along the way. I get along with most of the community, so I don&#39;t see a reason why I left in the first place. I figured that even if I wasn&#39;t in RuneScape emulation at the time, I could still just stay around for whatever discussion was running about in the forums. I&#39;ve also left once before this, but again, was lured back. I expected this to happen, really. I guess I could say that I missed some of you guys, so I decided randomly that I was going to log back in once more.


Another idea:
In the Mopar Monthly, you could add the top five most noticeable new members, possibly(?) potential staff - based off of other&#39;s opinions, and try to make it a little more community-based. If more of the community was involved with the rankings, then the more would read it, perhaps.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 14:06:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Suggestions</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>User Submission - Uncalled</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="521027">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Flame_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote]As for the “notable newcomer” section, I think that we could maybe have a section mentioning a newcomer who has really “shined” in the month, although I’m not sure it should be a section we strive to fill every month.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What a lot of readers have told me that they liked was that the whole ‘Shout-out and Nominations’ concept would ultimately help to increase or at the very minimum spark some activity within the contributing and helping side of the forums. This sort of category would be seen as getting new members to join and start contributing once they’re comfortable in the community, which is good to see. With your point on not striving to fill it every month, we have the option to alternate between a limitless number of sections that are pertaining to user nomination. To have this category would be helpful in singling out only one or two users, which I see as less needed than the Helpful Users category. Perhaps if we set up guidelines for what deems a user as an overall great contributor then we could find use for a category like this. Until then though it seems to me like a category that only gives a thank-you to one user, which isn’t what I am aiming for.[/quote]<br>
It’s unlikely for a new user to come around and start helping users, because people don’t really trust the advice given unless it’s from a reputable source. I think that having an award specifically targeted for “new members” could be a way to motivate them into getting themselves known in the community (for the right reasons) whether that’s through just becoming a part of the discussions in the debates section and giving good viewpoints, writing tutorials and snippets, or working on a development, but it will encourage new members (who may otherwise be less likely to get another award because of the size of the community and the point about how their information will be disregarded) to try for an award.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 14:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521027-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027.rss">User Submission - Uncalled</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>User Submission - Uncalled</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>As for the "notable newcomer" section, I think that we could maybe have a section mentioning a newcomer who has really "shined" in the month, although I'm not sure it should be a section we strive to fill every month.</blockquote>
What a lot of readers have told me that they liked was that the whole 'Shout-out and Nominations' concept would ultimately help to increase or at the very minimum spark some activity within the contributing and helping side of the forums. This sort of category would be seen as getting new members to join and start contributing once they're comfortable in the community, which is good to see. With your point on not striving to fill it every month, we have the option to alternate between a limitless number of sections that are pertaining to user nomination. To have this category would be helpful in singling out only one or two users, which I see as less needed than the Helpful Users category. Perhaps if we set up guidelines for what deems a user as an overall great contributor then we could find use for a category like this. Until then though it seems to me like a category that only gives a thank-you to one user, which isn't what I am aiming for.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 04:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521027-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027.rss">User Submission - Uncalled</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>User Submission - Uncalled</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="521027">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Flame_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Uncalled has been requested as an interview candidate by Loveandpower last week, yet I never got around to replying to him. I agree that Uncalled’s answers are straightforward, yet the concept behind the interview is to interview users who have contributed large amounts to the community. Quite frankly - and although this may be because I’m relatively new - I haven’t seen Uncalled do anything more than start a development and create a few decent looking graphics.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah, I agree. I have seen him around but I haven’t seen him do anything big or surprising, really.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="521027">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Flame_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I don’t support this idea for potential staff. With my new position it could easily be misinterpreted as me revealing private discussion, as well as it not being our place to publicly nominate users on a homepage that represents the name of the forums. I feel that we already cover the ‘Notable whatever’ in the varying sections of ‘Most Helpful Members,’ ‘Best Tutorials,’ and others that give users their own chance in the spotlight. If we wish to congratulate a site member for doing some notable, then we will reserve a small paragraph to explain what they’ve done and to congratulate them for it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree, and it’d also be unfair if we mentioned a user’s chance for promotion, they got excited and then it never materialised into anything - this would have a larger effect than if it was just a passing comment from another user because it’s on the main page of the forums and it is, in a sense, official.<br>
As for the “notable newcomer” section, I think that we could maybe have a section mentioning a newcomer who has really “shined” in the month, although I’m not sure it should be a section we strive to fill every month.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="3" data-topic="521027">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Flame_:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>May I get your opinion(s) on the blog post that he submitted (the part where he decides to rejoin the forums)? Overall I find it too bland, there needs to be more meat to it. With the right amount of work I can see this post turning into a nicely sized paragraph that is interesting enough to read. Until then, my answer is no for using this.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think it’s good but it isn’t too… “potent” - it’s too long for the covered content, and it almost feels like he’s attempting to write a story with it. If it had more of a meaning to it then I do think that it would be a good read but I’m going to agree with you and say that it’s not ready for the Monthly yet.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 03:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521027-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027.rss">User Submission - Uncalled</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>User Submission - Uncalled</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Uncalled has been requested as an interview candidate by Loveandpower last week, yet I never got around to replying to him. I agree that Uncalled’s answers are straightforward, yet the concept behind the interview is to interview users who have contributed large amounts to the community. Quite frankly - and although this may be because I’m relatively new - I haven’t seen Uncalled do anything more than start a development and create a few decent looking graphics.</p>
<p>I don’t support this idea for potential staff. With my new position it could easily be misinterpreted as me revealing private discussion, as well as it not being our place to publicly nominate users on a homepage that represents the name of the forums. I feel that we already cover the ‘Notable whatever’ in the varying sections of ‘Most Helpful Members,’ ‘Best Tutorials,’ and others that give users their own chance in the spotlight. If we wish to congratulate a site member for doing some notable, then we will reserve a small paragraph to explain what they’ve done and to congratulate them for it.</p>
<p>May I get your opinion(s) on the blog post that he submitted (the part where he decides to rejoin the forums)? Overall I find it too bland, there needs to be more meat to it. With the right amount of work I can see this post turning into a nicely sized paragraph that is interesting enough to read. Until then, my answer is no for using this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 03:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521027-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027.rss">User Submission - Uncalled</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>User Submission - Uncalled</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I definitely think we should consider Uncalled as an interview candidate for this month. His answers are to-the-point, yet also contain enough content to be interesting. With a few edits to make them read a bit better I think it’d be a really good read.</p>
<p>I agree with his idea although I’m not sure how we’d base it on others opinions without revealing the candidates. Also, I’m not sure we should say “this is the most noticeable, this is the second most noticeable, this is the third…” etc, because I think it should be a motivation tool instead of a competition.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 03:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521027-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027.rss">User Submission - Uncalled</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>User Submission - Uncalled</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Relaying a private message sent to me by Uncalled, leave feedback and opinions below.<br>
[hr]<br>
Okay, so the first one: Why did I decide to rejoin the forums?</p>
<p>Well, I decided to rejoin these forums for multiple different reasons. I mean, I’ve been with the community for a good amount of time, and I’ve made some great friends along the way. I get along with most of the community, so I don’t see a reason why I left in the first place. I figured that even if I wasn’t in RuneScape emulation at the time, I could still just stay around for whatever discussion was running about in the forums. I’ve also left once before this, but again, was lured back. I expected this to happen, really. I guess I could say that I missed some of you guys, so I decided randomly that I was going to log back in once more.</p>
<p>Another idea:<br>
In the Mopar Monthly, you could add the top five most noticeable new members, possibly(?) potential staff - based off of other’s opinions, and try to make it a little more community-based. If more of the community was involved with the rankings, then the more would read it, perhaps.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2013 03:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-521027-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/user-submission-uncalled/521027.rss">User Submission - Uncalled</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
