<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Trading problem [667]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trading-problem-667/539937</link>
    <description>Ok, so basically.. When i accept a trade with someone, it says &quot;You cannot trade yourself&quot; and then when i try to trade someone right after, it says 
&quot;Your already in a trade!&quot; but there is no trade screen for either person, and you cannot offer any items. 
And also, when you try to trade with someone without a total level of 500 it wont let you, I would also like to get rid of that. 
And once you &#39;trade&#39; someone but it doesnt work, if you follow them you cannot un-follow them.. if you try to walk away you can only move about 2 
steps and then you get pulled back to the player, making it unable to walk away without relogging. I would also like some help on that!
Thanks in advance.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 21:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trading-problem-667/539937.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Trading problem [667]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Search for 500, you’ll see something like <span class="bbcode-i">if (player.getTotalLevel() &lt; 500) return;</span> - remove that. As for the trading it seems to be completely broken, you will need to search for each string and dry-run the code to figure out the issues, it seems like the target player isn’t being found? or incorrectly being identified as your player, try looking over the method which returns the player, probably something like <span class="bbcode-i">PlayerHandler.getPlayer(plrName)</span>. As for the last issue, if they any non-movement packet is received (minus idle etc ofc) try toggling following. It must be in your movement handler somewhere, since it begins there must be a way to turn it off too.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trading-problem-667/539937/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trading-problem-667/539937/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 21:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539937-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trading-problem-667/539937.rss">Trading problem [667]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Trading problem [667]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@adamgulka adamgulka]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/adamgulka">@adamgulka</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok, so basically… When i accept a trade with someone, it says “You cannot trade yourself” and then when i try to trade someone right after, it says<br>
"Your already in a trade!" but there is no trade screen for either person, and you cannot offer any items.<br>
And also, when you try to trade with someone without a total level of 500 it wont let you, I would also like to get rid of that.<br>
And once you ‘trade’ someone but it doesnt work, if you follow them you cannot un-follow them… if you try to walk away you can only move about 2<br>
steps and then you get pulled back to the player, making it unable to walk away without relogging. I would also like some help on that!<br>
Thanks in advance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trading-problem-667/539937/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trading-problem-667/539937/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 20:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-539937-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/trading-problem-667/539937.rss">Trading problem [667]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
