<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>IB Music Guitar</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977</link>
    <description>Hi,

I&#39;m going to be taking the full IB diploma program (kinda like a harder AP) at my school, and one of my HL (higher level) courses is music, which I am a little screwed for. I have some background in music; I&#39;ve started piano at age 7 and passed ABRSM Grade 5 theory and the general piano examination (with respective scores 72/100 and 130/140 (I think..)) Because of the fact that I lost my dedication to piano five years ago, I have forgotten nearly all music theory. I had spent the past half-year relearning it, but progress does not seem to be coming at my expected rate. I had started learning electric guitar two years ago and I chose that as my main instrument for the course. I have heard many rumors (from credible sources) about electric guitarists receiving unfair bias because the electric guitar &quot;isn&#39;t a real instrument&quot; and because &quot;it&#39;s too easy&quot;, and if true, will be an obstacle for the next two years. As some of you read in my other thread about screaming (http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,554385.0.html), I like hard rock and hair metal, although I am open to most genres of music. My goal is to learn classical and jazz for the next to years (perhaps blues too, Ruby :D), although both styles are going to be a major pain in the ass.

For all the guitarists out there: do you have any tips for my two year venture? Also, I am having trouble choosing good songs to play. My teacher says that all students must perform a piece on the first day. I have a lot of trouble memorizing guitar solos even while using Guitar Pro, and this doesn&#39;t help the fact that my musical taste does not have too many &#39;expected&#39; guitar pieces. I&#39;m looking for songs with lengthly guitar solos if possible. Our teacher expects guitarists to play artists such as Hendrix, Vai, and Satriani, and this is going to be a difficult task for me. My level of playing is somewhere intermediate, although I do not know how to judge it. The last song with a solo I&#39;ve memorized almost note for note is The Trooper by Iron Maiden.

I hope some of you can help me out. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 10:39:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>IB Music Guitar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="451977">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ruby/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Ruby:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Queen</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Doin’ it right.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 10:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451977-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977.rss">IB Music Guitar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>IB Music Guitar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Team_Rocket, post:3, topic:451977”][quote author=Whackatre link=topic=554858.msg4063325#msg4063325 date=1343628038]<br>
My goal is to learn classical and jazz for the next to years (perhaps blues too, Ruby :D)<br>
[/quote]<br>
It looks like you’ve got your priorities straight.[/quote]</p>
<p>SOMEONE WHO UNDERSTANDS.</p>
<p>Unlike half of the guitarists in this community who are all heavy metal crazy, lol.</p>
<p>Also, Justin, you really can’t go wrong with playing some Queen if you’re looking for a song. I suggest crazy little thing called love, the solo sounds impressive and the entire last 40 seconds are just a blues improvisation, definitely a contender.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 09:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451977-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977.rss">IB Music Guitar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>IB Music Guitar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="1" data-topic="451977">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/whackatre/40/7608_1.png" class="avatar"> Whackatre:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My goal is to learn classical and jazz for the next to years (perhaps blues too, Ruby :D)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It looks like you’ve got your priorities straight.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 09:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451977-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977.rss">IB Music Guitar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>IB Music Guitar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ruby_Forums_Coder Ruby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ruby_forums_coder">@Ruby_Forums_Coder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Learning music theory is never easy, you landed yourself right in it by stopping playing piano.</p>
<p>I love piano, not as much as guitar, but you get my drift.</p>
<p>If you’re willing to come into blues, I’d suggest just getting say a 3-4 minute blues shuffle backing track, probably in A. This way you can show a whole load of licks and riffs. In a blues shuffle, I could do an entire solo using 3 notes for like 2 minutes without it getting boring, blues riffs are really easy to pick up and sound really impressive, so along with impressing your teacher, you’ll also impress your classmates.</p>
<p>For example, here’s a quick 3 bar blues lick I’ve just tabbed out:</p>
<p>|-----------8b-----|-------8–10br----10-8-|---------8b-----------------------------|</p>
<div class="md-table">
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>----10-10---------</th>
<th>—10------------------</th>
<th>–10------------------------------------</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>-------------------</td>
<td>-----------------------</td>
<td>----------------------------------------</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>-------------------</td>
<td>-----------------------</td>
<td>----------------------------------------</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>-------------------</td>
<td>-----------------------</td>
<td>----------------------------------------</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div><p>Ignore the hideous tabbing, please.</p>
<p>If you find any A blues shuffle track, you’ll be able to use that to start it off.<br>
I also suggest sliding into the first position.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 09:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451977-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977.rss">IB Music Guitar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>IB Music Guitar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi,</p>
<p>I’m going to be taking the full IB diploma program (kinda like a harder AP) at my school, and one of my HL (higher level) courses is music, which I am a little screwed for. I have some background in music; I’ve started piano at age 7 and passed ABRSM Grade 5 theory and the general piano examination (with respective scores 72/100 and 130/140 (I think…)) Because of the fact that I lost my dedication to piano five years ago, I have forgotten nearly all music theory. I had spent the past half-year relearning it, but progress does not seem to be coming at my expected rate. I had started learning electric guitar two years ago and I chose that as my main instrument for the course. I have heard many rumors (from credible sources) about electric guitarists receiving unfair bias because the electric guitar “isn’t a real instrument” and because “it’s too easy”, and if true, will be an obstacle for the next two years. As some of you read in my other thread about screaming (<a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,554385.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,554385.0.html</a>), I like hard rock and hair metal, although I am open to most genres of music. My goal is to learn classical and jazz for the next to years (perhaps blues too, Ruby :D), although both styles are going to be a major pain in the ass.</p>
<p>For all the guitarists out there: do you have any tips for my two year venture? Also, I am having trouble choosing good songs to play. My teacher says that all students must perform a piece on the first day. I have a lot of trouble memorizing guitar solos even while using Guitar Pro, and this doesn’t help the fact that my musical taste does not have too many ‘expected’ guitar pieces. I’m looking for songs with lengthly guitar solos if possible. Our teacher expects guitarists to play artists such as Hendrix, Vai, and Satriani, and this is going to be a difficult task for me. My level of playing is somewhere intermediate, although I do not know how to judge it. The last song with a solo I’ve memorized almost note for note is The Trooper by Iron Maiden.</p>
<p>I hope some of you can help me out. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 06:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-451977-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ib-music-guitar/451977.rss">IB Music Guitar</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
