<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The World&#39;s End</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-worlds-end/535208</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzA1MTk1MzY0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjkzNTUwMDE@._V1_SX214_.jpg[/img][/center]
Simon Pegg and Nick Frost, who woulda guessed!?
Okay so the movie starts off with the typical craving for a nostalgic trip down memory lane, Simon being the man to do so gathers all his college friends and takes them back home to complete the Golden Mile which is essentially a door to door with 12 bars drinking a pine at each. I&#39;m not going to lie, I did expect this to be some sort of Project X, 21 and over chip off, and oh boy was I completely wrong. So you&#39;ve probably heard of the term &quot;well that escalated quickly.&quot; Yeah well this movie is the definition of that term, literally it really is. When it happened I was completely mind fudgeed, didn&#39;t know what just happened and I was wondering what kind of maniac ruined a perfectly good Project X old man edition. Though the tables turned after watching that first fight scene, the fight scenes in this movie are really good actually and there&#39;s that Goku moment where one guy just go nuts and inspires everyone around him to just go nuts as well. The movie overall is just really well done, great mix of comedy and seriousness. Simon Pegg&#39;s character himself is actually probably the best I&#39;ve seen in a while. He&#39;s some sort of man child trying to bring back the good times from when he was a kid, you cant miss this because it&#39;s an obvious statement from the very start. Simon Pegg really is a man child in this movie, he&#39;s hilarious and cracks the jokes left and right without a doubt one of the funniest movies he&#39;s been in. You seen it coming because it&#39;s the same in every movie but the development with Nick Frost is there, it&#39;s inevitable and it really shows towards the ending of the movie as opposed to all of the friends kind of being equal throughout most of the movie. So the movie is coming to an end and really I sat there thinking, did they really just do that... waachaa, whch, whchch, what!? Though I must say that the very last scene is bad ass even though it ends up being a completely different story, who knows maybe a part 2? Doubt it though.

So overall I really enjoyed this movie, I would probably rate this one 8 pines out of 10.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 10:33:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-worlds-end/535208.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The World&#39;s End</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RandQm RandQm]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/randqm">@RandQm</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I wouldn’t watch it twice, but I enjoyed it.<br>
It’s such movie some will stop watching halfway through while others will praise it.<br>
I would rate it 6.5/10</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-worlds-end/535208/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-worlds-end/535208/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 10:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535208-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-worlds-end/535208.rss">The World&#39;s End</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The World&#39;s End</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzA1MTk1MzY0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjkzNTUwMDE@._V1_SX214_.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/center]<br>
Simon Pegg and Nick Frost, who woulda guessed!?<br>
Okay so the movie starts off with the typical craving for a nostalgic trip down memory lane, Simon being the man to do so gathers all his college friends and takes them back home to complete the Golden Mile which is essentially a door to door with 12 bars drinking a pine at each. I’m not going to lie, I did expect this to be some sort of Project X, 21 and over chip off, and oh boy was I completely wrong. So you’ve probably heard of the term “well that escalated quickly.” Yeah well this movie is the definition of that term, literally it really is. When it happened I was completely mind fudgeed, didn’t know what just happened and I was wondering what kind of maniac ruined a perfectly good Project X old man edition. Though the tables turned after watching that first fight scene, the fight scenes in this movie are really good actually and there’s that Goku moment where one guy just go nuts and inspires everyone around him to just go nuts as well. The movie overall is just really well done, great mix of comedy and seriousness. Simon Pegg’s character himself is actually probably the best I’ve seen in a while. He’s some sort of man child trying to bring back the good times from when he was a kid, you cant miss this because it’s an obvious statement from the very start. Simon Pegg really is a man child in this movie, he’s hilarious and cracks the jokes left and right without a doubt one of the funniest movies he’s been in. You seen it coming because it’s the same in every movie but the development with Nick Frost is there, it’s inevitable and it really shows towards the ending of the movie as opposed to all of the friends kind of being equal throughout most of the movie. So the movie is coming to an end and really I sat there thinking, did they really just do that… waachaa, whch, whchch, what!? Though I must say that the very last scene is bad ass even though it ends up being a completely different story, who knows maybe a part 2? Doubt it though.</p>
<p>So overall I really enjoyed this movie, I would probably rate this one 8 pines out of 10.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-worlds-end/535208/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-worlds-end/535208/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 10:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-535208-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-worlds-end/535208.rss">The World&#39;s End</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
