<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Respawn points [pi]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/respawn-points-pi/470035</link>
    <description>so i want to add where when you die you can set a respawn point and it saves how would i do this or if you know eney tuts for it or like it near that idea plz link me</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 18:59:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/respawn-points-pi/470035.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Respawn points [pi]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Team_Rocket Team_Rocket]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/team_rocket">@Team_Rocket</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hm, a refreshing concept. You’re wanting a Mark Spawn System. The Player selects the Marked destination, and upon their Death, instead of sending the Player back to your original Coordinates, it re-directs them to their selected Coordinates. This is relatively simple if you don’t need to get too complicated. Wanting to prove a point; feedback on a concept; etc.</p>
<p>Create these Strings to be saved in your Character Files amongst your other things.</p>
<p>Declare a Condition in reference to which Destination they’ll be going to.</p>
<p>Add an exception or prerequisite to your</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Method, or however your Base may choose to do this. (Player class might be a good place to start checking)</p>
<p>Now comes the fun part! Yay! You choose how your Player-Characters are able to select their own Destination Coordinates upon Death.</p>
<p>Should they use a Command? No, there should absolutely <span class="bbcode-b">NOT</span> be a Command, because regular Players shouldn’t have access to them whatsoever. This is my opinion, however, and It’s honestly up to you and your Team.</p>
<p>How about the itemClick Packets? Well, I wouldn’t go this route, but this may still be a completely viable option for you.</p>
<p>I would use a piece of Equipment such as a special Amulet or Ring which only allows a Player to do this when worn. Of course there would be a few changes made to the Mark Spawn System to accommodate this.</p>
<p>TL;DR    A quick run-down of how this can be done. I don’t know of anyone who’s written such a Tutorial or Snippet (snippet in this case). I’m afraid you might have to learn. Even though you’ll find many similar preexisting examples already written for you Server-sided. No, I’m not saying anyone should follow the techniques and style of P.I. Based Sources.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/respawn-points-pi/470035/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/respawn-points-pi/470035/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 18:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470035-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/respawn-points-pi/470035.rss">Respawn points [pi]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Respawn points [pi]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kill_boy_98 kill boy 98]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kill_boy_98">@kill_boy_98</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>so i want to add where when you die you can set a respawn point and it saves how would i do this or if you know eney tuts for it or like it near that idea plz link me</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/respawn-points-pi/470035/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/respawn-points-pi/470035/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 18:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-470035-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/respawn-points-pi/470035.rss">Respawn points [pi]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
