<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Please someone help me understand how this works!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-someone-help-me-understand-how-this-works/436887</link>
    <description>#tormented demon
8351:40      886:150   1149:1   1249:1   1201:1   1319:1   1289:1   1185:1   1247:1   1147:1   1432:1   1113:1   1373:1   892:42   829:20   565:20   560:40   561:67   1149:1
14484:1   3140:1   4087:1   4585:1   1187:1   6585:1

ok red was all in 1 line below the #tormented demon and black was under it just for clarification (if it even matters)...

Anyways my question is I understand 8351 is the npc&#39;s id and the 40 behind the : is the drop rate of such drops from this monster.
And d claws is 14484 and 1 is the number it drops.
So 8351:40  14484:1
But how the heck does this thingy work ok it has a :40% chance to drop anything? or what the other drops are all diffrent but dont have no like rare sign on them in this case dragon claws. so shouldnt dragon claws drop at the same rate everything else does? like what make it drop diffrent rate from  4585 or whatever.. I need to know this as im going to be changing my servers drops and crap around and its really annoying figuring this out... So can someone please explain how this works in more detail then just 

#tormented demon
8351:40      886:150   1149:1
Npc id : drop ratio       item id: amount to be dropped      Item id: amount to be dropped


Also, this is a [pi] and erasedpkz mix or whatever if that helps. also what means better drop rate 1 or 100 behind the npc id. Thanks!!  (sorry if i sound stupid im new obviously to doing this and i want to learn so be nice).



Ok, to get to the point so yall can understand this... Ok lets say I want td&#39;s to drop bandos chestplate every time and ags every 1-4 drops or so.. how would i add these into its system using the above.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 18:26:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-someone-help-me-understand-how-this-works/436887.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Please someone help me understand how this works!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Froggg Froggg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/froggg">@Froggg</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="hashtag">#tormented</span> demon<br>
8351:40      886:150   1149:1   1249:1   1201:1   1319:1   1289:1   1185:1   1247:1   1147:1   1432:1   1113:1   1373:1   892:42   829:20   565:20   560:40   561:67   1149:1<br>
14484:1   3140:1   4087:1   4585:1   1187:1   6585:1</p>
<p>ok red was all in 1 line below the <span class="hashtag">#tormented</span> demon and black was under it just for clarification (if it even matters)…</p>
<p>Anyways my question is I understand 8351 is the npc’s id and the 40 behind the : is the drop rate of such drops from this monster.<br>
And d claws is 14484 and 1 is the number it drops.<br>
So 8351:40  14484:1<br>
But how the heck does this thingy work ok it has a :40% chance to drop anything? or what the other drops are all diffrent but dont have no like rare sign on them in this case dragon claws. so shouldnt dragon claws drop at the same rate everything else does? like what make it drop diffrent rate from  4585 or whatever… I need to know this as im going to be changing my servers drops and crap around and its really annoying figuring this out… So can someone please explain how this works in more detail then just</p>
<p><span class="hashtag">#tormented</span> demon<br>
8351:40      886:150   1149:1<br>
Npc id : drop ratio       item id: amount to be dropped      Item id: amount to be dropped</p>
<p>Also, this is a [pi] and erasedpkz mix or whatever if that helps. also what means better drop rate 1 or 100 behind the npc id. Thanks!!  (sorry if i sound stupid im new obviously to doing this and i want to learn so be nice).</p>
<p>Ok, to get to the point so yall can understand this… Ok lets say I want td’s to drop bandos chestplate every time and ags every 1-4 drops or so… how would i add these into its system using the above.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-someone-help-me-understand-how-this-works/436887/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-someone-help-me-understand-how-this-works/436887/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 18:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-436887-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/please-someone-help-me-understand-how-this-works/436887.rss">Please someone help me understand how this works!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
