<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hunted Love--The second story in an amazing drama!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633</link>
    <description>As Francis was sitting lazily on the couch, refilling and unloading his shotgun over and over mechanically, he heard something. Sitting up straight, he strained his ears to hear what it was. It sounded like...no! They were back!

He jumped up and fully loaded his shotgun. Running outside, he barred the door--no way they were finding his playboys. Damn horny zombies!!

He began shooting the zombies, their arms and legs flying off, battering the other zombies. He got hard from this, seeing the red fluids spew out, almost like semen.

Suddenly, he heard a cry. Looking up, he had but a fraction of a second to notice a hunter leaping at him. He tried to shove it away, but to no avail. The hunter had fully mounted him, pressing its ass against his hips. This hunter was different from the rest; he could sense it.

It was something in his eyes. It showed emotion, caring, for those around him. It wasn&#39;t the soulless face of the masses. It was so alluring, beckoning him to venture into it. He had to.

He grabbed the hunter&#39;s head and drew it forward in an embrace unlike anything he&#39;d ever experienced before. It was so full of passion, so worthy of his entire existence. 

Suddenly, he was on his hands and knees, preparing to be entered. This was exhilarating; he so longed to be filled by the white hot goo that was produced by his partner.

As he was buttfucked, he realized that he had to take a shit. Caught up in the moment, he got even harder when he shat onto the hunter&#39;s dick. It was entrancing, the way it spread itself all over his long, pulsing rod. He watched with desire as the hunter spread the shit all over his rotting balls, giving them a brighter color than they had before.

He felt a hard piercing on his penis, and he looked down and saw the hunter chewing on it with delight. This further turned him on, and he eventually shot his hot goo out of all the holes that the hunter had cut in his penis.

Suddenly, he felt a large pain in his torso. He looked down, and saw that the hunter had pierced his stomach. This was nothing but satisfaction for Francis, sweet bliss. It felt so relieving to be filled with blood and semen. This was what he had lived his entire life to fulfill.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 06:44:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hunted Love--The second story in an amazing drama!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zuppers zuppers]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zuppers">@zuppers</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just put them all in one post, im getting confused about which ones I haven’t read lool.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340633-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633.rss">Hunted Love--The second story in an amazing drama!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunted Love--The second story in an amazing drama!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>so this is the survivors perspective, same as the first part?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 04:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340633-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633.rss">Hunted Love--The second story in an amazing drama!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Hunted Love--The second story in an amazing drama!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@geel9 geel9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/geel9">@geel9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As Francis was sitting lazily on the couch, refilling and unloading his shotgun over and over mechanically, he heard something. Sitting up straight, he strained his ears to hear what it was. It sounded like…no! They were back!</p>
<p>He jumped up and fully loaded his shotgun. Running outside, he barred the door–no way they were finding his playboys. Damn horny zombies!!</p>
<p>He began shooting the zombies, their arms and legs flying off, battering the other zombies. He got hard from this, seeing the red fluids spew out, almost like semen.</p>
<p>Suddenly, he heard a cry. Looking up, he had but a fraction of a second to notice a hunter leaping at him. He tried to shove it away, but to no avail. The hunter had fully mounted him, pressing its ass against his hips. This hunter was different from the rest; he could sense it.</p>
<p>It was something in his eyes. It showed emotion, caring, for those around him. It wasn’t the soulless face of the masses. It was so alluring, beckoning him to venture into it. He had to.</p>
<p>He grabbed the hunter’s head and drew it forward in an embrace unlike anything he’d ever experienced before. It was so full of passion, so worthy of his entire existence.</p>
<p>Suddenly, he was on his hands and knees, preparing to be entered. This was exhilarating; he so longed to be filled by the white hot goo that was produced by his partner.</p>
<p>As he was buttfucked, he realized that he had to take a shit. Caught up in the moment, he got even harder when he shat onto the hunter’s dick. It was entrancing, the way it spread itself all over his long, pulsing rod. He watched with desire as the hunter spread the shit all over his rotting balls, giving them a brighter color than they had before.</p>
<p>He felt a hard piercing on his penis, and he looked down and saw the hunter chewing on it with delight. This further turned him on, and he eventually shot his hot goo out of all the holes that the hunter had cut in his penis.</p>
<p>Suddenly, he felt a large pain in his torso. He looked down, and saw that the hunter had pierced his stomach. This was nothing but satisfaction for Francis, sweet bliss. It felt so relieving to be filled with blood and semen. This was what he had lived his entire life to fulfill.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 03:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340633-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hunted-love-the-second-story-in-an-amazing-drama/340633.rss">Hunted Love--The second story in an amazing drama!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
