<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Goliath RsPs! 317 Client Revised!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goliath-rsps-317-client-revised/554359</link>
    <description>Hey everyone, I&#39;m a player from Goliath RsPs![url=http://goliath-ps.com/]http://goliath-ps.com/[/url] It&#39;s a great friendly community that is looking for new players now! It&#39;s content packed, 317 loading higher revision, Goliath-PS, Auto-donations, auto-vote, Donator XP Boosts, Nex, 100+ Achievements, and much more! Eventually looking for staff members! After we get to a certain number of players, a staff position will be given out to a random, worthy player. Come join now in all the fun! I promise you&#39;ll have just as much fun as I am. So, its a great, friendly, and all around amazing community, especially when we get a lot of players rolling on in. Have fun guys and enjoy, plus you get up to 8 vote scroll per voting period! thats crazy good. 1m and 1 vote point, or 10mins of 30% xp bonus!


[center][font=times new roman][size=24pt]IMPORTANT![/size][/font][/center]
[spoiler]Friendly thing though, our VPN is about to run out, we need a total of $75 to keep the server alive and running! We only have 3 days to save the server! Also, about another $10 to renew the site. But, who can help keep the server alive will receive an extra gift for saving the server![/spoiler]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 01:24:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goliath-rsps-317-client-revised/554359.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Goliath RsPs! 317 Client Revised!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@GoliathRsPs GoliathRsPs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goliathrsps">@GoliathRsPs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey everyone, I’m a player from Goliath RsPs!<a href="http://goliath-ps.com/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://goliath-ps.com/</a> It’s a great friendly community that is looking for new players now! It’s content packed, 317 loading higher revision, Goliath-PS, Auto-donations, auto-vote, Donator XP Boosts, Nex, 100+ Achievements, and much more! Eventually looking for staff members! After we get to a certain number of players, a staff position will be given out to a random, worthy player. Come join now in all the fun! I promise you’ll have just as much fun as I am. So, its a great, friendly, and all around amazing community, especially when we get a lot of players rolling on in. Have fun guys and enjoy, plus you get up to 8 vote scroll per voting period! thats crazy good. 1m and 1 vote point, or 10mins of 30% xp bonus!</p>
<p>[center][font=times new roman][size=24pt]IMPORTANT![/size][/font][/center]<br>
[spoiler]Friendly thing though, our VPN is about to run out, we need a total of $75 to keep the server alive and running! We only have 3 days to save the server! Also, about another $10 to renew the site. But, who can help keep the server alive will receive an extra gift for saving the server![/spoiler]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goliath-rsps-317-client-revised/554359/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goliath-rsps-317-client-revised/554359/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 01:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-554359-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/goliath-rsps-317-client-revised/554359.rss">Goliath RsPs! 317 Client Revised!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
