<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting a Server Started</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306</link>
    <description>Well, I am 14 years old, and my name is Fares. It&#39;s not a familiar name you got with everyday, it&#39;s like &quot;Ferris Bueler&quot; as many of you will notice from my past of [b]no posting[/b], I&#39;ve been a member for a day. I am absolute that I will not be able to find what I want, or atleast a good enough reply that&#39;ll get me to understand it properly. The thing that isn&#39;t being replied in many forums, and the reply is that I would like someone with good sense of [b]knowledge[/b], to [b]explain[/b] to me, [b]exactly[/b] how, and where I could start my [b]own server[/b], and go right through to the [b]database[/b] so that I might be able to [b]change[/b]:

[ul][li]Commands[/li]
[li]Item codes ([i]IF[/i] possible)[/li][/ul]


[b]Pictures of tabs such as:[/b] Quest tab, Skill tab, etcetra. So anyways, I really would like someone to post a good reply, and/or a thread that has already been made. I would like someone to actually try to somehow walk me through. I will reward that player if their technique/information was correct. Please don&#39;t post 3 word posts &quot;Go forms bords!!!!!!&quot; I had that happen alot considering most people think that they know everything.

I am a windows user. I got winRaR. I have JDK and I am willing to download anything, virus free.

I would like whoever replies to actually tell me the requirements for the server they&#39;re letting me download. I will add the person on msn if they&#39;d like, and I want that person to actually feel comfortable around me, so we can share names, and the person could walk me through it. I know it&#39;s alot to ask for, but please. If you aren&#39;t up for the challenge/request I&#39;ve given, please feel free to not post, I wouldn&#39;t mind that. It&#39;ll save people alot of time. Thank you for great forums, and a great client!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 02:52:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Getting a Server Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@test1997 test1997]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/test1997">@test1997</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you meant this <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,342685.msg2648941.html#msg2648941" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">thread</a>. Thank you so much, no need for MSN or anything, explained it all. Plus, I’d like to request someone locking this thread.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 02:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-297306-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306.rss">Getting a Server Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting a Server Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dizzle11 dizzle11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dizzle11">@dizzle11</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok well i say to first leran things and get a feel for rsc you download the easyrsc source and check out yong min’s tut on how to edit what i need to know u can use the search option or even find those quite easy as they are on the first page of server development other then that if you have any other questions leave em here im sure someone will get to you best of luck</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 02:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-297306-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306.rss">Getting a Server Started</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Getting a Server Started</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@test1997 test1997]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/test1997">@test1997</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well, I am 14 years old, and my name is Fares. It’s not a familiar name you got with everyday, it’s like “Ferris Bueler” as many of you will notice from my past of <span class="bbcode-b">no posting</span>, I’ve been a member for a day. I am absolute that I will not be able to find what I want, or atleast a good enough reply that’ll get me to understand it properly. The thing that isn’t being replied in many forums, and the reply is that I would like someone with good sense of <span class="bbcode-b">knowledge</span>, to <span class="bbcode-b">explain</span> to me, <span class="bbcode-b">exactly</span> how, and where I could start my <span class="bbcode-b">own server</span>, and go right through to the <span class="bbcode-b">database</span> so that I might be able to <span class="bbcode-b">change</span>:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Commands[/li]<br>
[li]Item codes (<span class="bbcode-i">IF</span> possible)[/li][/ul]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Pictures of tabs such as:</span> Quest tab, Skill tab, etcetra. So anyways, I really would like someone to post a good reply, and/or a thread that has already been made. I would like someone to actually try to somehow walk me through. I will reward that player if their technique/information was correct. Please don’t post 3 word posts “Go forms bords!!!” I had that happen alot considering most people think that they know everything.</p>
<p>I am a windows user. I got winRaR. I have JDK and I am willing to download anything, virus free.</p>
<p>I would like whoever replies to actually tell me the requirements for the server they’re letting me download. I will add the person on msn if they’d like, and I want that person to actually feel comfortable around me, so we can share names, and the person could walk me through it. I know it’s alot to ask for, but please. If you aren’t up for the challenge/request I’ve given, please feel free to not post, I wouldn’t mind that. It’ll save people alot of time. Thank you for great forums, and a great client!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 02:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-297306-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/getting-a-server-started/297306.rss">Getting a Server Started</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
