<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749</link>
    <description>Released today, for some reason EVERYTHING is hidden, not just the bad things we do.


&lt;blockquote&gt;Shachtman analyzes the Wikileaks trove. There&#39;s no evidence, however, that they were part of any ongoing program as claimed by the Bush administration:

    Remnants of Saddam’s toxic arsenal, largely destroyed after the Gulf War, remained. Jihadists, insurgents and foreign (possibly Iranian) agitators turned to these stockpiles during the Iraq conflict — and may have brewed up their own deadly agents...

    In August 2004, for instance, American forces surreptitiously purchased what they believed to be containers of liquid sulfur mustard, a toxic “blister agent” used as a chemical weapon since World War I. The troops tested the liquid, and “reported two positive results for blister.” The chemical was then “triple-sealed and transported to a secure site” outside their base...

    [b]Even late in the war, WMDs were still being unearthed. In the summer of 2008, according to one WikiLeaked report, American troops found at least 10 rounds that tested positive for chemical agents.[/b] “These rounds were most likely left over from the [Saddam]-era regime. Based on location, these rounds may be an AQI [Al Qaeda in Iraq] cache. However, the rounds were all total disrepair and did not appear to have been moved for a long time.”

    The WMD diehards will likely find some comfort in these newly-WikiLeaked documents. Skeptics will note that these relatively small WMD stockpiles were hardly the kind of grave danger that the Bush administration presented in the run-up to the war.

    But the more salient issue may be how insurgents and Islamic extremists (possibly with the help of Iran) attempted to use these lethal and exotic arms. As Spencer noted earlier, a January 2006 war log claims that “neuroparalytic” chemical weapons were smuggled in from Iraq. That same month, then “chemical weapons specialists” were apprehended in Balad. These “foreigners” were there specifically “to support the chemical weapons operations.” The following month, an intelligence report refers to a “chemical weapons expert” that “provided assistance with the gas weapons.” What happened to that specialist, the WikiLeaked document doesn’t say.

I know of no incident when these weapons were actually used against US troops. And the irony, of course, is that it was the invasion that gave insurgents and Islamists access to these remnants.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
http://andrewsullivan.theatlantic.com/the_daily_dish/2010/10/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq.html

Isnt it amazing how people only bring up the wikileaks that feed their opinions, not any that may oppose.


http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Dfk0s71BVU&amp;feature=player_embedded


[img]http://www.wired.com/images_blogs/dangerroom/2010/10/97vials_300-660x491.jpg[/img]
&lt;blockquote&gt;By late 2003, even the Bush White House’s staunchest defenders were starting to give up on the idea that there were weapons of mass destruction in Iraq.

But for years afterward, WikiLeaks’ newly-released Iraq war documents reveal, U.S. troops continued to find chemical weapons labs, encounter insurgent specialists in toxins, and uncover weapons of mass destruction.

An initial glance at the WikiLeaks war logs doesn’t reveal evidence of some massive WMD program by the Saddam Hussein regime — the Bush administration’s most (in)famous rationale for invading Iraq. But chemical weapons, especially, did not vanish from the Iraqi battlefield. Remnants of Saddam’s toxic arsenal, largely destroyed after the Gulf War, remained. Jihadists, insurgents and foreign (possibly Iranian) agitators turned to these stockpiles during the Iraq conflict — and may have brewed up their own deadly agents.

In August 2004, for instance, American forces surreptitiously purchased what they believed to be containers of liquid sulfur mustard, a toxic “blister agent” used as a chemical weapon since World War I. The troops tested the liquid, and “reported two positive results for blister.” The chemical was then “triple-sealed and transported to a secure site” outside their base.

Three months later, in northern Iraq, U.S. scouts went to look in on a “chemical weapons” complex. “One of the bunkers has been tampered with,” they write. “The integrity of the seal [around the complex] appears intact, but it seems someone is interesting in trying to get into the bunkers.”

Meanwhile, the second battle of Fallujah was raging in Anbar province. In the southeastern corner of the city, American forces came across a “house with a chemical lab … substances found are similar to ones (in lesser quantities located a previous chemical lab.” The following day, there’s a call in another part of the city for explosive experts to dispose of a “chemical cache.”

Nearly three years later, American troops were still finding WMD in the region. An armored Buffalo vehicle unearthed a cache of artillery shells “that was covered by sacks and leaves under an Iraqi Community Watch checkpoint. “The 155mm rounds are filled with an unknown liquid, and several of which are leaking a black tar-like substance.” Initial tests were inconclusive. But later, “the rounds tested positive for mustard.”


Read More http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/#ixzz13F7iQDIk&lt;/blockquote&gt;
http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 05:14:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Radeon, post:9, topic:365749”][quote author=Frell link=topic=461943.msg3381614#msg3381614 date=1288068416]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>An initial glance at the WikiLeaks war logs doesn’t reveal evidence of some massive WMD program by the Saddam Hussein regime — the Bush administration’s most (in)famous rationale for invading Iraq. <span class="bbcode-b">But chemical weapons, especially, did not vanish from the Iraqi battlefield. Remnants of Saddam’s toxic arsenal, largely destroyed after the Gulf War, remained.</span> Jihadists, insurgents and foreign (possibly Iranian) agitators turned to these stockpiles during the Iraq conflict — and may have brewed up their own deadly agents.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><a href="http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/%5B/quote%5D" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/[/quote]</a></p>
<p>Contrary to what you believe, the part in bold opposes your argument. It affirms that Saddam destroyed what he could of his arsenal.</p>
<p>I can’t be bothered producing long rebuttals because most of what you bring up is silly and not worth the effort.[/quote]<br>
He no doubt destroyed what he could, but he didnt destroy them all. Oh and its not silly, I just went a few years before the wmd’s to explain what went on and why wmd’s werent the only reason we went to war.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 05:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MujaheD Radeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mujahed">@MujaheD</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:8, topic:365749”][quote]<br>
An initial glance at the WikiLeaks war logs doesn’t reveal evidence of some massive WMD program by the Saddam Hussein regime — the Bush administration’s most (in)famous rationale for invading Iraq. <span class="bbcode-b">But chemical weapons, especially, did not vanish from the Iraqi battlefield. Remnants of Saddam’s toxic arsenal, largely destroyed after the Gulf War, remained.</span> Jihadists, insurgents and foreign (possibly Iranian) agitators turned to these stockpiles during the Iraq conflict — and may have brewed up their own deadly agents.<br>
[/quote]<br>
<a href="http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/%5B/quote%5D" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/[/quote]</a></p>
<p>Contrary to what you believe, the part in bold opposes your argument. It affirms that Saddam destroyed what he could of his arsenal.</p>
<p>I can’t be bothered producing long rebuttals because most of what you bring up is silly and not worth the effort.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 05:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Frell, post:48, topic:365555”][quote author=Radeon link=topic=461757.msg3381270#msg3381270 date=1288047796]</p>
<ul>
<li>The weapons which America provided the Iraqis weren’t WMDs. They provided them with helicopters and short range rockets.</li>
<li>The UN inspectors didn’t find any WMDs and neither did the Americans after the war.</li>
<li>There were no terrorists or insurgents in Iraq prior to the invasion with the exception of the Kurdish Peshmerga which was formed by the CIA.<br>
[/quote]<br>
First one was disproved above, as to the second one, biological and chemical weapons were recovered constantly throughout the war and the majority of these are said to be left over from Saddams regime stockpile.</li>
</ul>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>An initial glance at the WikiLeaks war logs doesn’t reveal evidence of some massive WMD program by the Saddam Hussein regime — the Bush administration’s most (in)famous rationale for invading Iraq. <span class="bbcode-b">But chemical weapons, especially, did not vanish from the Iraqi battlefield. Remnants of Saddam’s toxic arsenal, largely destroyed after the Gulf War, remained.</span> Jihadists, insurgents and foreign (possibly Iranian) agitators turned to these stockpiles during the Iraq conflict — and may have brewed up their own deadly agents.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://www.wired.com/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/" target="_blank">WIRED</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:690/361;"><img src="https://media.wired.com/photos/5933d23509f4ce09698ece0f/191:100/pass/97vials_300.jpg" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://www.wired.com/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/" target="_blank">WikiLeaks Show WMD Hunt Continued in Iraq - With Surprising Results</a></h3>

<p>By late 2003, even the Bush White House’s staunchest defenders were starting to give up on the idea that there were weapons of mass destruction in Iraq. But WikiLeaks’ newly-released Iraq war documents reveal that for years afterward, U.S. troops...</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p>As to the third one, I dont see why Saddam gassed an entire town and not just the forces ‘revolting’. The majority of the deaths from the gassing were civilians and in a case like a mass gassing i would call that complete negligence. <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Halabja_poison_gas_attack">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Halabja_poison_gas_attack</a>. Unless you were talking about the act of genocide by Saddam in 1986.[/quote]<br>
Im glad you ignored my entire cited argument and commented on a teeny little paragraph at the bottom.</p>
<p>Oh and just to let you guys know the video was in no way related to the news article.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 04:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MujaheD Radeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mujahed">@MujaheD</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Unhandled, post:4, topic:365749”]I stopped at</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/lVjnL.png" alt width="161" height="81">[/quote]</p>
<p>You should have continued for the laugh, it even went as far as to say these weapons could have been used to target domestic areas in the USA.</p>
<p>Saddam previously possessed chemical weapons as is evidenced by his attacks on the Kurds and he never denied this, however he did claim to have destroyed them. The incidents which you cite of a few artillery shells containing mustard gas and such found buried or hidden honestly look like they were as a result of rogue Iraqi officers hiding them for their own benefit.</p>
<p>Do you honestly think Saddam attempted to bury a few artillery shells containing mustard gas and hence causing them to become unusable, so that he may take over the world with them?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 04:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ll try to give a more in depth respond later, but for now just something that I came across:</p>
<blockquote>In the southeastern corner of the city, American forces came across a “house with a chemical lab … substances found are similar to ones (in lesser quantities located a previous chemical lab.”</blockquote>
<p>That doesn’t mean that it was producing anything for Hussein’s regime. It could be resistance fighters making chemicals to aid their fight against the US.</p>
<p>Besides, from what I’ve read so far all they found was Mustard gas, which everyone knew they had. Technically it’s a WMD, but hardly one that justifies a war.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 12:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yes, Fox news and some other news network were the only ones who also broadcasted the finding of ### warheads sometime back in 05-06. The majority of our news networks are very liberal, so dont be surprised when you see the word fox tossed around in a discussion about a war. But you know, people with their heads on backwards will start the bullshit about Fox making up articles to give the war more hype, its a shame its the <span class="hashtag">#1</span> news network in the world.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 05:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I stopped at</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/lVjnL.png" alt width="161" height="81"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 05:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="365749">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 c|p:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>who are these ‘people’ and please show where they have explicitly cited ‘wikileaks’ in favor of their views only</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well seeings as how wikileaks released this in 2008 but it didnt make headlines till now says something, as wikileaks is always talked about here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 03:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cheese_Police c|p]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cheese_police">@Cheese_Police</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>who are these ‘people’ and please show where they have explicitly cited ‘wikileaks’ in favor of their views only</p>
<blockquote>If you want to confuse a liberal tell them you have to cut down a tree to make room for a windmill.</blockquote>
fuck, i almost choked on my smug for a second there
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Released today, for some reason EVERYTHING is hidden, not just the bad things we do.</p>
<blockquote>Shachtman analyzes the Wikileaks trove. There's no evidence, however, that they were part of any ongoing program as claimed by the Bush administration:
<pre><code>Remnants of Saddam’s toxic arsenal, largely destroyed after the Gulf War, remained. Jihadists, insurgents and foreign (possibly Iranian) agitators turned to these stockpiles during the Iraq conflict — and may have brewed up their own deadly agents...

In August 2004, for instance, American forces surreptitiously purchased what they believed to be containers of liquid sulfur mustard, a toxic “blister agent” used as a chemical weapon since World War I. The troops tested the liquid, and “reported two positive results for blister.” The chemical was then “triple-sealed and transported to a secure site” outside their base...

[b]Even late in the war, WMDs were still being unearthed. In the summer of 2008, according to one WikiLeaked report, American troops found at least 10 rounds that tested positive for chemical agents.[/b] “These rounds were most likely left over from the [Saddam]-era regime. Based on location, these rounds may be an AQI [Al Qaeda in Iraq] cache. However, the rounds were all total disrepair and did not appear to have been moved for a long time.”

The WMD diehards will likely find some comfort in these newly-WikiLeaked documents. Skeptics will note that these relatively small WMD stockpiles were hardly the kind of grave danger that the Bush administration presented in the run-up to the war.

But the more salient issue may be how insurgents and Islamic extremists (possibly with the help of Iran) attempted to use these lethal and exotic arms. As Spencer noted earlier, a January 2006 war log claims that “neuroparalytic” chemical weapons were smuggled in from Iraq. That same month, then “chemical weapons specialists” were apprehended in Balad. These “foreigners” were there specifically “to support the chemical weapons operations.” The following month, an intelligence report refers to a “chemical weapons expert” that “provided assistance with the gas weapons.” What happened to that specialist, the WikiLeaked document doesn’t say.
</code></pre>
<p>I know of no incident when these weapons were actually used against US troops. And the irony, of course, is that it was the invasion that gave insurgents and Islamists access to these remnants.</p>
</blockquote><br>
<a href="http://andrewsullivan.theatlantic.com/the_daily_dish/2010/10/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq.html" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://andrewsullivan.theatlantic.com/the_daily_dish/2010/10/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq.html</a>
<p>Isnt it amazing how people only bring up the wikileaks that feed their opinions, not any that may oppose.</p>
<div class="lazyYT" data-youtube-id="8Dfk0s71BVU" data-youtube-title="Proof of wmd's in iraq" data-width="480" data-height="270" data-parameters="feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque"></div>
<p><img src="http://www.wired.com/images_blogs/dangerroom/2010/10/97vials_300-660x491.jpg" alt width="660" height="491"></p>
<blockquote>By late 2003, even the Bush White House’s staunchest defenders were starting to give up on the idea that there were weapons of mass destruction in Iraq.
<p>But for years afterward, WikiLeaks’ newly-released Iraq war documents reveal, U.S. troops continued to find chemical weapons labs, encounter insurgent specialists in toxins, and uncover weapons of mass destruction.</p>
<p>An initial glance at the WikiLeaks war logs doesn’t reveal evidence of some massive WMD program by the Saddam Hussein regime — the Bush administration’s most (in)famous rationale for invading Iraq. But chemical weapons, especially, did not vanish from the Iraqi battlefield. Remnants of Saddam’s toxic arsenal, largely destroyed after the Gulf War, remained. Jihadists, insurgents and foreign (possibly Iranian) agitators turned to these stockpiles during the Iraq conflict — and may have brewed up their own deadly agents.</p>
<p>In August 2004, for instance, American forces surreptitiously purchased what they believed to be containers of liquid sulfur mustard, a toxic “blister agent” used as a chemical weapon since World War I. The troops tested the liquid, and “reported two positive results for blister.” The chemical was then “triple-sealed and transported to a secure site” outside their base.</p>
<p>Three months later, in northern Iraq, U.S. scouts went to look in on a “chemical weapons” complex. “One of the bunkers has been tampered with,” they write. “The integrity of the seal [around the complex] appears intact, but it seems someone is interesting in trying to get into the bunkers.”</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the second battle of Fallujah was raging in Anbar province. In the southeastern corner of the city, American forces came across a “house with a chemical lab … substances found are similar to ones (in lesser quantities located a previous chemical lab.” The following day, there’s a call in another part of the city for explosive experts to dispose of a “chemical cache.”</p>
<p>Nearly three years later, American troops were still finding WMD in the region. An armored Buffalo vehicle unearthed a cache of artillery shells “that was covered by sacks and leaves under an Iraqi Community Watch checkpoint. “The 155mm rounds are filled with an unknown liquid, and several of which are leaking a black tar-like substance.” Initial tests were inconclusive. But later, “the rounds tested positive for mustard.”</p>
<p>Read More <a href="http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/#ixzz13F7iQDIk">http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/#ixzz13F7iQDIk</a></p>
</blockquote><br>
<a href="http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/">http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2010/10/wikileaks-show-wmd-hunt-continued-in-iraq-with-surprising-results/</a>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 03:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-365749-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/chemical-weapons-were-found-in-iraq-numerous-times-since-invasion/365749.rss">Chemical weapons were found in Iraq numerous times since invasion</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
