<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Minorities End</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minorities-end/176173</link>
    <description>[b]Minorities End.[/b]

“Get your very best clothes on girl!” I shouted up the stairs, trying to keep my emotions back; “Get your very best clothes on.” I whispered, though it was supposed to be shouted I gave up. My back rested against the hallway wall I slid down against it and sat in the darkness. 

	By this time I didn’t expect to fight, or cause a riot. 

I sat for a few minutes in the darkness, thinking of things to say; how to keep Susie calm and get through the crowds. How could it have come to this after all these years? “I’m ready darling,” Said a voice from atop the stairs. “Where are we going it’s so late? And why are there so many people among the streets?” Susie asked after a pause. What could I tell her? I know she is strong, but how could I keep her from panic until the end? “Dear, come here” I paused, “Please just come down here”. “What’s wrong, you sound quite upset?” She asked, detecting my sadness. “Just come down here and hug me.” I asked as she ran down the stairs, nearly tripping at the bottom and falling into my arms. After a minute of embrace I asked her; “Please take my hand and don’t let go.”

We walked through the streets. Cars lay in wreck, some even on fire. “Dave, what is going on!?” She asked me, clinging to my arm. I couldn’t bring myself to tell her what had gone wrong. Instead I kept silent, avoiding the demolished ruins of our once great town, headed for the only place I had once been so alone yet didn’t feel alone at all. I decided on going the least conventional route as to avoid the crowds, through the backstreets of my town. The night was warm; though the sun hadn’t risen all day it still seemed like a hot wind. 

Suddenly out of a small house an old man ran out, screaming and trying to make us follow him in the opposite direction. “Come on lets go, we don’t have any time we have to go and fight, quickly follow me!” The man’s reaction was pleasant yet scary. “Just leave us please” I said calmly. “Come on, we have to go otherwise were all going to die” The man said, grabbing my arm. I twisted my arm and made him let go. “Dave, what the hell is going on?” Susie asked grabbing both my shoulders and looking into my eyes. “Don’t listen to him, just follow me” I said, being interrupted by the delirious man; “Come on girl, come with me, this man is obviously crazy.” The mad man attempted to grab Susie’s arm, seeing this I lost my temper and swung for the man. I stepped back from what I had done; the man lay there on the floor stunned. “I’m sorry, please just leave us be.” I said, “Come on Susie follow me.” The man got up and gave me a glance, he then ran in the opposite direction leaving me and Susie alone at last. 

“Please tell me what’s going on, I’m really scared” She asked me a second time pulling my arm to a stop. The moment came again where I had to choose to tell or whether to keep her in the dark. “I will tell you when we get there, please just keep following,” I kept my words short as I knew the time was almost up and my emotions almost gave way yet again. 

We arrived at the cliffs named after our town, Seaford. I had never been to the cliffs at night, only at day. To my surprise I couldn’t see anyone else there, apart from me and my girl. We walked to the top of the cliffs, Susie still clinging to my arm. As we were half way up 3 fighter jets in formation flew over our heads. “Wow Dave, look a plane!” Said Susie, making me laugh at a past joke we each shared. The sound of the jets afterburners shook the trees around us until they had passed the horizon. 

We reached the top of the cliffs, after 5 minutes of hard walking. I moved close to the edge and took a seat. “Come, sit here” I said to Susie. She walked over, again close to the edge and sat right next to me. I put my arm around her and watched the view, the sky was dark yet the clear skies and the moon left a reflection on the sea. “Please Dave, I’m really scared, tell me what’s going on now?” Susie asked for the final time. I held her close and told her how my day went; I explained how the world was coming to an end. “Instead of fighting and being upset, I thought I’d take you here to be together and watch one last wonder of the world” I told her after explaining of the world’s demise. 

We stood up and looked back over our town, half an inferno, half declining to ruin. I was glad I wasn’t a part of that. What perplexed me was that no one but me had had the idea of enjoying their last moments alive but instead chose to destroy our history and heritage. Whether anyone was to survive I knew out of the billions of people on the earth they wouldn’t pick us.

The cliff shook a little and the noise from the crowds began to die, as we turned around to face the southern seas the whole town that was rioting fell silent. We looked out onto the ocean the fighter jets headed our way; Shooting fireworks of the greatest display. The ground shook some more and the skies lit up bright, the lovers turned to each other for the final embrace. I love you they whispered as the world was destroyed.




______________________________________________________________________________


I thought I would post this here, though i think most of the responses will be Spam I decided to let it out on here.
It is my Coursework for English, its supposed to be &quot;Creative Writing&quot; so I decided to do this. I&#39;d like if you guys could rate/hate/masturbate and correct anything you think should be corrected.

I did have a much longer story that i was going to write, about how the whole day went, and how the end of the world came about. But unfortunately I got to 956 words of that and i wasn&#39;t even quarter of the way through. Of course its gotta be under 1,000 words so i decided to start again.

Thanks for all responses, and I&#39;d appreciate it if you could at least skim read it before posting anything. Ty

edit - just edited it after my sister read through and found a few things i should fix. Ty again.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 19:05:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minorities-end/176173.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Minorities End</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-b">Minorities End.</span></p>
<p>“Get your very best clothes on girl!” I shouted up the stairs, trying to keep my emotions back; “Get your very best clothes on.” I whispered, though it was supposed to be shouted I gave up. My back rested against the hallway wall I slid down against it and sat in the darkness.</p>
<pre><code>By this time I didn’t expect to fight, or cause a riot. 
</code></pre>
<p>I sat for a few minutes in the darkness, thinking of things to say; how to keep Susie calm and get through the crowds. How could it have come to this after all these years? “I’m ready darling,” Said a voice from atop the stairs. “Where are we going it’s so late? And why are there so many people among the streets?” Susie asked after a pause. What could I tell her? I know she is strong, but how could I keep her from panic until the end? “Dear, come here” I paused, “Please just come down here”. “What’s wrong, you sound quite upset?” She asked, detecting my sadness. “Just come down here and hug me.” I asked as she ran down the stairs, nearly tripping at the bottom and falling into my arms. After a minute of embrace I asked her; “Please take my hand and don’t let go.”</p>
<p>We walked through the streets. Cars lay in wreck, some even on fire. “Dave, what is going on!?” She asked me, clinging to my arm. I couldn’t bring myself to tell her what had gone wrong. Instead I kept silent, avoiding the demolished ruins of our once great town, headed for the only place I had once been so alone yet didn’t feel alone at all. I decided on going the least conventional route as to avoid the crowds, through the backstreets of my town. The night was warm; though the sun hadn’t risen all day it still seemed like a hot wind.</p>
<p>Suddenly out of a small house an old man ran out, screaming and trying to make us follow him in the opposite direction. “Come on lets go, we don’t have any time we have to go and fight, quickly follow me!” The man’s reaction was pleasant yet scary. “Just leave us please” I said calmly. “Come on, we have to go otherwise were all going to die” The man said, grabbing my arm. I twisted my arm and made him let go. “Dave, what the hell is going on?” Susie asked grabbing both my shoulders and looking into my eyes. “Don’t listen to him, just follow me” I said, being interrupted by the delirious man; “Come on girl, come with me, this man is obviously crazy.” The mad man attempted to grab Susie’s arm, seeing this I lost my temper and swung for the man. I stepped back from what I had done; the man lay there on the floor stunned. “I’m sorry, please just leave us be.” I said, “Come on Susie follow me.” The man got up and gave me a glance, he then ran in the opposite direction leaving me and Susie alone at last.</p>
<p>“Please tell me what’s going on, I’m really scared” She asked me a second time pulling my arm to a stop. The moment came again where I had to choose to tell or whether to keep her in the dark. “I will tell you when we get there, please just keep following,” I kept my words short as I knew the time was almost up and my emotions almost gave way yet again.</p>
<p>We arrived at the cliffs named after our town, Seaford. I had never been to the cliffs at night, only at day. To my surprise I couldn’t see anyone else there, apart from me and my girl. We walked to the top of the cliffs, Susie still clinging to my arm. As we were half way up 3 fighter jets in formation flew over our heads. “Wow Dave, look a plane!” Said Susie, making me laugh at a past joke we each shared. The sound of the jets afterburners shook the trees around us until they had passed the horizon.</p>
<p>We reached the top of the cliffs, after 5 minutes of hard walking. I moved close to the edge and took a seat. “Come, sit here” I said to Susie. She walked over, again close to the edge and sat right next to me. I put my arm around her and watched the view, the sky was dark yet the clear skies and the moon left a reflection on the sea. “Please Dave, I’m really scared, tell me what’s going on now?” Susie asked for the final time. I held her close and told her how my day went; I explained how the world was coming to an end. “Instead of fighting and being upset, I thought I’d take you here to be together and watch one last wonder of the world” I told her after explaining of the world’s demise.</p>
<p>We stood up and looked back over our town, half an inferno, half declining to ruin. I was glad I wasn’t a part of that. What perplexed me was that no one but me had had the idea of enjoying their last moments alive but instead chose to destroy our history and heritage. Whether anyone was to survive I knew out of the billions of people on the earth they wouldn’t pick us.</p>
<p>The cliff shook a little and the noise from the crowds began to die, as we turned around to face the southern seas the whole town that was rioting fell silent. We looked out onto the ocean the fighter jets headed our way; Shooting fireworks of the greatest display. The ground shook some more and the skies lit up bright, the lovers turned to each other for the final embrace. I love you they whispered as the world was destroyed.</p>
<hr>
<p>I thought I would post this here, though i think most of the responses will be Spam I decided to let it out on here.<br>
It is my Coursework for English, its supposed to be “Creative Writing” so I decided to do this. I’d like if you guys could rate/hate/masturbate and correct anything you think should be corrected.</p>
<p>I did have a much longer story that i was going to write, about how the whole day went, and how the end of the world came about. But unfortunately I got to 956 words of that and i wasn’t even quarter of the way through. Of course its gotta be under 1,000 words so i decided to start again.</p>
<p>Thanks for all responses, and I’d appreciate it if you could at least skim read it before posting anything. Ty</p>
<p>edit - just edited it after my sister read through and found a few things i should fix. Ty again.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minorities-end/176173/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minorities-end/176173/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 19:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-176173-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/minorities-end/176173.rss">Minorities End</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
