<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Fishing/Mining/Firemaking</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fishing-mining-firemaking/431531</link>
    <description>Hey guys,

So I decided to go back to my PI I was working on and I made my skilling area like i wanted, but i have some issues with the skills.
I have placed rocks, from copper/tin to rune and I can mine them all except adamant and rune cause from copper till mithril it says: You need a mining lvl of &quot;..&quot; to be able to mine this rock, which is correct, but with addy and rune, it doesnt come up with any message at all. This is also the case with fishing, there are fishing spots around my skilling area but whenever I click on them, it&#39;s the same as for the rune and addy rocks, it says the coords and object ID, but nothing happens, it doesnt start fishing or says i need some lvl. And for firemaking, whenever i try to light a log, it says: Firemaking is disabled.

I use the source and client from &quot;complete noob project insanity guide + tips on making your own rsps&quot; (something like that)

So I was wondering if anyone knows how to enable these skills so that they work properly.

If anyone could help me out I would be very grateful for that.

Regards,
Derpington</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 18:52:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fishing-mining-firemaking/431531.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Fishing/Mining/Firemaking</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Derpington Derpington]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/derpington">@Derpington</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys,</p>
<p>So I decided to go back to my PI I was working on and I made my skilling area like i wanted, but i have some issues with the skills.<br>
I have placed rocks, from copper/tin to rune and I can mine them all except adamant and rune cause from copper till mithril it says: You need a mining lvl of “…” to be able to mine this rock, which is correct, but with addy and rune, it doesnt come up with any message at all. This is also the case with fishing, there are fishing spots around my skilling area but whenever I click on them, it’s the same as for the rune and addy rocks, it says the coords and object ID, but nothing happens, it doesnt start fishing or says i need some lvl. And for firemaking, whenever i try to light a log, it says: Firemaking is disabled.</p>
<p>I use the source and client from “complete noob project insanity guide + tips on making your own rsps” (something like that)</p>
<p>So I was wondering if anyone knows how to enable these skills so that they work properly.</p>
<p>If anyone could help me out I would be very grateful for that.</p>
<p>Regards,<br>
Derpington</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fishing-mining-firemaking/431531/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fishing-mining-firemaking/431531/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 18:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-431531-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-fishing-mining-firemaking/431531.rss">[PI] Fishing/Mining/Firemaking</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
