<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PROJECT] Minecraft: The Hunger Games</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412</link>
    <description>My little brother has just finished reading [i]The Hunger Games[/i] written by Suzanne Collins. The Games are a really cool concept so maybe it could be transformed to minecraft?

Here&#39;s a quick summary of the the actual Games.

&lt;blockquote&gt;The Hunger Games takes place in an unidentified future time period after the destruction of North America, in a nation known as Panem. Panem consists of a wealthy Capitol and twelve surrounding, poorer districts. District 12, where the book begins, is located in the coal-rich region that was formerly Appalachia.

As punishment for a previous rebellion against the Capitol, every year, one boy and one girl between the ages of 12 and 18 from each district are selected at random and forced to participate in the Hunger Games: a televised event in which the participants, or &quot;tributes,&quot; must fight to the death in a dangerous, outdoor arena until only one remains. The story follows fatherless 16-year-old Katniss Everdeen, a girl from District 12, who volunteers for the 74th Games in place of her younger sister, Primrose. Also participating from District 12 is Peeta Mellark, a boy whom Katniss knows from school and who once gave her bread when her family was starving.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

[b]TL;DR[/b]: Kids ages 12-18 are placed into an unknown arena forced to survive and kill each other, for there may only be one victor..

Although it won&#39;t be identical. The arena will be very large and things such as items will be from the cornucopia, or dropped from above by administrators/Gamemakers.

Some plugins I want to get:

[ul][li]A fatigue mod, making you hunt and eat food - ADDED[/li]
[li]A mod that enhances the natural dangers around you - ADDED[/li]
[li]BoundaryKill - DONE[/li]
[li]Fire restrictions, so one spark won&#39;t destroy a whole forest[/li]
[li]mcMMO - Added[/li]
[li]Factions/alliance system (no land claiming of course)[/li]
[li]Name-hiding mod - ADDED[/li][/ul]

(A specific list of the plugins used will be updated)

Before a the Games start, each player will have an opportunity to train skills to gain advantages in the arena:

[B]Taming[/B]
Tired of your wolves being pathetic? Well now its time for you to stop being such a pathetic beast handler and increase your skill in Taming. Taming increases by engaging in combat with your Tamed wolves. Levels of Taming will offer benefits to your wolves such as damage reduction versus explosions, fire, fall damage, and all incoming damage. Offensive skills that increase the damage of the wolves and offer critical strike chance and a DoT applied to foes unlucky enough to be &quot;Gored&quot; by your wolves.

[B]Mining[/B]
Mining increases depending on the materials you mine. Mining ores will give much more XP than just mining stone. How much XP depends entirely on the rarity of the ore. Diamond and Lapis give the highest XP. High skill levels give blocks the chance to drop double the normal items, get this high enough and it will be guaranteed.

[B]Woodcutting[/B]
Its finally time to show the tree huggers who&#39;s boss, cutting down trees is the only way to level this currently. Higher skill levels will allow a double drop proc to happen, and if your skill is high enough it will be guaranteed.

[B]Repair[/B]
Thousands of days of being obsessed with dwarven craftsmanship will finally pay of, gained by reforging old and battered equipment, this skill helps the player use less resources when repairing with an anvil. Anvils are constructed via 9 Iron Ingots in a crafting table (Iron Block).

[B]Unarmed[/B]
Punching the hell out of monsters will gain you experience, but you shalt not be rewarded from abusing farm animals. Really, wheres the fun in taking out your aggression on Pigs? With this skill players can actually make unarmed useful for combat, great for combat even. Get this high enough and you can disarm what other players are holding and drop it to the ground.

[B]Archery[/B]
Shooting arrows was cool in vanilla minecraft... for about 5 minutes, this skill is looking to change that as archery will let your damage increase at higher levels, and you can eventually daze players providing a very beneficial pvp benefit. Higher levels of archery will let you retrieve arrows from corpses.

[B]Herbalism[/B]
This one is for the harvest moon fans, picking herbs up (flowers, mushrooms) and harvesting crops will help raise this skill. Its benefits include double drops from farming and increasing the effectiveness of bread and stew.

[B]Swords[/B]
This will give you even more reason to stab monsters between the eyes. Gaining skill in swords will help your swordsmanship of course, allowing you to perform a parry. Parries happen automagically and negate all damage. Higher skill levels will lead to parrying more often. High levels of Swords will let your gouge your enemies and bleed them to death.

[B]Axes[/B]
Embrace your inner viking with the axes skill. No longer are axes just for obsessively chopping down forests. With the axes skill, players will be able to do critical hits, instantly killing monsters and causing severe damage to players. As your skill increases, your chance to critically strike will too. At a certain skill level Axes damage will even be upgraded. What axe you use matters for the damage scaling, use a Diamond Axe for maximum damage.

[B]Acrobatics[/B]
Finally the days of spraining your ankle have paid off, no longer will you look down a 100 meter drop with fear. With the acrobatics skill your ability to negate fall damage increases. And how do you negate fall damage? By rolling of course, a secret passed down through the ages. Tap into this mysterious &#39;rolling&#39; ability by falling and training your body. If you&#39;re good enough you will never have to worry about fall damage again.

[b]Will cracked clients be allowed?[/b]
Yes, 

[b]Will flying be allowed?[/b]
No, it will not be allowed.

[b]What kind of mods/glitches are allowed?[/b]
I am thinking of allowing x-raying, since in the book they had some sort of glasses that gave them an advantage?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 11:58:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PROJECT] Minecraft: The Hunger Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Fires have been incredibly nerfed from the past though</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 11:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-411412-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412.rss">[PROJECT] Minecraft: The Hunger Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PROJECT] Minecraft: The Hunger Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reyx7 reyx7]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reyx7">@reyx7</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve seen multiple servers inspired by this idea before.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 20:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-411412-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412.rss">[PROJECT] Minecraft: The Hunger Games</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PROJECT] Minecraft: The Hunger Games</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kingdomkey01 kingdomkey01]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kingdomkey01">@kingdomkey01</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My little brother has just finished reading <span class="bbcode-i">The Hunger Games</span> written by Suzanne Collins. The Games are a really cool concept so maybe it could be transformed to minecraft?</p>
<p>Here’s a quick summary of the the actual Games.</p>
<blockquote>The Hunger Games takes place in an unidentified future time period after the destruction of North America, in a nation known as Panem. Panem consists of a wealthy Capitol and twelve surrounding, poorer districts. District 12, where the book begins, is located in the coal-rich region that was formerly Appalachia.
<p>As punishment for a previous rebellion against the Capitol, every year, one boy and one girl between the ages of 12 and 18 from each district are selected at random and forced to participate in the Hunger Games: a televised event in which the participants, or “tributes,” must fight to the death in a dangerous, outdoor arena until only one remains. The story follows fatherless 16-year-old Katniss Everdeen, a girl from District 12, who volunteers for the 74th Games in place of her younger sister, Primrose. Also participating from District 12 is Peeta Mellark, a boy whom Katniss knows from school and who once gave her bread when her family was starving.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">TL;DR</span>: Kids ages 12-18 are placed into an unknown arena forced to survive and kill each other, for there may only be one victor…</p>
<p>Although it won’t be identical. The arena will be very large and things such as items will be from the cornucopia, or dropped from above by administrators/Gamemakers.</p>
<p>Some plugins I want to get:</p>
<p>[ul][li]A fatigue mod, making you hunt and eat food - ADDED[/li]<br>
[li]A mod that enhances the natural dangers around you - ADDED[/li]<br>
[li]BoundaryKill - DONE[/li]<br>
[li]Fire restrictions, so one spark won’t destroy a whole forest[/li]<br>
[li]mcMMO - Added[/li]<br>
[li]Factions/alliance system (no land claiming of course)[/li]<br>
[li]Name-hiding mod - ADDED[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>(A specific list of the plugins used will be updated)</p>
<p>Before a the Games start, each player will have an opportunity to train skills to gain advantages in the arena:</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Taming</span><br>
Tired of your wolves being pathetic? Well now its time for you to stop being such a pathetic beast handler and increase your skill in Taming. Taming increases by engaging in combat with your Tamed wolves. Levels of Taming will offer benefits to your wolves such as damage reduction versus explosions, fire, fall damage, and all incoming damage. Offensive skills that increase the damage of the wolves and offer critical strike chance and a DoT applied to foes unlucky enough to be “Gored” by your wolves.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mining</span><br>
Mining increases depending on the materials you mine. Mining ores will give much more XP than just mining stone. How much XP depends entirely on the rarity of the ore. Diamond and Lapis give the highest XP. High skill levels give blocks the chance to drop double the normal items, get this high enough and it will be guaranteed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Woodcutting</span><br>
Its finally time to show the tree huggers who’s boss, cutting down trees is the only way to level this currently. Higher skill levels will allow a double drop proc to happen, and if your skill is high enough it will be guaranteed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Repair</span><br>
Thousands of days of being obsessed with dwarven craftsmanship will finally pay of, gained by reforging old and battered equipment, this skill helps the player use less resources when repairing with an anvil. Anvils are constructed via 9 Iron Ingots in a crafting table (Iron Block).</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Unarmed</span><br>
Punching the hell out of monsters will gain you experience, but you shalt not be rewarded from abusing farm animals. Really, wheres the fun in taking out your aggression on Pigs? With this skill players can actually make unarmed useful for combat, great for combat even. Get this high enough and you can disarm what other players are holding and drop it to the ground.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Archery</span><br>
Shooting arrows was cool in vanilla minecraft… for about 5 minutes, this skill is looking to change that as archery will let your damage increase at higher levels, and you can eventually daze players providing a very beneficial pvp benefit. Higher levels of archery will let you retrieve arrows from corpses.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Herbalism</span><br>
This one is for the harvest moon fans, picking herbs up (flowers, mushrooms) and harvesting crops will help raise this skill. Its benefits include double drops from farming and increasing the effectiveness of bread and stew.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Swords</span><br>
This will give you even more reason to stab monsters between the eyes. Gaining skill in swords will help your swordsmanship of course, allowing you to perform a parry. Parries happen automagically and negate all damage. Higher skill levels will lead to parrying more often. High levels of Swords will let your gouge your enemies and bleed them to death.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Axes</span><br>
Embrace your inner viking with the axes skill. No longer are axes just for obsessively chopping down forests. With the axes skill, players will be able to do critical hits, instantly killing monsters and causing severe damage to players. As your skill increases, your chance to critically strike will too. At a certain skill level Axes damage will even be upgraded. What axe you use matters for the damage scaling, use a Diamond Axe for maximum damage.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Acrobatics</span><br>
Finally the days of spraining your ankle have paid off, no longer will you look down a 100 meter drop with fear. With the acrobatics skill your ability to negate fall damage increases. And how do you negate fall damage? By rolling of course, a secret passed down through the ages. Tap into this mysterious ‘rolling’ ability by falling and training your body. If you’re good enough you will never have to worry about fall damage again.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will cracked clients be allowed?</span><br>
Yes,</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Will flying be allowed?</span><br>
No, it will not be allowed.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">What kind of mods/glitches are allowed?</span><br>
I am thinking of allowing x-raying, since in the book they had some sort of glasses that gave them an advantage?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 16:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-411412-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/project-minecraft-the-hunger-games/411412.rss">[PROJECT] Minecraft: The Hunger Games</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
