<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help on Catching Packets and mimicking caught packets</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-on-catching-packets-and-mimicking-caught-packets/103093</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve found a decent open source program that helps me catch packets but I realize that I know very little about how packets operate and the manner in which a server and a select cpu communicate so I was looking for some help.

Since I have caught the packets, I want some basic understanding of what this series of data indicate and how I can manipulate what I send to back to the server on my own via program or other sources.

Explanations, tutorial links, book suggestions or anything better than spam or flames would be appreciated.

The following is an explanation of the game:
What brought about this train of thought was a game called CastleWars on newgrounds.com
It seems that the game engine is run on the computer while the selected moves are sent to the server in order to limit the amount of data processed by the server. So, I thought why not simply lie to the server and have your side of the game do things that it would otherwise not be able to do...
In example, you can use cards in the game, so if I didn&#39;t have a card whose packet code I knew and wished to send, I could lie to the server and claim that I had said card and had played it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 07:15:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-on-catching-packets-and-mimicking-caught-packets/103093.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help on Catching Packets and mimicking caught packets</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aznph8playa aznph8playa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/aznph8playa">@aznph8playa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve found a decent open source program that helps me catch packets but I realize that I know very little about how packets operate and the manner in which a server and a select cpu communicate so I was looking for some help.</p>
<p>Since I have caught the packets, I want some basic understanding of what this series of data indicate and how I can manipulate what I send to back to the server on my own via program or other sources.</p>
<p>Explanations, tutorial links, book suggestions or anything better than spam or flames would be appreciated.</p>
<p>The following is an explanation of the game:<br>
What brought about this train of thought was a game called CastleWars on <a href="http://newgrounds.com" rel="nofollow noopener">newgrounds.com</a><br>
It seems that the game engine is run on the computer while the selected moves are sent to the server in order to limit the amount of data processed by the server. So, I thought why not simply lie to the server and have your side of the game do things that it would otherwise not be able to do…<br>
In example, you can use cards in the game, so if I didn’t have a card whose packet code I knew and wished to send, I could lie to the server and claim that I had said card and had played it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-on-catching-packets-and-mimicking-caught-packets/103093/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-on-catching-packets-and-mimicking-caught-packets/103093/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007 07:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-103093-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-on-catching-packets-and-mimicking-caught-packets/103093.rss">Help on Catching Packets and mimicking caught packets</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
