<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Member Guidelines</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/member-guidelines/516638</link>
    <description>When discussing the potential for members to be added to the MSCP CM rank, please don&#39;t allow personal conflict/grudges to cloud your judgment. Staff and MSCP CMs can view this board, so they can collaborate their views and knowledge to make a well informed decision. You should look at the following (as guidelines) when discussing a member:


[ul][li]Maturity[/li]
[li]High post quality[/li]
[li]Longevity[/li]
[li]Their behavior on the forum in general, such as infraction log, and linked accounts.[/li]
[li]Activity[/li][/ul]


I&#39;d rather not have elitist attitude people in here, at all. As explained in the main sticky, this board should have a pretty high standard. Now that we don&#39;t have a reputation system there is now quantitative way to decide who gets access, so we must take a more qualitative approach to deciding. Please don&#39;t broadcast this board, the user shouldn&#39;t really know they&#39;re under consideration.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 22:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Inside Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/member-guidelines/516638.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Member Guidelines</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When discussing the potential for members to be added to the MSCP CM rank, please don’t allow personal conflict/grudges to cloud your judgment. Staff and MSCP CMs can view this board, so they can collaborate their views and knowledge to make a well informed decision. You should look at the following (as guidelines) when discussing a member:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Maturity[/li]<br>
[li]High post quality[/li]<br>
[li]Longevity[/li]<br>
[li]Their behavior on the forum in general, such as infraction log, and linked accounts.[/li]<br>
[li]Activity[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>I’d rather not have elitist attitude people in here, at all. As explained in the main sticky, this board should have a pretty high standard. Now that we don’t have a reputation system there is now quantitative way to decide who gets access, so we must take a more qualitative approach to deciding. Please don’t broadcast this board, the user shouldn’t really know they’re under consideration.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/member-guidelines/516638/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/member-guidelines/516638/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 22:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-516638-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/member-guidelines/516638.rss">Member Guidelines</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
