<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Deltascape logout timer</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735</link>
    <description>how do i remove it? ;D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 07:43:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Deltascape logout timer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Girona Girona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/girona">@Girona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“powerknite7, post:1, topic:276738”][quote author=Girona link=topic=365387.msg2771559#msg2771559 date=1241163190]<br>
Powerknite7, learn English please. I feel like I want to cut my throat everytime I see your posts.</p>
<ol>
<li>Why would he need a Byte Searcher if you’re sure it’s in Client.java?</li>
<li>You suck at English!</li>
<li>You suck at helping people!</li>
<li>You just, suck!</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Atrix676, if you are sure it’s in a file like Powerknite7 above said his sure it’s in Client, you won’t need to download anything, just open it, get ya keyboard ready, CTRL+F, search</span><br>
[/quote]<br>
u’re rlly sad reported becous of off lang(privmassage) + u posted wrong help if axtrix client crashed ur faulth haha…[/quote]I read that, sorry, but you’re the sad one here. Seriously, look at all the other people who don’t get an infraction towards there account when they say <span class="bbcode-b">FUCK</span>? You think you are going to get me muted becasue I said <span class="bbcode-b">FUCK</span> in a PM to you? That is sad.</p>
<p>Also you moron you cannot report help that might be wrong if you don’t even know, seriously, if you do that, I am reporting your help because you are wrong - also how is it going to crash? Haha, seriously, you’re making me laugh.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: May 01, 2009, 01:56:43 am[/size][hr][quote=“powerknite7”]uhm correction , u said "fucktards who just go around thinking there on top insulting everyone.</p>
<p>Well guess what, you’re not on top, you’re a fucking bitch-ass nerd" and ur problem , look at you whou you think YOU are , iam trying to help peeps u yust say what rule you broke ,… when peeps break rule there is a report to moderator tab ,.  and i dont think iam on top becous i said , use report to mod option … so now stfu…[/quote]Is that all you do, you get heart-broken that members don’t like you so you report them? No, I actually try to help, you don’t even know what the <span class="bbcode-b">HELL</span> you are talking about! Yes, I say what rules they broke, I also report them, so moderators just don’t fucking mute them and don’t give a reason why so they know next time what they did?!</p>
<p>And no, I don’t think I am on top, that is just exactly you, I’ve gone through your last post, you’re just like that other retard BMTH, releasing shit that’s already been posted on page 1, insulting people with basic shit as <span class="bbcode-b">Homo, bitch, slut, noob</span> nothing else, cause you can’t think of a fucking good insult, I’m sick of you people on MoparScape, it is bloody ruining it. Seriosuly, just get the fuck off, come back when you “lern propr englash” and when you can follow actual rules, know what to report and what not to report, know how to actually help people, know how to understand what the fuck is going on before you post.</p>
<p>You probably don’t even know what a Boolean is, you probably just Googled your way out of the MoparScape Quiz like all the other losers like you on MoparScape, Umair was one of them he literally begged people to help them finish the Quiz because he <span class="bbcode-b">could not fucking read that you can Google search the answers!</span></p>
<p>Seriously, MoparScape hates the <span class="bbcode-b">FUCK</span> out of dickheads like you, just get off, learn English, learn Java, study the rules, stay the fuck out until you can do that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 07:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-276735-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735.rss">Deltascape logout timer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Deltascape logout timer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Girona Girona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/girona">@Girona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Powerknite7, learn English please. I feel like I want to cut my throat everytime I see your posts.</p>
<ol>
<li>Why would he need a Byte Searcher if you’re sure it’s in Client.java?</li>
<li>You suck at English!</li>
<li>You suck at helping people!</li>
<li>You just, suck!</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Atrix676, if you are sure it’s in a file like Powerknite7 above said his sure it’s in Client, you won’t need to download anything, just open it, get ya keyboard ready, CTRL+F, search</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 07:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-276735-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735.rss">Deltascape logout timer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Deltascape logout timer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>how do i remove it? ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 06:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-276735-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/deltascape-logout-timer/276735.rss">Deltascape logout timer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
