<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The consistency of Mopar</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719</link>
    <description>It&#39;s an interesting subject - Moparisthebest, MoparScape, GameDev, and finally MoparCraft all follow the same theme in that we supposedly support game hacking, and/or what would be viewed as cheating and experimenting with the game and its mechanics, but to what extent should Mopar support a rule-breakers view of the game at hand. We offer a cracked client, and go to extreme lengths to do so and ensure server upkeep while doing so but at what cost? The idea of this topic is to balance the books in terms of what each part of MoparCraft costs, and how much we have to give it.

Because right now, the server setup is largely correct and this is by no means a map reset vote, or anything like it. The first topic is cracked clients, the most taxing of all things on MoparCraft we go to extreme lengths to manage the upkeep and stability of the server while allowing these clients, largely, people agree that the players coming in from cracked clients aren&#39;t worth having anyhow (obviously, not all) and that if we disallowing cracked clients complex systems (to most of the traffic) could be removed like /login thus increasing the player activity (in theory).

On the flipside there are issues, for example, it&#39;s traditional for the players of MoparCraft to be able to play cracked so we may loose players, and even staff, which doesn&#39;t make the community look very good and caring if we&#39;re simply forcing loyal players out of the server community it also means that we potentially close off to a large portion of the MC community, those who haven&#39;t paid which could in turn lower the server activity (or more, incoming traffic) but I&#39;d put this down to the argument of quality vs quantity. Do we want an active community mainly composed of ban evaders, or rather an active community which will take time to grow composed of easily manageable people. Personally, for me disabling cracked clients is building on a bedrock foundation, whereas continually allowing them is building on an unstable and sandy foundation which as already proven cannot be sustained, and comes with terrible upkeep.

The second subject is that of the forums, we&#39;ve spent unbelievable amounts of time arguing over the server, implementing changes and what not but the forum seems to get ignored which I disagree with, just like Moparscape people get bored of what the forum is supposed to be about so stick around for the community and not so much the topic of the forum, this happens everywhere but more so with Minecraft, keeping an interest in the game for long periods of time won&#39;t happen for a lot of people even now with low activity such things are evident with people only coming back for updates this is why the focus needs to be not only on the server but rather on every aspect of MoparCraft including the website. 

I don&#39;t really have as much time as I&#39;d like to post long long topics, so I&#39;ve compressed the detail, but if you&#39;d like to discuss it properly I can always be found on the IRC. Now I have no intention of forcing this on anyone, or arguing beyond imagination for my points simply because I have too much other stuff to be doing so don&#39;t feel threatened by this proposition, I&#39;ve posted it in the staff section for a reason.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 02:49:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The consistency of Mopar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@omgilikepie omgilikepie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omgilikepie">@omgilikepie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>MITB makes a good point there. Having integration is/will be very helpful.</p>
<p>Rep++</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 02:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-463719-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719.rss">The consistency of Mopar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The consistency of Mopar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You are also completely ignoring the fact that /login gives us our forum integration, if that’s removed, there would be no reliable way of hooking up a minecraft account to a forum account, and then banning and anything else we want to do in the future like stats becomes impossible.</p>
<p>There are thousands of servers that require you to have a ‘paid’ client, MoparCraft certainly isn’t going to stick out in that crowd.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 01:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-463719-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719.rss">The consistency of Mopar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The consistency of Mopar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@omgilikepie omgilikepie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/omgilikepie">@omgilikepie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>While it may be “Harsh, but life” it still goes against what Mopar has always been about imo. Also, like Jamie said, with doing this we will probably lose a whole bunch of current active players, while some may already not be active, there is a decent majority that is. Players will come and go no matter what you do. Some get bored of the game, some have college/work, etc. Not sure if it would be a deciding factor or not, but I don’t want to think about the crazy mess of having to change over in game names, lwc, etc. to the new account names if people were to buy the game afterwards.</p>
<p>Yes, it will most likely bring more players, due to the fact of the people that play minecraft often will most of the time actually buy the game. That does not mean they will stay though, (Repeating myself here) because it is always uncertain what may come up in life to prevent us. There is also the fact that they may not like the plugins that we use. It seems like most people stray away from being vanilla now and want hundreds of plugins that just ruin a server I believe. While I do admit that is not everyone, from what I’ve seen, they do.</p>
<p>Unless I’m wrong, people who have bought the game can get on our server too can they not? I know Triston bought it and got his name changed over and all. So in all honesty if that is true, then making it where you can only connect with paid accounts would just get rid of xauth and maybe some of the cracked client griefers, they still do exist on paid accounts though. Jamie said in another topic that he posted today I think? an idea about having a way to register on the game that links your account already.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-463719-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719.rss">The consistency of Mopar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The consistency of Mopar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well it’s on the table as far as I’m concerned, we don’t even have what you may call an active playerbase so the minimum amount of members that loose out may have to get over it. If a plan is devised I doubt that would be the stopping factor at all.</p>
<p>The same logic you used to justify closing the server to cracked players can to be applied to that of loyal cracked players. It’s harsh, but it’s life.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 18:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-463719-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719.rss">The consistency of Mopar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The consistency of Mopar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kickingjamie kickingjamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kickingjamie">@kickingjamie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s hard to decide whether or not we want people who play with the cracked or without. I think I’d rather see a decently sized community over a massive community of rule breakers etc.</p>
<p>I only started playing minecraft with a cracked client and used it for a long time, cracked clients do tend to bring a lot of non serious players but you do occasionally get the decent player who wants to play minecraft and for whatever reason cannot buy it, closing the server to them seems harsh but it may end up being for the best.</p>
<p>Also if changing so we only allow cracked clients means that some of our current active players cant play anymore I highly suggest you don’t do it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 17:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-463719-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719.rss">The consistency of Mopar</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The consistency of Mopar</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s an interesting subject - Moparisthebest, MoparScape, GameDev, and finally MoparCraft all follow the same theme in that we supposedly support game hacking, and/or what would be viewed as cheating and experimenting with the game and its mechanics, but to what extent should Mopar support a rule-breakers view of the game at hand. We offer a cracked client, and go to extreme lengths to do so and ensure server upkeep while doing so but at what cost? The idea of this topic is to balance the books in terms of what each part of MoparCraft costs, and how much we have to give it.</p>
<p>Because right now, the server setup is largely correct and this is by no means a map reset vote, or anything like it. The first topic is cracked clients, the most taxing of all things on MoparCraft we go to extreme lengths to manage the upkeep and stability of the server while allowing these clients, largely, people agree that the players coming in from cracked clients aren’t worth having anyhow (obviously, not all) and that if we disallowing cracked clients complex systems (to most of the traffic) could be removed like /login thus increasing the player activity (in theory).</p>
<p>On the flipside there are issues, for example, it’s traditional for the players of MoparCraft to be able to play cracked so we may loose players, and even staff, which doesn’t make the community look very good and caring if we’re simply forcing loyal players out of the server community it also means that we potentially close off to a large portion of the MC community, those who haven’t paid which could in turn lower the server activity (or more, incoming traffic) but I’d put this down to the argument of quality vs quantity. Do we want an active community mainly composed of ban evaders, or rather an active community which will take time to grow composed of easily manageable people. Personally, for me disabling cracked clients is building on a bedrock foundation, whereas continually allowing them is building on an unstable and sandy foundation which as already proven cannot be sustained, and comes with terrible upkeep.</p>
<p>The second subject is that of the forums, we’ve spent unbelievable amounts of time arguing over the server, implementing changes and what not but the forum seems to get ignored which I disagree with, just like Moparscape people get bored of what the forum is supposed to be about so stick around for the community and not so much the topic of the forum, this happens everywhere but more so with Minecraft, keeping an interest in the game for long periods of time won’t happen for a lot of people even now with low activity such things are evident with people only coming back for updates this is why the focus needs to be not only on the server but rather on every aspect of MoparCraft including the website.</p>
<p>I don’t really have as much time as I’d like to post long long topics, so I’ve compressed the detail, but if you’d like to discuss it properly I can always be found on the IRC. Now I have no intention of forcing this on anyone, or arguing beyond imagination for my points simply because I have too much other stuff to be doing so don’t feel threatened by this proposition, I’ve posted it in the staff section for a reason.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 19:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-463719-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-consistency-of-mopar/463719.rss">The consistency of Mopar</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
