<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[508 Request] 508 Server And Client Request [508 Request]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003</link>
    <description>I have a 317 server and client, but i don&#39;t like it becuase there&#39;s no emotes, can&#39;t get shop.cfg to work correctly, and when i open the item.cfg and add an item to the shop it is always the wrong item! So, im just looking around for anyone who has the link to the download that has full emotes working, shop.cfg works, and item list is in order! I am also willing to accept a [Blank]510 Client And Server[Blank] If anyone has it please post it in here so i can download it! [b]OH,[/b] and i almost forgot...... make sure there is a models folder so i can make my own models [b]THANK YOU![/b]  ;)  ;)  ;)
Thanks To - Who Ever Puts The Link In This Post!  :P :cool: :P 

NOTE: If anyone is going to say search it up..........get off this topic now and never come back! I only want the link not for people to say search it because you&#39;ll have to find someone elses client and modify it all! Thats way to hard so someone just put the link in this post then everyone else may download the dang thing......      :rolleyes:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 21:08:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[508 Request] 508 Server And Client Request [508 Request]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Evil1 Evil_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evil1">@Evil1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There are several modifications to the rules, as well as a reformatting. Due to such changes, the new rules are being posted here instead of being updated in the old topic.</p>
<p>All of the following rules <em>must</em> be followed while posting in this section. Failure to do so will result in a lock and possible warnings or moderations.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">1. All topics in this section must be requests for help on a server. Any non-server related questions will be locked. Requesting a host, ‘coder’/programmer, server or client, or asking about a VPS also falls under being non-server related. That means for other sections on this site too.</span></p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>All topic bodies must follow this post.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>We are not a Spoonfeeding community. We do not teach in an oversimplified manner to discourage independent thought. We encourage independent thought, meaning you must help yourselves before requesting help. Failure to provide some sort of prior knowledge or work to the problem will result in a lock of the topic. This is final.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Excessive spamming or flaming, as a rule of thumb, will result in one to two week warnings or moderations. Repetitive excessive flaming will result in worse punishments. This means, the more posts full of excessive flaming there are in the topics, the worse each punishment will be individually. Same applies to spamming.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make sure the titles of your topics are easy to read and are completely relevant to the topic at hand. Though this rule may be bent from time to time, make sure you follow it. A moderator on a bad day could easily lock a topic for breaking this rule.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Advertising is strictly forbidden in this section AND all others. Multiple advertising will result in a mute or a ban as advertising is getting out of hand. Take it to the Server Status page located HERE.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>All the above rules may change time to time. The above rules are not exact, they are mere center guidelines for moderators. A moderator is not required to reply to a topic they locked, though they are encouraged to. The above are also mere major rules that apply throughout the section, but if a moderator has their own reason in locking a topic, so may it be.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 21:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375003-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003.rss">[508 Request] 508 Server And Client Request [508 Request]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[508 Request] 508 Server And Client Request [508 Request]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tom Tom]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tom">@Tom</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No requests as far as I know.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 19:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375003-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003.rss">[508 Request] 508 Server And Client Request [508 Request]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[508 Request] 508 Server And Client Request [508 Request]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ipwnu2day ipwnu2day]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ipwnu2day">@ipwnu2day</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have a 317 server and client, but i don’t like it becuase there’s no emotes, can’t get shop.cfg to work correctly, and when i open the item.cfg and add an item to the shop it is always the wrong item! So, im just looking around for anyone who has the link to the download that has full emotes working, shop.cfg works, and item list is in order! I am also willing to accept a [Blank]510 Client And Server[Blank] If anyone has it please post it in here so i can download it! <span class="bbcode-b">OH,</span> and i almost forgot… make sure there is a models folder so i can make my own models <span class="bbcode-b">THANK YOU!</span>  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:">  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"><br>
Thanks To - Who Ever Puts The Link In This Post!  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/cool.png?v=5" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"> <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p>NOTE: If anyone is going to say search it up…get off this topic now and never come back! I only want the link not for people to say search it because you’ll have to find someone elses client and modify it all! Thats way to hard so someone just put the link in this post then everyone else may download the dang thing…      :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 19:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-375003-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-request-508-server-and-client-request-508-request/375003.rss">[508 Request] 508 Server And Client Request [508 Request]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
