<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Revolution 2006-2007 remake #</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-2006-2007-remake/534500</link>
    <description>[center][b]Introduction:[/b]
Hello, and welcome to Revolution2006! We are a new revolution of remakes, this server is already longer than 1 month under development and the amount of content we have on this server is literally stunning. We have daily update batches released in our Update&#39;s section on the forums and if we look at the content of the server; &#39;Compared to any other server, have do definitely have the most content!&#39;. Now we are about done with the content we need players, so we try to become a bit more known. People might think that this will not be a succes, but we will definitely be! We might add a bit more costum content and we will advertise alot! So feel free to register on our forums and join today!!

[size=14pt]Our site :[/size]
revolution-2006.webs.com

[b]Our Gameplay:[/b]
Because we have a stunning amount of content it makes it all alot easier to play! The game become more &#39;complete&#39;. All the little things, thei&#39;re added! You can get you&#39;re beads from Aggie, you can milk cows, you can do what ever you want to! Everything is added well... Almost everything, literally everything will take us another little while to add.. But we&#39;ll do that over-time! Playing this server, is really easy!

[b]Features:[/b]
    - Great Economy. You can earn money by doing every single skill.
    - Every single skill is trainable. Total of twenty-one to choose from.
    - Custom, but decent Quests. Total of four to choose from.
    - Great combat system and triangle, which is quite important between danger zone users.
    - Easy usable teleporting by emotion tab and commands, like it used to be on classic private server.
    - More then twenty custom Treasure Trail tasks. Start them by killing monsters and finding your own clue scrolls.
    - Well coded chatting system. Ability to turn your chat offline or &#39;friends only&#39; and guests will see you offline. Very useful for known people, who doesn&#39;t want to be disturbed.
    - Very creative home area. A lot of features can be found right there.
    - Online browser client, for people that don&#39;t want to download a browser client.
    - Deskop clients also are available, for people that doesn&#39;t want to play from browsers.
    - HighScores to battle for best ranks and titles, automatically updated every three hours.
    - Player killing table, which lists our server Top 100 best player killers.
    - Monthly community events and wars between player made clans.
    - Great and respectful administrators, who doesn&#39;t spawn or cheat, but play fairly as other players.
    - Friendly, nice community and amazing moderators.
- As you know, we are going for perfection; 100% perfection! So everything we&#39;ve had back there in 2006 will be added on this server, including all it&#39;s minigames and activities! Castle Wars, Pest control and so forth. All the succesful minigame&#39;s and random event&#39;s are added to our server! Random sandwich lady, random Tree spirit/troll, Pheasant&#39;s random event, to much to mention! We love it to see players teleporting away by a random event, knowing they&#39;ll be rewarded afterwards! We have astrong and powerful dedicated server to host our server on so 0% lagg is absolutely gantureed
[/center]
[url=http://postimg.org/image/ozyspryyp/][img]http://s8.postimg.org/ozyspryyp/Picture.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://postimg.org/image/ps1goz35t/][img]http://s8.postimg.org/ps1goz35t/Picture2.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://postimg.org/image/yhyjptkn5/][img]http://s8.postimg.org/yhyjptkn5/Picture6.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://postimg.org/image/6cqovv9vl/][img]http://s8.postimg.org/6cqovv9vl/Picture9.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://postimg.org/image/nbznb4l35/][img]http://s8.postimg.org/nbznb4l35/Picture4343.png[/img][/url]

[url=http://postimg.org/image/ylsd62q4h/][img]http://s8.postimg.org/ylsd62q4h/Picture59459.png[/img][/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 01:51:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-2006-2007-remake/534500.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Revolution 2006-2007 remake #</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Flame3 John]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/flame3">@Flame3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Stay on topic, please.<br>
Good luck with the server, raze.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-2006-2007-remake/534500/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-2006-2007-remake/534500/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 01:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534500-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-2006-2007-remake/534500.rss">Revolution 2006-2007 remake #</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Revolution 2006-2007 remake #</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@raze9999 raze9999]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/raze9999">@raze9999</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Introduction:</span><br>
Hello, and welcome to Revolution2006! We are a new revolution of remakes, this server is already longer than 1 month under development and the amount of content we have on this server is literally stunning. We have daily update batches released in our Update’s section on the forums and if we look at the content of the server; ‘Compared to any other server, have do definitely have the most content!’. Now we are about done with the content we need players, so we try to become a bit more known. People might think that this will not be a succes, but we will definitely be! We might add a bit more costum content and we will advertise alot! So feel free to register on our forums and join today!!</p>
<p>[size=14pt]Our site :[/size]<br>
<a href="http://revolution-2006.webs.com" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">revolution-2006.webs.com</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Our Gameplay:</span><br>
Because we have a stunning amount of content it makes it all alot easier to play! The game become more ‘complete’. All the little things, thei’re added! You can get you’re beads from Aggie, you can milk cows, you can do what ever you want to! Everything is added well… Almost everything, literally everything will take us another little while to add… But we’ll do that over-time! Playing this server, is really easy!</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Features:</span><br>
- Great Economy. You can earn money by doing every single skill.<br>
- Every single skill is trainable. Total of twenty-one to choose from.<br>
- Custom, but decent Quests. Total of four to choose from.<br>
- Great combat system and triangle, which is quite important between danger zone users.<br>
- Easy usable teleporting by emotion tab and commands, like it used to be on classic private server.<br>
- More then twenty custom Treasure Trail tasks. Start them by killing monsters and finding your own clue scrolls.<br>
- Well coded chatting system. Ability to turn your chat offline or ‘friends only’ and guests will see you offline. Very useful for known people, who doesn’t want to be disturbed.<br>
- Very creative home area. A lot of features can be found right there.<br>
- Online browser client, for people that don’t want to download a browser client.<br>
- Deskop clients also are available, for people that doesn’t want to play from browsers.<br>
- HighScores to battle for best ranks and titles, automatically updated every three hours.<br>
- Player killing table, which lists our server Top 100 best player killers.<br>
- Monthly community events and wars between player made clans.<br>
- Great and respectful administrators, who doesn’t spawn or cheat, but play fairly as other players.<br>
- Friendly, nice community and amazing moderators.</p>
<ul>
<li>As you know, we are going for perfection; 100% perfection! So everything we’ve had back there in 2006 will be added on this server, including all it’s minigames and activities! Castle Wars, Pest control and so forth. All the succesful minigame’s and random event’s are added to our server! Random sandwich lady, random Tree spirit/troll, Pheasant’s random event, to much to mention! We love it to see players teleporting away by a random event, knowing they’ll be rewarded afterwards! We have astrong and powerful dedicated server to host our server on so 0% lagg is absolutely gantureed<br>
[/center]<br>
<a href="http://postimg.org/image/ozyspryyp/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://s8.postimg.org/ozyspryyp/Picture.png" alt width="" height=""></a>
</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="http://postimg.org/image/ps1goz35t/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://s8.postimg.org/ps1goz35t/Picture2.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://postimg.org/image/yhyjptkn5/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://s8.postimg.org/yhyjptkn5/Picture6.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://postimg.org/image/6cqovv9vl/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://s8.postimg.org/6cqovv9vl/Picture9.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://postimg.org/image/nbznb4l35/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://s8.postimg.org/nbznb4l35/Picture4343.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p><a href="http://postimg.org/image/ylsd62q4h/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://s8.postimg.org/ylsd62q4h/Picture59459.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-2006-2007-remake/534500/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-2006-2007-remake/534500/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 15:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-534500-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/revolution-2006-2007-remake/534500.rss">Revolution 2006-2007 remake #</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
