<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Clients and Servers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162</link>
    <description>As most of you already know by now (if you know me :)) I am a more hands on and visual person who learns from examples, well I got this example of a server to client code, which i understand the basics of and can now modify slightly or carry it over to another program. I have managed to stop the client from closing its socket after performing a task so i can reuse it.

But now I want to make it so every time a client connects, a new id is assigned to them (while still having the older one open) and they can choose their ID (they set their id in the client, I would like to make it so when one client presses save, the file gets saved on the server.

Any help with this please? Sample code appreciated :)

I would like AT LEAST 15 users to be able to connect, but more would help. (my application is a database sort, but also a integrated chat to communicate)

I read the knock knock tutorial on sun and this code:
http://www.kodejava.org/examples/216.html  &lt;-- this taugth me more then stuff on sun o.o</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 04:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Clients and Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@quest_rs quest rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/quest_rs">@quest_rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sorry but I’m no English genius as it is not my first language or 2nd or even close (ollie and frank please consider that and try to interpret things from other perspectives and not just assuming a person leeches for the hell of it). I think everyone misunderstood what I was requesting. I know java is about understanding the concept to be able to apply it, and explanation is what I was asking for, sometimes even an example code just to see how things fit. Just because I did not understand the knock knock example I requested another one on here (which sdouble broke down into a more simple, THANK YOU!) unlike other members on here who are arrogant for having a “java guru” gif attached under their users.</p>
<p>If I needed just code for a chat server and client I know my way to google, but I wanted to understand this idea of assigning ID’s or even know where to begin (sure the server but wdf?).</p>
<p>And I asked for this explanation because I am not making a chat/server program, but it is similar. The application is more of a database.</p>
<p>Thanks once again sdouble and  VB7 Rocks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204162-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss">Clients and Servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clients and Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sdouble sdouble]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sdouble">@sdouble</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Anyone can learn how to code.  The trick of programming is knowing how to get from point A to point B.  Having a problem and then developing a solution that solves that problem is what matters.  You said you’ve managed to take the code from them and edit it to be added to another program.  Digging around in a bag of tricks for the answer will not help you in the long run, yet planning something out and then implementing it will.  The hardest part of programming isn’t writing the code, it’s figuring out what you need to do to make that code effective.  With someone giving you the answer this time, you’ll likely never have this EXACT problem again.  Because someone told you how to do it.  But what if you have a problem you’ve never experienced before?  You dig around and there is no answer.  Here’s an example:  You want to write a chat client/server that allows many different clients.  You ask people how to go about doing this, they tell you.  You take what they said then write the code.  Now you want to change the chat client/server into a card game that tracks everything through a database.  What now?  There is a lot to do.  But thankfully, you know how to assign IDs to clients.  But there is all of this other logic you have to figure out.  You have to handle the database connection, the server for the clients to connect to, tracking and dealing the cards, chat with a possibility of private messages, scoring, rules of the games, etc.  Again, writing the code for each is easy.  You connect to the database and do this.  You check the cards that are dealt and do that.  But how do you put it all together?  When do you do each?  How do you manage multiple games being played?</p>
<p>Asking someone to tell you how to do it this time won’t help you in the future when you have something else to figure out.  But figuring out how to piece together your projects from the beginning will make it easier than having a complicated project and not knowing how to plan it out and piece it together because you’ve never had to do that yet.  Simple problems = simple solutions.  But if you’ve never had to figure out your own solutions for the simple problems, when you encounter a difficult problem that requires a difficult solution, you’ll be up the creek because you haven’t developed the experience with solving these problems.</p>
<p>Anyway, an answer to your question: “Assigning an ID” should be no problem.  Think of what all of the clients have in common: the server.  So naturally, the server will be assigning IDs.  It will know which IDs are already used.  When the client connects, make it ask for an ID.  The server says “Your ID is Boat1” and the client says “Thanks, piss off” and now you have your ID.  Client2 connects and says “What the hell is my ID?” And the server says “Your ID is Boat2”  Then the client says “Thanks, piss off”  Now you have 2 clients and a server.  Clients Boat1 and Boat2.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 19:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204162-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss">Clients and Servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clients and Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>there is no analogy that will stop you being an idiot</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 09:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204162-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss">Clients and Servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clients and Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@quest_rs quest rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/quest_rs">@quest_rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ollie, post:5, topic:204162”][quote author=quest rs link=topic=269653.msg2215091#msg2215091 date=1210042485]<br>
I am a more hands on and visual person who learns from examples<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>its easier to say, <span class="bbcode-i">“I cannot code, i like to copy and paste.”</span>[/quote]<br>
oh wow you’re dissing some one who is new to java by trying to manipulate a statement-you deserve a cookie for that.</p>
<p>Seriously, theres something called learning styles, google it.</p>
<p>and frank by “dumified” I meant like an example situation besides knock knock, like relating memory references as rooms in a building with numbers (a real life scenario?), but thanks anyways… i’ll try mopar he’s pretty good at explaining stuff.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 01:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204162-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss">Clients and Servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clients and Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ollie Ollie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ollie">@Ollie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="204162">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 quest rs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I am a more hands on and visual person who learns from examples</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>its easier to say, <span class="bbcode-i">“I cannot code, i like to copy and paste.”</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 01:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204162-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss">Clients and Servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clients and Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>there is no dumbed down explanation</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 11:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204162-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss">Clients and Servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clients and Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@quest_rs quest rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/quest_rs">@quest_rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yes but I dont understand how I can use it to assign a new id to the new connection?</p>
<p>I understand that i have to accept the connection and start a new thread, but how can i give it a specific id so if they click a button, i know which user is clicking the button?</p>
<p>a little “dumified” explanation  :o?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204162-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss">Clients and Servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clients and Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@VB7_Rocks VB7 Rocks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vb7_rocks">@VB7_Rocks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you look deeper into the Knock Knock client/server on the sun website, there’s a MultiThreadedKnockKnock server that can accept multiple connections, I’ll find a link for you in a second.</p>
<p>Edit: Found it, very bottom of this page under the “Supporting Multiple Clients” heading: <a href="http://java.sun.com/docs/books/tutorial/networking/sockets/clientServer.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.sun.com/docs/books/tutorial/networking/sockets/clientServer.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 02:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204162-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss">Clients and Servers</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Clients and Servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@quest_rs quest rs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/quest_rs">@quest_rs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As most of you already know by now (if you know me :)) I am a more hands on and visual person who learns from examples, well I got this example of a server to client code, which i understand the basics of and can now modify slightly or carry it over to another program. I have managed to stop the client from closing its socket after performing a task so i can reuse it.</p>
<p>But now I want to make it so every time a client connects, a new id is assigned to them (while still having the older one open) and they can choose their ID (they set their id in the client, I would like to make it so when one client presses save, the file gets saved on the server.</p>
<p>Any help with this please? Sample code appreciated <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I would like AT LEAST 15 users to be able to connect, but more would help. (my application is a database sort, but also a integrated chat to communicate)</p>
<p>I read the knock knock tutorial on sun and this code:<br>
<a href="http://www.kodejava.org/examples/216.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.kodejava.org/examples/216.html</a>  &lt;-- this taugth me more then stuff on sun o.o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 02:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-204162-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/clients-and-servers/204162.rss">Clients and Servers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
