<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704</link>
    <description>I remember seeing ProjectP2P taken off of Moparscape.org for the fact that it was ran by a complete retard who was out to take peoples money.

Why is RSCE still allowed here? It&#39;s not taking peoples money, but it&#39;s taking out every other server, and not by it&#39;s advertising or because it is a good server.

Kryptix (Luke) had his website exploited by Lukesq (Lukeidiot). After his website was &#39;hacked&#39; into, he started talking to the hacker. Who told him of atleast 5 different exploits in the RSCD source. And ever since then every &#39;new server&#39; that comes about, gets hacked and redirected into RSCE. 
When the website was hacked Kryptix banned Lukesq. Then he started to talk to Lukesq a lot about how he exploited and exactly what exploits there was, and then Lukesq became unbanned and magically gained 2-3 Party hat&#39;s on RSCEmulation. 
Obviously Kryptix has Lukesq going around hacking into all these websites for him and then giving him shit on his server for that reason.

No, No, I don&#39;t have any &#39;proof&#39; that could really hold up. But everytime a server gets hacked it gets redirected to RSCEmulation.. Is this seriously how it&#39;s going to be from now on? It&#39;s getting ridiculous. Atleast leave this open for discussion.. don&#39;t lock it just because I have no proof. Maybe someone else does?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:25:00 am[/size][hr]Btw, wasn&#39;t Kryptix&#39;s IP found on RSCD under the admin&#39;s account?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:32:01 am[/size][hr][quote=&quot;ecstacy, post:32, topic:314547&quot;]Great server!! would be nice to play, only  thing is kryptix is constantly hacking the server and site............ 

actionpk.sytes.net not takes you to RSCE&#39;s home page[/quote][br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:34:45 am[/size][hr][quote=&quot;pesterd, post:124, topic:301062&quot;]server has not died there are many things that are being done behind the scenes t prevent such an attack again.
please bear in there as the owners of RSCEmulation are the ones behind the attack we urge you to not play their server due to the fags that they are but meh..

the server is being extensively worked on.[/quote][br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:42:01 am[/size][hr]&lt;blockquote&gt;The saddest thing was he said that was a proxy, even though I had already saw the IP here in the RSCE thread. 

Apparently registering on phishing and php/sql exploit forums was something he immersed himself in not too long ago. Someone seems to have a bit too much time on there hands...&lt;/blockquote&gt;[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:44:28 am[/size][hr]&lt;blockquote&gt;Quote from: The_AFKer on November 01, 2009, 07:24:59 pm
76.106.188.14 same IP. Host name: c-76-106-188-14.hsd1.fl.comcast.net

L2proxy.

Sadly this kid deleted our database, he won&#39;t get away with it though. We have all the information on him and we&#39;ll do what we have to.

The server will be up and running soon, with higher exprates for a couple of days since the DB is completly gone and we&#39;ve got no backups of it&lt;/blockquote&gt;
[b]ALL IN ALL RSCEMULATION GIVES MOPARSCAPE A BAD NAME ASWELL AS RUNESCAPE CLASSIC PRIVATE SERVERS. I DON&#39;T SEE WHY ANYONE STILL PLAYS IT, MAYBE BECAUSE THEY&#39;RE BEING FORCED TO BY EVERY OTHER DECENT SERVER BEING HACKED FROM THEM?[/b]

[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:50:53 am[/size][hr]Kryptix (Luke) may seem like a nice guy, and pretend he doesn&#39;t know about any of this shit. But he really does, and he&#39;s all for it. It wouldn&#39;t suprise me if he was the one who paid Lukesq to hack the rest of the servers, I know he gave him shit on RSCE for sure</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 23:34:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="7" data-topic="317757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kryptix/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar">
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>What is considered solid proof?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It would of course depend on what it was proof of.  It is very hard to get solid proof, but an example I can think of is when my server was attacked we found an IRC server with a hidden channel accessed by a password and when you went in there the op kept issuing commands to attack my server, this server was hosted on the same dedicated as an RSC forum.  That is solid proof that that RSC forum was attacking my site.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 23:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve talked to numerous people over the last few months, all accusing others of hacking, attacking, DDosing, cheating people out of their money and everything of that nature.  I have always asked for solid proof of such activity so I could take action against the offender, but when proof is provided it is circumstantial at best and usually proves absolutely nothing.  I have come to the conclusion that whoever is doing this malicious stuff is a complete idiot and furthermore a script kiddie that uses exploits others have written because they couldn’t program themselves out of a cardboard box.  Also, on the side of the people being attacked, you all know I have been attacked countless times in the past and have always managed to find a way to block it and get around it so it has no effect on the server, there is always a way.  At least learn how to do simple, everyday things like looking at logs, null routing IPs and some simple iptables rules.  With a few minor bash scripting skills you can hack up a script in no time to ban offenders automatically by adding it as a cronjob.</p>
<p>Basically, I don’t want to hear about this petty bickering and attacking on this website unless you have SOLID proof of the attacker.  If you request I will help you to the best of my ability to fight off such an attack, but I’m not going to just ban anyone on the slightest chance they might be a skiddie.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 17:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Peter Peeter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/peter">@Peter</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Actually the hacking (read: SQL injection) was done by LukeSQ (yes, I verified this myself) and he also hacked RSCE.</p>
<p>As for every server LukeSQ hacked and directed to RSCE… was because Luke was letting him stay there. It’s something I frown upon and I’ve already told him so. As far as I know, he’s currently banned from RSCE.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 17:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@efs efs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/efs">@efs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ITT: kids who believe that crying “OMG DDOS” will solve the world’s problems</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/14</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 16:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dear_god1 dear god]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dear_god1">@dear_god1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yer all jus’ jealous yo.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/13</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 15:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jessekinss Jessekinss]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jessekinss">@Jessekinss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So many reports against the kid, and like usual, nothing is being looked into.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 14:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ProjectP2P ProjectP2P]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/projectp2p">@ProjectP2P</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="317757">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/kryptix/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar">
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote author=ProjectP2P link=topic=414219.msg3052329#msg3052329 date=1260158781]Your stupid Kryptix, Your not IP banned, You even created an account on there WITH that IP.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Matt, I’ve never been able to access Project P2P from my IP that you claim was attacking your server. Ever since you re-released Project P2P I haven’t been able to view the site or ping the IP address. People would always paste me links saying, “ROFLMFAO LOOK WHAT MATTS DOING NOW!” and I’d be greeted with a “Server not found” error generated by Firefox.</p>
<p>Either you’re lying or your host is clueless, because I have <span class="bbcode-b">not</span> attacked you or anyone else’s server. As you have already discovered, my IP is static and only changes when I request a change. You had my IP from the original Project P2P as you’ve already shown above. There’s a reason why you’re the only person claiming that I DoS attack servers.</p>
<p>Here’s a screenshot to back up my claim:</p>
<p><img src="http://img704.imageshack.us/img704/3132/77181665.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>As you can see, I’m clearly unable to access the website or ping the IP address which also means I wouldn’t be able to attack your server.</p>
<p>Not only that but my UK internet connection is a mere 2mB/s. I never get a download speed faster than 400kB/s. It’s no-where near enough to bring down a dedicated server that’s probably on a 100mB/s connection.</p>
<p>As you said in your previous post, your host provider aren’t exactly the brightest crayon in the box:</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>FYI - I had to act stupid to my dedicated server support people, they barely speak english and understand what the shit I was talking about, so if you speak stupid to stupid… They’ll understand. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you’re really not lying that I completely agree with you. I suggest you ask them to double check as like I said, I’ve never been able to access Project P2P from my IP address ever since you re-opened it.</p>
<p>I know you may well think I’m stupid but you and me both know I wouldn’t be stupid enough to attack a rival server from my own personal IP address knowing full well you’ll go to any measure possible to see me being removed from MoparScape. That would indeed be playing right into your hands. Like I said, if you’re really not lying I suggest you speak to your host.</p>
<p>EDIT: Ah, I see how you quickly edited your post. Did a lie catch up on you?[/quote]</p>
<p>No, I just didn’t bother argueing with you again, it’s pointless. Which is why I removed my post.</p>
<p>But, what time did you take that screenshot? Yesterday morning, for about 7 hours, my website was down due to my provider having technical difficulties. (Says so in my changelog)</p>
<p>EDIT - Looking back in my logs for the server I actually DID re-ip ban you via the system. Why? Because your IP was caught “Dosing” my server. That’s why you OBVIOUSLY cannot access the page.</p>
<p>Have a good December, and good luck to your server.</p>
<p>-Matt</p>
<p>And what are you trying to get on about here? Your showing me nonsense that I don’t give 2 shits for. Anyways, good luck to whoever is trying to get rsce removed from here… probably won’t happen.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 11:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ecko Ecko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ecko">@Ecko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://www.forumspile.com/Post-Can_beat_up_yours.gif" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 11:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@meatstick meatstick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/meatstick">@meatstick</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lukeidiot is a skiddie. /thread</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 11:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bong bong]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bong">@bong</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Braa, post:7, topic:317704”][quote author=Miles` link=topic=414219.msg3051105#msg3051105 date=1260096146]<br>
LOL^</p>
<p>Wasn’t Stork taken off of Moparscape’s advertising for attacking other servers…<br>
[/quote]<br>
Yeah it was, and the same should be done so to RSCEmulation.[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 11:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Braa Braa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/braa">@Braa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Miles`, post:6, topic:317704”]LOL^</p>
<p>Wasn’t Stork taken off of Moparscape’s advertising for attacking other servers…[/quote]<br>
Yeah it was, and the same should be done so to RSCEmulation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 10:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Miles1 Miles`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/miles1">@Miles1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>LOL^</p>
<p>Wasn’t Stork taken off of Moparscape’s advertising for attacking other servers…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 10:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ProjectP2P ProjectP2P]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/projectp2p">@ProjectP2P</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>I remember seeing ProjectP2P taken off of Moparscape.org for the fact that it was ran by a complete retard who was out to take peoples money.</blockquote>
<p>Thanks btw, But Remember, I guarantee you, Kryptix here is taking money as well… and so is angel too probably, so like I said before why did I take the heavy blame for it? Over some simple edited chatlogs, awesome. People believe what they want to believe I guess. Oh and my complete retardedness kept this server running for more then a year and a half so far now? Fantastic. Still up too btw… <em>cough</em></p>
<p>Anyways back on topic.</p>
<p>Luke was DDoSing my server as well.</p>
<p>I gave it to “Moparisthebest” but he didn’t really do anything because according to him, something simple could stop the attack. But even so, it’s still DDoSing.</p>
<hr>
<p><a href="http://i72.photobucket.com/albums/i172/matt1029/lolluke3.jpg" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://i72.photobucket.com/albums/i172/matt1029/lolluke3.jpg</a></p>
<p><a href="http://i72.photobucket.com/albums/i172/matt1029/lolluke2.jpg" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://i72.photobucket.com/albums/i172/matt1029/lolluke2.jpg</a></p>
<p><a href="http://i72.photobucket.com/albums/i172/matt1029/lolluke.jpg" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://i72.photobucket.com/albums/i172/matt1029/lolluke.jpg</a></p>
<p>And yea, there’s his IP.</p>
<p>Do whatever.</p>
<p>AND YES… This is his real IP, I have access to phpmyadmin on a site called RSCSociety, Luke (like a retard) registered there as well, and I saw his IP (same as the one above in the pictures)</p>
<p>FYI - I had to act stupid to my dedicated server support people, they barely speak english and understand what the shit I was talking about, so if you speak stupid to stupid… They’ll understand. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 10:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kurt69 kurt69]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kurt69">@kurt69</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>not accusing but i heard a lot of people saying on action saying that each time it got hacked you (kryptix) logged in for about 2 minutes each time prior to the the hacking. dunno if its just speculation but would be good for you to clear the air about those:D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JUMPHIM JUMPHIM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jumphim">@JUMPHIM</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>THIS IS GONNA BE THE END 4 ALL RSC PRIVATE SERVERS ALL KEEPS WANTED WAS 4 A PK SERVER THATS IT THE GUY IS NOT TRYING TO GET MONEY HE IS PKER THIS IS THE SAME SHIT THAT HAPPENED ON RSCPK THAT WAS A GOOD SERVER BUT THERE WORE HATTERS YOUR SERVER WAS O RIGHT LUKE BUT I BEEN AROUND 4 A VERY LONG TIME I TRY TO PLAY RSC AGAIN AND I JUST DONT WONT TO WASTE MY TIME SKILLING  SO THE ONLY THING THAT I WANT TO DO AT THIS POINT IS PK IAM NOT POINTING FINGERS ANY MORE WHO EVER IS DOING THIS LOOKS LIKE THE SAME GUY THAT DID IT TO RSCPK</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 02:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JUMPHIM JUMPHIM]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jumphim">@JUMPHIM</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>luke who do you think it is and y?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 19:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Braa Braa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/braa">@Braa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I remember seeing ProjectP2P taken off of <a href="http://Moparscape.org" rel="nofollow noopener">Moparscape.org</a> for the fact that it was ran by a complete retard who was out to take peoples money.</p>
<p>Why is RSCE still allowed here? It’s not taking peoples money, but it’s taking out every other server, and not by it’s advertising or because it is a good server.</p>
<p>Kryptix (Luke) had his website exploited by Lukesq (Lukeidiot). After his website was ‘hacked’ into, he started talking to the hacker. Who told him of atleast 5 different exploits in the RSCD source. And ever since then every ‘new server’ that comes about, gets hacked and redirected into RSCE.<br>
When the website was hacked Kryptix banned Lukesq. Then he started to talk to Lukesq a lot about how he exploited and exactly what exploits there was, and then Lukesq became unbanned and magically gained 2-3 Party hat’s on RSCEmulation.<br>
Obviously Kryptix has Lukesq going around hacking into all these websites for him and then giving him shit on his server for that reason.</p>
<p>No, No, I don’t have any ‘proof’ that could really hold up. But everytime a server gets hacked it gets redirected to RSCEmulation… Is this seriously how it’s going to be from now on? It’s getting ridiculous. Atleast leave this open for discussion… don’t lock it just because I have no proof. Maybe someone else does?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:25:00 am[/size][hr]Btw, wasn’t Kryptix’s IP found on RSCD under the admin’s account?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:32:01 am[/size][hr][quote=“ecstacy, post:32, topic:314547”]Great server!! would be nice to play, only  thing is kryptix is constantly hacking the server and site…</p>
<p><a href="http://actionpk.sytes.net" rel="nofollow noopener">actionpk.sytes.net</a> not takes you to RSCE’s home page[/quote][br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:34:45 am[/size][hr][quote=“pesterd, post:124, topic:301062”]server has not died there are many things that are being done behind the scenes t prevent such an attack again.<br>
please bear in there as the owners of RSCEmulation are the ones behind the attack we urge you to not play their server due to the fags that they are but meh…</p>
<p>the server is being extensively worked on.[/quote][br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:42:01 am[/size][hr]</p><blockquote>The saddest thing was he said that was a proxy, even though I had already saw the IP here in the RSCE thread.
<p>Apparently registering on phishing and php/sql exploit forums was something he immersed himself in not too long ago. Someone seems to have a bit too much time on there hands…</p>
</blockquote>[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:44:28 am[/size][hr]<blockquote>Quote from: The_AFKer on November 01, 2009, 07:24:59 pm<br>
76.106.188.14 same IP. Host name: <a href="http://c-76-106-188-14.hsd1.fl.comcast.net" rel="nofollow noopener">c-76-106-188-14.hsd1.fl.comcast.net</a>
<p>L2proxy.</p>
<p>Sadly this kid deleted our database, he won’t get away with it though. We have all the information on him and we’ll do what we have to.</p>
<p>The server will be up and running soon, with higher exprates for a couple of days since the DB is completly gone and we’ve got no backups of it</p>
</blockquote><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">ALL IN ALL RSCEMULATION GIVES MOPARSCAPE A BAD NAME ASWELL AS RUNESCAPE CLASSIC PRIVATE SERVERS. I DON’T SEE WHY ANYONE STILL PLAYS IT, MAYBE BECAUSE THEY’RE BEING FORCED TO BY EVERY OTHER DECENT SERVER BEING HACKED FROM THEM?</span>
<p>[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 05, 2009, 01:50:53 am[/size][hr]Kryptix (Luke) may seem like a nice guy, and pretend he doesn’t know about any of this shit. But he really does, and he’s all for it. It wouldn’t suprise me if he was the one who paid Lukesq to hack the rest of the servers, I know he gave him shit on RSCE for sure</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 07:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-317704-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/rscemulation-why-is-it-still-allowed-to-be-advertised-here/317704.rss">RSCEmulation = Why is it still allowed to be advertised here?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
