<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wtf messed up applet. update: pic, working now. no explanation though</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-messed-up-applet-update-pic-working-now-no-explanation-though/364367</link>
    <description>ok this may be dumb. but i have no idea why it is happening. ok i am just playing around with javascript objects and interactions between java and javascript. last night i got it working like i wanted. did not change any code today. and it did not work at all and was throwing a calling method on NPObject error. didnt get that error last night as far as i know nothing has changed with anything since last night. ok that was the first problem so then i tried fixing it so now i have changed the source code. this is the only method in the applet: [code]public void writeToConsole(String outPut)
	{
		//JSObject window = JSObject.getWindow(this);
		//JSObject objectO = (JSObject) window.eval(&quot;new objectO();&quot;);
		//String outPut = (String) objectO.getMember(&quot;outVal&quot;);
		//int height = Integer.parseInt((String) objectO.getMember(&quot;height&quot;));
		//Graphics g = getGraphics();
	    //g.drawString(outPut, 10, 10);
		System.out.println(outPut);
	}[/code] all that stuff commented out was part of the code b4 i changed it, except for the int height i added that today. that is what is in the class because i decompiled it to see if eclipse wasnt building it but no it was compiled. b4 i didnt have the outPut parameter i was trying something because i can print out to the console from the javascript like this: [code]myApplet.Packages.java.lang.System.out.println(&#39;string&#39;)[/code] so i was thinking if i can pass a string to println() i should be able to a method of mine. that is my current problem. but i am getting weird output. in the code i had set outPut to = &#39;isnt getting the string&#39; and that was beening output in the console and drawing a string in the applet. even though the drawString was commented out. so i deleted making outPut = &#39;isnt getting string&#39;. but that was still printing out to the console and applet even though when i decompiled the class the change to outPut wasnt there. i am just messing around b/c i am bored and wanting to learn somethings, so its not extremely important that i get help but i would like to understand my errors and what is going on. if u would like me to make a vid or take a pic i can get that or need more information i can supply that too. thx
[img]http://hok7wa.bay.livefilestore.com/y1pH9ejLhcR3bKoCpQZFD0jTruhpDhgik3hXbUeLOL0NSA1Ik3lmi5zW3ZM26MGoBW_-G3sH0qWBV589FBkSsPqaNySuuW1iU58/wth.jpg?psid=1[/img]
edit: added a picture of the output coming from a string that doesnt exist... like i said b4 output did = &#39;isnt getting the string&#39; but i deleted it from the code as u can see but some how the code is still receiving it.
edit2: i got back on my computer today and ran the program again, i did not recompile or anything, everything was is the same as it was when i turned my computer off. maybe it was a weird bug idk. does the jvm keep stuff in memory after it has been exited? that is the only thing that i can think of that would have caused this, but it doesnt make sense to me if that would be the case. if anyone has any info pls comment so i can learn. thx.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 02:04:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-messed-up-applet-update-pic-working-now-no-explanation-though/364367.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Wtf messed up applet. update: pic, working now. no explanation though</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xryz xryz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xryz">@xryz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok this may be dumb. but i have no idea why it is happening. ok i am just playing around with javascript objects and interactions between java and javascript. last night i got it working like i wanted. did not change any code today. and it did not work at all and was throwing a calling method on NPObject error. didnt get that error last night as far as i know nothing has changed with anything since last night. ok that was the first problem so then i tried fixing it so now i have changed the source code. this is the only method in the applet: <code>public void writeToConsole(String outPut)
	{
		//JSObject window = JSObject.getWindow(this);
		//JSObject objectO = (JSObject) window.eval("new objectO();");
		//String outPut = (String) objectO.getMember("outVal");
		//int height = Integer.parseInt((String) objectO.getMember("height"));
		//Graphics g = getGraphics();
	    //g.drawString(outPut, 10, 10);
		System.out.println(outPut);
	}</code> all that stuff commented out was part of the code b4 i changed it, except for the int height i added that today. that is what is in the class because i decompiled it to see if eclipse wasnt building it but no it was compiled. b4 i didnt have the outPut parameter i was trying something because i can print out to the console from the javascript like this: <code>myApplet.Packages.java.lang.System.out.println('string')</code> so i was thinking if i can pass a string to println() i should be able to a method of mine. that is my current problem. but i am getting weird output. in the code i had set outPut to = ‘isnt getting the string’ and that was beening output in the console and drawing a string in the applet. even though the drawString was commented out. so i deleted making outPut = ‘isnt getting string’. but that was still printing out to the console and applet even though when i decompiled the class the change to outPut wasnt there. i am just messing around b/c i am bored and wanting to learn somethings, so its not extremely important that i get help but i would like to understand my errors and what is going on. if u would like me to make a vid or take a pic i can get that or need more information i can supply that too. thx<br>
<img src="http://hok7wa.bay.livefilestore.com/y1pH9ejLhcR3bKoCpQZFD0jTruhpDhgik3hXbUeLOL0NSA1Ik3lmi5zW3ZM26MGoBW_-G3sH0qWBV589FBkSsPqaNySuuW1iU58/wth.jpg?psid=1" alt width="" height=""><br>
edit: added a picture of the output coming from a string that doesnt exist… like i said b4 output did = ‘isnt getting the string’ but i deleted it from the code as u can see but some how the code is still receiving it.<br>
edit2: i got back on my computer today and ran the program again, i did not recompile or anything, everything was is the same as it was when i turned my computer off. maybe it was a weird bug idk. does the jvm keep stuff in memory after it has been exited? that is the only thing that i can think of that would have caused this, but it doesnt make sense to me if that would be the case. if anyone has any info pls comment so i can learn. thx.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-messed-up-applet-update-pic-working-now-no-explanation-though/364367/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-messed-up-applet-update-pic-working-now-no-explanation-though/364367/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 02:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-364367-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wtf-messed-up-applet-update-pic-working-now-no-explanation-though/364367.rss">Wtf messed up applet. update: pic, working now. no explanation though</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
