<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Any 718 clients available with a working cache?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/any-718-clients-available-with-a-working-cache/478537</link>
    <description>Hi, I downloaded a nice server with a SOF and a GE but I need a client. I have looked everywhere to try find a working client with a downloadable cache and I just cannot find one. It&#39;s either all the links are broken or the cache doesn&#39;t mix with the client. Are there any working 718 clients? preferably with the Matrix Client.

P.S: Don&#39;t say you fond one in one search or something like that because if you actually take time to look at the link to the client it is usually broken or it just doesn&#39;t work.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 08:36:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/any-718-clients-available-with-a-working-cache/478537.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Any 718 clients available with a working cache?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Krajix Krajix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/krajix">@Krajix</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi, I downloaded a nice server with a SOF and a GE but I need a client. I have looked everywhere to try find a working client with a downloadable cache and I just cannot find one. It’s either all the links are broken or the cache doesn’t mix with the client. Are there any working 718 clients? preferably with the Matrix Client.</p>
<p>P.S: Don’t say you fond one in one search or something like that because if you actually take time to look at the link to the client it is usually broken or it just doesn’t work.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/any-718-clients-available-with-a-working-cache/478537/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/any-718-clients-available-with-a-working-cache/478537/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 08:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-478537-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/any-718-clients-available-with-a-working-cache/478537.rss">Any 718 clients available with a working cache?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
