<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] HybridPVP Godwars!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-hybridpvp-godwars/390456</link>
    <description>Hey guys I was playing around in god wars the other day and I stumbled across there being no boss&#39;s in the chambers :| so I searched there spawn locations and changed them in my spawn.cfg file and i moved the spawns anyways the boss&#39;s are like weird spiders and stuff so i was wondering how do i change the look of the god wars boss&#39;s and make them u know actuarial god wars :P
I cant actually get into some chambers because the client freeze&#39;s up but if i could get the correct boss&#39;s then i could spawn them else were and make like a little minigame out of it :P but if someone knows how to fix this could u please help me?! thanks!

~matt~</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 04:45:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-hybridpvp-godwars/390456.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] HybridPVP Godwars!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hydravision hydravision]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hydravision">@hydravision</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey guys I was playing around in god wars the other day and I stumbled across there being no boss’s in the chambers <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> so I searched there spawn locations and changed them in my spawn.cfg file and i moved the spawns anyways the boss’s are like weird spiders and stuff so i was wondering how do i change the look of the god wars boss’s and make them u know actuarial god wars <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
I cant actually get into some chambers because the client freeze’s up but if i could get the correct boss’s then i could spawn them else were and make like a little minigame out of it <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> but if someone knows how to fix this could u please help me?! thanks!</p>
<p>~matt~</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-hybridpvp-godwars/390456/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-hybridpvp-godwars/390456/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 04:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-390456-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-hybridpvp-godwars/390456.rss">[PI] HybridPVP Godwars!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
