<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help with a model</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-model/354447</link>
    <description>okay, so after running my server and went on my client i found out all of the shortbows come up as a sword under me (but they all fire arrows normally and specials work), but if i go on another client with &quot;working&quot; shortbows they show normally as they would on any other server.  What should i do so that they show normally on my normal client? I believe this is a model problem, but i am new to editing clients so i am not sure.  Help with this problem would be kindly appreciated.  Thank you in advance. :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 02:17:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-model/354447.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help with a model</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@livingpro livingpro]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/livingpro">@livingpro</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>okay, so after running my server and went on my client i found out all of the shortbows come up as a sword under me (but they all fire arrows normally and specials work), but if i go on another client with “working” shortbows they show normally as they would on any other server.  What should i do so that they show normally on my normal client? I believe this is a model problem, but i am new to editing clients so i am not sure.  Help with this problem would be kindly appreciated.  Thank you in advance. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-model/354447/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-model/354447/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 02:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-354447-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/need-help-with-a-model/354447.rss">Need help with a model</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
