<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592</link>
    <description>Ok well GTA:IV came and i booted up the PS3 and played it and first impressions: what a game! It obviously has some flaws but thats ok because you can get around those. Firstly lets start with the single player.
[size=12pt][u]Single Player[/u][/size]
[size=11pt][u]General[/u][/size]
Well the thing that really pisses me off is the controls, they have changed from classic GTA to bloody annoying. But you can choose to have classic controls but these prove to be fiddly and hard to use in the new game so i don&#39;t advise it. The genral gameplay is pretty much classic GTA roaming around beating up hobos and picking up hookers on faggios so don&#39;t expect anything different. Some great new features include being able to pick up objects to lob at unsuspecting fat people and windows. This isn&#39;t as entirely great as it sounds as it doesn&#39;t always work some objects that should be able to be picked up can&#39;t and throwing is almost an impossible task for dead accuracy. 
[size=11pt][u]Missions[/u][/size]
Ok so in previous incarnations of the game you got a big glowing red circle to stand in for a mission, not anymore. It is just a little arrow point down to where you must go this isn&#39;t as showy as before it looks more discreet and keeps realism in the game. Missions in general are typical GTA, go kill some druggies and get my money kill this guy etc etc. Some missions you will receive over your mobile phone that need to be done instantly otherwise it has an affect on the story. By this i mean that if someone, lets says your cousin, calls you and says &#39;i need help please come pick me up&#39; and you decide to do a different mission in place of this one then you get an angry call after completeting the other mission where you find out your cousin has just had his ass spanked by several russian guys and is now at the hospital. Obviously this means you don&#39;t have to do the other mission and instead you get a replacement mission which undoubtedly leads to the same ending anyway. Not all missions are work in the world of GTA:IV some are fun, there is a particularly good mission near the begining where you and your cousin must go and see a show that is on down the road. Obviously you can just press X or whatever you press on 360 and skip this but that is never as much fun. Other more casual missions include taking your girlfriend out on a date to go and play a few frames of bowling. This is a hard minigame and definately tryed my patience. 
Edit: The missions after time start to get samey and reptitive, you often find yourself doing the exact same mission over and over again. Also as you get deeper into the game you start to complete missions just to get them out of the way and not because you want to do them it saps the fun from the game but its not all negative as some missions are exciting and are a laugh but the average run of the mill mission is exactly the same as the last few missions so you soon tire of this and find yourself just roaming the streets blowing stuff up for the hell of it.
[size=11pt][u]Driving[/u][/size]
This is where some of the flaws with GTA:IV come in, my main concern is that when you brake using L2 you cant turn at the same time so you are set going straight. Obviously the handbrake is more use and when you whack a car around a corner at 100mph its alot more fun as you slide around the corner like you should do. Controlling the handbrake turn is incredibly hard in some cars but once you have a knack for it there will be no problems. Just sling the car round and then push in the oppisite direction to counteract the force and you are away. Handling is extremely skewif, in GTA:SA most cars you could sling around like quadbikes and it would be awesome fun. But now you turn too hard the car just spins turn to little nothing happens turn just right you go wide so my advice is stick with the handrake or a sports car. Strictly speaking this next bit shouldnt be under this category but i couldn&#39;t be bothered to make another one, planes are not included in this GTA as most of you will know just to ease anyone&#39;s mind it is not because Rockstar are afraid people will fly them in to buildings its because they just aren&#39;t practical in such a small area which i must say i disagree with. Now for the PS3 owners that have this, i must mention sixaxis. Sixaxis is incredibly fiddly for driving and flying, in a boat its not too bad and on a bike its  acceptable but i must warn anyone trying to do it in a heli that they will crash extremely soon and in a big ball of fire. Speaking of fire something else that concerns me (and i know i sound like a grumpy old man but hell i survive) is the fact that cars are almost impossible to blow up and extremely easy to roll. Those GTA veterans that are reading this will know that the law in GTA is if you roll your car it blows up. Not anymore it is exremely hard now, you can&#39;t even keep crashing into stuff to blow up your car, it just loses power and your engine cuts out. how gay is that?
[size=11pt][u]Storyline[/u][/size]
Its great, more in depth than ever before and it has a purpose for you blowing stuff up and executing people( which you can do in a fantastic menagery of blood thirsty ways) i won&#39;t ruin for those that havnt got the game but the basics is he has come from somewhere in europe( either romain or poland or somewhere like that maybe even russia i cant remember) and he has come searching for the american dream or so he says. After a few missions you find out more as to why he is truly here and it isn&#39;t long before you get your first girlfriend either so the story develops and you can shape to how you want aswell.
[u][size=12pt]Multiplayer[/size][/u]
[size=11pt][u]General[/u][/size]
Generally it rocks, no more info needed :D but of course i will give it to you. It is the first GTA game ever to have online multiplayer GTA:SA had offline multiplayer which frankly sucked, you could only get in one vehicel between the two of you, there could only be two of you and the camera was crappy. So now with PSN and XboxLive GTA:IV has a great online potential. There are several game types from the usual deathmatch to the not so usual cops and robbers. There is of course free roam online where you and a few mates can do whatever the hell you want around the city for however long you want. Gameplay is pretty much identical to offline so no need to worry that you won&#39;t enjoy it because some aspects are tweaked etc. No its perfect, you can get up to 7 people in a party and all climb onto a bus and have a 7 man drive by. Alternatively you can hop on to faggios with your mates and play jousting for a laugh. If you go for the serious games they all revolve around cash and not score. Its not like COD4:MW where you need x amount of kills to win its all about cash which you can win and lose over the course of a game by dieing, killing, jacking rides, and finding it. Its all about money and thats what counts. 
Hope you enjoy my review, as i get further into the game i will edit this more and more</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 20:00:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidude36 Brolapse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidude36">@davidude36</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nohope your bump wasn’t really that well thought out, this thread is quite old and your post didn’t really add anything.</p>
<p>So hey I’m locking it.</p>
<p>Sanga282: In case you want this unlocked feel free to pm me.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/76</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 20:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-76</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hmm dunno bout that</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/75</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 18:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-75</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nohope nohope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nohope">@nohope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>but their was gud reason!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/74</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 12:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-74</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Thebeanie TheBeanie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thebeanie">@Thebeanie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>way to grave dig</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/73</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 06:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-73</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nohope nohope]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nohope">@nohope</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>dis game is gr8 i luv it omg i play it all da time but didnt finish it u no wat im saying</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/72</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 00:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-72</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jme, post:69, topic:202592”]I was kinda bored shooting shit in my apartment place with a sniper, and something caught me eye lol</p>
<p><img src="http://img233.imageshack.us/img233/883/gtabongxs9.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/quote]<br>
Theres always tonnes of wierd shit like that</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/71</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 18:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-71</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cruzer Cruzer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruzer">@Cruzer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The Bohan apartment has a book called Blasphemy &amp; Madness Do’s and Don’ts</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/70</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 09:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was kinda bored shooting shit in my apartment place with a sniper, and something caught me eye lol</p>
<p><img src="http://img233.imageshack.us/img233/883/gtabongxs9.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/69</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 04:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-69</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A little disappointed with the lack of ‘other’ activities available and how little mods are there for Niko.  Ahwell.  It’s still awesome.  Really awesome.  I haven’t been bored of the campaign yet.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/68</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 01:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-68</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>18mb</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/67</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 22:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-67</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="65" data-topic="202592">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/mr.chris/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> Mr.Chris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Edit - Patch is shit, didn’t do jack, lol.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>how big was it?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/66</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-66</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Edit - Patch is shit, didn’t do jack, lol.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/65</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 01:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-65</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="62" data-topic="202592">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/sanga282/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> sanga282:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Ok then <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> do you reckon it will come out on PSP?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The game is too big for UMD which is why they never directly ported the other GTA games to the psp they made newer smaller versions but with same maps etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/64</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 01:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-64</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>YESSS. GTA online patch is out!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/63</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 01:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-63</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“cooper, post:60, topic:202592”][quote author=sanga282 link=topic=267262.msg2216022#msg2216022 date=1210194765]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah Microsoft paid up $50m for exclusive downloadable content for the xbox 360, although the playstation 3 is getting their own dlc near the end of the year.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah i heard about the esclusive content which sucks abit considering it was originally a Playstation exclusive minus the gameboy and the PC</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Gameboy?!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah they had GTA and GTA Advance<br>
[/quote]<br>
Oh, I thought he was referring to a GTA: 4 Port for gameboy.[/quote]<br>
Ok then <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> do you reckon it will come out on PSP?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/62</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 00:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-62</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Jesus christ, GTA sold more units on it’s first day than Halo 3 did on it’s first week.</p>
<p>GTA first week sales have broken any previous launch record for a game, movie or musics first week sales. $500 million dollars in the first week, when they were expecting $400 million and the previous record was by Spiderman 3 with $380 million.</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="http://www.mtv.com/favicon.ico" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="http://www.mtv.com/news/1586971/grand-theft-auto-iv-posts-record-first-week-sales/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MTV News</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:690/388;"><img src="https://mtv.mtvnimages.com/uri/mgid:ao:image:mtv.com:7470?quality=0.8&amp;format=jpg&amp;width=1440&amp;height=810&amp;.jpg" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="http://www.mtv.com/news/1586971/grand-theft-auto-iv-posts-record-first-week-sales/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">'Grand Theft Auto IV' Posts Record First-Week Sales</a></h3>

<p>Game publisher reports that it sold 3.6 million copies on first day of release.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/61</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 00:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-61</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“sanga282, post:59, topic:202592”][quote author=cooper link=topic=267262.msg2215605#msg2215605 date=1210137643]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah Microsoft paid up $50m for exclusive downloadable content for the xbox 360, although the playstation 3 is getting their own dlc near the end of the year.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah i heard about the esclusive content which sucks abit considering it was originally a Playstation exclusive minus the gameboy and the PC</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Gameboy?!<br>
[/quote]<br>
Yeah they had GTA and GTA Advance[/quote]<br>
Oh, I thought he was referring to a GTA: 4 Port for gameboy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/60</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 22:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-60</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“cooper, post:57, topic:202592”][quote author=sanga282 link=topic=267262.msg2215467#msg2215467 date=1210115560]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah Microsoft paid up $50m for exclusive downloadable content for the xbox 360, although the playstation 3 is getting their own dlc near the end of the year.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yeah i heard about the esclusive content which sucks abit considering it was originally a Playstation exclusive minus the gameboy and the PC<br>
[/quote]<br>
Gameboy?![/quote]<br>
Yeah they had GTA and GTA Advance</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/59</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 21:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-59</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Evan1 Evan`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/evan1">@Evan1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“ThugLife, post:41, topic:202592”]GTA IV is a framework for later games in the GTA 4 series, just like GTA 3 had none of those features, that was the framework for vice city and san andreas.<br>
Plus the fact the xbox 360 uses standard dvds for games (Not HD DVD) which the max size for a standard dvd is around 8 - 9gb which restricts the game lots. As you people are basically saying it feels empty and the size of the full game (whats on the disk) is around 7gb they don’t have much room to add extra features do they?</p>
<p>So if you think about it, like many of the pod casts and interviews etc from rockstar developers the xbox 360 is holding back GTA IV and like rockstar have said that the next GTA will not be on the xbox 360 due to the restrictions it gives the game. Think about all the stuff they could add onto it if they was only developing the game for the Playstation 3? As the ps3 actually uses blu-ray for games and a dual layer blu-ray disk holds upto 50gb of data, its already been proven that a 50gb+ console game is possible after konami reports that their new Metal gear solid 4 uses up every single spare kb left on the disks they have to use (All 50gb since they are using dual layered disks.</p>
<p>Back on the point, i know i may seem very defensive of the game but alot of people are not looking at it properly, its an entirely new game like GTA 3 was no one complained about that lacking features or new controls did they? All that bundled with the xbox 360 restrictions is pretty much your reason to why GTA 4 is lacking some of the features san andreas had.[/quote]Probably because gta 3 was really good at the time,</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/58</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 05:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cooper cooper]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cooper">@cooper</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“sanga282, post:56, topic:202592”][quote author=ThugLife link=topic=267262.msg2215466#msg2215466 date=1210115332]<br>
Yeah Microsoft paid up $50m for exclusive downloadable content for the xbox 360, although the playstation 3 is getting their own dlc near the end of the year.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Yeah i heard about the esclusive content which sucks abit considering it was originally a Playstation exclusive minus the gameboy and the PC[/quote]<br>
Gameboy?!</p>
<p>[quote=“sanga282, post:53, topic:202592”][quote author=ThugLife link=topic=267262.msg2215461#msg2215461 date=1210108682]<br>
The old consoles is what held back GTA from realism, the game is not about realism. Rockstar have obviously always wanted to make it as realistic as possible but obviously the old hardware held them back. Plus, you are the first person to complain about the phone feature, i still don’t see any valid argument to why the phone is bad from you. Sure its a new feature and took a while (Minutes) to get used to, but i don’t get how its not better than just having markers on the map pop up and a box in the corner telling you that you have unlocked some missions? Instead one of the old people who you get missions off text you the next persons number or they call you and you get their number stored in the phone, also i’m sure when rockstar thought of the phone that they did not have realism in mind.<br>
[/quote]<br>
At the end of the day it comes down to a matter of opinion but basically i don’t like the phone because you get missions that require a phone to do it just not how the game should be its GTA, its about dodgy meetins in back alleys and bodies in trunks not a mobile phone, next he will have a laptop. But if still you don’t agree then we will have to agreee to disagree because otherwise we are just going to keep posting messages argueing with each other[/quote]<br>
Well, even in the old ones they had phones, I remember them in Vice city [I think LC had payphone missions]. As the real world changes with texting, so does a game that attempts to be as realistic as possible.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/57</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 05:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah i heard about the esclusive content which sucks abit considering it was originally a Playstation exclusive minus the gameboy and the PC</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/56</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 23:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah Microsoft paid up $50m for exclusive downloadable content for the xbox 360, although the playstation 3 is getting their own dlc near the end of the year.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/55</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 23:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>If you read the wiki Article, there is a hint towards new content for the Xbox 360. Or rather a statement.</p>
<p>“It has been confirmed that episodic content will be released exclusively for the Xbox 360. Microsoft officially announced a “strategic alliance” with Rockstar Games over the rights to some episodic content through their Xbox Live service at their X06 event.”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/54</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 22:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-54</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>At the end of the day it comes down to a matter of opinion but basically i don’t like the phone because you get missions that require a phone to do it just not how the game should be its GTA, its about dodgy meetins in back alleys and bodies in trunks not a mobile phone, next he will have a laptop. But if still you don’t agree then we will have to agreee to disagree because otherwise we are just going to keep posting messages argueing with each other</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/53</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 22:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-53</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>GTA:IV - My Review</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tL tL]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tl">@tL</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The old consoles is what held back GTA from realism, the game is not about realism. Rockstar have obviously always wanted to make it as realistic as possible but obviously the old hardware held them back. Plus, you are the first person to complain about the phone feature, i still don’t see any valid argument to why the phone is bad from you. Sure its a new feature and took a while (Minutes) to get used to, but i don’t get how its not better than just having markers on the map pop up and a box in the corner telling you that you have unlocked some missions? Instead one of the old people who you get missions off text you the next persons number or they call you and you get their number stored in the phone, also i’m sure when rockstar thought of the phone that they did not have realism in mind.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592/52</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 21:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-202592-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/gta-iv-my-review/202592.rss">GTA:IV - My Review</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
