<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Brooklyn-Scape 317+ [Looking for Full Team, PM for Reward Details]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-looking-for-full-team-pm-for-reward-details/540447</link>
    <description>[center][b][u][size=18pt]Brooklyn-Scape[/size][/u][/b][/center]
[center][b]Hello, My name is David and i&#39;m currently looking for a coder and a web designer. What i&#39;m looking for is someone who is willing to work hard, and not stop unless the problem is fixed. I&#39;m looking to start a revolutionary RSPS, A Balanced hybrid server. where PvP is just as important as PvM, A server where people are excited to play, and where it takes more than a day to get 99 Everything, I want this to be a server where people who are sick of Shitty RSPS come to play, because we are going to be great![/b][/center]

[center][b][u][size=18pt]Information about Brooklyn-Scape[/size][/u][/b][/center]
[center][b]Brooklyn-Scape will be a medium paced server with Medium EXP Rates, and Medium Drop Rates, where you need to play for more than a day to be a high level, we will &quot;NOT&quot; have any custom items, We will be original RuneScape, I don&#39;t want many custom things, other than custom teleports, and custom commands. Our staff will not be a huge staff group, and only dedicated, well balanced and well experienced players will obtain staff positions. We will be hosting on the best of the best Equipment all paid by me ofc. I will be buying the Domain, Webhost, and VPS, And anything else we may need. I currently do not have any source or a Client, This will all be obtained once i have a codeand web designer.[/b][/center]

[center][b][u][size=18pt]Reward Details[/size][/u][/b][/center]
[center][b]If your intrested please private message me or Email me at davidjmarch1994@gmail.com Either one works.[/b][/center]

[b]Thanks,
-David march[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 16:51:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-looking-for-full-team-pm-for-reward-details/540447.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Brooklyn-Scape 317+ [Looking for Full Team, PM for Reward Details]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zashi2014 Zashi2014]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zashi2014">@Zashi2014</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">[size=18pt]Brooklyn-Scape[/size]</span></span>[/center]<br>
[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Hello, My name is David and i’m currently looking for a coder and a web designer. What i’m looking for is someone who is willing to work hard, and not stop unless the problem is fixed. I’m looking to start a revolutionary RSPS, A Balanced hybrid server. where PvP is just as important as PvM, A server where people are excited to play, and where it takes more than a day to get 99 Everything, I want this to be a server where people who are sick of Shitty RSPS come to play, because we are going to be great!</span>[/center]</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">[size=18pt]Information about Brooklyn-Scape[/size]</span></span>[/center]<br>
[center]<span class="bbcode-b">Brooklyn-Scape will be a medium paced server with Medium EXP Rates, and Medium Drop Rates, where you need to play for more than a day to be a high level, we will “NOT” have any custom items, We will be original RuneScape, I don’t want many custom things, other than custom teleports, and custom commands. Our staff will not be a huge staff group, and only dedicated, well balanced and well experienced players will obtain staff positions. We will be hosting on the best of the best Equipment all paid by me ofc. I will be buying the Domain, Webhost, and VPS, And anything else we may need. I currently do not have any source or a Client, This will all be obtained once i have a codeand web designer.</span>[/center]</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">[size=18pt]Reward Details[/size]</span></span>[/center]<br>
[center]<span class="bbcode-b">If your intrested please private message me or Email me at <a href="mailto:davidjmarch1994@gmail.com">davidjmarch1994@gmail.com</a> Either one works.</span>[/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Thanks,<br>
-David march</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-looking-for-full-team-pm-for-reward-details/540447/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-looking-for-full-team-pm-for-reward-details/540447/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 16:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-540447-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/brooklyn-scape-317-looking-for-full-team-pm-for-reward-details/540447.rss">Brooklyn-Scape 317+ [Looking for Full Team, PM for Reward Details]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
