<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>LFM: Building an open-source scriptable &quot;info client&quot;</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lfm-building-an-open-source-scriptable-info-client/551137</link>
    <description>Basically, I&#39;ve found out that the OSBuddy people aren&#39;t planning on implementing scripting anytime soon. As a result I&#39;ve been wanting to roll my own client, but having no knowledge on (Java-specific) reflection and the internal workings of Runescape, I&#39;ve kind of lost hope that this is something I can do by myself, particularly given the general difficulty of finding up-to-date information. I would be able to learn, and the &quot;mechanics&quot; don&#39;t seem too complicated, but it would take me too long to get the Runescape-specific know-how on my own.

I basically want to create - initially - a bare-bones Runescape &quot;container&quot;. From there, I&#39;d like to build and gradually expand support for reading and interpreting game state, and start designing an API. I&#39;ve looked at a few bots, most of which use more Java for their &quot;scripting&quot; needs. I&#39;d prefer to operate with a different language, though I&#39;m not quite sure which one.

The project would be open-source, not only because it makes it easier to extend and improve, but to serve as an example - based on my own googling, it definitely couldn&#39;t hurt. :D

Does this seem interesting to anyone?  :P</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 19:48:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lfm-building-an-open-source-scriptable-info-client/551137.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>LFM: Building an open-source scriptable &quot;info client&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@matzie matzie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/matzie">@matzie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Write two scripts that depend on a variable of a player, and see how this plan works out :o This is a good thing to theorize before you build it, because it will lead to many changes in your implementation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lfm-building-an-open-source-scriptable-info-client/551137/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lfm-building-an-open-source-scriptable-info-client/551137/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 19:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551137-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lfm-building-an-open-source-scriptable-info-client/551137.rss">LFM: Building an open-source scriptable &quot;info client&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>LFM: Building an open-source scriptable &quot;info client&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@robhol robhol]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/robhol">@robhol</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Basically, I’ve found out that the OSBuddy people aren’t planning on implementing scripting anytime soon. As a result I’ve been wanting to roll my own client, but having no knowledge on (Java-specific) reflection and the internal workings of Runescape, I’ve kind of lost hope that this is something I can do by myself, particularly given the general difficulty of finding up-to-date information. I would be able to learn, and the “mechanics” don’t seem too complicated, but it would take me too long to get the Runescape-specific know-how on my own.</p>
<p>I basically want to create - initially - a bare-bones Runescape “container”. From there, I’d like to build and gradually expand support for reading and interpreting game state, and start designing an API. I’ve looked at a few bots, most of which use more Java for their “scripting” needs. I’d prefer to operate with a different language, though I’m not quite sure which one.</p>
<p>The project would be open-source, not only because it makes it easier to extend and improve, but to serve as an example - based on my own googling, it definitely couldn’t hurt. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p>Does this seem interesting to anyone?  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lfm-building-an-open-source-scriptable-info-client/551137/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lfm-building-an-open-source-scriptable-info-client/551137/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 17:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551137-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/lfm-building-an-open-source-scriptable-info-client/551137.rss">LFM: Building an open-source scriptable &quot;info client&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
