<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux printing strange behavior</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-printing-strange-behavior/416402</link>
    <description>So I was at school today and we needed to print out some project files. I hadn&#39;t set up a printer with Ubuntu before, but it didn&#39;t seem to hard.

I browse all the printers on the network, select the one I need, and start printing. Sounds simple enough right? Well it wasn&#39;t. If you&#39;ve ever tried to print to a Dell printer in Linux, you know that your options are limited in terms of drivers. Not finding the correct drivers, I decided to just use the alternate printer in the class; an HP ColorSphere 5700dn. Go through the motions again, correct driver is found so I&#39;m thinking &quot;I can finally print these damn pages&quot;.

Wrong. Little did I know, attempting to access a printer from a non-campus machine requires a CA(Campus Administrator)&#39;s approval. Finally got the approval (they added me to a whitelist), try printing again. Still didn&#39;t work. So I try the initial printer again (tried searching/building my own drivers), and it doesn&#39;t work.

Finally, being past the point of frustration, I try setting up the printer once more. After 5 attempts, I get it to work; but something seems odd about the printer settings. First of all, it didn&#39;t print from the selected printer (I selected to print from the original, and it printed from the color). Second (probably the most obvious) the driver that was loaded was for the original printer; not the color. I asked everyone I could think of at the campus how this could have happened. They all told me it shouldn&#39;t have (I recreated it for them). So I come here to ask what could have possibly caused this to happen.

tl;dr Two printers in the room (HP and Dell), tried printing to the HP, prints to the Dell with the HP driver loaded.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 15:35:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Technology</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-printing-strange-behavior/416402.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Linux printing strange behavior</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://localhost:631" class="onebox" target="_blank">http://localhost:631</a></p>
<p>And look around?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-printing-strange-behavior/416402/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-printing-strange-behavior/416402/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 15:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-416402-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-printing-strange-behavior/416402.rss">Linux printing strange behavior</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Linux printing strange behavior</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I was at school today and we needed to print out some project files. I hadn’t set up a printer with Ubuntu before, but it didn’t seem to hard.</p>
<p>I browse all the printers on the network, select the one I need, and start printing. Sounds simple enough right? Well it wasn’t. If you’ve ever tried to print to a Dell printer in Linux, you know that your options are limited in terms of drivers. Not finding the correct drivers, I decided to just use the alternate printer in the class; an HP ColorSphere 5700dn. Go through the motions again, correct driver is found so I’m thinking “I can finally print these damn pages”.</p>
<p>Wrong. Little did I know, attempting to access a printer from a non-campus machine requires a CA(Campus Administrator)'s approval. Finally got the approval (they added me to a whitelist), try printing again. Still didn’t work. So I try the initial printer again (tried searching/building my own drivers), and it doesn’t work.</p>
<p>Finally, being past the point of frustration, I try setting up the printer once more. After 5 attempts, I get it to work; but something seems odd about the printer settings. First of all, it didn’t print from the selected printer (I selected to print from the original, and it printed from the color). Second (probably the most obvious) the driver that was loaded was for the original printer; not the color. I asked everyone I could think of at the campus how this could have happened. They all told me it shouldn’t have (I recreated it for them). So I come here to ask what could have possibly caused this to happen.</p>
<p>tl;dr Two printers in the room (HP and Dell), tried printing to the HP, prints to the Dell with the HP driver loaded.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-printing-strange-behavior/416402/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-printing-strange-behavior/416402/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 06:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-416402-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/linux-printing-strange-behavior/416402.rss">Linux printing strange behavior</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
