<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Espeon Dialogue Tutorial [508]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351</link>
    <description>[center]Espeon 508 Dialogue Tutorial [/center]

[b][u]Difficulty 2/10[/u][/b]

The reason I&#39;m writing this tutorial is simply because I was pretty clueless on how to get NPC dialogue working on Espeon&#39;s 508... I&#39;ve only been working with Espeon for 2 days thus far and it definitely was a bit of a struggle to get used to. After asking for help on these forums and no answers, oh and not too add the fact that there&#39;s almost nothing out there explaining how to do this.. I decided to write up a quick and simple tutorial. Let&#39;s begin then...

First things first, you&#39;re going to have to choose your NPC or object which you would like to add the dialogue to... Once you&#39;ve chosen which NPC or object you would like to use, you&#39;ll need to navigate to either objectoption1/2 or NpcOption1/2, depending on your choice. Both files are found in:
 [b]\src\net\com\espeon\net\packethandler[/b]

Open up the file. If you chose to use the NPCoption file(s) then you&#39;re going to have to search the following:
[code]switch (npcId) {[/code]

If you chose the objectoption file(s) then you&#39;re going to have to search the following:
[code]switch (p.clickId) {[/code]

Now under this we&#39;re going to want to add a simple case with an ID depending on the object or NPC you have selected to use. In this example I show you my starter NPC,
[code]
case 129:
			p.getActionSender().setString(p, &quot;Starter Packages:&quot;, 230, 1);
			p.getActionSender().setString(p, &quot;250k Gold&quot;, 230, 2);
			p.getActionSender().setString(p, &quot;COMING SOON&quot;, 230, 3);
			p.getActionSender().setString(p, &quot;COMING SOON&quot;, 230, 4);
			p.getActionSender().showChatboxInterface(p, 230);
			p.optionArray[3] = true;
               }
break;[/code]
There&#39;s no REAL need but this is a tutorial so I might aswell explain what the code above does.

First you see the Case ID, like I stated above that&#39;s just the NPC or Object case. 

Secondly you see some strings, As you add more strings, the line number will need to be changed ... this chatbox interface has only 4 lines (I&#39;m pretty sure)... So no more than 4 times can you set a string.
Now, in Player.java there&#39;s a variable [b]optionArray[/b]. That variable is assigned to a int called [b]maxArrays[/b] and that int has a value of [b]10[/b]. You can increase the value in the future if you&#39;re going to need more dialogues than 10.

I have 3 optionArrays, used on 3 different things. In this I&#39;m using the starter package one. This happened to be the 3rd optionArray that I had used, which gives the answer to why the value is [b][3][/b] below. Of course your may be different... Make sure you check your source hasn&#39;t used any of the same numbers.
[code]p.optionArray[3] = true;[/code]
What below does is quite self explanatory, it sets a string to the chatbox interface ID [b]230[/b] on line [b]1[/b]. That string containing [b]Starter Packages:[/b]. 
[code]p.getActionSender().setString(p, &quot;Starter Packages:&quot;, 230, 1);[/code]

Okay so now we have that done you can save the file. Here&#39;s where it got a bit tricky for me... When you click on my NPC it&#39;s going to show those strings and all, but they&#39;re not going to do anything... I always thought that the buttons on chatbox interfaces were handled in the actionbuttons.java class... But that is not the case in Espeon. Navigate to:
[b]src\net\com\espeon\net\packethandler\OptionClicking.java[/b]

Once open, you are going to find a switch statement for option clicking, and underneath that all the cases for it. When you click on the first string in my dialogue my server outputs the option &#39;2&#39; into my console... why 2? Well 1 is the title in the chatbox interface, and is not clickable or needed.

Okay so now I know my number for my option, I got to find that case ID [b](2)[/b] in [b]OptionClicking.java[/b]... This is what mine looks like:
[code]
case 2:
if (player.optionArray[3]) {
					Engine.playerItems.addItem(player, 995, 250000);
					player.getstarted = 1;

			} 
break;[/code]
Take note of the fact that your case may have more or possibly even no if statements in it.  

Okay so obviously you&#39;re going to use the &#39;case 2&#39; when creating more dialogues, etc... that&#39;s why the &#39;optionArray&#39; is made, so that with a simple &#39;if&#39; statement you can easily execute your code..  Alright so when I click on 
[code]p.getActionSender().setString(p, &quot;250k Gold&quot;, 230, 2);[/code]
I&#39;m going to get 250k as you can see from the code below. (995 being the item ID for coins, and 250000 being the number of that item.)
[code]Engine.playerItems.addItem(player, 995, 250000);
					player.getstarted = 1;
[/code]

Honestly it&#39;s pretty easy when you know how to do it.. the tutorial is more for people who have no clue about how dialogue is handled in this base (espeon 508).

Anyways, [size=18pt]Thanks :)[/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 23:09:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Espeon Dialogue Tutorial [508]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@justinxg27 justinxg27]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/justinxg27">@justinxg27</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“chillwitm888, post:2, topic:439351”]I didn’t know people still used espeon o-0…<br>
&amp; this is fairly basic… =.=[/quote]I don’t know too much of what people use these days considering the fact I only touch 508 revision. Yeah it’s fairly basic but believe me when I say this is a bitch if you’ve never worked in Espeon before, and worked on bulby or pali… But like I said also… There’s like no tutorial on how to do this out there… (from my research), so It’s just to help others…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 23:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439351-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351.rss">Espeon Dialogue Tutorial [508]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Espeon Dialogue Tutorial [508]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chillwitm888 chillwitm888]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chillwitm888">@chillwitm888</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I didn’t know people still used espeon o-0…<br>
&amp; this is fairly basic… =.=</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 23:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439351-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351.rss">Espeon Dialogue Tutorial [508]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Espeon Dialogue Tutorial [508]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@justinxg27 justinxg27]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/justinxg27">@justinxg27</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Espeon 508 Dialogue Tutorial [/center]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">Difficulty 2/10</span></span></p>
<p>The reason I’m writing this tutorial is simply because I was pretty clueless on how to get NPC dialogue working on Espeon’s 508… I’ve only been working with Espeon for 2 days thus far and it definitely was a bit of a struggle to get used to. After asking for help on these forums and no answers, oh and not too add the fact that there’s almost nothing out there explaining how to do this… I decided to write up a quick and simple tutorial. Let’s begin then…</p>
<p>First things first, you’re going to have to choose your NPC or object which you would like to add the dialogue to… Once you’ve chosen which NPC or object you would like to use, you’ll need to navigate to either objectoption1/2 or NpcOption1/2, depending on your choice. Both files are found in:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">\src\net\com\espeon\net\packethandler</span></p>
<p>Open up the file. If you chose to use the NPCoption file(s) then you’re going to have to search the following:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>If you chose the objectoption file(s) then you’re going to have to search the following:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Now under this we’re going to want to add a simple case with an ID depending on the object or NPC you have selected to use. In this example I show you my starter NPC,</p>
<p><code>
case 129:
			p.getActionSender().setString(p, "Starter Packages:", 230, 1);
			p.getActionSender().setString(p, "250k Gold", 230, 2);
			p.getActionSender().setString(p, "COMING SOON", 230, 3);
			p.getActionSender().setString(p, "COMING SOON", 230, 4);
			p.getActionSender().showChatboxInterface(p, 230);
			p.optionArray[3] = true;
               }
break;</code><br>
There’s no REAL need but this is a tutorial so I might aswell explain what the code above does.</p>
<p>First you see the Case ID, like I stated above that’s just the NPC or Object case.</p>
<p>Secondly you see some strings, As you add more strings, the line number will need to be changed … this chatbox interface has only 4 lines (I’m pretty sure)… So no more than 4 times can you set a string.<br>
Now, in Player.java there’s a variable <span class="bbcode-b">optionArray</span>. That variable is assigned to a int called <span class="bbcode-b">maxArrays</span> and that int has a value of <span class="bbcode-b">10</span>. You can increase the value in the future if you’re going to need more dialogues than 10.</p>
<p>I have 3 optionArrays, used on 3 different things. In this I’m using the starter package one. This happened to be the 3rd optionArray that I had used, which gives the answer to why the value is <span class="bbcode-b">[3]</span> below. Of course your may be different… Make sure you check your source hasn’t used any of the same numbers.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>What below does is quite self explanatory, it sets a string to the chatbox interface ID <span class="bbcode-b">230</span> on line <span class="bbcode-b">1</span>. That string containing <span class="bbcode-b">Starter Packages:</span>.</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Okay so now we have that done you can save the file. Here’s where it got a bit tricky for me… When you click on my NPC it’s going to show those strings and all, but they’re not going to do anything… I always thought that the buttons on chatbox interfaces were handled in the actionbuttons.java class… But that is not the case in Espeon. Navigate to:<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">src\net\com\espeon\net\packethandler\OptionClicking.java</span></p>
<p>Once open, you are going to find a switch statement for option clicking, and underneath that all the cases for it. When you click on the first string in my dialogue my server outputs the option ‘2’ into my console… why 2? Well 1 is the title in the chatbox interface, and is not clickable or needed.</p>
<p>Okay so now I know my number for my option, I got to find that case ID <a>b</a>[/b] in <span class="bbcode-b">OptionClicking.java</span>… This is what mine looks like:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">case 2:
if (player.optionArray[3]) {
					Engine.playerItems.addItem(player, 995, 250000);
					player.getstarted = 1;

			} 
break;[/code]
Take note of the fact that your case may have more or possibly even no if statements in it.  

Okay so obviously you're going to use the 'case 2' when creating more dialogues, etc... that's why the 'optionArray' is made, so that with a simple 'if' statement you can easily execute your code..  Alright so when I click on 
[code]p.getActionSender().setString(p, "250k Gold", 230, 2);[/code]
I'm going to get 250k as you can see from the code below. (995 being the item ID for coins, and 250000 being the number of that item.)
[code]Engine.playerItems.addItem(player, 995, 250000);
					player.getstarted = 1;</code></pre>
<p>Honestly it’s pretty easy when you know how to do it… the tutorial is more for people who have no clue about how dialogue is handled in this base (espeon 508).</p>
<p>Anyways, [size=18pt]Thanks :)[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 22:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-439351-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/espeon-dialogue-tutorial-508/439351.rss">Espeon Dialogue Tutorial [508]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
