<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423</link>
    <description>[size=18pt][u][b]A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater[/b][/u][/size]

Contents:
&gt;0 Contents
0.0 Preface
1.0 Part 1: The Updater Base
1.1 Introduction
1.2 The &#39;Updater&#39; Class
1.2.1 Introduction
1.2.2 Class Fields
1.2.3 Constructor
1.2.4 Loading the classes
1.2.5 Checking the version number
1.3 The &#39;TransformerBase&#39; Class
1.3.1 Introduction
1.3.2 Class Fields
1.3.3 Constructor
1.3.4 Abstract methods
1.3.4.1 Update
1.3.4.2 runNow
1.3.5 Set Class Reader
1.3.6 Set Class Node
1.3.7 Get &amp; Put
1.3.8 Get Class
1.3.9 The fun stuff
1.3.9.1 Add Interface
1.3.9.2 Add Method to Return Static Field [1]
1.3.9.3 Add Method to Return Static Field [2]
1.3.9.4 Add Method to Return Non-Static Field [1]
1.3.9.5 Add Method to Return Non-Static Field [2]


[b][u][size=18pt]Preface[/size][/u][/b]

Before continuing with this tutorial I will make some foolish assumptions:

[ul][li]You have the latest version of Object Web ASM, this is critical because you will not be able to use this tutorial without it. You can get it [url=http://asm.objectweb.org]here[/url][/li][li]You have some basic skill in ObjectWeb ASM, i.e. knowing the basic constructors of the basic, most used classes and how to, somewhat, utilize these classes.[/li][li]You are competent in Java – this is vital, you should not even be thinking about attempting to read this tutorial if you cannot yet program in Java properly (NOTE: This does not mean programming for bots, e.g. Ibot). Good Java tutorials may be found either: [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,25.0.html] here[/url] or [url=http://java.sun.com/docs/books/tutorial/]here[/url][/li][li]You are using a good IDE, I recommend either Eclipse or IntelliJ IDEA.[/li][/ul]

	Now, if you meet all the requirements you may proceed with the tutorial. If you do not meet the requirements I suggest not continuing with this tutorial because not only will you not learn anything about Java and ASM but you [b]will[/b] learn how to &#39;Cut and Paste&#39; code.



[size=18pt][u][b]Part 1: The Updater Base[/b][/u][/size]
[size=16pt][u][b]1.1: Introduction[/b][/u][/size]
	The Updater Base, or the Base of the Updater, is a compilation of the core classes of the Updater, without them the Updater would be nothing. The base to the updater is like the Linux kernel to, for example, Ubuntu. The base will, for now, contain only two classes: the main Updater class itself containing the main method, and the &#39;Transformer&#39; class which contains all the methods required for transformation of classes.

[size=16pt][u][b]1.2: The Updater Class[/b][/u][/size]
[size=14pt][u][b]1.2.1: Introduction[/b][/u][/size]
	The &#39;Updater&#39; Class is the core class containing the main method used to run the Updater itself. I will start with this class mainly because without it none of the code in the classes to follow would make sense. So in you IDE of choice create a new project, I called mine &#39;ASM_Updater&#39; but you can call yours whatever you want. In the projects source repository add a new Class &#39;Updater&#39; (put it in a decent package). And now to begin.
[size=14pt][u][b]
1.2.2: Fields[/b][/u][/size]

The Updater class has several fields used throughout the Updater. These are as follows:

[code=java]
HashMap&lt;String, String&gt; CLASSES = new HashMap&lt;String, String&gt;();// This is where the transformers will put all the Defined classes e.g. add(“Node”, nd), where nd is the name of the class in the RS Source and Node is our name for it.

HashMap&lt;String, String&gt; FIELDS = new HashMap&lt;String, String&gt;(); // Same as CLASSES but for fields.

ClassReader[] loaded = null; // Where the Updater class will dump all the loaded ClassReaders, the transformer classes will then iterate through them to find classes to carry out transformations.

long rsBuildTime,pattenTime, fileTime, totalTime; // Used for debugging
[/code]

[size=14pt][u][b]1.2.3: The Constructor[/b][/u][/size]
	In updaters the constructor of the main Updater class is where all the main “action” is called from. This is the design we are going to use:

Parameters: String == the path to the RS class files.

Start the timer -&gt; set the path to the path specified in the parameters -&gt; load the classes into memory -&gt; iterate through the class files until we find the “client” -&gt; run that class through the version getting method -&gt; make one call to each transformer -&gt; stop the timer -&gt; collect all timing information -&gt; print out timing information at the very end.

If you did not understand that... don&#39;t worry!

So currently our constructor look a bit like this:

[code=java]
public Updater(String path) {

	/* Code goes here */

}
[/code]

	So first things first we&#39;ll set the path variable we set up to the one specified by the user. After doing this, if you look back at our layout, we start the timer. So now you code should look something like this:

[code=java]
public Updater(String path) {

	long start = System.currentTimeMillis();

}
[/code]

	Then, we load all the classes. Somewhere below create a method with the name “loadClasses” and the parameters (String path), and then make a call to this method below the last line of the constructor. We will come back the the loadClasses method a little bit later on. When we call “loadClasses”, all the files that are found by the method “loadClasses” are then loaded into ClassReaders and then dumped into the variable loaded (which, as you know, is an array of ClassReaders). 
	
	So now we need to find out which ClassReader contains the byte of the class “client” so we can pass it off to our method which finds the RS version number. To do this you will need to iterate through the ClassReaders until you find one with the name client. Now that you&#39;ve done all of that you constructor should look somewhat like this:

[code=java]
public Updater(String path) {

	long start = System.currentTimeMillis();

	loadClasses(path);
	for(ClassReader cr : loaded) {
		if(cr.getClassName().equals(“client”) {
			/* When it gets here we have found the Client ClassReader */
		}
	}

}
[/code]

	Now we have acquired the client ClassReader we need to pass it off to a method that will examine it to get the version number. This method is getRSVersionNumber(ClassReader cr) and will then return the current RS version, we&#39;ll come back to this method later. In your IF clause insert a call to getRSVersionNumber and pass on the current ClassReader to it.
	Since the  getRSVersionNumber returns the RS version number we can just stick it right inside a System.out.println() statement. Now we can jump right the way outside our FOR clause.
	After the FOR clause is where we would put all the calls to the transformers, so for now just put a TODO comment in to show that we need to put the calls to our transformers here. So our constructor should look somewhat like this now:

[code=java]
public Updater(String path) {

	this.path = path;
	long start = System.currentTimeMillis();

	loadClasses(this.path);
	for(ClassReader cr : loaded) {
		if(cr.getClassName().equals(“client”) {
			System.out.println(“RS build is: ” + getRSVersionNumber(cr));
		}
	}
	
	/* TODO Insert calls to transformers */

}
[/code]

	The rest of the constructor is just used for getting the times and stuff, and since I&#39;m going to “spoon feed” you, you&#39;ll have to work that out for yourself.

[size=14pt][u][b]1.2.4 Loading the classes[/b][/u][/size]

	Now we are going to see how to load the class files into our ClassReader array, which isn&#39;t too hard. Skip this section if you already know how to load files into ClassReaders. Currently our loadClasses method looks like so:

[code=java]
public void loadClasses(String path) {

	/* Code goes here */

}
[/code]

	First things first we&#39;re going to need to create a instance of File so we can see what is in our specified directory and since the path variable will just be a folder you&#39;ll need to insert a call to  System.getProperty(“user.dir”) in the constructor of this File object. Now we need to initiate the “loaded” variable but the thing is: we don&#39;t know how many files we are going to need to load. So simple create an integer and then iterate through the files checking that they are not directories and incrediment that integer each time. Like so:

[code=java]
int files = 0;
for (String file : f.list()) {
		f (!new File(file).isDirectory()) {
		files++;
	}
}
[/code]

	Now we know how many files we are going to load we can initiate the “loaded” variable and then put a ClassReader object into each part of the array like so:

[code=java]
loaded = new ClassReader[files];
for(int i=0;i&lt;files;i++){
	FileInputStream fis;
	fis = new FileInputStream(f.listFiles()[i]);
	loaded[i] = new ClassReader(fis);
}
[/code]

	Remember to insert the correct try/catch block where applicable. And there you have it. You have now loaded all the RS class files into ClassReaders. You can even put a little System.out.println at the end to specify how many files have been loaded.

[size=14pt][u][b]1.2.5: Getting the RS version number[/b][/u][/size]

	This is the final method in the updater class, and likewise the final part in the updater section. As well as being the last, it is also the hardest out of all the methods in this class. So let us begin. You should have already created a code-less method for this and that will look like this:

[code=java]
public int getRSVersionNumber(ClassReader cr) {

	/* Code goes here */

}
[/code]

	For this method we use the ClassNode class of the tree package which is in a separate jar file from the core API that we have just been using so you may need to make some updates to your build path. This is how you do it:

 [code=java]
public int getRSVersionNumber(ClassReader cr) {

	ClassNode cn = new ClassNode(); //Creates a new instance of the ClassNode
	cr.accept(cn, 0); //Make the ClassReader accept the ClassNode as its classVisitor
	List methods = cn.methods; //A list of all the methods in this class
	for(int i=0;i&lt;methods.size;i++) {
		MethodNode mn = methods.get(i); //Get the current method from the list “methods”
		if(mn.name.contains(“main”)) { //Check to see if the method is the main method
			AbstractInsnNode[] ain = mn.instructions.toArray(); //Creates an array of AbstractInsnNodes which can be used to check out the different bytecode instructions
			for(int j=0;j&lt;ain.length;j++) {
				AbstractInsnNode insn = ain[j];
				if(insn instanceof IntInsnNode) { //Checks to see if the current instruction is to do with ints, e.g. BIPUSH instructions
					IntInsnNode iin = insn;
					int operand = iin.operand; // Get the operand of that instruction
					if(operand != 503 &amp;&amp; operand != 765
									&amp;&amp; (operand &gt; 480 &amp;&amp; operand &lt; 500) { //Checks to see that we have not found the width, height or any other numbers that Jagex may put in there to throw us off
						return operand; //If it is none of these numbers then we have found the version number!
					}
				}
			}
		}
	}
}

}
[/code]

Make sure to put in any try/catch clauses and class casts where necessary. You could add timers if you wanted, but I&#39;m going to leave that out for now. If you have followed the tutorial correctly you should now have a working Updater class! Now for the TransformerBase class!

[size=16pt][u][b]1.3: The TransformerBase Class[/b][/u][/size]
[size=14pt][u][b]1.3.1: Introduction[/b][/u][/size]

The TransformerBase class is the super class of all of you transformation classes, e.g. NodeTransformer. It contains all the necessary methods for the updating procedure to be carried out. So create you new TransformerBase class in you IDE of choice, typically this class has been put in the same package as the Updater class but it doesn&#39;t matter too much.

[size=14pt][u][b]1.3.2: The Fields[/b][/u][/size]

The TransformerBase class has several fields which are below:

[code=java]
public Updater updater; //The updater of this TransformerBase class.

Public ClassReader theCurrentClassReader; //The current class reader, i.e. The one having analsys performed on it

public ClassNode theCurrentClassNode; //The same as above but a ClassNode instead.
[/code]

That is all I am going to publish for now because I am going swimming training for a couple hours, so see if you can design your own TransformerBase class and then compare it to my own class. Thanks for reading! Please point out any errors.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 01:34:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>because you cant</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 01:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why not eliminate the “(sort of)”?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@joey0101 joey0101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/joey0101">@joey0101</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“super_, post:15, topic:195423”][quote author=joey0101 link=topic=259890.msg2160455#msg2160455 date=1207365414]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Sorry about the harsh criticism . . .</p>
<p>If you don’t enjoy reading Java, how can you stand writing it?</p>
<p>Also, here is some material on the JVM; juicy stuff on bytecode is in chapter 6 (hang on!): <a href="http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/VMSpecTOC.doc.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/VMSpecTOC.doc.html</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I know how a Java class works -.-<br>
[/quote]<br>
dont seem so[/quote]</p>
<p>Maybe not from that guide, but I have read many tutorials on BCEL, including the one by yakman, and you can learn (sort of) how a class works from those.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 14:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@super_OLDACCOUNT super_OLDACCOUNT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/super_oldaccount">@super_OLDACCOUNT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“joey0101, post:14, topic:195423”][quote author=White Castle link=topic=259890.msg2159950#msg2159950 date=1207355813]<br>
Sorry about the harsh criticism . . .</p>
<p>If you don’t enjoy reading Java, how can you stand writing it?</p>
<p>Also, here is some material on the JVM; juicy stuff on bytecode is in chapter 6 (hang on!): <a href="http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/VMSpecTOC.doc.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/VMSpecTOC.doc.html</a><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I know how a Java class works -.-[/quote]<br>
dont seem so</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 05:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@joey0101 joey0101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/joey0101">@joey0101</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“White Castle, post:13, topic:195423”]Sorry about the harsh criticism . . .</p>
<p>If you don’t enjoy reading Java, how can you stand writing it?</p>
<p>Also, here is some material on the JVM; juicy stuff on bytecode is in chapter 6 (hang on!): <a href="http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/VMSpecTOC.doc.html%5B/quote%5D" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/VMSpecTOC.doc.html[/quote]</a></p>
<p>I know how a Java class works -.-</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@White_Castle White Castle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/white_castle">@White_Castle</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sorry about the harsh criticism . . .</p>
<p>If you don’t enjoy reading Java, how can you stand writing it?</p>
<p>Also, here is some material on the JVM; juicy stuff on bytecode is in chapter 6 (hang on!): <a href="http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/VMSpecTOC.doc.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/VMSpecTOC.doc.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 00:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Aye, the tutorial is shit. You mention bytecode <span class="bbcode-i">once</span>, and it’s not in a context of saying ANYTHING about how a class works. Really not too adaptable thus far, is’t?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 21:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@super_OLDACCOUNT super_OLDACCOUNT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/super_oldaccount">@super_OLDACCOUNT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“BAsh(CntLgn), post:10, topic:195423”][quote author=joey0101 link=topic=259890.msg2157736#msg2157736 date=1207259287]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>ayy this is that one annoying rscheata kid back from aresbot forums</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Me? I was never at aresbot forums…[br][br][size=1]Posted on: April 03, 2008, 11:04:24 AM[/size][hr]God, I never knew that posting a (crap, maybe) tutorial would get me such a big fucking over.<br>
[/quote]<br>
Hate to say it but this is MITB.[/quote]<br>
qft</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 19:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BAsh_CntLgn BAsh(CntLgn)]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bash_cntlgn">@BAsh_CntLgn</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“joey0101, post:9, topic:195423”][quote author=super_ link=topic=259890.msg2157656#msg2157656 date=1207254963]<br>
ayy this is that one annoying rscheata kid back from aresbot forums<br>
[/quote]<br>
Me? I was never at aresbot forums…[br][br][size=1]Posted on: April 03, 2008, 11:04:24 AM[/size][hr]God, I never knew that posting a (crap, maybe) tutorial would get me such a big fucking over.[/quote]<br>
Hate to say it but this is MITB.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 14:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@joey0101 joey0101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/joey0101">@joey0101</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Me? I was never at aresbot forums…[br][br][size=1]Posted on: April 03, 2008, 11:04:24 AM[/size][hr]God, I never knew that posting a (crap, maybe) tutorial would get me such a big fucking over.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 21:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@super_OLDACCOUNT super_OLDACCOUNT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/super_oldaccount">@super_OLDACCOUNT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ayy this is that one annoying rscheata kid back from aresbot forums</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 20:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@joey0101 joey0101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/joey0101">@joey0101</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“frank_, post:6, topic:195423”][quote author=joey0101 link=topic=259890.msg2156209#msg2156209 date=1207189232]<br>
The code in that isn’t optimized for speed nor has it been proof read… But yeah, i see what you mean.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public Updater(String path) {

	long start = System.currentTimeMillis();

}</code></pre>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>if you can justify this, i wont think that you are a twat</p>
<p>on the whole, i found this guide overly misleading and used the asm library in a largely inefficient manner[/quote]</p>
<p>Then you may indeed think that I am a twat. I think I shall rewrite this whole thing…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 15:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@frank frank_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frank">@frank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="195423">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/joey0101/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> joey0101:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>The code in that isn’t optimized for speed nor has it been proof read… But yeah, i see what you mean.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>[quote=“joey0101, post:1, topic:195423”][code=java]<br>
public Updater(String path) {</p>
<pre><code>long start = System.currentTimeMillis();
</code></pre>
<p>}<br>
[/code][/quote]<br>
if you can justify this, i wont think that you are a twat</p>
<p>on the whole, i found this guide overly misleading and used the asm library in a largely inefficient manner</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 03:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@joey0101 joey0101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/joey0101">@joey0101</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The code in that isn’t optimized for speed nor has it been proof read… But yeah, i see what you mean.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: April 02, 2008, 03:24:49 PM[/size][hr][quote=“Ollie, post:4, topic:195423”]i didnt read through it all, i want to enjoy tonight (no offence towards you, i just dont want to read java this evening)[/quote]<br>
No one would choose to read Java Ollie… I can barely read through a tutorial myself -.-</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 02:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ollie Ollie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ollie">@Ollie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>the thought is good, but i mean cmon,</p>
<p><code>
			getRSVersionNumber(cr);
			System.out.println(“RS build is: ” + RSBuild);</code><br>
why not make it return the version number rather then create a global variable, its little things like this which will set you back</p>
<p>i didnt read through it all, i want to enjoy tonight (no offence towards you, i just dont want to read java this evening)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 02:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@joey0101 joey0101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/joey0101">@joey0101</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ollie, post:2, topic:195423”]yuk,<br>
but nice try[/quote]<br>
Whats that supposed to mean? Its either shit or not shit.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 02:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ollie Ollie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ollie">@Ollie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yuk,<br>
but nice try</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 01:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@joey0101 joey0101]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/joey0101">@joey0101</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=18pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</span></span>[/size]</p>
<p>Contents:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>0 Contents<br>
0.0 Preface<br>
1.0 Part 1: The Updater Base<br>
1.1 Introduction<br>
1.2 The ‘Updater’ Class<br>
1.2.1 Introduction<br>
1.2.2 Class Fields<br>
1.2.3 Constructor<br>
1.2.4 Loading the classes<br>
1.2.5 Checking the version number<br>
1.3 The ‘TransformerBase’ Class<br>
1.3.1 Introduction<br>
1.3.2 Class Fields<br>
1.3.3 Constructor<br>
1.3.4 Abstract methods<br>
1.3.4.1 Update<br>
1.3.4.2 runNow<br>
1.3.5 Set Class Reader<br>
1.3.6 Set Class Node<br>
1.3.7 Get &amp; Put<br>
1.3.8 Get Class<br>
1.3.9 The fun stuff<br>
1.3.9.1 Add Interface<br>
1.3.9.2 Add Method to Return Static Field [1]<br>
1.3.9.3 Add Method to Return Static Field [2]<br>
1.3.9.4 Add Method to Return Non-Static Field [1]<br>
1.3.9.5 Add Method to Return Non-Static Field [2]</p>
</blockquote>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">[size=18pt]Preface[/size]</span></span></p>
<p>Before continuing with this tutorial I will make some foolish assumptions:</p>
<p>[ul][li]You have the latest version of Object Web ASM, this is critical because you will not be able to use this tutorial without it. You can get it <a href="http://asm.objectweb.org" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>[/li][li]You have some basic skill in ObjectWeb ASM, i.e. knowing the basic constructors of the basic, most used classes and how to, somewhat, utilize these classes.[/li][li]You are competent in Java – this is vital, you should not even be thinking about attempting to read this tutorial if you cannot yet program in Java properly (NOTE: This does not mean programming for bots, e.g. Ibot). Good Java tutorials may be found either: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,25.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"> here</a> or <a href="http://java.sun.com/docs/books/tutorial/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>[/li][li]You are using a good IDE, I recommend either Eclipse or IntelliJ IDEA.[/li][/ul]</p>
<pre><code>Now, if you meet all the requirements you may proceed with the tutorial. If you do not meet the requirements I suggest not continuing with this tutorial because not only will you not learn anything about Java and ASM but you [b]will[/b] learn how to 'Cut and Paste' code.
</code></pre>
<p>[size=18pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Part 1: The Updater Base</span></span>[/size]<br>
[size=16pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">1.1: Introduction</span></span>[/size]<br>
The Updater Base, or the Base of the Updater, is a compilation of the core classes of the Updater, without them the Updater would be nothing. The base to the updater is like the Linux kernel to, for example, Ubuntu. The base will, for now, contain only two classes: the main Updater class itself containing the main method, and the ‘Transformer’ class which contains all the methods required for transformation of classes.</p>
<p>[size=16pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">1.2: The Updater Class</span></span>[/size]<br>
[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">1.2.1: Introduction</span></span>[/size]<br>
The ‘Updater’ Class is the core class containing the main method used to run the Updater itself. I will start with this class mainly because without it none of the code in the classes to follow would make sense. So in you IDE of choice create a new project, I called mine ‘ASM_Updater’ but you can call yours whatever you want. In the projects source repository add a new Class ‘Updater’ (put it in a decent package). And now to begin.<br>
[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b"><br>
1.2.2: Fields</span></span>[/size]</p>
<p>The Updater class has several fields used throughout the Updater. These are as follows:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">HashMap&lt;String, String&gt; CLASSES = new HashMap&lt;String, String&gt;();// This is where the transformers will put all the Defined classes e.g. add(“Node”, nd), where nd is the name of the class in the RS Source and Node is our name for it.

HashMap&lt;String, String&gt; FIELDS = new HashMap&lt;String, String&gt;(); // Same as CLASSES but for fields.

ClassReader[] loaded = null; // Where the Updater class will dump all the loaded ClassReaders, the transformer classes will then iterate through them to find classes to carry out transformations.

long rsBuildTime,pattenTime, fileTime, totalTime; // Used for debugging</code></pre>
<p>[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">1.2.3: The Constructor</span></span>[/size]<br>
In updaters the constructor of the main Updater class is where all the main “action” is called from. This is the design we are going to use:</p>
<p>Parameters: String == the path to the RS class files.</p>
<p>Start the timer -&gt; set the path to the path specified in the parameters -&gt; load the classes into memory -&gt; iterate through the class files until we find the “client” -&gt; run that class through the version getting method -&gt; make one call to each transformer -&gt; stop the timer -&gt; collect all timing information -&gt; print out timing information at the very end.</p>
<p>If you did not understand that… don’t worry!</p>
<p>So currently our constructor look a bit like this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public Updater(String path) {

	/* Code goes here */

}</code></pre>
<pre><code>So first things first we'll set the path variable we set up to the one specified by the user. After doing this, if you look back at our layout, we start the timer. So now you code should look something like this:
</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public Updater(String path) {

	long start = System.currentTimeMillis();

}</code></pre>
<pre><code>Then, we load all the classes. Somewhere below create a method with the name “loadClasses” and the parameters (String path), and then make a call to this method below the last line of the constructor. We will come back the the loadClasses method a little bit later on. When we call “loadClasses”, all the files that are found by the method “loadClasses” are then loaded into ClassReaders and then dumped into the variable loaded (which, as you know, is an array of ClassReaders). 

So now we need to find out which ClassReader contains the byte of the class “client” so we can pass it off to our method which finds the RS version number. To do this you will need to iterate through the ClassReaders until you find one with the name client. Now that you've done all of that you constructor should look somewhat like this:
</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public Updater(String path) {

	long start = System.currentTimeMillis();

	loadClasses(path);
	for(ClassReader cr : loaded) {
		if(cr.getClassName().equals(“client”) {
			/* When it gets here we have found the Client ClassReader */
		}
	}

}</code></pre>
<pre><code>Now we have acquired the client ClassReader we need to pass it off to a method that will examine it to get the version number. This method is getRSVersionNumber(ClassReader cr) and will then return the current RS version, we'll come back to this method later. In your IF clause insert a call to getRSVersionNumber and pass on the current ClassReader to it.
Since the  getRSVersionNumber returns the RS version number we can just stick it right inside a System.out.println() statement. Now we can jump right the way outside our FOR clause.
After the FOR clause is where we would put all the calls to the transformers, so for now just put a TODO comment in to show that we need to put the calls to our transformers here. So our constructor should look somewhat like this now:
</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public Updater(String path) {

	this.path = path;
	long start = System.currentTimeMillis();

	loadClasses(this.path);
	for(ClassReader cr : loaded) {
		if(cr.getClassName().equals(“client”) {
			System.out.println(“RS build is: ” + getRSVersionNumber(cr));
		}
	}
	
	/* TODO Insert calls to transformers */

}</code></pre>
<pre><code>The rest of the constructor is just used for getting the times and stuff, and since I'm going to “spoon feed” you, you'll have to work that out for yourself.
</code></pre>
<p>[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">1.2.4 Loading the classes</span></span>[/size]</p>
<pre><code>Now we are going to see how to load the class files into our ClassReader array, which isn't too hard. Skip this section if you already know how to load files into ClassReaders. Currently our loadClasses method looks like so:
</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public void loadClasses(String path) {

	/* Code goes here */

}</code></pre>
<pre><code>First things first we're going to need to create a instance of File so we can see what is in our specified directory and since the path variable will just be a folder you'll need to insert a call to  System.getProperty(“user.dir”) in the constructor of this File object. Now we need to initiate the “loaded” variable but the thing is: we don't know how many files we are going to need to load. So simple create an integer and then iterate through the files checking that they are not directories and incrediment that integer each time. Like so:
</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">int files = 0;
for (String file : f.list()) {
		f (!new File(file).isDirectory()) {
		files++;
	}
}</code></pre>
<pre><code>Now we know how many files we are going to load we can initiate the “loaded” variable and then put a ClassReader object into each part of the array like so:
</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">loaded = new ClassReader[files];
for(int i=0;i&lt;files;i++){
	FileInputStream fis;
	fis = new FileInputStream(f.listFiles()[i]);
	loaded[i] = new ClassReader(fis);
}</code></pre>
<pre><code>Remember to insert the correct try/catch block where applicable. And there you have it. You have now loaded all the RS class files into ClassReaders. You can even put a little System.out.println at the end to specify how many files have been loaded.
</code></pre>
<p>[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">1.2.5: Getting the RS version number</span></span>[/size]</p>
<pre><code>This is the final method in the updater class, and likewise the final part in the updater section. As well as being the last, it is also the hardest out of all the methods in this class. So let us begin. You should have already created a code-less method for this and that will look like this:
</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public int getRSVersionNumber(ClassReader cr) {

	/* Code goes here */

}</code></pre>
<pre><code>For this method we use the ClassNode class of the tree package which is in a separate jar file from the core API that we have just been using so you may need to make some updates to your build path. This is how you do it:
</code></pre>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public int getRSVersionNumber(ClassReader cr) {

	ClassNode cn = new ClassNode(); //Creates a new instance of the ClassNode
	cr.accept(cn, 0); //Make the ClassReader accept the ClassNode as its classVisitor
	List methods = cn.methods; //A list of all the methods in this class
	for(int i=0;i&lt;methods.size;i++) {
		MethodNode mn = methods.get(i); //Get the current method from the list “methods”
		if(mn.name.contains(“main”)) { //Check to see if the method is the main method
			AbstractInsnNode[] ain = mn.instructions.toArray(); //Creates an array of AbstractInsnNodes which can be used to check out the different bytecode instructions
			for(int j=0;j&lt;ain.length;j++) {
				AbstractInsnNode insn = ain[j];
				if(insn instanceof IntInsnNode) { //Checks to see if the current instruction is to do with ints, e.g. BIPUSH instructions
					IntInsnNode iin = insn;
					int operand = iin.operand; // Get the operand of that instruction
					if(operand != 503 &amp;&amp; operand != 765
									&amp;&amp; (operand &gt; 480 &amp;&amp; operand &lt; 500) { //Checks to see that we have not found the width, height or any other numbers that Jagex may put in there to throw us off
						return operand; //If it is none of these numbers then we have found the version number!
					}
				}
			}
		}
	}
}

}</code></pre>
<p>Make sure to put in any try/catch clauses and class casts where necessary. You could add timers if you wanted, but I’m going to leave that out for now. If you have followed the tutorial correctly you should now have a working Updater class! Now for the TransformerBase class!</p>
<p>[size=16pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">1.3: The TransformerBase Class</span></span>[/size]<br>
[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">1.3.1: Introduction</span></span>[/size]</p>
<p>The TransformerBase class is the super class of all of you transformation classes, e.g. NodeTransformer. It contains all the necessary methods for the updating procedure to be carried out. So create you new TransformerBase class in you IDE of choice, typically this class has been put in the same package as the Updater class but it doesn’t matter too much.</p>
<p>[size=14pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">1.3.2: The Fields</span></span>[/size]</p>
<p>The TransformerBase class has several fields which are below:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">public Updater updater; //The updater of this TransformerBase class.

Public ClassReader theCurrentClassReader; //The current class reader, i.e. The one having analsys performed on it

public ClassNode theCurrentClassNode; //The same as above but a ClassNode instead.</code></pre>
<p>That is all I am going to publish for now because I am going swimming training for a couple hours, so see if you can design your own TransformerBase class and then compare it to my own class. Thanks for reading! Please point out any errors.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 21:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-195423-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-comprehensive-guide-to-writing-an-asm-updater/195423.rss">A Comprehensive Guide to Writing an ASM Updater</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
