<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server&#39;s IP?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-ip/120736</link>
    <description>I really need help, I been working on my server, went to put it online, and only I could access it. I asked my friend to try it he said it didn&#39;t work. I think its a problem in my IP address for the server. Do I use my computer IP or internet IP?

I have a ton of routing in my house, very confusing. I get my internet by the main wireless router in my basement, sends a signal to another wireless router in my dad&#39;s office where its connected to another wireless thing into my wireless bridge...very confusing, might make everything harder for me...

Its weird because when I have my server running, only I can get on using my computer IP, 127.0.0.1, and putting no ip at all...


anyone know my problem?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 23:51:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-ip/120736.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server&#39;s IP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@icescape icescape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/icescape">@icescape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I really need help, I been working on my server, went to put it online, and only I could access it. I asked my friend to try it he said it didn’t work. I think its a problem in my IP address for the server. Do I use my computer IP or internet IP?</p>
<p>I have a ton of routing in my house, very confusing. I get my internet by the main wireless router in my basement, sends a signal to another wireless router in my dad’s office where its connected to another wireless thing into my wireless bridge…very confusing, might make everything harder for me…</p>
<p>Its weird because when I have my server running, only I can get on using my computer IP, 127.0.0.1, and putting no ip at all…</p>
<p>anyone know my problem?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-ip/120736/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-ip/120736/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 23:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-120736-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/servers-ip/120736.rss">Server&#39;s IP?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
