<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Divine-Reality | Bounty Hunter | Zulrah | Iron man &amp; More</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divine-reality-bounty-hunter-zulrah-iron-man-more/551761</link>
    <description>[center]Hello,

Welcome to Divine-reality&#39;s official advertisement thread. I would just like to point out that we are currently in the process of designing a more suitable and appealing thread but we felt it was necessary to get our advertisement pages back up in the meantime. 

As we&#39;ve all come to know text is boring and dull so I&#39;ll keep this short and simple.

- Our most notable features -

As we are a server attempting to emulate OSRS with our own kick and twist to the outcome we believe we have truly developed a server that most players are able to enjoy. We constantly hear feedback from new players that they are enjoying the server and it is one of the best they have played. While we know we aren&#39;t there and there&#39;s plenty of work to be done, we have definitely placed higher than some servers delivering quality content, a stable and reliable server and a staff-team that is always on-hand and active.


[url=http://divine-reality.net]Join now[/url]


We are loading OSRS data this means we are introducing all of OSRS features i.e Items, Npcs, Gfx, Animations, Objects. 

[img]http://i.imgur.com/GoiTKvI.png[/img]


[img]http://i.imgur.com/6NdHq1G.png[/img][/center]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 03:32:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divine-reality-bounty-hunter-zulrah-iron-man-more/551761.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Divine-Reality | Bounty Hunter | Zulrah | Iron man &amp; More</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@antony2255 antony2255]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/antony2255">@antony2255</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]Hello,</p>
<p>Welcome to Divine-reality’s official advertisement thread. I would just like to point out that we are currently in the process of designing a more suitable and appealing thread but we felt it was necessary to get our advertisement pages back up in the meantime.</p>
<p>As we’ve all come to know text is boring and dull so I’ll keep this short and simple.</p>
<ul>
<li>Our most notable features -</li>
</ul>
<p>As we are a server attempting to emulate OSRS with our own kick and twist to the outcome we believe we have truly developed a server that most players are able to enjoy. We constantly hear feedback from new players that they are enjoying the server and it is one of the best they have played. While we know we aren’t there and there’s plenty of work to be done, we have definitely placed higher than some servers delivering quality content, a stable and reliable server and a staff-team that is always on-hand and active.</p>
<p><a href="http://divine-reality.net" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Join now</a></p>
<p>We are loading OSRS data this means we are introducing all of OSRS features i.e Items, Npcs, Gfx, Animations, Objects.</p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/GoiTKvI.png" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/6NdHq1G.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divine-reality-bounty-hunter-zulrah-iron-man-more/551761/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divine-reality-bounty-hunter-zulrah-iron-man-more/551761/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 03:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-551761-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/divine-reality-bounty-hunter-zulrah-iron-man-more/551761.rss">Divine-Reality | Bounty Hunter | Zulrah | Iron man &amp; More</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
