<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569</link>
    <description>Ahhh.  This is suicide.  Heh.  I thought I&#39;d already posted this here.. but it seems I didn&#39;t.  It&#39;s a little story I wrote on the RuneScape forum over a couple of weeks.

Have a read if you like.  I realise there&#39;re a lot of errors, especially punctually.  It&#39;s far from complete.
___________________________

[center][u]Prologue[/u][/center]

Everything is working according to my plan..

My wrath knows no boundaries, but the boundaries know my wrath- all too well. I will break loose soon, and every race shall be manipulated into slaves.

Zamorak the pretender.. he will soon be obliterated, and each of his followers with him. Yes, everything is working according to my plan..

Foul, wretched humans. Short, dotted dwarfs. Proud, though feeble elves. Gnomes.. Hahahaha.

I cannot help but notice one human though. You. I observe your every move, every day, every hour, every minute, every second. You are a pitiful excuse for a possible threat, but a threat still you are. Oh and that, Wise Old Man. Wise, yes... He knows me. He&#39;s one of the few left who recognize my name. You&#39;ll both become minions, under my name. Useless you will be, although humorous to me. Humorous to watch such established hero-like figures beg for death, mercy, and curse my very name.

Foolish though humans are, I must be lenient with them.. they are after all, setting me free; digging up my temples, altars and relics. They are granting me breath, in some form of thinking.

And you, adventurer. You have been most helpful. You&#39;ve given the humans even more reason to dig passionately, in hopes of finding something of great worth. Not to mention freeing my priest from that weak Zamorak&#39;s temple.. Finally, I have one who can carry out my bidding, and will do so without hesitation.

I will come for you, first of all. Keep a keen eye, adventurer. Hero of the people. Quester of the lands.

I will come for you. And wreak havoc upon this land. I shall rule, once more.

[center][u]Foresight[/u][/center]

&quot;Indulge your thirst for blood. Embrace the craving for murder.&quot; A tall, red, smoke devil grasped my neck, and glared into my begging eyes unmercifully. It didn&#39;t flinch, It didn&#39;t twitch, It didn&#39;t live. I prayed and prayed, but this only seemed to create a stronger connection with It.

&quot;Pray.. Yes.. Beg for life, my child. Let the anger flow through your veins and I will set you free, forever.&quot;

Still, I prayed. Still, I hoped. Still, I wondered. Wondered how such a being could come to existence. Wondered why it was in my home. Wondered why it was with me; I was but a young man, venturing the lands of Misthalin. I had nothing, no-one; no enemies, no friends, no family, no allies- I had nothing, no-one.

&quot;You fight so eagerly with hope as your shield; defending you from reality, and with imagination as your weapon; striking me down in your mind, escaping this nightmare. If you will not allow anger to be one with you, then I.. I SHALL CORRUPT YOU WITH CHAOS AND ANGER MYSELF!&quot; In saying this, It lifted back what seemed to be It&#39;s arm, and in it a weapon that could only have been suitable for the devil himself. With what could only have been described as a &#39;thrust&#39;, It pushed the sword towards me carelessly.

At this very moment, I woke. My nightmare was finished, yet it seemed so... real. More real than the word &#39;real&#39; could ever mean to you. Beyond reality, if you will.

This nightmare- it had became apparent- had cost me several moons. I&#39;d noticed that as I caught the very moon itself in the corner of my eye, out of my window, with beautiful rays of white light emanating from it, shining through and revealing clouds, invisible without the moon&#39;s being.

&quot;Strange,&quot; I battled with logic in my mind.

Realization had fallen upon me; I wasn&#39;t sweating, which is usually a key component in a nightmare; I didn&#39;t wake up screaming and shifting, which is only natural..

Strange indeed.

Perhaps it wasn&#39;t a nightmare, but foresight..

I had barely managed to rotate my head fully to get a definite view of the moon, and its beautiful surroundings. I hadn&#39;t thought much of the nightmare; I was dazzled by the exceptional sight of the moon, and the perfect breeze that gently wrapped around my face and legs, making me shiver.

I love nights like this, I reminded myself.

Suddenly, the strangest of occurrences took place, directly in front of my window; a man seemed to be digging into the soil in the patch of grass mirroring my garden, casting it aside angrily, then kicking the spade he dug with to remove any excess compost that remained clinging to it.

I couldn&#39;t decipher who he was; it was dark and he was quite far away. With eventuality my eyes adjusted fully to the lighting of the world, and my sight improved, allowing me to see who he was. I just had to wait for him to turn around and show his facial appearance...

Although this may sound a little odd to you, I had mastered the skill of jumping out of my bed and immediately readying myself in my own unique fighting stance. I had practiced doing it every night and morning, for.. well, for as long as I can remember..

Becoming restless and curious, I carried out &#39;the leap of destiny&#39; (The name of the aforementioned various movements) and rushed towards the window with haste.

I ran my hands softly against the wooden windowsill, appreciating my caring mood and the texture of the wood. I crouched a little, revealing only the top half of my head and the tips of my fingers to whoever would be looking in and through my window.

Finally! His face had turned towards me! &quot;I know him,&quot; I thought to myself, sighing in disappointment.

It was the &#39;mad-man&#39; who roamed around; muttering words only he could comprehend; warning people of a violent hallucination that seemed so real to you, that if seen, would invoke such chaos in you that death was inevitably the &#39;only way out&#39;.

I feared he was performing a ritual of sorts, so I took my sword up.

My sword wasn&#39;t long, nor was it short. It was smithed with the finest elemental ore, and crafted into what it became.

Due to the ore&#39;s colour, the sword itself glowed a neon purple, and sometimes, if you concentrated enough, you could see small sprinkles of magical dust slipping off of the sword and into the wind&#39;s hands.

I loved my sword. It made me appear unique. Mentioning not the source from which my sword was created to anyone, my lips proved secure and trustworthy.

Rushing silently through my garden, hearing the periodical grunts of the mad-man, the gravel-crunching noise which surrounded him when he slammed the spade into the ground, and my light footsteps upon the grass, I remained calm.

Concealing myself behind a rather conveniently placed bush, I pondered my next move; Should I wait, or should I attack?

I decided to wait; I didn&#39;t want to reveal myself to him as of yet, and came to the conclusion that he would eventually divulge information relevant to his current actions.

I was still in an appreciative mood. It&#39;s the kind of mood you get when you&#39;re happy. No. Grateful. Grateful you&#39;re alive, and what possessions and relationships with other people you have.

I appreciated the grass. Its soft, naturally pleasant texture; its slow, graceful sway in the gentlest of breezes; its gray-green colour; its delicate surface, granting me soundless steps...

I appreciated the bush. Its tiny leaves flowing in the direction the breeze sent it, then returning carefully to its foremost place on its branch; its size, perfectly providing me with cover.

I appreciated the sword. I slid my hands down it slowly, smiling and sighing happily, admiring the cold and exhilarating texture the elemental metal possessed.

I turned round to find my position, I had became aware, exposed. I was instantly confused, asking myself how the mad-man could&#39;ve possibly seen me through the bush; I was perfectly hidden by it.

He laughed with an uncaring face.

I was unsure of what I should do. Stand up. Remain crouching. These options sang irritatingly and constantly in my mind. I decided to stand.

&quot;How can you see me, old man?&quot; I looked at him fully knowing of my tough appearance. I almost smiled because I knew that I looked like a hero of great.

&quot;Hahahaha! What were you hiding behind, boy!? Was it a boulder!? A bush!? A crate!!!? Hahahaha!&quot; He laughed snarlingly, coughs interrupting his every second word. He seemed to be the perfect villainous character.

I&#39;d became slightly confused. I darent question the bush&#39;s being, and at the same time, my sanity; it was definitely there. Alongside the confusion, embarrassment began to mock me.

The once proud smile morphed into a smile of doubt. I chuckled a little, too. Though none of these happy emotions were indeed happy.

A great man, known as the &#39;Wise Old Man&#39; told me once that humans think of roughly one million things every second. At this very moment, I could hear his voice saying it.

I wondered, associating the apparently factual commment with my current state of different feelings, thoughts and such- could he have been right?

Eventually I overcame all of the unimportant issues that pressed against my mind. Like foot soldiers on ladders attempting to climb onto a wall, the issues attacked and attacked, whilst my mind fended them off by knocking down the ladders and piercing their being with arrows.

Mustering normality again, I managed to mutter some words.

&quot;You&#39;re the mad-man here, not me. How in the God&#39;s names did you see me through the bush?&quot; In saying these defensive words, I pushed my empty hand down hoping to touch something. Green shrubbery, rather than something, I pleaded with Guthix.

Nothing. A soft breeze caressed my hand, swirling around it, through my fingers, chilling the tips of my fingernails. It felt as though the breeze itself was attempting to comfort me.

Noticing my hand&#39;s movement, the mad-man smirked and dug again.

I looked downwards to where the bush was. I raised one eyebrow and opened my mouth in awe. Following, fear struck me ruthlessly, causing me to scream.

I seen black smoke. A devil, with eyes like rubies glowing, glared at me, enticing my fear to expose itself through other means, rather than screaming.

I staggered a little and shouted, &quot;GET BACK FROM ME! GET BACK! YOU&#39;RE NOT REAL! AHHHHHH!&quot;

I could hear snarling yet again. The sound drew my concentration not to the smoke devil which crouched before me, but to the mad-man.

He was busy digging; muttering words of old, disregarding my screams for help.

Fearfully, I looked back down onto the evil smoke to find the source of the laughing. Still, It glared into my eyes. I couldn&#39;t help but remember It from my strange dream, but that was minuscule in comparison to the fear I felt.

&quot;You fight so eagerly with hope as your shield; defending you from reality, and with imagination as your weapon; striking me down in your mind, escaping this nightmare. If you will not allow anger to be one with you, then I.. I SHALL CORRUPT YOU WITH CHAOS AND ANGER MYSELF!&quot; It screamed at me angrily, and I could feel death&#39;s embrace approach my life; the shock was too much to handle.

I could directly associate It&#39;s words with those which were in my dream. I shivered and stared absently into the devil&#39;s eyes. It grabbed my arm with its hands and casted me towards the mad-man.

I turned my head to look at him. He was awaiting my falling arrival with open arms, and droplets of sweat were pouring down his face. He showed no emotion.

Catching me the palms of his hands, he threw me to the ground, although as I looked up at him, I realized I was lower than the ground itself. Panicking horribly, I looked to my left and my right, analysing my surroundings.

I couldn&#39;t help but notice the soil that surrounded me like a wall. Dirt began to fall on me, and once again I heard snarling.

I was the reason he dug.

&quot;Wake.. time.. come on.. wake up,&quot; a heavenly voice fluttered around my ears making little sense, yet giving me great comfort. I smiled as I listened.

&quot;Wake up! It&#39;s time to get up! Come on! Hurry! You have to go, now! Wake up,&quot; the heavenly voice became more realistic by the second and my awareness rose to the highest of heights. I looked up to find a girl shaking me. I recognized her face. I couldn&#39;t help but think of the dream I&#39;d had. It was a dream; I was waking from it.

&quot;Alright, enough of this. Some cold water should do the trick!&quot;

I was completely awake, but my eyes were still slightly closed. Upon hearing &quot;cold water&quot;, I groaned and tried to open my eyes as fast as I possibly could. They kept closing as I forced them open. My mind was willing me to sleep again, but I would rather wake up than have cold water poured over me only then to be brought to my senses!

&quot;I&#39;m awake, I&#39;m awake! Put the water away,&quot; I almost sobbed in agony whilst I begged.

I looked briefly to my left and right. I could see soil. Lots of soil. I began quaking in fear - it wasn&#39;t a dream. I was going to die. Hallucinations? Hopefully not. Help me, please help me, I begged to Guthix in my mind.

I looked down to my chest as I felt pressure upon it. I saw a hand with a Black glove on it, then as I followed the wrist to the arm, eventually to the face, I recognized the person who stood above me. It was my partner.

I sighed with relief, and a tear fell from my eye. Luckily Dayna didn&#39;t notice it.

&quot;Are you ok? You seem pretty shook up. I&#39;m not gonna ask how you got in here,&quot; she continued after a deep breath, &quot;but I&#39;m really concerned. I can&#39;t leave you in your own house anymore. I mean, does somebody have something against you or.. nevermind. Let&#39;s talk about it later. We&#39;ve got business to take care of.&quot;

I nodded and stood up sharply. Waving my hands all over my body and occasionally slapping myself, I banished the dust from my clothes.

&quot;Wait, Dayna,&quot; a drop of sweat fell from my brow and I panicked - I couldn&#39;t see my sword anywhere.

&quot;What&#39;s up?&quot; her face cared about my words, and I liked that.

&quot;I can&#39;t see my sword, I mean, I had it last night. Last I had it, I was right behind that bu-&quot; I suddenly realised that there was no bush.

&quot;That what?&quot; she inquired. &quot;Wait, your sword!? How in Guthix&#39;s name could you have lost your sword! Oh dear Guthix, this is a problem indeed. We&#39;ll need to find it.&quot;

I nodded quickly without a second thought, and smiled invisibly, reminding myself how much I loved Dayna. She was perfect.

Dayna had long blond hair, which at the tips, grew more darker. Her skin was angelic; not too white, and not too brown. Her lips were a luscious pink, and when she bit them, I couldn&#39;t help but fall in love with her even more. She bit her lip when she was shocked, but sometimes.. she bit her lip when she was trying to be seductive. No, not trying - she was seductive.

I proceeded along the dirty path that lead to my house as Dayna assumed leadership of the group - I followed her. Her hair bounced behind her back and streamed downwards like a beautiful waterfall whilst she walked along the path. It almost touched her brown, leather boots.

She eventually entered my house, and with that, she lifted her arm above her head and landed her hand on it, then let it flow through her hair and let out a big sigh.

&quot;Look, we need to go. Do you still have that dragon dagger your father gave you? It&#39;s poisonous, but it will have to do. We can&#39;t be bothered about a clean job when we have no weapons to do it properly.&quot; she didn&#39;t seem enthusiastic about this job, and I couldn&#39;t figure out why; she usually loved it - every second of it.

&quot;I do. Hang on and I&#39;ll get it. But, when we get back, can we look for my sword? I couldn&#39;t have lost it. No, I haven&#39;t lost it.&quot; in speaking I reached over to a small set of dust-infested drawers and opened the top one.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 12:26:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What a surprise…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 12:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparscape4lifez moparscape4lifez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparscape4lifez">@moparscape4lifez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="13" data-topic="208569">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/revein/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> reVein:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You are very childish stupid and block headed…If u wanna know my achievements Here are just some of them… I was programing computer at the age of 6 and built my first computer at the age of 7 though the years I have done web programing for people, designed my own programs, I have help design and program games for Sony and EA Games, was on of the programmers for the Anti-virus Avast witch is way better then Norton I might add, I have Designed programs for Apple, I have fought Leukemia at the age of 14 and beat it, and used my make a wish to meet bill gates and He said I was a Genius and Hired me at the age of 16 and I am currently almost ready to retire at the age of 25 with two homes one three million dollar home in Washington And One one 2.5 Million dollar home in Hawaii. Well there u go I’m tired and g2 bed P.S I’m going to ignore u now I don’t like to talk to people who act Childish I’ve got better things to do then to talk to a sad and pathetic person like you…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>ROFL at the age of 7 I found out I’m Messiah from the creator of the universe and I have the power to go forward or back in time. At the age of 10 from tapping into the energy of Jesus Christ himself I figured out how to travel to different stars by a means of a special device I engineered that could bend the universe to any form I want too… it was all simply a matter of putting in coordinates and after the universe was bended I could just walk a step… but I walked a thousand light years. Anyways I met a alien called Teal and we joined forces to fight aliens who want to take over the universe as supreme beings we obviously don’t care about them but a story needs a enemy or it will be boring. Anyways the enemy race called themselves the Daleks. Armed with only a plunger as their main weapon they could suck the shit out of your ass! and make you eat it.</p>
<p><img src="http://www.bbc.co.uk/doctorwho/gallery/s2_12-13gallery/800/daleks.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>It was all good until the Daleks came in their mothership traveling for 5000 thousand years to get to earth (I have the power of time travel don’t forget so it took me a matter of seconds to go into the future and at the year 5000 the Daleks destroyed Earth.</p>
<p>I didn’t care I just went back in time to this present and forgot everything that ever happened…</p>
<p>The End.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/23</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ilyaostr9 io9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ilyaostr9">@ilyaostr9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Project Evolution, post:18, topic:208569”][quote author=jme link=topic=274851.msg2442551#msg2442551 date=1221527282]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Her skin was angelic; not too white, <span class="bbcode-b">and not too brown</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Fkn racist…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">niggers have feelings too</span><br>
[/quote]<br>
That just showed your racism.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>You are very childish stupid and block headed…If u wanna know my achievements Here are just some of them… I was programing computer at the age of 6 and built my first computer at the age of 7 though the years I have done web programing for people, designed my own programs, I have help design and program games for Sony and EA Games, was on of the programmers for the Anti-virus Avast witch is way better then Norton I might add, I have Designed programs for Apple, I have fought Leukemia at the age of 14 and beat it, and used my make a wish to meet bill gates and He said I was a Genius and Hired me at the age of 16 and I am currently almost ready to retire at the age of 25 with two homes one three million dollar home in Washington And One one 2.5 Million dollar home in Hawaii. Well there u go I’m tired and g2 bed P.S I’m going to ignore u now I don’t like to talk to people who act Childish I’ve got better things to do then to talk to a sad and pathetic person like you…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What a cute story, your really good at writing fictional stories about yourself.[/quote]</p>
<p>You have completely missed the point of both of those jokes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/22</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 05:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_Evolution Project Evolution]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_evolution">@Project_Evolution</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No I think the world would be better if you did.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 22:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_bank the bank]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_bank">@the_bank</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Project Evolution, post:18, topic:208569”][quote author=jme link=topic=274851.msg2442551#msg2442551 date=1221527282]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Her skin was angelic; not too white, <span class="bbcode-b">and not too brown</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Fkn racist…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">niggers have feelings too</span><br>
[/quote]<br>
That just showed your racism.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>You are very childish stupid and block headed…If u wanna know my achievements Here are just some of them… I was programing computer at the age of 6 and built my first computer at the age of 7 though the years I have done web programing for people, designed my own programs, I have help design and program games for Sony and EA Games, was on of the programmers for the Anti-virus Avast witch is way better then Norton I might add, I have Designed programs for Apple, I have fought Leukemia at the age of 14 and beat it, and used my make a wish to meet bill gates and He said I was a Genius and Hired me at the age of 16 and I am currently almost ready to retire at the age of 25 with two homes one three million dollar home in Washington And One one 2.5 Million dollar home in Hawaii. Well there u go I’m tired and g2 bed P.S I’m going to ignore u now I don’t like to talk to people who act Childish I’ve got better things to do then to talk to a sad and pathetic person like you…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What a cute story, your really good at writing fictional stories about yourself.[/quote]Go die.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 21:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jme, post:17, topic:208569”]Fkn racist…</p>
<p>niggers have feelings too[/quote]</p>
<p>Oh come on… out of all the text there, that’s all you could come up with?</p>
<p>Project Evolution, I’d rather that, if you were on my side or whatever, you’d comment on the story rather than defend me from people you needn’t.  Thanks for the help though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 16:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Project_Evolution Project Evolution]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/project_evolution">@Project_Evolution</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“jme, post:17, topic:208569”][quote author=I Br3ndan I link=topic=274851.msg2245548#msg2245548 date=1211919665]<br>
Her skin was angelic; not too white, <span class="bbcode-b">and not too brown</span><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Fkn racist…</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">niggers have feelings too</span>[/quote]<br>
That just showed your racism.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="13" data-topic="208569">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/revein/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> reVein:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>You are very childish stupid and block headed…If u wanna know my achievements Here are just some of them… I was programing computer at the age of 6 and built my first computer at the age of 7 though the years I have done web programing for people, designed my own programs, I have help design and program games for Sony and EA Games, was on of the programmers for the Anti-virus Avast witch is way better then Norton I might add, I have Designed programs for Apple, I have fought Leukemia at the age of 14 and beat it, and used my make a wish to meet bill gates and He said I was a Genius and Hired me at the age of 16 and I am currently almost ready to retire at the age of 25 with two homes one three million dollar home in Washington And One one 2.5 Million dollar home in Hawaii. Well there u go I’m tired and g2 bed P.S I’m going to ignore u now I don’t like to talk to people who act Childish I’ve got better things to do then to talk to a sad and pathetic person like you…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What a cute story, your really good at writing fictional stories about yourself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="208569">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 I Br3ndan I:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Her skin was angelic; not too white, <span class="bbcode-b">and not too brown</span></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Fkn racist…</p>
<p>niggers have feelings too</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 01:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@army_life army_life]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/army_life">@army_life</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tl;dr</p>
<p>I skimmed and just by the look of it… it looks in a nicer word ‘not straight’</p>
<p><img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"> Good job typing though waste of time imo</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not the type of person who’d flare up because of a silly incident like this.  Forgiven and forgotten, absolutely.  Anyway, I digress.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 20:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Were you created to make me laugh?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 17:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reVein reVein]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/revein">@reVein</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You are very childish stupid and block headed…If u wanna know my achievements Here are just some of them… I was programing computer at the age of 6 and built my first computer at the age of 7 though the years I have done web programing for people, designed my own programs, I have help design and program games for Sony and EA Games, was on of the programmers for the Anti-virus Avast witch is way better then Norton I might add, I have Designed programs for Apple, I have fought Leukemia at the age of 14 and beat it, and used my make a wish to meet bill gates and He said I was a Genius and Hired me at the age of 16 and I am currently almost ready to retire at the age of 25 with two homes one three million dollar home in Washington And One one 2.5 Million dollar home in Hawaii. Well there u go I’m tired and g2 bed P.S I’m going to ignore u now I don’t like to talk to people who act Childish I’ve got better things to do then to talk to a sad and pathetic person like you…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>What the hell are you talking about?   <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=6" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 16:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@reVein reVein]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/revein">@reVein</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>NO OFFENCE BUT fuck u… u idiot ur family idiot… mother fucker why dont he fucking lock the topic if he dont want people to thank him…what else people want to say??? + why he sticked this shit</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 15:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Interesting, Adam.  That’s a new concept for me to understand and take into account.  Thanks for letting me in on that, and thanks for the compliments.</p>
<p>Tamorak`, you have my thanks too.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 15:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tamorak Tamorak`]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tamorak">@Tamorak</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like this. It seems very interesting  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 20:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mod_Adam Adam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_adam">@Mod_Adam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Really a great plot. All the really needs work is your grammar: sentence structure, parallelism, etc.</p>
<p>Example of un unparallel sentence in your story:</p>
<blockquote>I looked to my left and my right</blockquote>
<p>Should be:<br>
I looked to my left and <span class="bbcode-b">to</span> my right</p>
<p>Great story though. I know this is from May, but it was only about 7 threads down, so it’s not really gravedigging.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 05:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>How… something more original?  It came straight from my mind, I didn’t get any ideas from anyone else… and it has nothing to do with RuneScape apart from the mention of <span class="bbcode-i">some</span> names.  Thanks for posting, I guess.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 16:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goatee goatee]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goatee">@goatee</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You really could have written something more original. Why are you writing about Runescape? I feel mean saying it because you obviously spent some time on this but … it’s runescape.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 04:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“la­wl, post:2, topic:208569”]who the fuck would make a story about runescape</p>
<p>faggot[/quote]</p>
<p>Lots of people.  This is <span class="bbcode-i">loosely</span> based on RuneScape2, and that’s just because it’s against the rules to make a random story there.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="3" data-topic="208569">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Silver Lining:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Worst. Fan-fic. Ever.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why do you think that?  Thanks for not absolutely flaming the hell out of me.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="4" data-topic="208569">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/cruzer/40/5_6bca9977b612b7aeef77ba1ec1cd67b3.png" class="avatar"> Cruzer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I lol’d.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d rather you posted something constructive if you didn’t like it please.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cruzer Cruzer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cruzer">@Cruzer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I lol’d.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 06:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Silver_Lining Silver Lining]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/silver_lining">@Silver_Lining</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Worst. Fan-fic. Ever.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 01:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lawl lawl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lawl">@lawl</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>who the fuck would make a story about runescape</p>
<p>faggot</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 01:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Br3ndan_I I Br3ndan I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_br3ndan_i">@I_Br3ndan_I</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ahhh.  This is suicide.  Heh.  I thought I’d already posted this here… but it seems I didn’t.  It’s a little story I wrote on the RuneScape forum over a couple of weeks.</p>
<p>Have a read if you like.  I realise there’re a lot of errors, especially punctually.  It’s far from complete.</p>
<hr>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u">Prologue</span>[/center]</p>
<p>Everything is working according to my plan…</p>
<p>My wrath knows no boundaries, but the boundaries know my wrath- all too well. I will break loose soon, and every race shall be manipulated into slaves.</p>
<p>Zamorak the pretender… he will soon be obliterated, and each of his followers with him. Yes, everything is working according to my plan…</p>
<p>Foul, wretched humans. Short, dotted dwarfs. Proud, though feeble elves. Gnomes… Hahahaha.</p>
<p>I cannot help but notice one human though. You. I observe your every move, every day, every hour, every minute, every second. You are a pitiful excuse for a possible threat, but a threat still you are. Oh and that, Wise Old Man. Wise, yes… He knows me. He’s one of the few left who recognize my name. You’ll both become minions, under my name. Useless you will be, although humorous to me. Humorous to watch such established hero-like figures beg for death, mercy, and curse my very name.</p>
<p>Foolish though humans are, I must be lenient with them… they are after all, setting me free; digging up my temples, altars and relics. They are granting me breath, in some form of thinking.</p>
<p>And you, adventurer. You have been most helpful. You’ve given the humans even more reason to dig passionately, in hopes of finding something of great worth. Not to mention freeing my priest from that weak Zamorak’s temple… Finally, I have one who can carry out my bidding, and will do so without hesitation.</p>
<p>I will come for you, first of all. Keep a keen eye, adventurer. Hero of the people. Quester of the lands.</p>
<p>I will come for you. And wreak havoc upon this land. I shall rule, once more.</p>
<p>[center]<span class="bbcode-u">Foresight</span>[/center]</p>
<p>“Indulge your thirst for blood. Embrace the craving for murder.” A tall, red, smoke devil grasped my neck, and glared into my begging eyes unmercifully. It didn’t flinch, It didn’t twitch, It didn’t live. I prayed and prayed, but this only seemed to create a stronger connection with It.</p>
<p>“Pray… Yes… Beg for life, my child. Let the anger flow through your veins and I will set you free, forever.”</p>
<p>Still, I prayed. Still, I hoped. Still, I wondered. Wondered how such a being could come to existence. Wondered why it was in my home. Wondered why it was with me; I was but a young man, venturing the lands of Misthalin. I had nothing, no-one; no enemies, no friends, no family, no allies- I had nothing, no-one.</p>
<p>“You fight so eagerly with hope as your shield; defending you from reality, and with imagination as your weapon; striking me down in your mind, escaping this nightmare. If you will not allow anger to be one with you, then I… I SHALL CORRUPT YOU WITH CHAOS AND ANGER MYSELF!” In saying this, It lifted back what seemed to be It’s arm, and in it a weapon that could only have been suitable for the devil himself. With what could only have been described as a ‘thrust’, It pushed the sword towards me carelessly.</p>
<p>At this very moment, I woke. My nightmare was finished, yet it seemed so… real. More real than the word ‘real’ could ever mean to you. Beyond reality, if you will.</p>
<p>This nightmare- it had became apparent- had cost me several moons. I’d noticed that as I caught the very moon itself in the corner of my eye, out of my window, with beautiful rays of white light emanating from it, shining through and revealing clouds, invisible without the moon’s being.</p>
<p>“Strange,” I battled with logic in my mind.</p>
<p>Realization had fallen upon me; I wasn’t sweating, which is usually a key component in a nightmare; I didn’t wake up screaming and shifting, which is only natural…</p>
<p>Strange indeed.</p>
<p>Perhaps it wasn’t a nightmare, but foresight…</p>
<p>I had barely managed to rotate my head fully to get a definite view of the moon, and its beautiful surroundings. I hadn’t thought much of the nightmare; I was dazzled by the exceptional sight of the moon, and the perfect breeze that gently wrapped around my face and legs, making me shiver.</p>
<p>I love nights like this, I reminded myself.</p>
<p>Suddenly, the strangest of occurrences took place, directly in front of my window; a man seemed to be digging into the soil in the patch of grass mirroring my garden, casting it aside angrily, then kicking the spade he dug with to remove any excess compost that remained clinging to it.</p>
<p>I couldn’t decipher who he was; it was dark and he was quite far away. With eventuality my eyes adjusted fully to the lighting of the world, and my sight improved, allowing me to see who he was. I just had to wait for him to turn around and show his facial appearance…</p>
<p>Although this may sound a little odd to you, I had mastered the skill of jumping out of my bed and immediately readying myself in my own unique fighting stance. I had practiced doing it every night and morning, for… well, for as long as I can remember…</p>
<p>Becoming restless and curious, I carried out ‘the leap of destiny’ (The name of the aforementioned various movements) and rushed towards the window with haste.</p>
<p>I ran my hands softly against the wooden windowsill, appreciating my caring mood and the texture of the wood. I crouched a little, revealing only the top half of my head and the tips of my fingers to whoever would be looking in and through my window.</p>
<p>Finally! His face had turned towards me! “I know him,” I thought to myself, sighing in disappointment.</p>
<p>It was the ‘mad-man’ who roamed around; muttering words only he could comprehend; warning people of a violent hallucination that seemed so real to you, that if seen, would invoke such chaos in you that death was inevitably the ‘only way out’.</p>
<p>I feared he was performing a ritual of sorts, so I took my sword up.</p>
<p>My sword wasn’t long, nor was it short. It was smithed with the finest elemental ore, and crafted into what it became.</p>
<p>Due to the ore’s colour, the sword itself glowed a neon purple, and sometimes, if you concentrated enough, you could see small sprinkles of magical dust slipping off of the sword and into the wind’s hands.</p>
<p>I loved my sword. It made me appear unique. Mentioning not the source from which my sword was created to anyone, my lips proved secure and trustworthy.</p>
<p>Rushing silently through my garden, hearing the periodical grunts of the mad-man, the gravel-crunching noise which surrounded him when he slammed the spade into the ground, and my light footsteps upon the grass, I remained calm.</p>
<p>Concealing myself behind a rather conveniently placed bush, I pondered my next move; Should I wait, or should I attack?</p>
<p>I decided to wait; I didn’t want to reveal myself to him as of yet, and came to the conclusion that he would eventually divulge information relevant to his current actions.</p>
<p>I was still in an appreciative mood. It’s the kind of mood you get when you’re happy. No. Grateful. Grateful you’re alive, and what possessions and relationships with other people you have.</p>
<p>I appreciated the grass. Its soft, naturally pleasant texture; its slow, graceful sway in the gentlest of breezes; its gray-green colour; its delicate surface, granting me soundless steps…</p>
<p>I appreciated the bush. Its tiny leaves flowing in the direction the breeze sent it, then returning carefully to its foremost place on its branch; its size, perfectly providing me with cover.</p>
<p>I appreciated the sword. I slid my hands down it slowly, smiling and sighing happily, admiring the cold and exhilarating texture the elemental metal possessed.</p>
<p>I turned round to find my position, I had became aware, exposed. I was instantly confused, asking myself how the mad-man could’ve possibly seen me through the bush; I was perfectly hidden by it.</p>
<p>He laughed with an uncaring face.</p>
<p>I was unsure of what I should do. Stand up. Remain crouching. These options sang irritatingly and constantly in my mind. I decided to stand.</p>
<p>“How can you see me, old man?” I looked at him fully knowing of my tough appearance. I almost smiled because I knew that I looked like a hero of great.</p>
<p>“Hahahaha! What were you hiding behind, boy!? Was it a boulder!? A bush!? A crate!!!? Hahahaha!” He laughed snarlingly, coughs interrupting his every second word. He seemed to be the perfect villainous character.</p>
<p>I’d became slightly confused. I darent question the bush’s being, and at the same time, my sanity; it was definitely there. Alongside the confusion, embarrassment began to mock me.</p>
<p>The once proud smile morphed into a smile of doubt. I chuckled a little, too. Though none of these happy emotions were indeed happy.</p>
<p>A great man, known as the ‘Wise Old Man’ told me once that humans think of roughly one million things every second. At this very moment, I could hear his voice saying it.</p>
<p>I wondered, associating the apparently factual commment with my current state of different feelings, thoughts and such- could he have been right?</p>
<p>Eventually I overcame all of the unimportant issues that pressed against my mind. Like foot soldiers on ladders attempting to climb onto a wall, the issues attacked and attacked, whilst my mind fended them off by knocking down the ladders and piercing their being with arrows.</p>
<p>Mustering normality again, I managed to mutter some words.</p>
<p>“You’re the mad-man here, not me. How in the God’s names did you see me through the bush?” In saying these defensive words, I pushed my empty hand down hoping to touch something. Green shrubbery, rather than something, I pleaded with Guthix.</p>
<p>Nothing. A soft breeze caressed my hand, swirling around it, through my fingers, chilling the tips of my fingernails. It felt as though the breeze itself was attempting to comfort me.</p>
<p>Noticing my hand’s movement, the mad-man smirked and dug again.</p>
<p>I looked downwards to where the bush was. I raised one eyebrow and opened my mouth in awe. Following, fear struck me ruthlessly, causing me to scream.</p>
<p>I seen black smoke. A devil, with eyes like rubies glowing, glared at me, enticing my fear to expose itself through other means, rather than screaming.</p>
<p>I staggered a little and shouted, “GET BACK FROM ME! GET BACK! YOU’RE NOT REAL! AHHHHHH!”</p>
<p>I could hear snarling yet again. The sound drew my concentration not to the smoke devil which crouched before me, but to the mad-man.</p>
<p>He was busy digging; muttering words of old, disregarding my screams for help.</p>
<p>Fearfully, I looked back down onto the evil smoke to find the source of the laughing. Still, It glared into my eyes. I couldn’t help but remember It from my strange dream, but that was minuscule in comparison to the fear I felt.</p>
<p>“You fight so eagerly with hope as your shield; defending you from reality, and with imagination as your weapon; striking me down in your mind, escaping this nightmare. If you will not allow anger to be one with you, then I… I SHALL CORRUPT YOU WITH CHAOS AND ANGER MYSELF!” It screamed at me angrily, and I could feel death’s embrace approach my life; the shock was too much to handle.</p>
<p>I could directly associate It’s words with those which were in my dream. I shivered and stared absently into the devil’s eyes. It grabbed my arm with its hands and casted me towards the mad-man.</p>
<p>I turned my head to look at him. He was awaiting my falling arrival with open arms, and droplets of sweat were pouring down his face. He showed no emotion.</p>
<p>Catching me the palms of his hands, he threw me to the ground, although as I looked up at him, I realized I was lower than the ground itself. Panicking horribly, I looked to my left and my right, analysing my surroundings.</p>
<p>I couldn’t help but notice the soil that surrounded me like a wall. Dirt began to fall on me, and once again I heard snarling.</p>
<p>I was the reason he dug.</p>
<p>“Wake… time… come on… wake up,” a heavenly voice fluttered around my ears making little sense, yet giving me great comfort. I smiled as I listened.</p>
<p>“Wake up! It’s time to get up! Come on! Hurry! You have to go, now! Wake up,” the heavenly voice became more realistic by the second and my awareness rose to the highest of heights. I looked up to find a girl shaking me. I recognized her face. I couldn’t help but think of the dream I’d had. It was a dream; I was waking from it.</p>
<p>“Alright, enough of this. Some cold water should do the trick!”</p>
<p>I was completely awake, but my eyes were still slightly closed. Upon hearing “cold water”, I groaned and tried to open my eyes as fast as I possibly could. They kept closing as I forced them open. My mind was willing me to sleep again, but I would rather wake up than have cold water poured over me only then to be brought to my senses!</p>
<p>“I’m awake, I’m awake! Put the water away,” I almost sobbed in agony whilst I begged.</p>
<p>I looked briefly to my left and right. I could see soil. Lots of soil. I began quaking in fear - it wasn’t a dream. I was going to die. Hallucinations? Hopefully not. Help me, please help me, I begged to Guthix in my mind.</p>
<p>I looked down to my chest as I felt pressure upon it. I saw a hand with a Black glove on it, then as I followed the wrist to the arm, eventually to the face, I recognized the person who stood above me. It was my partner.</p>
<p>I sighed with relief, and a tear fell from my eye. Luckily Dayna didn’t notice it.</p>
<p>“Are you ok? You seem pretty shook up. I’m not gonna ask how you got in here,” she continued after a deep breath, “but I’m really concerned. I can’t leave you in your own house anymore. I mean, does somebody have something against you or… nevermind. Let’s talk about it later. We’ve got business to take care of.”</p>
<p>I nodded and stood up sharply. Waving my hands all over my body and occasionally slapping myself, I banished the dust from my clothes.</p>
<p>“Wait, Dayna,” a drop of sweat fell from my brow and I panicked - I couldn’t see my sword anywhere.</p>
<p>“What’s up?” her face cared about my words, and I liked that.</p>
<p>“I can’t see my sword, I mean, I had it last night. Last I had it, I was right behind that bu-” I suddenly realised that there was no bush.</p>
<p>“That what?” she inquired. “Wait, your sword!? How in Guthix’s name could you have lost your sword! Oh dear Guthix, this is a problem indeed. We’ll need to find it.”</p>
<p>I nodded quickly without a second thought, and smiled invisibly, reminding myself how much I loved Dayna. She was perfect.</p>
<p>Dayna had long blond hair, which at the tips, grew more darker. Her skin was angelic; not too white, and not too brown. Her lips were a luscious pink, and when she bit them, I couldn’t help but fall in love with her even more. She bit her lip when she was shocked, but sometimes… she bit her lip when she was trying to be seductive. No, not trying - she was seductive.</p>
<p>I proceeded along the dirty path that lead to my house as Dayna assumed leadership of the group - I followed her. Her hair bounced behind her back and streamed downwards like a beautiful waterfall whilst she walked along the path. It almost touched her brown, leather boots.</p>
<p>She eventually entered my house, and with that, she lifted her arm above her head and landed her hand on it, then let it flow through her hair and let out a big sigh.</p>
<p>“Look, we need to go. Do you still have that dragon dagger your father gave you? It’s poisonous, but it will have to do. We can’t be bothered about a clean job when we have no weapons to do it properly.” she didn’t seem enthusiastic about this job, and I couldn’t figure out why; she usually loved it - every second of it.</p>
<p>“I do. Hang on and I’ll get it. But, when we get back, can we look for my sword? I couldn’t have lost it. No, I haven’t lost it.” in speaking I reached over to a small set of dust-infested drawers and opened the top one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 20:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-208569-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-old-one-watches/208569.rss">&quot;The Old One Watches&quot;</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
