<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>StonerScape! *IN CREATION NEED TIPS!***</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stonerscape-in-creation-need-tips/308388</link>
    <description>[u][b]StonerScape Project[/b][/u]

Hey everyone, i am deciding to start a new server and im gonna be making it called StonerScape :P i haven&#39;t really done much yet as i do have some help requests in the server help section for some things i am missing. But i do got all the custom editing in the client under control. I really wanna finish this project here is some thing&#39;s its gonna have.

[b]______________________________________________[/b]

[u][b]Marijuana System[/b][/u]
-There is Marijuana which is a custom edited guam leaf, what you&#39;re gonna be able to do is steal from a stall didn&#39;t decide which one yet it will be level 50 thieving req, it will say, you have stole 1 gram of Marijuana. 
-I have The rolling paper thing figured out  :P
The Silk Stall will say, you have received 1 blunt wrap and 1 zig-zag. Then i&#39;ll re name some note things in the items list.

Right now im just planning out the System that involves Marijuana. Later i&#39;ll have seed stalls give you like 1 speed pill and stuff like that.

-I haven&#39;t really did much yet in this besides some of the Marijuana part  :P Im posting my ideas atm. Umm i&#39;ll post pics soon as i get the &quot;marijuana&quot; system done i&#39;ll post pics of that.

-Pics (not many yet just the pics i wanna show u) i need the idea for the joint! so i can complete my code with use item and so when u use zig zag and marijuana u get join :)
--Only have zig-zag pic atm posting marijuana one in morning.
[IMG]http://i38.tinypic.com/28incic.png[/img]


[IMG]http://i35.tinypic.com/10dyz5c.png[/img]

One thing before i can get the Marijuana system back in progress, what should i use for the joint?

Thx Reply and gimme some tips for this project and get creds if it helps!


::Need Tips::</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 22:21:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stonerscape-in-creation-need-tips/308388.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>StonerScape! *IN CREATION NEED TIPS!***</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Skillapwnz Skillapwnz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/skillapwnz">@Skillapwnz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">StonerScape Project</span></span></p>
<p>Hey everyone, i am deciding to start a new server and im gonna be making it called StonerScape <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> i haven’t really done much yet as i do have some help requests in the server help section for some things i am missing. But i do got all the custom editing in the client under control. I really wanna finish this project here is some thing’s its gonna have.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">______________________________________________</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Marijuana System</span></span><br>
-There is Marijuana which is a custom edited guam leaf, what you’re gonna be able to do is steal from a stall didn’t decide which one yet it will be level 50 thieving req, it will say, you have stole 1 gram of Marijuana.<br>
-I have The rolling paper thing figured out  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>
The Silk Stall will say, you have received 1 blunt wrap and 1 zig-zag. Then i’ll re name some note things in the items list.</p>
<p>Right now im just planning out the System that involves Marijuana. Later i’ll have seed stalls give you like 1 speed pill and stuff like that.</p>
<p>-I haven’t really did much yet in this besides some of the Marijuana part  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> Im posting my ideas atm. Umm i’ll post pics soon as i get the “marijuana” system done i’ll post pics of that.</p>
<p>-Pics (not many yet just the pics i wanna show u) i need the idea for the joint! so i can complete my code with use item and so when u use zig zag and marijuana u get join <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
–Only have zig-zag pic atm posting marijuana one in morning.<br>
<img src="http://i38.tinypic.com/28incic.png" alt width="190" height="266"></p>
<p><img src="http://i35.tinypic.com/10dyz5c.png" alt width="190" height="262"></p>
<p>One thing before i can get the Marijuana system back in progress, what should i use for the joint?</p>
<p>Thx Reply and gimme some tips for this project and get creds if it helps!</p>
<p>::Need Tips::</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stonerscape-in-creation-need-tips/308388/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stonerscape-in-creation-need-tips/308388/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 22:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-308388-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/stonerscape-in-creation-need-tips/308388.rss">StonerScape! *IN CREATION NEED TIPS!***</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
