<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What happened?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-happened/222084</link>
    <description>This site used to be a load of fun, we would all be together and know who everyone be one big crappy family.  Now all I see as I log on for the first time in forever are a bunch of newbs with no idea how to do anything, just picking up where all of us left off... no one from the old old days, before moparscape 3.0 or whatever crap it was was released that I see is online. (silab does not count, she equals to 99% of the intelligence this is on this site i would guess, anyway I am curious to see what will happen to these servers now as JAGeX has released their new high detail version.  I&#39;m even more interested to see what happens if all of the remaining real programmers on this site leave and give it to the new people.  I guess I will just have to wait and see, see you all in 5 months...  Hopefully...</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 08:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-happened/222084.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What happened?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Itachi_Uchiha Itachi Uchiha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/itachi_uchiha">@Itachi_Uchiha</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This site used to be a load of fun, we would all be together and know who everyone be one big crappy family.  Now all I see as I log on for the first time in forever are a bunch of newbs with no idea how to do anything, just picking up where all of us left off… no one from the old old days, before moparscape 3.0 or whatever crap it was was released that I see is online. (silab does not count, she equals to 99% of the intelligence this is on this site i would guess, anyway I am curious to see what will happen to these servers now as JAGeX has released their new high detail version.  I’m even more interested to see what happens if all of the remaining real programmers on this site leave and give it to the new people.  I guess I will just have to wait and see, see you all in 5 months…  Hopefully…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-happened/222084/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-happened/222084/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 08:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-222084-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-happened/222084.rss">What happened?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
