<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Findbitmap in taskbar; how to change windowfocus</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/findbitmap-in-taskbar-how-to-change-windowfocus/307984</link>
    <description>Hello there. I&#39;ve been looking to change the focus of window between different programs I&#39;ve got running, and my thought was to do this by scanning the taskbar with findbitmapin for the associated icon for the program I need. Oddly enough, SCAR doesn&#39;t seem able to do this reliably, sometimes it&#39;ll click in the area just above the program I want, sometimes it won&#39;t detect anything at all, sometimes it clicks randomly and miles away from what I really want it to... Now I&#39;ve done a little testing, and when I make it writeln the received x,y coordinates, where it clicks is *really* where the findbitmapin says it found the bitmap.

Has anyone had this problem before? Is there a more reliable way to change windowfocus with a script? (I don&#39;t want to mess around with making it hit alt-tab and whatnot)
Thanks! :D[br][br][size=1]Posted on: October 13, 2009, 08:04:15 pm[/size][hr]Solution was found, and I&#39;ll share it here. Changing window focus can only be done by changing to the active SCAR target window, calling &quot;ActivateClient&quot;. Combine this with Set/GetClientWindowHandle and FindWindowTitlePart and you can create something that works.
[code]begin
 activateclient;
 handle:=GetClientWindowHandle;
[...code...]
 if(findwindowtitlepart(&#39;C:\WINDOWS\system32\cmd.exe&#39;,true))then
  begin ActivateClient;
  [...code for cmd prompt...]
  SetClientWindowHandle(handle);    //return focus to original target window
  activateclient;
  end;
[..more code..]
end[/code]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 22:31:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/findbitmap-in-taskbar-how-to-change-windowfocus/307984.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Findbitmap in taskbar; how to change windowfocus</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@medy medy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/medy">@medy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello there. I’ve been looking to change the focus of window between different programs I’ve got running, and my thought was to do this by scanning the taskbar with findbitmapin for the associated icon for the program I need. Oddly enough, SCAR doesn’t seem able to do this reliably, sometimes it’ll click in the area just above the program I want, sometimes it won’t detect anything at all, sometimes it clicks randomly and miles away from what I really want it to… Now I’ve done a little testing, and when I make it writeln the received x,y coordinates, where it clicks is <em>really</em> where the findbitmapin says it found the bitmap.</p>
<p>Has anyone had this problem before? Is there a more reliable way to change windowfocus with a script? (I don’t want to mess around with making it hit alt-tab and whatnot)<br>
Thanks! :D[br][br][size=1]Posted on: October 13, 2009, 08:04:15 pm[/size][hr]Solution was found, and I’ll share it here. Changing window focus can only be done by changing to the active SCAR target window, calling “ActivateClient”. Combine this with Set/GetClientWindowHandle and FindWindowTitlePart and you can create something that works.</p>
<p><code>begin
 activateclient;
 handle:=GetClientWindowHandle;
[...code...]
 if(findwindowtitlepart('C:\WINDOWS\system32\cmd.exe',true))then
  begin ActivateClient;
  [...code for cmd prompt...]
  SetClientWindowHandle(handle);    //return focus to original target window
  activateclient;
  end;
[..more code..]
end</code></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/findbitmap-in-taskbar-how-to-change-windowfocus/307984/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/findbitmap-in-taskbar-how-to-change-windowfocus/307984/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 22:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-307984-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/findbitmap-in-taskbar-how-to-change-windowfocus/307984.rss">Findbitmap in taskbar; how to change windowfocus</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
