<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Le bouclier du temps: La marque du dragon</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133</link>
    <description>I am really hoping someone has had to read this book before, and can explain it to me.
I have to read it for my French class, but the problem is I don&#39;t understand anything going on in in, nor does the rest of the class.
My teacher is a bitch and won&#39;t help us with it. I&#39;ve been in French Immersion my whole life, but this was written in France, so the French is different than what I learn.
I will need anything like a brief summery on characters, summery of the book or even chapters. I&#39;ll take whatever I can get for this project.
A small donation will be made to who ever can help me out.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 05:33:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Le bouclier du temps: La marque du dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Holic Holic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/holic">@Holic</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>That helps a bit, but if I’m not mistake,  that’s from the back of the book. heh.<br>
Thanks though, I’m sure it’ll help.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 05:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210133-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133.rss">Le bouclier du temps: La marque du dragon</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Le bouclier du temps: La marque du dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eh_Pretty_Easy Eh Pretty Easy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eh_pretty_easy">@Eh_Pretty_Easy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A new series of youth fiction, reading from 11 years! For fans of science fiction After years spent in England to complete his education, David, teen aged 14 and sole heir of the family Grendel, is revealing a strange destiny: it is the last time Shield, responsible for restore the course of history when it is disturbed. The Grendel is not a family like any other. Each member has the gift of travel through time and the universe. For this, they use the bridge, unique and valuable machine shelter in the basement of the Manoir de Fer, the old family home of Grendel, Grandville.</p>
<p>David Grendel is in danger: his past fades gradually and undermines its future. To stop this strange phenomenon, the Shield of Time is to visit the snowy forests of transylvanie around the year 1480. There, the cruel Vlad Tepes, better known as Dracula, fights his brother, Radu terrible, to retain the throne of Wallachia.<br>
And it seems that during a previous mission, Marcus, the father of David, has chosen the wrong side …</p>
<p>Shit translation, but I guess that’s good.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 22:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210133-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133.rss">Le bouclier du temps: La marque du dragon</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Le bouclier du temps: La marque du dragon</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Holic Holic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/holic">@Holic</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am really hoping someone has had to read this book before, and can explain it to me.<br>
I have to read it for my French class, but the problem is I don’t understand anything going on in in, nor does the rest of the class.<br>
My teacher is a bitch and won’t help us with it. I’ve been in French Immersion my whole life, but this was written in France, so the French is different than what I learn.<br>
I will need anything like a brief summery on characters, summery of the book or even chapters. I’ll take whatever I can get for this project.<br>
A small donation will be made to who ever can help me out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-210133-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/le-bouclier-du-temps-la-marque-du-dragon/210133.rss">Le bouclier du temps: La marque du dragon</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
