<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>DDoS Threats [SOLVED]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ddos-threats-solved/443307</link>
    <description>Turns out somebody somehow got access to my No-IP account and deleted my hostnames. I got them back. Thanks everyone.

===============================================================================================
Normally I wouldn&#39;t be bothered, but this post got me due to its decent grammar.

[quote=&quot;VengenceIsPower, post:1, topic:3383&quot;]My, My:

From the time of my departure, much has occurred in this server. Kids will be kids though. Unless my demands are met, this server shall meet it&#39;s demise as previously stated. Regardless, within 3 days from this post, the server will recieve downtime due to &quot;vps issues&quot; and possible &quot;non-hacking&quot; related errors, but I can assure you it is a lie. Whatever, whenever you do, remember this. Enigmas are very hard to break, and even harder to form.

While you scramble frantically to figure out what I may do, how I may attack, remember this: We are Legion, We do not Forget, We do not Firgive. And we never will stop pursuing the hunt, even if it takes months of dormancy to achieve our goals.

Remember us, PR

And most of all, remember that:

KSUW   SY   DJMT

Our demands are as follows:

Current Developer Skyru be demoted and castrated in public for ineffiency and lack of programming knowlege.

Player Luna be sodomized by a Colt.

Player Zack to immediately be removed from both forums and server.

Player Salthesexy be immediately removed as a developer.

Meet these, and a permanant solution may not be necessary. Goodbye.[/quote]

I don&#39;t want to be infracted for advertising, but if you want the full article it is [url=http://projectrainbow.net/smf/index.php?topic=6083.msg39610]here[/url] (remove it if you think it&#39;s advertising).

He&#39;s hiding under a Tor address.

Real or fake? Should I be scared? My server runs on a VPS with 300mb/300mb speeds.

Oh and it looks like he doesn&#39;t like web developers.

[quote=&quot;VengenceIsPower, post:12, topic:3222&quot;][quote author=Ruby link=topic=6083.msg39592#msg39592 date=1338186623]
[quote author=VengenceIsPower link=topic=6083.msg39588#msg39588 date=1338186346]
[quote author=Ruby link=topic=6083.msg39587#msg39587 date=1338186087]
100% Bullshit, you&#39;re pretending to be the one hacking team this world cannot find. You would not be fucking around with a private server. Take your vengance and take the power from it right up your ass.
[/quote]

I&#39;d much rather lol as you try to stop me with your l337 programming skillz.

..Oh wait, you&#39;re a web developer lol.

[/quote]

Being a website developer takes more programming languages than an in-game developer on private servers.
[/quote]

Good sir, I was never a rsps developer. Trust me, website devs are more artists than real programmers. Hence why you all use styling languages.[/quote]


Whac</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 07:08:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ddos-threats-solved/443307.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>DDoS Threats [SOLVED]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whackatre Whackatre]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whackatre">@whackatre</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Turns out somebody somehow got access to my No-IP account and deleted my hostnames. I got them back. Thanks everyone.</p>
<p>===============================================================================================<br>
Normally I wouldn’t be bothered, but this post got me due to its decent grammar.</p>
<p>[quote=“VengenceIsPower, post:1, topic:3383”]My, My:</p>
<p>From the time of my departure, much has occurred in this server. Kids will be kids though. Unless my demands are met, this server shall meet it’s demise as previously stated. Regardless, within 3 days from this post, the server will recieve downtime due to “vps issues” and possible “non-hacking” related errors, but I can assure you it is a lie. Whatever, whenever you do, remember this. Enigmas are very hard to break, and even harder to form.</p>
<p>While you scramble frantically to figure out what I may do, how I may attack, remember this: We are Legion, We do not Forget, We do not Firgive. And we never will stop pursuing the hunt, even if it takes months of dormancy to achieve our goals.</p>
<p>Remember us, PR</p>
<p>And most of all, remember that:</p>
<p>KSUW   SY   DJMT</p>
<p>Our demands are as follows:</p>
<p>Current Developer Skyru be demoted and castrated in public for ineffiency and lack of programming knowlege.</p>
<p>Player Luna be sodomized by a Colt.</p>
<p>Player Zack to immediately be removed from both forums and server.</p>
<p>Player Salthesexy be immediately removed as a developer.</p>
<p>Meet these, and a permanant solution may not be necessary. Goodbye.[/quote]</p>
<p>I don’t want to be infracted for advertising, but if you want the full article it is <a href="http://projectrainbow.net/smf/index.php?topic=6083.msg39610" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a> (remove it if you think it’s advertising).</p>
<p>He’s hiding under a Tor address.</p>
<p>Real or fake? Should I be scared? My server runs on a VPS with 300mb/300mb speeds.</p>
<p>Oh and it looks like he doesn’t like web developers.</p>
<p>[quote=“VengenceIsPower, post:12, topic:3222”][quote author=Ruby link=topic=6083.msg39592#msg39592 date=1338186623]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>100% Bullshit, you’re pretending to be the one hacking team this world cannot find. You would not be fucking around with a private server. Take your vengance and take the power from it right up your ass.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d much rather lol as you try to stop me with your l337 programming skillz.</p>
<p>…Oh wait, you’re a web developer lol.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Being a website developer takes more programming languages than an in-game developer on private servers.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Good sir, I was never a rsps developer. Trust me, website devs are more artists than real programmers. Hence why you all use styling languages.[/quote]</p>
<p>Whac</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ddos-threats-solved/443307/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ddos-threats-solved/443307/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 07:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-443307-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ddos-threats-solved/443307.rss">DDoS Threats [SOLVED]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
