<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907</link>
    <description>Well some noob PMed me this

[quote=&quot;PLENIS&quot;]Hey man

I got this in my pm and I&#39;m spreading it around.. looks like it&#39;s from Renegays... Wanna help me hand it around mate? 

Could only fit a little...but it&#39;s still good

A few people are doing it with me. Just let me know if you&#39;re in, Blazin and Xion deserve everything that comes to them so we&#39;re leaking their crap lol. Long live Sythe!




[quote]

Glitches And Bugs - By The ReNeGade Group (www.renegade-crew.com)

Glitches found working as of March 17th, 2007

Table Of Contents:

1. The Basic Information
2. Terms And Agreements
3. Warnings
4. The Castle Wars Glitch (Sheeps/Imps)
5. The Dueling Arena Glitch (Remove Staked Items)
6. Teleporting Above Level 20 Wilderness/While Teleblocked (Side Effects Happen)
7. Dragging People Into The Wilderness (Ignoring Ditch)
8. Next Releases
9. Closing Information



1. The Basic Information

The ReNeGade Group formed in Oct. 2006 in plain boredom, as we grew, we focused on runescape cheats. One of our team members, Prohibited, thought it would be cool if we searched for glitches on runescape, and we found that pretty fun so we continued to do so, and made documents of them. We have discovered 53 bugs/glitches to date! We only publish the ones that we&#39;re pretty sure still work, and after we have no use for them.


2. Terms And Agreements

The glitches/bugs that you use here have a chance to get you banned if you are caught. By using the ones we have provided for you, you agree to understand that it is up to you to use them, and if you get banned, it is not our fault in the least. Furthermore, we take no responsibility for your actions with these glitches/bugs so no &quot;NO JAGEX PLZ UNBAN ME DESE GUYZ CALLED RENGEDE GROOP TOLD ME 2 AN TEY SED HOW 2&quot;.

3. Warnings

There are side effects to some of these bugs such as teleporting above level 20 wilderness that might get you stuck in runescape, such as teleporting but ending up in the ocean. ALWAYS BRING TELEPORTING RUNES WHILE DOING THIS. Also, do not bring valuable items while doing any of these.

4. The Castle Wars Glitch (Sheeps/Imps)

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Required before you start:                                                                                                         
GamaTool Version v5 And Up (Downloadable at http://rapidshare.com/files/27550915/GamaTool.zip)     
Members account on RuneScape  
A games necklace                                                                                               
A Zammy/Sara Prayer Book OR A holy/unholy amulet                                                                      
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

4a. First you will need to download the GamaTool if you don&#39;t already have it, If you have any reason to not trust this file please do not download it. I know personally that it&#39;s safe but I don&#39;t wish to be blamed for any wrong doings, so if you are cautious I advise you not to download it.

4b. After you download it, set the gama to 43, speed to about 28 and traction to 60. This will deliver the best results.

4c. Once finished setting those, click &quot;On&quot; on the bottom-right corner, if all successful, a &#39;Operate&#39; and &#39;Advanced&#39; tab should now appear. Go into any members world, go to castle wars and be sure to have a games necklace and prayer book or amulet. If you have a zammy book or unholy amulet, go to the sara team, if you have a sara book or holy amulet, go to the zamorak team.

4d. Once in the waiting room, you will be a sheep or imp, MAKE SURE THE GAMATOOL IS SET ON, now if the gama tool is on, it should have interface id&#39;s in the &quot;Operate&quot; tab, find Interface 2263 and set it to True (This is the inventory interface, it will force the server to show the inventory)

4e. After you set it to true, runescape should freeze a little then you should be able to see your inventory, go back to the gama tool and back to the operate tab, find Action ID 4478 and set it to false (this is what stops you from teleporting), now use the games necklace to teleport to barbarian outpost. If you did everything right, you should still be a sheep/imp.

5. The Dueling Arena Glitch (Remove Staked Items)

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Required before you start:                                                                                                         
GamaTool Version v5 And Up (Downloadable at http://rapidshare.com/files/27550915/GamaTool.zip)     
Members account on RuneScape                                                                                               
Stuff to stake (obviously)
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

5a. First you will need to download the GamaTool if you don&#39;t already have it, If you have any reason to not trust this file please do not download it. I know personally that it&#39;s safe but I don&#39;t wish to be blamed for any wrong doings, so if you are cautious I advise you not to download it.

5b. After you download it, set the gama to 64, speed to about 51 and traction to 60. This will deliver the best results.

5c. Once finished setting those, click &quot;On&quot; on the bottom-right corner, if all done successful, a &#39;Operate&#39; and &#39;Advanced&#39; tab should now appear. Go into any members world, and go to the duel arena. 

5d. Use the bank there and get stuff to stake, maybe an iron dagger or something, just to test it out first, start off small. 

5e. After that, duel someone, put up the item you wish to stake, accept, then when in the duel open up the gama tool, THIS MUST BE DONE FAST OR YOU&#39;LL BE KILLED, go to the &quot;Operate&quot; tab, find Interface 3921 and set it to true.

5f. If done right, you will have the stake screen once again in the duel, remove what you staked, click accept and then click close on that interface, you will have the item back in your inventory and if you lose the duel, you keep your item.
[/quote][/quote]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 May 2007 18:39:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SWAT SWAT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/swat">@SWAT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i got another 1</p>
<p>Name:  Adramax<br>
Posts:  0 (N/A per day)<br>
Position:  CBA to Post<br>
Rep:  10</p>
<p>Date Registered:  Today at 15:29:48<br>
Last Active:  Today at 15:38:42</p>
<p>[quote=“Adramax”]Great guide, everything but the disconnecting enemy one works. Only thing I ask is that you give it to some people, time for revenge on these guys…</p>
<p>[quote]RUNESCAPE 2 OFFICIAL EXPLOIT GUIDE/PROGRAMS</p>
<p><a href="http://www.rs2cheating.us/forums/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rs2cheating.us/forums/</a></p>
<p>Written by ? ? Acid B?´? ? ?<br>
With the help of…<br>
Lynx (Helped program <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip</a>)<br>
Raz0r556 (Helped program <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip</a>)<br>
Chag5 (wanted name in credits)</p>
<p>TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THE USE OF THIS GUIDE</p>
<p>We are not responsible for ANY damages caused to Jagex and/or the <a href="http://runescape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">runescape.com</a> game by the use of this guide. Everything posted in this guide is not to be used whilst playing runescape, it is purely for educational purposes.<br>
By reading this guide you agree to keep it exclusive to <a href="http://rs2cheating.us" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rs2cheating.us</a> and do not discuss the contents of this guide anywhere other than the aforementioned site. You will also NOT attempt to pass <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip</a> off as your own. It remains the properly of <a href="http://rs2cheating.us" rel="nofollow noopener">rs2cheating.us</a>.</p>
<p>IF I SEE THIS GUIDE ON ANY OF THOSE OTHER FAGGY CHEATING/FAN SITES I’LL BAN WHOEVER LEAKED IT AND TAKE DOWN THE RAPIDSHARE. IT IS AVAILABLE ONLY TO ADMINS/MODS/DONATORS OF <a href="http://RS2CHEATING.US" rel="nofollow noopener">RS2CHEATING.US</a> (NOT REGULAR USERS).</p>
<p>Thanks<br>
~Acidburn</p>
<p>Now let’s get to the cheating!</p>
<p>(This is a skeleton exploit guide, many other exploits can be done but these are the staple exploits. Others can be found in the donating members forum [hidden] in our site)</p>
<p>Contents<br>
0. Intro<br>
1: Fighting sploits<br>
Dueling<br>
1 Logging during duels<br>
2 Changing opts at second screen<br>
3 Hitting through prayer<br>
Wilderness<br>
1. Skulling enemy<br>
2. Disconnecting enemy during battle<br>
Non-wilderness	<br>
1. Attacking anyone in any house</p>
<p>2: Monetary gain exploits (disregarding fighting sploits)<br>
1. Other player has accepted, orly?<br>
2. The flawless scam.<br>
3. Money appearance hack.</p>
<p>3: Site exploits<br>
<a href="http://www.rs2cheating.us/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=773" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rs2cheating.us/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=773</a></p>
<p>4: Useful links and guides<br>
1. Proxying<br>
2. Proxying software<br>
3. Some nice tools</p>
<p>5: Closing statement<br>
The end!</p>
<p>Before we start, you’ll need this (or those of you with technical knowledge can use artmoney or WPE PRO but it’s easier to use this). <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip</a></p>
<p>Browser settings will be automatically detected and the program targetted using wpecontrol.dll. No configuration required.</p>
<p>1- FIGHTING SPLOITS</p>
<p>Y’all remember those screenshots I posted a while ago? Well here’s how I did some of them. This is probably the highlight of the guide (for pure fun anyway).</p>
<p>These fall into three categories really, dueling, wilderness and non-wilderness/dueling.</p>
<p>Dueling</p>
<p>1<br>
The first exploit we’re talking about here is logging during a duel.</p>
<p>You can use this so you NEVER lose a duel. If you’re about to lose, you can send a d/c packet at the server which will disconnect you instantly.</p>
<p>(X’ing out has the same effect but it may not ping time-out at the exact time. This WILL.</p>
<p>Open WPE(rs232) <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zipand" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zipand</a> make sure your browser is targetted by the dll. Go to the text editor part of the program (packet sender) and enter the following details in:</p>
<p>| 00 04 04 04 FF EF CC A1 3A |</p>
<p>(Include the |'s, they tell the program where to put the packet headers)</p>
<p>Click “Send” and you should be instantly disconnected from the duel.</p>
<p>THIS DOES NOT WORK IN WILDERNESS.</p>
<p>2<br>
The second exploit involves changing options AT THE SECOND SCREEN.</p>
<p>You can use this for making the duel range only or so, at the second screen. This way a level 3 can beat a lvl 126 quite easily (if he has no range equipment). Works best with magic in my experience.</p>
<p>Open WPE(rs232) <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip</a> and change the filter to the following:</p>
<p>1st chain: 00 00 00 FF FF A4<br>
2nd chain: 00 00 00 FF 00 00</p>
<p>(From position in chain found)</p>
<p>3</p>
<p>The final dueling exploit is hitting through prayer. (Boring I know, but it can make a huge difference in duels)</p>
<p>The applications for this are obvious, so I’ll skip the crap let’s get onto how to do it.</p>
<p>1st chain: 00 A9 A9 A9 0F<br>
2nd chain: 00 AB A9 A9 0F</p>
<p>(From position in chain found)</p>
<p>Wilderness</p>
<p>Ok so here’s the part most of you have been waiting for. Only two exploits in this section but they are VERY useful.</p>
<p>1</p>
<p>Making any opponent skull <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip</a></p>
<p>Requirements:<br>
You must be in combat with the player you wish to skull.<br>
The fight must be single area combat zone (working on patch for this… You can download the update when I make it using the d/l section on our site…)</p>
<p>Just get the user ID (click the goddamn button you fools) and send the following packet:</p>
<p>| FF FF FF D5 05 A5 VAR1 |</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Disconnecting your opponent mid-battle. <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip</a></p>
<p>The best update in my opinion, disconnection.</p>
<p>If you do this in the middle of the battle, the opposing player will stand there unable to move his character (applet crash their side) so you can kill them freely.</p>
<p>Get the user ID and send the following packet:</p>
<p>| 00 04 04 04 FF EF CC A1 3A VAR1 |</p>
<p>Non-wilderness</p>
<p>Only one exploit so far here guys, sorry.</p>
<p>More available in our forums I guess…</p>
<ol>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Attacking people anywhere in someone’s house. (They don’t lose items unfortunately).</p>
<p>Just filter the following:</p>
<p>1st chain: DD EE E0 01<br>
2nd chain: D0 AB A9 02 02 02</p>
<p>(from start)</p>
<p>2- MONETARY GAIN EXPLOITS</p>
<p>Here’s the section where we get our pee-hats <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> lol</p>
<ol>
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>“Other player has accepted” message on second screen.</p>
<p>THIS ONLY LASTS FOR 2 SECONDS. BE QUICK.</p>
<p>Trade with someone and go to the second screen. <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip</a></p>
<p>Get the user ID and remove your cash (Or get someone to show you a good item in second screen, like a pile of cash…) and send this packet:</p>
<p>| C3 C3 C3 VAR C3 C3 C3 |</p>
<p>The message will appear for 2 seconds and allow you to accept the trade through. BE QUICK OR YOU’LL MISS IT.</p>
<p>Free items ftw.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Changing items flawlessly (WIll show up on second screen only) <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/29636788/WPE_rs232_.zip</a></p>
<p>You can use this to change say, a veracs helm for a veracs skirt in trade. (MUST HAVE BOTH ITEMS IN INVENTORY)</p>
<p>Select an item and get the item ID. Select the second item, and get the second item ID, then filter the following:</p>
<p>1st chain: VAR1 00 00 01 VAR1<br>
2nd chain: VAR2 00 00 01 VAR2</p>
<p>I told you it was simple.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>This is the only place in this guide we use the money switcher, this will change the LOOK of an item rather than it’s value.</p>
<p>Just select your cash in runescape and change the value from it’s current value to whatever. Say 10k to 10m, then go out and trade someone. (If you make it appear as 10m, anyone trading you will see 10m but will receive 10k.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>SITE EXPLOITS</li>
</ol>
<p>Site exploits can be found… here: <a href="http://www.rs2cheating.us/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=773" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.rs2cheating.us/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=773</a></p>
<p>(This is in case the guide is leaked. It is posted in the admin forum solely due to legal… uh… hiccups. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> )</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<p>USEFUL LINKS AND GUIDES</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Proxying</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Proxying with firefox/IE is easy.</p>
<p>For any retards who can’t do it, here’s a quick-ass guide.</p>
<p>FIREFOX</p>
<p>Go to tools&gt;options&gt;general settings&gt;connection settings</p>
<p>Click “Use http proxy” and paste an ip/port from a proxylist site…</p>
<p><a href="http://www.samair.ru/proxy" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.samair.ru/proxy</a> or google “proxy list”</p>
<p>INTERNET EXPLORER</p>
<p>Go to tools &gt; options &gt; connection settings &gt; lan settings and change the ip the same as you would in FF.</p>
<p>Also you can use cgi proxies… (simple way) just google “cgi proxy” for a few</p>
<p><a href="http://xroxy.net/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://xroxy.net/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.anonymous.org/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.anonymous.org/</a></p>
<p>SOCKS PROXIES</p>
<p>If you want to SOCKS proxy a java applet, the best way is to program your own for the exact ports, etc. Get a friend to run it (or direct traffic yourself.)</p>
<p>Here’s a simple guide to programming a simple proxy in vb using winsock controls…</p>
<p><a href="http://proxy.oflameron.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://proxy.oflameron.com/</a></p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Torbutton for firefox is great. Sorry I just had to share this lol.</p>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="https://tor.eff.org//" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tor.eff.org</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:690/345;"><img src="https://www.torproject.org/static/images/tor-project-logo-onions.png" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://tor.eff.org//" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Tor Project | Privacy &amp; Freedom Online</a></h3>

<p>Defend yourself against tracking and surveillance. Circumvent censorship.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>

<p>Just install and run vidalida and proxyway at the same time. Then install torbutton for FIREFOX and right click tor to change ip. Not bad eh?</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>An old, but great site:</p>
<p><a href="http://library.2ya.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://library.2ya.com</a> for all your devilish needs.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.serialz.ws" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.serialz.ws</a> for a few serials. (DON’T DOWNLOAD KEYGENS, THEY’RE ALL VIRUSES)</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Thanks to everyone at rscheating for keeping us afloat with your generous donations.</p>
<p>If you’re not from rscheating and you’re reading this, then rest assured the links will not stay up for long. However, if you enjoyed this guide then please register at our website and maybe donate some cash to us? We have a private forum with LOTS of new exploits that aren’t mentioned here and much more besides. We are a tight-knit community and the recent changes in rule 12 won’t change us one iota, unlike the other sites! Like I said before, this is a really small guide and the majority is on our website.</p>
<p>I will be releasing a much smaller version of this guide to maybe entice more users to our site. Please if you have read this, do not hand it out everywhere. We want to keep our activities as secret as possible, Jagex have the ability to fix these bugs remember.</p>
<p>Thank you and goodbye!</p>
<p>[/quote][/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2007 18:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90907-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss">What the fuck? A virus?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_robby mod robby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_robby">@mod_robby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“BaracudaX, post:7, topic:90907”]wtf? i dont get it so some noob spammed u is there a problem?[/quote] They beleive there is a virus or something inside the persons soposaby a “Gramma tool” but people suspect there is a virus in the file.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2007 03:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90907-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss">What the fuck? A virus?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BaracudaX BaracudaX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/baracudax">@BaracudaX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wtf? i dont get it so some noob spammed u is there a problem?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2007 00:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90907-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss">What the fuck? A virus?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@teric6 teric6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teric6">@teric6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve seen this posted alot, please don’t lock this to keep people informed <span class="bbcode-b">NOT</span> to go-ahead and use it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 23:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90907-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss">What the fuck? A virus?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SWAT SWAT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/swat">@SWAT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>look at this</p>
<p>Date Registered:  Today at 18:53:40<br>
Last Active:  Today at 19:30:29</p>
<p>i am 95% sure that its a virus</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 23:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90907-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss">What the fuck? A virus?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@teric6 teric6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teric6">@teric6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ok i’m doing so now!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 23:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90907-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss">What the fuck? A virus?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SWAT SWAT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/swat">@SWAT</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i think its a virus he doesn’t have any posts on the forum…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 23:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90907-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss">What the fuck? A virus?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Click_Here Click Here]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/click_here">@Click_Here</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This should be Reported To an Admin or a G Mod, And they will look into it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 23:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90907-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss">What the fuck? A virus?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What the fuck? A virus?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@teric6 teric6]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/teric6">@teric6</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well some noob PMed me this</p>
<p>[quote=“PLENIS”]Hey man</p>
<p>I got this in my pm and I’m spreading it around… looks like it’s from Renegays… Wanna help me hand it around mate?</p>
<p>Could only fit a little…but it’s still good</p>
<p>A few people are doing it with me. Just let me know if you’re in, Blazin and Xion deserve everything that comes to them so we’re leaking their crap lol. Long live Sythe!</p>
<p>[quote]</p>
<p>Glitches And Bugs - By The ReNeGade Group (<a href="http://www.renegade-crew.com" rel="nofollow noopener">www.renegade-crew.com</a>)</p>
<p>Glitches found working as of March 17th, 2007</p>
<p>Table Of Contents:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>The Basic Information</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Terms And Agreements</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Warnings</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Castle Wars Glitch (Sheeps/Imps)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Dueling Arena Glitch (Remove Staked Items)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Teleporting Above Level 20 Wilderness/While Teleblocked (Side Effects Happen)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Dragging People Into The Wilderness (Ignoring Ditch)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Next Releases</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Closing Information</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Basic Information</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>The ReNeGade Group formed in Oct. 2006 in plain boredom, as we grew, we focused on runescape cheats. One of our team members, Prohibited, thought it would be cool if we searched for glitches on runescape, and we found that pretty fun so we continued to do so, and made documents of them. We have discovered 53 bugs/glitches to date! We only publish the ones that we’re pretty sure still work, and after we have no use for them.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Terms And Agreements</li>
</ol>
<p>The glitches/bugs that you use here have a chance to get you banned if you are caught. By using the ones we have provided for you, you agree to understand that it is up to you to use them, and if you get banned, it is not our fault in the least. Furthermore, we take no responsibility for your actions with these glitches/bugs so no “NO JAGEX PLZ UNBAN ME DESE GUYZ CALLED RENGEDE GROOP TOLD ME 2 AN TEY SED HOW 2”.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Warnings</li>
</ol>
<p>There are side effects to some of these bugs such as teleporting above level 20 wilderness that might get you stuck in runescape, such as teleporting but ending up in the ocean. ALWAYS BRING TELEPORTING RUNES WHILE DOING THIS. Also, do not bring valuable items while doing any of these.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>The Castle Wars Glitch (Sheeps/Imps)</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<h2>Required before you start:<br>
GamaTool Version v5 And Up (Downloadable at <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/27550915/GamaTool.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/27550915/GamaTool.zip</a>)<br>
Members account on RuneScape<br>
A games necklace<br>
A Zammy/Sara Prayer Book OR A holy/unholy amulet</h2>
<p>4a. First you will need to download the GamaTool if you don’t already have it, If you have any reason to not trust this file please do not download it. I know personally that it’s safe but I don’t wish to be blamed for any wrong doings, so if you are cautious I advise you not to download it.</p>
<p>4b. After you download it, set the gama to 43, speed to about 28 and traction to 60. This will deliver the best results.</p>
<p>4c. Once finished setting those, click “On” on the bottom-right corner, if all successful, a ‘Operate’ and ‘Advanced’ tab should now appear. Go into any members world, go to castle wars and be sure to have a games necklace and prayer book or amulet. If you have a zammy book or unholy amulet, go to the sara team, if you have a sara book or holy amulet, go to the zamorak team.</p>
<p>4d. Once in the waiting room, you will be a sheep or imp, MAKE SURE THE GAMATOOL IS SET ON, now if the gama tool is on, it should have interface id’s in the “Operate” tab, find Interface 2263 and set it to True (This is the inventory interface, it will force the server to show the inventory)</p>
<p>4e. After you set it to true, runescape should freeze a little then you should be able to see your inventory, go back to the gama tool and back to the operate tab, find Action ID 4478 and set it to false (this is what stops you from teleporting), now use the games necklace to teleport to barbarian outpost. If you did everything right, you should still be a sheep/imp.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>The Dueling Arena Glitch (Remove Staked Items)</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<h2>Required before you start:<br>
GamaTool Version v5 And Up (Downloadable at <a href="http://rapidshare.com/files/27550915/GamaTool.zip" rel="nofollow noopener">http://rapidshare.com/files/27550915/GamaTool.zip</a>)<br>
Members account on RuneScape<br>
Stuff to stake (obviously)</h2>
<p>5a. First you will need to download the GamaTool if you don’t already have it, If you have any reason to not trust this file please do not download it. I know personally that it’s safe but I don’t wish to be blamed for any wrong doings, so if you are cautious I advise you not to download it.</p>
<p>5b. After you download it, set the gama to 64, speed to about 51 and traction to 60. This will deliver the best results.</p>
<p>5c. Once finished setting those, click “On” on the bottom-right corner, if all done successful, a ‘Operate’ and ‘Advanced’ tab should now appear. Go into any members world, and go to the duel arena.</p>
<p>5d. Use the bank there and get stuff to stake, maybe an iron dagger or something, just to test it out first, start off small.</p>
<p>5e. After that, duel someone, put up the item you wish to stake, accept, then when in the duel open up the gama tool, THIS MUST BE DONE FAST OR YOU’LL BE KILLED, go to the “Operate” tab, find Interface 3921 and set it to true.</p>
<p>5f. If done right, you will have the stake screen once again in the duel, remove what you staked, click accept and then click close on that interface, you will have the item back in your inventory and if you lose the duel, you keep your item.<br>
[/quote][/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 23:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-90907-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/what-the-fuck-a-virus/90907.rss">What the fuck? A virus?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
