<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Portforwarding</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding/321149</link>
    <description>Yup, Its me again, the noob who can&#39;t code or anything on his own, So I&#39;m coming to the pro&#39;s of the portforwarding.

Yes, I tried uTurrent.
Yes, I went to my ip adress, allowed exceptions.
Yes, I&#39;m wi-fi.
Yes, I am a noob.
Yes, I need your help.

I have honestly tried everything, I&#39;ve had about 6 friends, who all have there own server, try and help me, but they can&#39;t.

I&#39;m using wi-fi on a windows xp, and it just won&#39;t work, noone can connect to my server, and its making me really sad.

I need my server up before Christmas, because I am moving, and I&#39;m going to get a vps, so guys, please help, its really important, I&#39;ll try and pay you if you can help..

Pritchardthomas@yahoo.com
or pm me, and We&#39;ll chat for a bit, and I may give you teamviewer Id and Pass.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 22, 2009, 09:05:31 pm[/size][hr]Noone, can help?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 11:55:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding/321149.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Portforwarding</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@i0wn3v3ry i0wn3v3ry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i0wn3v3ry">@i0wn3v3ry</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yup, Its me again, the noob who can’t code or anything on his own, So I’m coming to the pro’s of the portforwarding.</p>
<p>Yes, I tried uTurrent.<br>
Yes, I went to my ip adress, allowed exceptions.<br>
Yes, I’m wi-fi.<br>
Yes, I am a noob.<br>
Yes, I need your help.</p>
<p>I have honestly tried everything, I’ve had about 6 friends, who all have there own server, try and help me, but they can’t.</p>
<p>I’m using wi-fi on a windows xp, and it just won’t work, noone can connect to my server, and its making me really sad.</p>
<p>I need my server up before Christmas, because I am moving, and I’m going to get a vps, so guys, please help, its really important, I’ll try and pay you if you can help…</p>
<p><a href="mailto:Pritchardthomas@yahoo.com">Pritchardthomas@yahoo.com</a><br>
or pm me, and We’ll chat for a bit, and I may give you teamviewer Id and Pass.[br][br][size=1]Posted on: December 22, 2009, 09:05:31 pm[/size][hr]Noone, can help?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding/321149/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding/321149/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 11:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-321149-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/portforwarding/321149.rss">Portforwarding</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
