<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>UPTDScape - Reviving The Legacy</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039</link>
    <description>[center][img]http://faloria.net/cdn/LOGO.png[/img][/center]
[center]I thought the guidelines were a little messy. For my tastes anyway, sowwy :P[/center]

So realization struck around a week ago when I realized I still love the aspect of RuneScape private servers, plus, coding them isn&#39;t exactly rocket science either. After playing other games such as Minecraft which also has a server development team called Bukkit which made me think their should be some main source of up-to date server which would be simple to use and modular, similar to Bukkit in a way.

Bukkit has something called plugins which allow the server to pick up on them and use them, basically, drop a file in a folder and the server then reads the file and executes it with the main server files, thus eliminating the need for editing server files internally. A little about me, I used to play RuneScape six years ago and loved the game, couldn&#39;t really remember why I left more than likely got ripped of in some sort of trade xD Also, I own and maintain a site of mine http://tzeale.com. Not really used anymore but will be where the project will be updated and maintained with places for bug reporting and webclient.

Aims of the project would be modular addon support and would aim to update in parallel with the the main game, not exactly but that&#39;s what a team&#39;s for, basically trying to emulate closely as possible to the main game over at runescape.com. I have background experience in 3D Java game development and also HTML, PHP and so fourth. Currently, I&#39;m the only one in so far, i&#39;m looking for people with moderate Java programming experience. And preferably people who&#39;ve created their own source/client in the community. 

Feel free to contact me either through either;

[ul][li]Email: [email]Jack35@hotmail.co.uk[/email][/li]
[li]Skype: Danster39[/li][/ul]

Or just on the forums here regarding the project.

~Jarrrk</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 22:01:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>UPTDScape - Reviving The Legacy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@192.168.0.158 192.168.0.158]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/192.168.0.158">@192.168.0.158</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thanks, and I can’t remember. I made this account a long time ago and only just remembered the credentials. xD</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 22:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-461039-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039.rss">UPTDScape - Reviving The Legacy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UPTDScape - Reviving The Legacy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@I_Hybrid_I1 I_Hybrid_I]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_hybrid_i1">@I_Hybrid_I1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>dafuq is wrong with your username?</p>
<p>OT: Goodluck man.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-461039-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039.rss">UPTDScape - Reviving The Legacy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>UPTDScape - Reviving The Legacy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@192.168.0.158 192.168.0.158]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/192.168.0.158">@192.168.0.158</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[center]<img src="http://faloria.net/cdn/LOGO.png" alt width="" height="">[/center]<br>
[center]I thought the guidelines were a little messy. For my tastes anyway, sowwy :P[/center]</p>
<p>So realization struck around a week ago when I realized I still love the aspect of RuneScape private servers, plus, coding them isn’t exactly rocket science either. After playing other games such as Minecraft which also has a server development team called Bukkit which made me think their should be some main source of up-to date server which would be simple to use and modular, similar to Bukkit in a way.</p>
<p>Bukkit has something called plugins which allow the server to pick up on them and use them, basically, drop a file in a folder and the server then reads the file and executes it with the main server files, thus eliminating the need for editing server files internally. A little about me, I used to play RuneScape six years ago and loved the game, couldn’t really remember why I left more than likely got ripped of in some sort of trade xD Also, I own and maintain a site of mine <a href="http://tzeale.com" rel="nofollow noopener">http://tzeale.com</a>. Not really used anymore but will be where the project will be updated and maintained with places for bug reporting and webclient.</p>
<p>Aims of the project would be modular addon support and would aim to update in parallel with the the main game, not exactly but that’s what a team’s for, basically trying to emulate closely as possible to the main game over at <a href="http://runescape.com" rel="nofollow noopener">runescape.com</a>. I have background experience in 3D Java game development and also HTML, PHP and so fourth. Currently, I’m the only one in so far, i’m looking for people with moderate Java programming experience. And preferably people who’ve created their own source/client in the community.</p>
<p>Feel free to contact me either through either;</p>
<p>[ul][li]Email: <a href="mailto:Jack35@hotmail.co.uk" data-bbcode="true">Jack35@hotmail.co.uk</a>[/li]<br>
[li]Skype: Danster39[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>Or just on the forums here regarding the project.</p>
<p>~Jarrrk</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 16:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-461039-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/uptdscape-reviving-the-legacy/461039.rss">UPTDScape - Reviving The Legacy</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
