<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056</link>
    <description>I have been attempting to design the greatest economy for over a year now. The #1 challenge I have always stumbled across and what I do have to give kudos to Jagex somewhat battling is the factor that items just become too populated.

Before I begin with what I have come up with to battle this let me go into some detail in what I call &quot;a real economy&quot;. I have suggested this on several servers and well quite frankly I am surprised there aren&#39;t more spawn servers, considering all the servers I have seen players are point blank - LAZY. 

I can understand that this is a server, and nobody want&#39;s to have to gain stuff like on Runescape. But in reality it&#39;s the one and only true way of keeping an economy somewhat stable.

So let me explain...

I believe an economy is stabilized by low to somewhat medium level armor etc in the stores, limited number of runes in the store, no skiller resources such as ores in the stores. 

A real economy depends on the players to make the resources to sell to each other. A mage buys runes off of the grand exchange or whatever the trading is(forums etc ) 

Furthermore, a real ecnomy depends on not only npc drops, not only skiller drops, but a random drop table or in what I consider my version of &quot;slayer rewards.&quot; These rewards would be like for example nosepeg may be a drop from spectres, and you can get the pieces to make the slayer helmet. 

Another part of an economy is just like jagex, they make new models and bring them into the game. Well many of us are not modelers like the wanderer and such so what I designed were to make what I call &quot;rotating shops&quot;. At random times between once a week to once every two months one or two stores would have an entire different stock or it would have for example a magic robe shop with low level stuff may have blue wizard robes one week, the next it will have the black robes. 

Now, when I ran my server I had what I called &quot;gold or legend items&quot; these were actually trim products. These items were only put into a store for perhaps an  hour or two once a week. There would be no notification of it being added etc. The item would be essentially a money drainer from the economy. Meaning, the item will cost a fair bit. I had it where about 200-300m was an average money gain for about 3-4 days work on my server. The trim item would cost around 165-175m if not a little more. You make it so players do keep a little gold but you hit them hard. 

Another good idea is to give regular items sometimes a small bonus or an odd effect that isn&#39;t in runescape. For example, I made it so the different dragon masks would have a stat bonus depending on the color mask. For example red mask - 15% extra chance of better accuracy while mask was equipped. The masks were gained similar to the shop gold/legend item except instead of a store it was once a week for about half a day it would be a random drop from a random monster. Sometimes I would give a hint sometimes I wouldn&#39;t.  The drop needs to be VERY rare.

Now, let&#39;s continue on to &quot;how do we efficiently drain the economy without upsetting the players&quot; I have always found by making one item discontinued for let&#39;s say six months - to a year if the server lasts that long that is, you replace it with another item that can be gained in the similar fashion it was originally obtained. 


I don&#39;t claim for this tactic to be perfect, nor do I claim this is the best economy. However, I can say with confidence that if you start this economy and stay solid with it. Players will eventually join, and players will go by the economy. It makes merching actually happen on a server.

I hope this long topic has helped you understand how to design a proper economy. If you have any  questions feel free to ask. If you have any comments or changes that you believe would be beneficial feel free to comment on that as well.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 07:03:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>oh the seeds part was merely an example sorry if that wasn’t very clear.</p>
<p>When I ran fj at the end you could get from killing(it wasn’t considered a rare, it was like bones it would just randomly appear sometimes but not always but you could always get other drops instead of a seed of course! (same with ores/bars sometimes )</p>
<p>Whenever you planted a seed into the patch and after you harvested you would have like a 30% chance of getting it back, the higher the level seed the lesser the chance. Skillers could also get it from haystacks. It was my form of “seed thieving” so to speak. But instead you could get various skiller items ( generally you got lower level gems, lower to medium level seeds, etc )</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 07:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tutorial Tutorial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tutorial">@Tutorial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Loveandpower, post:12, topic:453056”][quote author=Tutorial link=topic=555905.msg4070735#msg4070735 date=1344321362]<br>
The dullest factor is simply making players earn their items. It shouldn’t be necessary to add temporary items; however, the biggest thing that affects an economy is the amount of players a server maintains on a daily basis. If you are a server with around 50 players, maybe you should consider having a higher drop rate, but if you have a server that is more populated it would only seem logical to decrease the rate.</p>
<p>There are tons of factors that affect the economy, but the only piece of advice I can give is to: limit item accessibility, creating an ideal drop rate for the community, and ignoring complaints about the economy. If you give in to one person, you will most likely give in to others. Also, if the majority of your players are complaining, you might want to either: A) reconsider your rates, or B) getting more active players.<br>
[/quote]exactly, the issue is you have to start them off with high rates in the beginning. I’ve ran servers before where rates were like 1 out of 100 before. They will just camp there, sadly, most rsps the  boss are just too easy. They are able to camp there because the items to make trips longer are EASY to get. I mean seriously, you can just go to a store and buy a seed? no thanks.[/quote]<br>
If the only way a person can go about getting a seed is by killing npcs, this might be bad and good. You would have to consider the following perspectives:</p>
<p>Combat - If someone that trained combat on a daily basis killed monsters and got at least drops that included 20 of any type of seed, this might be a good idea; however, I would not suggest going too high or too low. No one is going to spend forever killing monsters just to train farming.</p>
<p>Skiller - The only possible way a skiller would be able to get seeds for training farming would be to buy them or to create a main account. Most of the time, skillers make accounts that  contain only non-combat stats simply because they dislike combat. If someone did actually sell seeds, I’m sure they would not sell cheap. Plus, no one is going to pay an arm and a leg for skilling materials.</p>
<p>I don’t see a problem with adding a few of the lower level seeds to a shop, but as an opinion, I would not spend a ton of time slaying for seeds.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 06:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>My starter is 25 gp and bronze hatchet and pickaxe. :s</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 16:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Tutorial, post:11, topic:453056”]The dullest factor is simply making players earn their items. It shouldn’t be necessary to add temporary items; however, the biggest thing that affects an economy is the amount of players a server maintains on a daily basis. If you are a server with around 50 players, maybe you should consider having a higher drop rate, but if you have a server that is more populated it would only seem logical to decrease the rate.</p>
<p>There are tons of factors that affect the economy, but the only piece of advice I can give is to: limit item accessibility, creating an ideal drop rate for the community, and ignoring complaints about the economy. If you give in to one person, you will most likely give in to others. Also, if the majority of your players are complaining, you might want to either: A) reconsider your rates, or B) getting more active players.[/quote]exactly, the issue is you have to start them off with high rates in the beginning. I’ve ran servers before where rates were like 1 out of 100 before. They will just camp there, sadly, most rsps the  boss are just too easy. They are able to camp there because the items to make trips longer are EASY to get. I mean seriously, you can just go to a store and buy a seed? no thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 18:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tutorial Tutorial]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tutorial">@Tutorial</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The dullest factor is simply making players earn their items. It shouldn’t be necessary to add temporary items; however, the biggest thing that affects an economy is the amount of players a server maintains on a daily basis. If you are a server with around 50 players, maybe you should consider having a higher drop rate, but if you have a server that is more populated it would only seem logical to decrease the rate.</p>
<p>There are tons of factors that affect the economy, but the only piece of advice I can give is to: limit item accessibility, creating an ideal drop rate for the community, and ignoring complaints about the economy. If you give in to one person, you will most likely give in to others. Also, if the majority of your players are complaining, you might want to either: A) reconsider your rates, or B) getting more active players.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/11</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 06:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>An approach I will most likely be taking is, “dynamic drops”, if an item becomes too abundant among players, the drop rates of that item will be slower, and the price will go up.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/the">@The</a> guy who posted that starter: My starter only consits of 3 items: Bronze dagger, bronze pickaxe, and a bronze hatchet. I feel that’s all that is need to being an RSPS.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/10</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 02:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@vManlyMan vManlyMan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vmanlyman">@vManlyMan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“RS PS, post:5, topic:453056”]This is kind of like what I am doing with my server making it economy and for people who want to work and are not lazy.<br>
This is the starter in my server I am developing.</p>
<p><code>Starter:
500K GP
Iron Full Helm
Iron Platebody
Iron Platelegs
Iron Scimitar
Iron Kiteshield
Amulet of Strength
100 Air Runes
100 Mind Runes
100 Fire Runes
100 Water Runes
100 Earth Runes
100 Chaos Runes
Shortbow
300 Bronze Arrows
Iron Pickaxe
Iron Hatchet
Tinderbox
Knife
Spade
</code></p>
<p>Shops only range from bronze - adamant the rest you have to work for it gives players a challenge, I sadly see no servers like these I love these types of economies.[/quote]</p>
<p>I think 500k is way too much.  Maybe around 25-50k would be better.  Give them the items they need to make things rather than just give it to them.  Like a pickaxe to mine essence to make runes rather than just give them runes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 02:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“marcbob, post:7, topic:453056”]Because 90% of players would instantly quit if given nothing. People are even more retarded on servers then rs.[/quote]That’s their loss then.  You shouldn’t have to give anything to the players for them to stay.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 01:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marcbob marcbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcbob">@marcbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Because 90% of players would instantly quit if given nothing. People are even more retarded on servers then rs.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 23:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“RS PS, post:5, topic:453056”]This is kind of like what I am doing with my server making it economy and for people who want to work and are not lazy.<br>
This is the starter in my server I am developing.</p>
<p><code>Starter:
500K GP
Iron Full Helm
Iron Platebody
Iron Platelegs
Iron Scimitar
Iron Kiteshield
Amulet of Strength
100 Air Runes
100 Mind Runes
100 Fire Runes
100 Water Runes
100 Earth Runes
100 Chaos Runes
Shortbow
300 Bronze Arrows
Iron Pickaxe
Iron Hatchet
Tinderbox
Knife
Spade
</code></p>
<p>Shops only range from bronze - adamant the rest you have to work for it gives players a challenge, I sadly see no servers like these I love these types of economies.[/quote]Why would you give a starter at all?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 22:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@RS_PS RS PS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rs_ps">@RS_PS</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is kind of like what I am doing with my server making it economy and for people who want to work and are not lazy.<br>
This is the starter in my server I am developing.</p>
<p><code>Starter:
500K GP
Iron Full Helm
Iron Platebody
Iron Platelegs
Iron Scimitar
Iron Kiteshield
Amulet of Strength
100 Air Runes
100 Mind Runes
100 Fire Runes
100 Water Runes
100 Earth Runes
100 Chaos Runes
Shortbow
300 Bronze Arrows
Iron Pickaxe
Iron Hatchet
Tinderbox
Knife
Spade
</code></p>
<p>Shops only range from bronze - adamant the rest you have to work for it gives players a challenge, I sadly see no servers like these I love these types of economies.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 20:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“asshole_rule, post:2, topic:453056”]tl;dr but I did read some…</p>
<p>An economy like this requires a lot of players, which most rsps’s just can’t have. Also a lot of time, which most players aren’t willing to put in.[/quote]only if a person swaps to it after they spoiled the players. I started an economy simlar to this and the “skillers” of rsps did eventualy start to network with each other and help others get on. I do admit it’s hard to keep players but it’s well worth it.</p>
<p>[quote=“imsuperman05, post:3, topic:453056”][quote=Loveandpower]<br>
A real economy depends on the players to make the resources to sell to each other. A mage buys runes off of the grand exchange or whatever the trading is(forums etc )<br>
[/quote]This is the only paragraph that makes sense.[/quote]I see nothing hard about comprehending it Rodrigo</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 13:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@imsuperman05 imsuperman05]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/imsuperman05">@imsuperman05</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>A real economy depends on the players to make the resources to sell to each other. A mage buys runes off of the grand exchange or whatever the trading is(forums etc )</blockquote>This is the only paragraph that makes sense.
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 07:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asshole_rule asshole_rule]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asshole_rule">@asshole_rule</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tl;dr but I did read some…</p>
<p>An economy like this requires a lot of players, which most rsps’s just can’t have. Also a lot of time, which most players aren’t willing to put in.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 07:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My Dream Ecnomy</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loveandpower Loveandpower]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loveandpower">@Loveandpower</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have been attempting to design the greatest economy for over a year now. The <span class="hashtag">#1</span> challenge I have always stumbled across and what I do have to give kudos to Jagex somewhat battling is the factor that items just become too populated.</p>
<p>Before I begin with what I have come up with to battle this let me go into some detail in what I call “a real economy”. I have suggested this on several servers and well quite frankly I am surprised there aren’t more spawn servers, considering all the servers I have seen players are point blank - LAZY.</p>
<p>I can understand that this is a server, and nobody want’s to have to gain stuff like on Runescape. But in reality it’s the one and only true way of keeping an economy somewhat stable.</p>
<p>So let me explain…</p>
<p>I believe an economy is stabilized by low to somewhat medium level armor etc in the stores, limited number of runes in the store, no skiller resources such as ores in the stores.</p>
<p>A real economy depends on the players to make the resources to sell to each other. A mage buys runes off of the grand exchange or whatever the trading is(forums etc )</p>
<p>Furthermore, a real ecnomy depends on not only npc drops, not only skiller drops, but a random drop table or in what I consider my version of “slayer rewards.” These rewards would be like for example nosepeg may be a drop from spectres, and you can get the pieces to make the slayer helmet.</p>
<p>Another part of an economy is just like jagex, they make new models and bring them into the game. Well many of us are not modelers like the wanderer and such so what I designed were to make what I call “rotating shops”. At random times between once a week to once every two months one or two stores would have an entire different stock or it would have for example a magic robe shop with low level stuff may have blue wizard robes one week, the next it will have the black robes.</p>
<p>Now, when I ran my server I had what I called “gold or legend items” these were actually trim products. These items were only put into a store for perhaps an  hour or two once a week. There would be no notification of it being added etc. The item would be essentially a money drainer from the economy. Meaning, the item will cost a fair bit. I had it where about 200-300m was an average money gain for about 3-4 days work on my server. The trim item would cost around 165-175m if not a little more. You make it so players do keep a little gold but you hit them hard.</p>
<p>Another good idea is to give regular items sometimes a small bonus or an odd effect that isn’t in runescape. For example, I made it so the different dragon masks would have a stat bonus depending on the color mask. For example red mask - 15% extra chance of better accuracy while mask was equipped. The masks were gained similar to the shop gold/legend item except instead of a store it was once a week for about half a day it would be a random drop from a random monster. Sometimes I would give a hint sometimes I wouldn’t.  The drop needs to be VERY rare.</p>
<p>Now, let’s continue on to “how do we efficiently drain the economy without upsetting the players” I have always found by making one item discontinued for let’s say six months - to a year if the server lasts that long that is, you replace it with another item that can be gained in the similar fashion it was originally obtained.</p>
<p>I don’t claim for this tactic to be perfect, nor do I claim this is the best economy. However, I can say with confidence that if you start this economy and stay solid with it. Players will eventually join, and players will go by the economy. It makes merching actually happen on a server.</p>
<p>I hope this long topic has helped you understand how to design a proper economy. If you have any  questions feel free to ask. If you have any comments or changes that you believe would be beneficial feel free to comment on that as well.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 06:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-453056-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-dream-ecnomy/453056.rss">My Dream Ecnomy</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
