<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964</link>
    <description>[i][b]Crack. Light thud. Creek.[/b][/i] Noises coming from around the floor as you&#39;re in the beginning stages of sleep, waking you up.

&quot;[i]Mom...?[/i]&quot; You whimper out, looking beside you. &quot;[i]I heard noises...[/i]&quot; 
&quot;[i]It&#39;s the house, honey. It&#39;s old so the wood creeks sometimes.[/i]&quot; She replies.
&quot;[i]How does it creek by it self? Can you please see if there&#39;s someone there?[/i]&quot; You ask, knowing she&#39;s there to protect you.
&quot;[i]Okay.[/i]&quot; She opens the closet and gestures around. &quot;See? Nothing there&quot;.
&quot;[i]And the bed?[/i]&quot;
She checks under the bed with you. &quot;[i]See? There&#39;s nothing there. Only dust. Go to sleep now, okay, honey?[/i]&#39;&#39; 

It&#39;s not me. I&#39;m on your side, I haven&#39;t moved. You can&#39;t see me or it. But me and it can see each other. And it&#39;s whispering at you. I can&#39;t tell what it&#39;s saying. I don&#39;t speak the language or whatever that is. Tell your mom to check the corner! Who am I kidding, you can&#39;t hear me. Your mom forgot to check the corners. The most important part. It&#39;s there. It&#39;s RIGHT THERE. The noises you heard? It ran back to the corner. It can&#39;t get past me. Your mom&#39;s asleep, now. It&#39;s given away that you&#39;re not alone. They say that before you die, your life flashes before your eyes in seconds. That&#39;s not true. These vivid hallucinations that you call dreams are actually visions of what was actually supposed to happen in your life. It&#39;s the only time you&#39;re in contact with me. Well, partially. That falling dream? You were supposed to fall to your death. That person you were about to kiss before your mom woke you up for school? Yep, supposed to be your current partner. When you woke up randomly in the middle of the night? It almost had you. And I&#39;m sorry. It&#39;s always trying to get you. And I know I won&#39;t be there all the time. It will get through me. 

Remember that time when you went in a room and forgot what you were doing? Or that&#39;s what it seemed? It tried to get you. You blanked out - you didn&#39;t forget. It was too quick for me. You never trip unintentionally. It pushes you to try and take you out. You can&#39;t see it, which makes people think it was natural human senses - as in &quot;you tripped over your footing&quot;. I cushioned your fall so the best you got was a scrape of your elbow, or knee, or hand. I&#39;m sorry that I couldn&#39;t stop it good enough.

When your grandfather passed away, it was there. Standing by the grave. Watching as they lower him into the ground. As they lowered him, it went down with him into the grave. No face, one posture. As soon as the soil covered the casket, it dissolved into the casket.

When you read &quot;don&#39;t look behind you&quot;, your natural instincts and temptation makes you look behind you to satisfy your feeling of fright to relax yourself assuring that there&#39;s no one there. It went back in the corner. It knows you&#39;re fully aware now... As you&#39;re reading this- did you hear that? It just hopped to that corner on your right. It knows you&#39;re aware it&#39;s there. Look to your right. Focus your hearing. You can&#39;t see it. But you may be able to hear it... Do you hear it? I&#39;m pretty sure you could feel its presence. I mean, you always hide your feet with your blanket when you&#39;re sleeping. How did you know to do that? You have to focus. Feel its presence. It connects me with you. If we get connected, you can see it and you can keep your distance. But you can&#39;t get away from it. Death and it are related. When you were born, so was I. And so was it. We each have our own.

What I love about this is that you think it&#39;s the enemy. It&#39;s trying to get you away from me and return you where you belong. But I won&#39;t let it. You&#39;re mine.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 18:06:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Cole1497 Cole1497]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cole1497">@Cole1497</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>reading this at 12 in the afternoon doesnt have the same effect</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/9</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 18:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553964-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss">&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xdeathstarsx x Albi x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xdeathstarsx">@xdeathstarsx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ur worse than mopman</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 16:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553964-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss">&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Travas Travas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/travas">@Travas</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>u gave me nite mares</p>
<p>wayyy 2 spooky</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 19:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553964-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss">&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Ambokile, post:5, topic:553964”][quote author=siege engine link=topic=672886.msg4499629#msg4499629 date=1448713085]<br>
Im not going to read  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"><br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Don’t worry, we wouldn’t want you to strain yourself.[/quote]nice</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 18:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553964-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss">&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ambokile Ambokile]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ambokile">@Ambokile</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="553964">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 siege engine:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Im not going to read  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Don’t worry, we wouldn’t want you to strain yourself.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 23:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553964-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss">&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@siege_engine siege engine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/siege_engine">@siege_engine</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im not going to read  <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 12:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553964-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss">&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yesw</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 09:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553964-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss">&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 08:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553964-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss">&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@goudont goudont]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/goudont">@goudont</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Crack. Light thud. Creek.</span></span> Noises coming from around the floor as you’re in the beginning stages of sleep, waking you up.</p>
<p>“<span class="bbcode-i">Mom…?</span>” You whimper out, looking beside you. “<span class="bbcode-i">I heard noises…</span>”<br>
“<span class="bbcode-i">It’s the house, honey. It’s old so the wood creeks sometimes.</span>” She replies.<br>
“<span class="bbcode-i">How does it creek by it self? Can you please see if there’s someone there?</span>” You ask, knowing she’s there to protect you.<br>
“<span class="bbcode-i">Okay.</span>” She opens the closet and gestures around. “See? Nothing there”.<br>
"<span class="bbcode-i">And the bed?</span>"<br>
She checks under the bed with you. "<span class="bbcode-i">See? There’s nothing there. Only dust. Go to sleep now, okay, honey?</span>’’</p>
<p>It’s not me. I’m on your side, I haven’t moved. You can’t see me or it. But me and it can see each other. And it’s whispering at you. I can’t tell what it’s saying. I don’t speak the language or whatever that is. Tell your mom to check the corner! Who am I kidding, you can’t hear me. Your mom forgot to check the corners. The most important part. It’s there. It’s RIGHT THERE. The noises you heard? It ran back to the corner. It can’t get past me. Your mom’s asleep, now. It’s given away that you’re not alone. They say that before you die, your life flashes before your eyes in seconds. That’s not true. These vivid hallucinations that you call dreams are actually visions of what was actually supposed to happen in your life. It’s the only time you’re in contact with me. Well, partially. That falling dream? You were supposed to fall to your death. That person you were about to kiss before your mom woke you up for school? Yep, supposed to be your current partner. When you woke up randomly in the middle of the night? It almost had you. And I’m sorry. It’s always trying to get you. And I know I won’t be there all the time. It will get through me.</p>
<p>Remember that time when you went in a room and forgot what you were doing? Or that’s what it seemed? It tried to get you. You blanked out - you didn’t forget. It was too quick for me. You never trip unintentionally. It pushes you to try and take you out. You can’t see it, which makes people think it was natural human senses - as in “you tripped over your footing”. I cushioned your fall so the best you got was a scrape of your elbow, or knee, or hand. I’m sorry that I couldn’t stop it good enough.</p>
<p>When your grandfather passed away, it was there. Standing by the grave. Watching as they lower him into the ground. As they lowered him, it went down with him into the grave. No face, one posture. As soon as the soil covered the casket, it dissolved into the casket.</p>
<p>When you read “don’t look behind you”, your natural instincts and temptation makes you look behind you to satisfy your feeling of fright to relax yourself assuring that there’s no one there. It went back in the corner. It knows you’re fully aware now… As you’re reading this- did you hear that? It just hopped to that corner on your right. It knows you’re aware it’s there. Look to your right. Focus your hearing. You can’t see it. But you may be able to hear it… Do you hear it? I’m pretty sure you could feel its presence. I mean, you always hide your feet with your blanket when you’re sleeping. How did you know to do that? You have to focus. Feel its presence. It connects me with you. If we get connected, you can see it and you can keep your distance. But you can’t get away from it. Death and it are related. When you were born, so was I. And so was it. We each have our own.</p>
<p>What I love about this is that you think it’s the enemy. It’s trying to get you away from me and return you where you belong. But I won’t let it. You’re mine.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 08:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553964-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/wanting-you-a-creepy-story-by-me/553964.rss">&quot;Wanting you&quot; a creepy story by me</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
