<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>View of Progression</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540</link>
    <description>Progression is a rather complicated concept. However, describing it is rather simple. The dictionary defines progression as, &quot;a series with a definite pattern of advance&quot;. It&#39;s a well known fact that progression means a step forward. The complication comes when progression is attempted. There is no &#39;one-size-fits-all&#39; solution despite popular belief. This short article of sorts will take a bit more of a look at progression and it&#39;s dependencies.

The definition is the first key step in reaching a goal through the use of progression. Firstly, it&#39;s important to remember that goals cannot be achieved without progression being made. That&#39;s the key principal. Progression requires a pattern of success and what makes it a pattern repetition. It&#39;s important to learn what works and what doesn&#39;t. This means that all actions or ideas implemented must be monitored in hopes of finding a pattern that allows for success. Documenting every change is the path to progression. 

Whilst this is true, a particular pattern will not work when certain factors change. As said previously, there is no &#39;one-size-fits-all- solution. When there is change, our methods must also. I&#39;m not going to give an example for every idea that i touch upon because what works for one example would not share any similarities to any other cases of patterns being applied. Changing factors are caused by events. Documentation allows for us to clearly identify these events and to alter the pattern so that it continues to be as efficient.

So what causes progression? Every idea implemented to push forward success must have one of the following:

[ul][li]Self-Learning - Wherever the idea of progression is used in a community setting, the members must be able to learn without spoon feeding them information. Anything that an individual learns by him/herself will be converted to wisdom over time. I think it&#39;s rather clear how this contributes to progression. [/li]
[li]Sufficient Power - Without power of anything, progression cannot be made. It simply does not work. In a community environment, respect means a lot more than member privileges. It&#39;s important to never forget this. An idea presented by a respected member of a community will have a higher success rate.[/li]
[li]Fear - Fear is what runs the world. It&#39;s what turns large groups of people into sheep. Luckily, people are afraid of many things. The amount of insecurities that people have are amazing.[/li][/ul]


In conclusion, progression is rather simple to achieve. This doesn&#39;t mean that the pathway to our goals should be rushes or taken carelessly. Feel free to throw in your comments or conflicting ideas about it here. I wrote this ages ago but never bothered to post it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 09:59:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ollie Ollie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ollie">@Ollie</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Eye of the beholder.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 09:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Unhandled Unhandled]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/unhandled">@Unhandled</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go get a philosophy degree and write a book about nothing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/9</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 20:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Some people I know see “Progression” as “more of something”. This can only positive, but used in a negative context.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/8</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 16:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javacisnotrecognized _^_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javacisnotrecognized">@Javacisnotrecognized</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d like to add a thought to this: A fundamental (And neccessary) element to progression is awareness of information. In this context, by “awareness” I mean roughly, “Acquired knowlege that is considered in and has the possibility of altering a decision”. For example, you’re going to eat that apple on the counter. If you “know” the apple is rotten, but aren’t “aware” that it is is rotten (Or how its rottenness could influence your decision to eat it), then you might eat it anyway. (Not a very good example, but I think it conveys what I’m talking about)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/7</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 13:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Fear is the path to the dark side. Fear leads to anger. Anger leads to hate. Hate leads to suffering.</p>
<p>On a more serious note, you list a few things that lead to progression. But you don’t explain why they do. Knowledge doesn’t mean progression. If all cavemen just knew everything they knew at that time, it doesn’t explain why we have computers now. It’s the creativity and the guts to combine your knowledge that leads to progression. It often leads to nothing, but in some occasions it will lead to something.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 12:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“sanga282, post:4, topic:257540”][quote author=Tree link=topic=339997.msg2634991#msg2634991 date=1232452659]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>this seems more of a statement than an argument or discussion</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A statement allows for debate or discussion.<br>
[/quote]<br>
touché<br>
but as it is worded it just seems more of an expression of opinon rather than something to comment on[/quote]</p>
<p>It wasn’t really my intention to post it but i wanted to express my thoughts on something. I don’t do it often enough lately.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 12:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Tree, post:3, topic:257540”][quote author=sanga282 link=topic=339997.msg2634989#msg2634989 date=1232452570]<br>
this seems more of a statement than an argument or discussion<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>A statement allows for debate or discussion.[/quote]<br>
touché<br>
but as it is worded it just seems more of an expression of opinon rather than something to comment on</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A statement allows for debate or discussion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 11:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this seems more of a statement than an argument or discussion</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 11:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>View of Progression</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Progression is a rather complicated concept. However, describing it is rather simple. The dictionary defines progression as, “a series with a definite pattern of advance”. It’s a well known fact that progression means a step forward. The complication comes when progression is attempted. There is no ‘one-size-fits-all’ solution despite popular belief. This short article of sorts will take a bit more of a look at progression and it’s dependencies.</p>
<p>The definition is the first key step in reaching a goal through the use of progression. Firstly, it’s important to remember that goals cannot be achieved without progression being made. That’s the key principal. Progression requires a pattern of success and what makes it a pattern repetition. It’s important to learn what works and what doesn’t. This means that all actions or ideas implemented must be monitored in hopes of finding a pattern that allows for success. Documenting every change is the path to progression.</p>
<p>Whilst this is true, a particular pattern will not work when certain factors change. As said previously, there is no 'one-size-fits-all- solution. When there is change, our methods must also. I’m not going to give an example for every idea that i touch upon because what works for one example would not share any similarities to any other cases of patterns being applied. Changing factors are caused by events. Documentation allows for us to clearly identify these events and to alter the pattern so that it continues to be as efficient.</p>
<p>So what causes progression? Every idea implemented to push forward success must have one of the following:</p>
<p>[ul][li]Self-Learning - Wherever the idea of progression is used in a community setting, the members must be able to learn without spoon feeding them information. Anything that an individual learns by him/herself will be converted to wisdom over time. I think it’s rather clear how this contributes to progression. [/li]<br>
[li]Sufficient Power - Without power of anything, progression cannot be made. It simply does not work. In a community environment, respect means a lot more than member privileges. It’s important to never forget this. An idea presented by a respected member of a community will have a higher success rate.[/li]<br>
[li]Fear - Fear is what runs the world. It’s what turns large groups of people into sheep. Luckily, people are afraid of many things. The amount of insecurities that people have are amazing.[/li][/ul]</p>
<p>In conclusion, progression is rather simple to achieve. This doesn’t mean that the pathway to our goals should be rushes or taken carelessly. Feel free to throw in your comments or conflicting ideas about it here. I wrote this ages ago but never bothered to post it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 11:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257540-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/view-of-progression/257540.rss">View of Progression</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
