<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fiction</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860</link>
    <description>EditL things I need to do:
1. Expand on the wasteland description a bit more - it&#39;s quite boring right now imo.
2. I don&#39;t like the flow of &quot;events&quot; and sentences so I will probably be redoing it.

First draft of some fiction I am writing.
WARNING: massive tl;dr ahead, proceed with caution. You have been warned.
[hr]


The clearing was stirring. Creatures and animals cried in harmony as they woke from their stupor, their cries piercing the night, echoing beyond the reaches of the giant forest trees. The lake surface was undisturbed except by the occasional breeze, sending ripple flowing across it.

A deer approached the lake timidly, ears alert for any sound of danger, for many rumours had been circulated about that lake. Creatures had been known to disappear when pausing for a drink and the animals had many wild theories explaining the phenomena, ranging from rogue gnomes to a sea monster that had made the lake it&#39;s lair, emerging every few months to feast upon the unlucky beast that happened upon the lake at that night. The deer looked around inquisitively, then seemed to decide there was no imminent danger and trotted to the lake. It bent down and starting sipping water from it.

[center]***[/center]

Slav stared at the barren wasteland ahead of him. He purred with contentment. It was a strange feeling, being near so much death he could hear the echoes of long gone soldiers fighting for long lost causes, after being forced to live near throbbing streams of life energy. He took the time to siphon energy from the area; he was of the opinion that one could never have enough energy on his person, and this belief had saved his life multiple times.

Slav felt the tug again, and this time it came with a sense of unmistakable urgency. The voice, it seemed, was impatient to fulfill it&#39;s mysterious goal. Slav felt a pang of annoyance; he had not had a good night&#39;s sleep for a long time and was finally feeling weary of all the travel and searching that brought this point about; he quickly banished his disgruntled feelings with a vision of the reward waiting for him after the months of pain he had spent trying to find his goal, and he steeled his heart and took his first steps in the wasteland.

A significant difference in his surroundings was immediately felt. It was a slippery, intangible feeling he could not quite place his finger upon - indeed, he would have likely missed it had it not been for his alertness, waiting for a difference somewhere. He closed his eyes and concentrated on senses beyond vision and hearing, senses that even he did not yet fully understand - and there it was, right there infront of him, a flowing torrent of death energy that could be harnessed by people like him, those who had forsaken life. The life energy around him scampered away as it sensed a strange darkness in this soul, and Slav welcomed the change. Life energy was frivolous and it made him tend to forget about the worries of life - as if he needed another thing to worry about. He could not force it away in crowded places for fear of attracting unwanted attention to himself - he had noticed that he tended to operate much smoother outside the light where his influences grew weaker, unprotected by the veils of shadows he weaved around himself. The death energy had noticed the void of energy around Slav and hesitantly approaching him with caution born of the fear of life energy which had been, after all, caressing the young man few moments ago. Then suddenly it took over the fleeing life energy and surrounded Slav, who felt a invigorating rush replace his weariness and fatigue. With a much needed boost to his morale, Slav continued deeper in the wasteland.

The wasteland around Slav was a flat, unimaginative piece of land with dreary, boring landscapes and scenery and harsh weather conditions - all natural conditions, considering the power death had over the wasteland. It was broken only by the occasional forest which contained remains of the life energy death had failed to obliterate. The land was charcoal black all around him as though an awful fire had ravaged the land until there was no more to eat at. Few creatuers lived here - there was just not enough resources for maintaining more than the few that lived in the wasteland. Vultures soared overhead as Slav advanced deeper in the wasteland, and he came across a scattered pile of animal bones being picked at by scavenger birds too weak and frightened to attack a living organism head on. Soon enough, Slav felt a distinct unease. It seemed that even the very stars chose not to shine on such an unsightly location, leaving the wasteland looking very bleak indeed. It ate away at the very soul - it was almost as if he could hear death and see the horrors that had created this wasteland occurring once more before his very eyes. It was death on a much greater scale than he was used to, much greater than those deaths he had caused long ago...

After what felt like an extremely long time walking through the same scenery, Slav started noticing insubstantial changes with increasing frequency, things like a rusty iron sword or moldy remains of an ancient catapult surrounded by arrows littering the earth around it. He was very close to his goal, he could feel it&#39;s proximity - and so could the voice, it seemed, as the tug spurred him on faster and faster to his destination. Slav was impatient as well, to finally see the result of his investigation, his searching, his months spent sleeping on the rough terrain under the merciless sun and into the freezing night. The urge was a desperation now; if he did not reach his destination soon, he would collapse. He couldn&#39;t go on, not even with the amounts of death energy this place contained - and it contained an abundance of death energy indeed - it seemed an unremembered war had occurred here for unknown reasons leading to the creation of this wasteland. His body was failing him, and he broke into a sprint - he could not take it anymore, he had to reach the destination, had to get there soon -

Suddenly he could see an enormous crater that had to be at least half a kilometre diameter. He knew that this was his goal; the ever-present tug was pulling him that direction, the voice unrelenting in it&#39;s will to finally complete it&#39;s aim after the long months and years. Pausing only for a few moments to catch his breath, he continued on to the crater in a zombie-like trance. It was as if it had completely taken over his mind. He could think of nothing else than to see what was at the bottom of that crater - and the closer he got, the more he had a feeling it would be a terrible discovery unearthed. He could not stop now however, not after he had gotten this far. He felt the strength of death energy intensify and felt the strangest of disturbances in it. They were massing together infront of the crater, in a very strange way that he had failed to notice a while back. It seemed like an army formation, as if they were expecting an enemy and were readying themselves to attack something. Sudden realization hit Slav and he quickly threw a mental shield around his body - and not a moment too soon, for the energy had suddenly surged towards him with blazing speeds, barraging his shield with the power of death.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:56:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Fiction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I guess so, I’ll read over it tomorrow and think of something to do.<br>
Also yay for stupid names</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/6</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-417860-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860.rss">Fiction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fiction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chassy13 Chassy13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chassy13">@chassy13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I didn’t really read through the whole thing, but you can remove he from some sentences, because the reader will assume it’s happening to him anyway (implying that Slav is the only character). I’m at school right now so I don’t have time to read through it all. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-417860-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860.rss">Fiction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fiction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Just something I’m doing on my own.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="417860">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/jordiescape/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Jordiescape:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>he he he he he he he he he he he he SO MANY ‘HE’</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with you but I thought it was better than so many Slav’s. What do you suggest I do?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-417860-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860.rss">Fiction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fiction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ExtremeX-Scape Ryley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/extremex-scape">@ExtremeX-Scape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tl;dr<br>
Kidding, Look’s good.</p>
<p>Is this for school, or just something you feel like doing on your own?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 15:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-417860-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860.rss">Fiction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fiction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jordiescape Jordiescape]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jordiescape">@Jordiescape</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>he he he he he he he he he he he he SO MANY ‘HE’</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 15:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-417860-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860.rss">Fiction</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fiction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>EditL things I need to do:</p>
<ol>
<li>Expand on the wasteland description a bit more - it’s quite boring right now imo.</li>
<li>I don’t like the flow of “events” and sentences so I will probably be redoing it.</li>
</ol>
<p>First draft of some fiction I am writing.<br>
WARNING: massive tl;dr ahead, proceed with caution. You have been warned.<br>
[hr]</p>
<p>The clearing was stirring. Creatures and animals cried in harmony as they woke from their stupor, their cries piercing the night, echoing beyond the reaches of the giant forest trees. The lake surface was undisturbed except by the occasional breeze, sending ripple flowing across it.</p>
<p>A deer approached the lake timidly, ears alert for any sound of danger, for many rumours had been circulated about that lake. Creatures had been known to disappear when pausing for a drink and the animals had many wild theories explaining the phenomena, ranging from rogue gnomes to a sea monster that had made the lake it’s lair, emerging every few months to feast upon the unlucky beast that happened upon the lake at that night. The deer looked around inquisitively, then seemed to decide there was no imminent danger and trotted to the lake. It bent down and starting sipping water from it.</p>
<p>[center]***[/center]</p>
<p>Slav stared at the barren wasteland ahead of him. He purred with contentment. It was a strange feeling, being near so much death he could hear the echoes of long gone soldiers fighting for long lost causes, after being forced to live near throbbing streams of life energy. He took the time to siphon energy from the area; he was of the opinion that one could never have enough energy on his person, and this belief had saved his life multiple times.</p>
<p>Slav felt the tug again, and this time it came with a sense of unmistakable urgency. The voice, it seemed, was impatient to fulfill it’s mysterious goal. Slav felt a pang of annoyance; he had not had a good night’s sleep for a long time and was finally feeling weary of all the travel and searching that brought this point about; he quickly banished his disgruntled feelings with a vision of the reward waiting for him after the months of pain he had spent trying to find his goal, and he steeled his heart and took his first steps in the wasteland.</p>
<p>A significant difference in his surroundings was immediately felt. It was a slippery, intangible feeling he could not quite place his finger upon - indeed, he would have likely missed it had it not been for his alertness, waiting for a difference somewhere. He closed his eyes and concentrated on senses beyond vision and hearing, senses that even he did not yet fully understand - and there it was, right there infront of him, a flowing torrent of death energy that could be harnessed by people like him, those who had forsaken life. The life energy around him scampered away as it sensed a strange darkness in this soul, and Slav welcomed the change. Life energy was frivolous and it made him tend to forget about the worries of life - as if he needed another thing to worry about. He could not force it away in crowded places for fear of attracting unwanted attention to himself - he had noticed that he tended to operate much smoother outside the light where his influences grew weaker, unprotected by the veils of shadows he weaved around himself. The death energy had noticed the void of energy around Slav and hesitantly approaching him with caution born of the fear of life energy which had been, after all, caressing the young man few moments ago. Then suddenly it took over the fleeing life energy and surrounded Slav, who felt a invigorating rush replace his weariness and fatigue. With a much needed boost to his morale, Slav continued deeper in the wasteland.</p>
<p>The wasteland around Slav was a flat, unimaginative piece of land with dreary, boring landscapes and scenery and harsh weather conditions - all natural conditions, considering the power death had over the wasteland. It was broken only by the occasional forest which contained remains of the life energy death had failed to obliterate. The land was charcoal black all around him as though an awful fire had ravaged the land until there was no more to eat at. Few creatuers lived here - there was just not enough resources for maintaining more than the few that lived in the wasteland. Vultures soared overhead as Slav advanced deeper in the wasteland, and he came across a scattered pile of animal bones being picked at by scavenger birds too weak and frightened to attack a living organism head on. Soon enough, Slav felt a distinct unease. It seemed that even the very stars chose not to shine on such an unsightly location, leaving the wasteland looking very bleak indeed. It ate away at the very soul - it was almost as if he could hear death and see the horrors that had created this wasteland occurring once more before his very eyes. It was death on a much greater scale than he was used to, much greater than those deaths he had caused long ago…</p>
<p>After what felt like an extremely long time walking through the same scenery, Slav started noticing insubstantial changes with increasing frequency, things like a rusty iron sword or moldy remains of an ancient catapult surrounded by arrows littering the earth around it. He was very close to his goal, he could feel it’s proximity - and so could the voice, it seemed, as the tug spurred him on faster and faster to his destination. Slav was impatient as well, to finally see the result of his investigation, his searching, his months spent sleeping on the rough terrain under the merciless sun and into the freezing night. The urge was a desperation now; if he did not reach his destination soon, he would collapse. He couldn’t go on, not even with the amounts of death energy this place contained - and it contained an abundance of death energy indeed - it seemed an unremembered war had occurred here for unknown reasons leading to the creation of this wasteland. His body was failing him, and he broke into a sprint - he could not take it anymore, he had to reach the destination, had to get there soon -</p>
<p>Suddenly he could see an enormous crater that had to be at least half a kilometre diameter. He knew that this was his goal; the ever-present tug was pulling him that direction, the voice unrelenting in it’s will to finally complete it’s aim after the long months and years. Pausing only for a few moments to catch his breath, he continued on to the crater in a zombie-like trance. It was as if it had completely taken over his mind. He could think of nothing else than to see what was at the bottom of that crater - and the closer he got, the more he had a feeling it would be a terrible discovery unearthed. He could not stop now however, not after he had gotten this far. He felt the strength of death energy intensify and felt the strangest of disturbances in it. They were massing together infront of the crater, in a very strange way that he had failed to notice a while back. It seemed like an army formation, as if they were expecting an enemy and were readying themselves to attack something. Sudden realization hit Slav and he quickly threw a mental shield around his body - and not a moment too soon, for the energy had suddenly surged towards him with blazing speeds, barraging his shield with the power of death.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 15:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-417860-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/fiction/417860.rss">Fiction</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
