<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help. Read Please</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-read-please/383749</link>
    <description>I know this may sound crazy, but i need help getting my client to read server. You can Pm me for details or offer for help. Ok, so im trying to get somebody to help me with this. I will upload the client and server i done tried to change to become online but it still doesn&#39;t. I want online so it will give me motivation to keep on coding. I used to code back in the day as you can check my old posts, but it has been some years. When i used to code its when Czar was the bomb. SO yeah im kinda lost with them right now. I would pay some cash but i&#39;m a broke 17 year old just trying to make it somewhere in the Development community. If you could help though please respond.

EDIT:: 21 read, and no replies. ouch..</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 07:02:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-read-please/383749.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help. Read Please</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_d_d_s_xx xx d d s xx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_d_d_s_xx">@xx_d_d_s_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I know this may sound crazy, but i need help getting my client to read server. You can Pm me for details or offer for help. Ok, so im trying to get somebody to help me with this. I will upload the client and server i done tried to change to become online but it still doesn’t. I want online so it will give me motivation to keep on coding. I used to code back in the day as you can check my old posts, but it has been some years. When i used to code its when Czar was the bomb. SO yeah im kinda lost with them right now. I would pay some cash but i’m a broke 17 year old just trying to make it somewhere in the Development community. If you could help though please respond.</p>
<p>EDIT:: 21 read, and no replies. ouch…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-read-please/383749/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-read-please/383749/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 07:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-383749-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-read-please/383749.rss">Help. Read Please</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
