<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192</link>
    <description>[center][IMG]http://i438.photobucket.com/albums/qq110/Mason_013/psvsgimp.png[/img][/center]

[hr/]

[center][u]What do you like best?[/u][/center]

[hr/]

[center][img]http://30gms.com/images/uploads/new_ps_logo.jpg[/img][/center]
[center][url=https://www.photoshop.com/]Photoshop[/url][/center]
[center]A popular high-end image editor for the Macintosh and Windows from Adobe. The original Mac versions were the first to bring affordable image editing down to the personal computer level in the late 1980s. Since then, Photoshop has become the de facto standard in image editing. Although it contains a large variety of image editing features, one of Photoshop&#39;s most powerful capabilities is layers, which allows images to be rearranged under and over each other for placement. Photoshop is designed to read from and convert to a raft of graphics formats, but uses its own native format for layers (.PSD extension). See Photoshop plug-in and Photoshopped.

[b]Layers Are Often Essential[/b]

It would be extremely difficult to develop the CD-ROM jewel case cover below without layers. If only one layer were available, each and every image element would have to be aligned perfectly on top of the existing image. There would be no way to change the placement because each piece becomes merged into a single bitmapped image, replacing what was previously there. Without having all elements in view and being able to move them around in different ways, it would be virtually impossible to derive the most pleasing effect. See image editor.

[img]http://content.answers.com/main/content/img/CDE/_PSD1.GIF[/img]
 
[b]Photoshop Layers [/b] 

The image above is built in 23 layers plus a background layer, enabling the individual elements to be moved independently of the others. The layer window (below) shows the layers. The arrow is pointing to the view option (the &quot;eye&quot;) in the chip shadow layer. Clicking the eye toggles between making the layer invisible and bringing it back into view.[/center]
[center][img]http://content.answers.com/main/content/img/CDE/_PSD2.GIF[/img][/center]
[center][size=8pt]WikiAnswers[/size][/center]

[hr/]

[hr/]

[center][img]http://enticingthelight.files.wordpress.com/2009/04/gimp-logo1.jpg[/img][/center]
[center][url=http://www.gimp.org/]GIMP[/url]
[center]Tools used to manipulate images can be accessed via the toolbox, through menus and dialogue windows. They include filters and brushes, as well as transformation, selection, layer and masking tools.

Colour: GIMP has several ways of selecting colours including palettes, colour choosers and using an eyedropper tool to select a colour on the canvas. The built in colour choosers include RGB/HSV selector or scales, water-colour selector, CMYK (cyan, magenta, yellow, key(black)) selector and a colour-wheel selector. Colours can also be selected using hexadecimal colour codes as used in HTML colour selection. Indexed colour and RGB colour spaces are supported natively in GIMP, other colour spaces are supported using decomposition where each channel of the new colour space becomes a black and white image. CMYK, LAB and HSV (hue, saturation, value) are supported this way. Colour blending can be achieved using the blend tool, by applying a gradient to the surface of an image and using GIMPs colour modes. Gradients are also integrated into tools such as the brush tool, when the user paints this way the output colour slowly changes. There are a number of default gradients included with GIMP, a user can also create custom gradients with tools provided. 
Selections and paths: in GIMP there are several tools that can be used to create selections including a rectangular and circular selection tool, free select tool, and fuzzy select tool (also known as magic wand). More advanced selection tools include the select by colour tool for selecting contiguous regions of colour and the scissors select tool which creates selections semi-automatically between areas of highly contrasting colours. GIMP also supports a quick mask mode where a user can use a brush to paint the area of a selection, visibly this looks like a red coloured overlay being added or removed. The foreground select tool is an implementation of Simple Interactive Object Extraction (SIOX) a method used to perform the extraction of foreground elements, such as a person or a tree in focus. The Paths Tool allows a user to create vectors (also known as Bézier curves). Paths can be used to create complex selections around natural curves, paths can also be named, saved, and painted (or &quot;stroked&quot;) with brushes, patterns, or various line styles. 
Image editing: there are many tools that can be used for editing images in GIMP, the more common tools include a paint brush, pencil, airbrush, eraser and ink tools used to create new or blended pixels. Tools such as the bucket fill and blend tools are used to change large regions of space in an image and can be used to help blend images. GIMP also has a selection of smart tools, which are tools that use more complex mathematics to enable a user to do things that otherwise would be time consuming or impossible; these smart tools include the clone tool that copies pixels using a brush, the healing brush which copies pixels from an area and corrects the tone and colour where it is being used. The perspective clone tool works in a similar way to the clone tool previously mentioned but also allows a user to correct for distance changes. The blur and sharpen tool is a brush that blurs and sharpens. Finally the dodge and burn tool is a brush that makes target pixels lighter (dodges) or darker (burns).
A list of GIMP transform tools include the align tool, move, crop, rotate, scale, shear, perspective and flit tools. 
 
Animation showing three docked and tabbed dialogs: layers, channels, and paths.Layers, layer masks and channels: an image being edited in GIMP can consist of many layers sitting in a stack, The GIMP user manual suggests that &quot;A good way to visualize a GIMP image is as a stack of transparencies&quot; where in GIMP terminology each transparency is a layer. Each layer in an image is made up of several channels. In an RGB image there are normally 3 or 4 channels, each consisting of a red, green and blue channel. Colour sublayers look like slightly different grey images, but when put together they make a complete image. The fourth channel that may be part of a layer is the alpha channel (or layer mask), this channel measures opacity where a whole or part of an image can be completely visible, partially visible or invisible. 
Text layers can be created using the text tool, allowing a user to write on an image. Text layers can be transformed in several ways, such as converting it to a path or selection.

Automation, scripts and plug-ins: GIMP has approximately 150 standard effects and filters, including Drop Shadow, Blur, Motion blur and Noise.
GIMP operations can be automated with scripting languages. The Script-Fu is a Scheme based extension language implemented using TinyScheme, GIMP can also be scripted in Perl, Python (Python-fu), or Tcl. 
GIMP has support for several methods of sharpening and blurring images including the blur and sharpen tool. The unsharp mask tool is used to sharpen an image selectively - it only sharpens areas of an image that are sufficiently detailed. The unsharp mask tool is considered to give more targeted results for photographs than a normal sharpening filter. The Selective Gaussian Blur tool works in a similar way, except it blurs areas of an image with little detail.

GEGL: The Generic Graphics Library (GEGL) was first introduced as part of GIMP on the 2.6 release of GIMP. This initial introduction does not yet exploit all of the capabilities of GEGL; as of the 2.6 release GIMP can use GEGL to perform high bit depth colour operations, because of this less information is lost when performing colour operations. When fully integrated, GEGL will allow GIMP to have a higher colour bit depth and also a better non-destructive workflow. 
File formats: GIMP supports saving and loading a large number of different file formats, GIMP&#39;s native format XCF is designed to store an image including all features specific to GIMP such as layers, channels and vectors; XCF is named after the eXperimental Computing Facility where GIMP was authored. [/center]
[size=8pt]Wikipedia[/size]


[hr/]

[center][u]What do you like best?[/u][/center]

[hr/]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 08:46:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Some people would rather just buy it like i did <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 08:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n33bz0rpl0x `Aaron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n33bz0rpl0x">@n33bz0rpl0x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>People also use GIMP more because they don’t know how to torrent Photoshop.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 16:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@zyle1992 Zymus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zyle1992">@zyle1992</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>GIMP FTEW</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 06:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kihomura Kihomura]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kihomura">@kihomura</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Photoshop; don’t even mention it being hard to use, it’s not. You just don’t know how to use it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 05:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lin Lin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lin">@Lin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="2" data-topic="310192">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 B2300 T4nk:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Photoshop.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 03:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Reisyukaku Reisyukaku]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/reisyukaku">@Reisyukaku</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>photoshop is free… you just need to know how to get it free.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 03:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="20" data-topic="310192">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 B2300 T4nk:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Gimp is like solving a chinese test.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>which i aced :3</p>
<p>mmm and yh idk what to say for stability, my gimp crashes 9/10 times trying to change paint colors, creating a layer, or increasing/decreasing brush sizes… :s</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 21:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Reaper_X The Reaper X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_reaper_x">@The_Reaper_X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“cocoa, post:13, topic:310192”]Only because it’s free etc etc.[/quote]What’s the etcetera.</p>
<p>I agree though, GIMP. I don’t do much with graphics though, so most of the time I only need layers so <a href="http://Paint.NET">Paint.NET</a> is there for me. Mind you, I could really care a less how pretty my pictures are.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 21:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I actually thought more people would vote Photoshop</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 21:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@B2300_T4nk B2300 T4nk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b2300_t4nk">@B2300_T4nk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Gimp is like solving a chinese test.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 20:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the1337legend the1337legend]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the1337legend">@the1337legend</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Gimp b.c it has a cexi name :3</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@n33bz0rpl0x `Aaron]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n33bz0rpl0x">@n33bz0rpl0x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>On Windows i use Photoshop and on Linux i use GIMP.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 16:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Javafire Javafire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javafire">@Javafire</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>photoshop is both stable and more customizable than gimp if you know how to use it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 16:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fat_Cookies Fat Cookies]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fat_cookies">@Fat_Cookies</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I prefer photoshop since it is used practically everywhere, nobody actually pays for it and I have already familiarized myself with it. I must also add that there are an unimaginable amount of tuts and help on photoshop so you will never get stuck.</p>
<p>I do have GIMP on Arch however I hardly use it.<br>
inb4 moparisthebest goes on about GIMP, Linux and open source software etc etc etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 15:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@r0ckstar96 r0ckstar96]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r0ckstar96">@r0ckstar96</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Gimp ftw</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 12:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="12" data-topic="310192">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/primadude/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Primadude:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Gimp for Stability; PhotoShop for the best image creating. Photoshop always crashes on me, however Gimp is fine.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Mhm photoshop does crash alot to the point it just drives me up the wall… literally</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 12:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@cocoa cocoa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cocoa">@cocoa</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d say Gimp, and lemme answer for Moparisthebest as well, Gimp.</p>
<p>Only because it’s free etc etc.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 11:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@primadude Primadude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/primadude">@primadude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Gimp for Stability; PhotoShop for the best image creating. Photoshop always crashes on me, however Gimp is fine.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 11:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="10" data-topic="310192">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/treber/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> Treber:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I have a high recommendation for Photoshop consider its features and what its capable of. I know lots of people cannot afford Photoshop and all its extension packs and what not but if you we’re smart, you would just download it from a torrent site e.g. ThePirateBay.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>but alot of things photoshop can do so can GIMP. (somethings)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 07:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Treber Treber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/treber">@Treber</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have a high recommendation for Photoshop consider its features and what its capable of. I know lots of people cannot afford Photoshop and all its extension packs and what not but if you we’re smart, you would just download it from a torrent site e.g. ThePirateBay.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 07:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TabbyKiller TabbyKiller]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tabbykiller">@TabbyKiller</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mr Mopar, post:5, topic:310192”]There both good but…I like gimp better,<br>
its easier to use.[/quote]<br>
O contra. I find photoshop much easier and better to use</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 06:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@B2300_T4nk B2300 T4nk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b2300_t4nk">@B2300_T4nk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“IceTICKER, post:7, topic:310192”]Photoshop.[/quote] Wa?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 06:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@IceTICKER IceTICKER]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/iceticker">@IceTICKER</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Photoshop.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 05:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@B2300_T4nk B2300 T4nk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b2300_t4nk">@B2300_T4nk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Mr Mopar, post:5, topic:310192”]There both good but…I like gimp better,<br>
its easier to use.[/quote] I find Photoshop easy and GIMP hard :S</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 05:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Photoshop vs GIMP?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr_Mopar1 Mr Mopar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr_mopar1">@Mr_Mopar1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>There both good but…I like gimp better,<br>
its easier to use.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 05:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-310192-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/photoshop-vs-gimp/310192.rss">Photoshop vs GIMP?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
