<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Unable to connect</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve read many topics about this and can&#39;t seem to find the answer. So i guess this is my last option.

So the error is... I can&#39;t connect using my No-IP Address. Using 127.0.0.0 and 0.0.0.0 is perfectly fine but using my No-IP address doesn&#39;t work at all. So i tried opening my ports in my firewalls  and port forwarding (which was already done just redid it). Then i tried again but it didn&#39;t work. I tried renewing my No-IP address. Still didn&#39;t work. AFTER ALL THAT WORK I was able to accomplish one small thing. When the server is turned on my Runelocus status checker would say it&#39;s online!! I would a receive a connection my my status checker but for some reason I still couldn&#39;t connect. The client works fine. I tested it on other 508 servers (Mine is also 508). So I know it isn&#39;t my client. My firewalls are all allowing port 43594 and my router is open. I have no idea how to fix it. If ANY of you have any ideas please post.

There is also an error i get when i try to connect.

error_game_Js5connect

Many posts say that this error is caused because the server is offline. But MY server was online. I ran it AFTER I turned on the server. My status checker even confirms it&#39;s online so I&#39;m pretty sure it is online 100%. I ran my server before the no-ip worked before as well. Just for some reason yesterday it got busted.

So if anyone knows how to fix or may know how to fix PLEASE post.

Thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 18:12:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Unable to connect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vusta Vusta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vusta">@Vusta</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Awesome thanks. Got any idea how to fix this?[br][br][size=1]Posted on: August 11, 2009, 12:27:43 pm[/size][hr]I’ve added you and still no response? Okay… Also does anyone else know how to fix?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 18:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-294559-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559.rss">Unable to connect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Unable to connect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@CPUsquad CPUsquad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/cpusquad">@CPUsquad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>il help you out m8 just im me at <a href="mailto:izaaz1996@yahoo.com">izaaz1996@yahoo.com</a> or pm me at moparscape im online all day</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 18:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-294559-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559.rss">Unable to connect</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Unable to connect</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Vusta Vusta]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/vusta">@Vusta</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve read many topics about this and can’t seem to find the answer. So i guess this is my last option.</p>
<p>So the error is… I can’t connect using my No-IP Address. Using 127.0.0.0 and 0.0.0.0 is perfectly fine but using my No-IP address doesn’t work at all. So i tried opening my ports in my firewalls  and port forwarding (which was already done just redid it). Then i tried again but it didn’t work. I tried renewing my No-IP address. Still didn’t work. AFTER ALL THAT WORK I was able to accomplish one small thing. When the server is turned on my Runelocus status checker would say it’s online!! I would a receive a connection my my status checker but for some reason I still couldn’t connect. The client works fine. I tested it on other 508 servers (Mine is also 508). So I know it isn’t my client. My firewalls are all allowing port 43594 and my router is open. I have no idea how to fix it. If ANY of you have any ideas please post.</p>
<p>There is also an error i get when i try to connect.</p>
<p>error_game_Js5connect</p>
<p>Many posts say that this error is caused because the server is offline. But MY server was online. I ran it AFTER I turned on the server. My status checker even confirms it’s online so I’m pretty sure it is online 100%. I ran my server before the no-ip worked before as well. Just for some reason yesterday it got busted.</p>
<p>So if anyone knows how to fix or may know how to fix PLEASE post.</p>
<p>Thanks</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 18:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-294559-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/unable-to-connect/294559.rss">Unable to connect</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
