<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Source release</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545</link>
    <description>[quote=&quot;Stork, post:1, topic:173846&quot;]Stuff you can&#39;t do in this board:
1.   Make offensive posts. They&#39;ll be removed, and you could be moderated.
2.   Play the superiority game (to clarify, I&#39;m talking about &#39;My server is better than yours&#39;, &#39;You can&#39;t code&#39;, etc). This is an informative community, so posts should be helpful. Criticism is fine, just keep it constructive.
3.   Recruit server teams. If you want to get a team together for working on a project, that&#39;s great, but don&#39;t make threads about it here.
4.   Discuss: compile errors, basic java programming, compiling tools (i.e. ultimate batch compilers!). The first two can be fixed by visiting the Sun website and checking out the java tutorials, and the second can be fixed with apache ant ([url=http://ant.apache.org/]http://ant.apache.org/[/url])
5.   Post c&amp;p tutorials. This board is for development, not copy &amp; pasting.
6.   Discuss problems with particular servers, for example: &quot;Why can&#39;t I connect to google.com?&quot;, or &quot;Why doesn&#39;t Edge-PKz work?&quot;. These questions should be made on the thread where the server is advertised, if there is one.
7.   Make posts informing us how well your project is coming along. By that, I mean &quot;List of stuff nearly done! Fletching: 20%, Bank withdrawing: 80%&quot;, etc.
8.      Keep the drama out of this section.

These guidelines can and probably will be updated. Make sure you familiarize yourself with them.
Please also note that these are guidelines, not concrete rules, though straying from them will result in consequences, the severity of which is at the discretion of the moderation team.

Lothy EDIT: Please note that there is now a child board for all Runescape CLASSIC server advertisement topics. Post your server advertisements there from now on to avoid having action taken against your account.

[quote=Lothy]First off, this section is for Runescape Class server discussion only. Any Rs2 related threads will be locked and the author will receive a permanent mute. We do not show leniency when it comes to things like this.

Second of all, all RSC server advertisement must be posted [url=http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,119.0.html]here[/url]. If you choose to post it in the wrong section, we will take action against your account. 

It&#39;s that simple.[/quote][/quote]

Show me in the guide line rules where you cant post sources?


RSCshadow full src and www..

*

kinda rude and unfair topic gets edited and locked where no where does it state you cant release sources..

So what people on here have friends who are mods and they bitch and moan to them to get a topic closed? lets follow the forum rules shall we?

@Kihomura how them 8 subs on youtube treating ya?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 00:05:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Source release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kihomura Kihomura]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kihomura">@kihomura</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright, I’ve had enough of you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 00:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-351545-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545.rss">Source release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@5_1 5 1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/5_1">@5_1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Why ARE YOU SO STUPID???</p>
<p>All of those sources in that topic were ALL RELEASED BY THE OWNERS OF THE SERVERS</p>
<p>Jesus, Eric… I didn’t know you were this stupid.</p>
<p>Ban this kid already</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 23:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-351545-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545.rss">Source release</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Source release</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@king-pk king-pk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/king-pk">@king-pk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Stork, post:1, topic:173846”]Stuff you can’t do in this board:</p>
<ol>
<li>Make offensive posts. They’ll be removed, and you could be moderated.</li>
<li>Play the superiority game (to clarify, I’m talking about ‘My server is better than yours’, ‘You can’t code’, etc). This is an informative community, so posts should be helpful. Criticism is fine, just keep it constructive.</li>
<li>Recruit server teams. If you want to get a team together for working on a project, that’s great, but don’t make threads about it here.</li>
<li>Discuss: compile errors, basic java programming, compiling tools (i.e. ultimate batch compilers!). The first two can be fixed by visiting the Sun website and checking out the java tutorials, and the second can be fixed with apache ant (<a href="http://ant.apache.org/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://ant.apache.org/</a>)</li>
<li>Post c&amp;p tutorials. This board is for development, not copy &amp; pasting.</li>
<li>Discuss problems with particular servers, for example: “Why can’t I connect to <a href="http://google.com" rel="nofollow noopener">google.com</a>?”, or “Why doesn’t Edge-PKz work?”. These questions should be made on the thread where the server is advertised, if there is one.</li>
<li>Make posts informing us how well your project is coming along. By that, I mean “List of stuff nearly done! Fletching: 20%, Bank withdrawing: 80%”, etc.</li>
<li>
<pre><code> Keep the drama out of this section.
</code></pre>
</li>
</ol>
<p>These guidelines can and probably will be updated. Make sure you familiarize yourself with them.<br>
Please also note that these are guidelines, not concrete rules, though straying from them will result in consequences, the severity of which is at the discretion of the moderation team.</p>
<p>Lothy EDIT: Please note that there is now a child board for all Runescape CLASSIC server advertisement topics. Post your server advertisements there from now on to avoid having action taken against your account.</p>
<p>[quote=Lothy]First off, this section is for Runescape Class server discussion only. Any Rs2 related threads will be locked and the author will receive a permanent mute. We do not show leniency when it comes to things like this.</p>
<p>Second of all, all RSC server advertisement must be posted <a href="http://moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/board,119.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">here</a>. If you choose to post it in the wrong section, we will take action against your account.</p>
<p>It’s that simple.[/quote][/quote]</p>
<p>Show me in the guide line rules where you cant post sources?</p>
<p>RSCshadow full src and www…</p>
<ul>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
<p>kinda rude and unfair topic gets edited and locked where no where does it state you cant release sources…</p>
<p>So what people on here have friends who are mods and they bitch and moan to them to get a topic closed? lets follow the forum rules shall we?</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="/u/kihomura">@Kihomura</a> how them 8 subs on youtube treating ya?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 23:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-351545-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/source-release/351545.rss">Source release</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
