<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello, everyone. I request .. a lot of assistance</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hello-everyone-i-request-a-lot-of-assistance/502269</link>
    <description>Hello everyone,
I&#39;m here because of no particular reason. I&#39;m fairly new to the RuneScape Private Server scene and I&#39;ve been interested in working with it. I have very little programming experience, but I relatively know how they work. I have messed around with Java just a little, but I&#39;m probably not going to be able to code my own everything like some of you probably can.

As I&#39;m sure this post will piss someone off because I&#39;m acting like I want everyone to spoon-feed me these answers, but I&#39;ve been looking for hours and haven&#39;t found a decent server that I can modify without wanting to redo the entire thing.

I am more-or-less asking for a few tips for new wanna-be server owners, for someone that wishes to learn The Ways of the Brokedness of the Private Servers. I found them quite intriguing especially learning how flexible people have made their own.

Right, I&#39;m looking for some sort of base that is fairly-newb-friendly and is quite plain. I don&#39;t want this entire pre-made thing laying at my feet waiting for me to squish it, I need something with.. a couple of &quot;examples&quot; or whatever of how I may do this, because I have absolutely no idea how to have a decent customized server running after researching the majority of my day (8 or so hours).

Anyways, please leave any tips you may have for me or recommend me something to use (please don&#39;t do 317 .. I&#39;d rather something around the 5XX - 6XX revisions (suggestions only)). I&#39;m pretty bad at learning this, even the thousands of guides on this isn&#39;t helping me, since they&#39;re all about how to port forward! I want to be able to make a real server that is different from the rest, or at least something so I can say I&#39;m not being cheap and copying everything in the damn world.

Well, thanks.
- Lildirt</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 10:32:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hello-everyone-i-request-a-lot-of-assistance/502269.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hello, everyone. I request .. a lot of assistance</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Lildirt Lildirt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lildirt">@Lildirt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello everyone,<br>
I’m here because of no particular reason. I’m fairly new to the RuneScape Private Server scene and I’ve been interested in working with it. I have very little programming experience, but I relatively know how they work. I have messed around with Java just a little, but I’m probably not going to be able to code my own everything like some of you probably can.</p>
<p>As I’m sure this post will piss someone off because I’m acting like I want everyone to spoon-feed me these answers, but I’ve been looking for hours and haven’t found a decent server that I can modify without wanting to redo the entire thing.</p>
<p>I am more-or-less asking for a few tips for new wanna-be server owners, for someone that wishes to learn The Ways of the Brokedness of the Private Servers. I found them quite intriguing especially learning how flexible people have made their own.</p>
<p>Right, I’m looking for some sort of base that is fairly-newb-friendly and is quite plain. I don’t want this entire pre-made thing laying at my feet waiting for me to squish it, I need something with… a couple of “examples” or whatever of how I may do this, because I have absolutely no idea how to have a decent customized server running after researching the majority of my day (8 or so hours).</p>
<p>Anyways, please leave any tips you may have for me or recommend me something to use (please don’t do 317 … I’d rather something around the 5XX - 6XX revisions (suggestions only)). I’m pretty bad at learning this, even the thousands of guides on this isn’t helping me, since they’re all about how to port forward! I want to be able to make a real server that is different from the rest, or at least something so I can say I’m not being cheap and copying everything in the damn world.</p>
<p>Well, thanks.</p>
<ul>
<li>Lildirt</li>
</ul>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hello-everyone-i-request-a-lot-of-assistance/502269/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hello-everyone-i-request-a-lot-of-assistance/502269/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 10:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-502269-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/hello-everyone-i-request-a-lot-of-assistance/502269.rss">Hello, everyone. I request .. a lot of assistance</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
