<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reason 4</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reason-4/152211</link>
    <description>Anybody got their teeth into Reason 4 yet? Got it this evening, only had a quick play, but my first thoughts are &quot;omfg this is awesome&quot;.

I was a bit worried, because my PC was too slow to play a couple of the demo tracks, but I haven&#39;t had any problems with CPU usage yet, maybe some of the demo tracks are a bit on the instrument-heavy side?

Thor isn&#39;t quite what I expected it to be, but then I only understand half of it, need to do some reading up and have a longer fuck around with it before I can pass judgement too much. The stuff they added to the sequencer is useful, but my personal wow at the moment is the arpeggiator - the most boring part of the new release is seriously the most fun shit ever. I love love love how you can just randomly chuck in arps on the fly while recording/jamming just by holding multiple notes down, and then stop it when you want and carry on jamming, all without touching the mouse or computer keyboard.

Reason 4 ftw.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 06:09:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reason-4/152211.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Reason 4</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mopman Mopman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mopman">@Mopman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Anybody got their teeth into Reason 4 yet? Got it this evening, only had a quick play, but my first thoughts are “omfg this is awesome”.</p>
<p>I was a bit worried, because my PC was too slow to play a couple of the demo tracks, but I haven’t had any problems with CPU usage yet, maybe some of the demo tracks are a bit on the instrument-heavy side?</p>
<p>Thor isn’t quite what I expected it to be, but then I only understand half of it, need to do some reading up and have a longer fuck around with it before I can pass judgement too much. The stuff they added to the sequencer is useful, but my personal wow at the moment is the arpeggiator - the most boring part of the new release is seriously the most fun shit ever. I love love love how you can just randomly chuck in arps on the fly while recording/jamming just by holding multiple notes down, and then stop it when you want and carry on jamming, all without touching the mouse or computer keyboard.</p>
<p>Reason 4 ftw.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reason-4/152211/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reason-4/152211/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 06:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-152211-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/reason-4/152211.rss">Reason 4</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
