<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234</link>
    <description>http://vidyascape.no-ip.org/
http://www.upload.ee/files/4726571/vidyascape_launcher.jar.html 

What is /v/scape?
It is basically the most advanced and ACCURATE 2006 remake with 60 working quests, daily-weekly updates, 6 developers, xp rates are 2.25x ,  about 30 online players on weekdays, and much more on weekends.
But instead of just being a plain old 2006 server we have merged content with a later build, this allows us to use the better models Jagex provided at the time (Goblins, Unicorns,ect) aswell as some items that aren&#39;t acquirable on other 2006 servers, for example Elegant clothing.

What can I get if I donate?
We do not accept donations whatsoever, there are no donators or members benefits, no one should get an advantage for paying.

How frequent are updates?
If not daily they will probably come out a day after, our updates for bugs are frequent and we pay close attention for what the community has to say. 
But every weekend we have huge updates that add a huge amount of content such as quests or mini games

How big is the community at the moment?
Right now /v/ was only a small community peaking at 60-70 players, but we have decided that its time to advertise to get more people playing outside of 4chan.

Whats currently in the game?
Currently all items are in the game, we have 60 quests with more coming in the future, nearly all areas are accessible, Duel Arena, Barrows, nearly all skills perfectly implemented and much more.


How can I play?
Just simply download our .jar file from one of these mirrors and just run it and clicking &quot;Existing user&quot; and just type in any desired username and password and you should just jump into the game

List of features
-All skills perfectly implemented
-All npcs have their appropriate spawns
-An already thriving economy
-Infinite run 
-Barrows
-Removed chat filter
-commands such as ::yell (Global chat), ::hideyell, ::hidecolor, ::report, ::home (Lumbridge teleport)
-Duel Arena working perfectly with staking
-Daily updates
-Weekly content updates
-XP rate is x2.25
-Castle Wars and Pest control 
-Whole music system
-Much, much more, just give me some more time to think about it.

Why come here?
Besides rune2006, we are the only other ONLINE 2006 remake today.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 02:16:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Loading_please_wait1 Loading please wait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/loading_please_wait1">@Loading_please_wait1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[ul][quote=“atno1, post:7, topic:553234”]actually i agree the xp rate should be higher, however i am not the owner, nor the developers, nor the admin, im just advertising. you will have to talk to the developers on this issue[/quote]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">•Server advertisements must be posted by the server’s owner only. Do not create an advertisement thread if you do not own the server!</span></p>
<p>That was the rule, but that was posted in 2013 not sure if that is still the case or if they just didn’t update the rules since then. But just letting you know before you get an infraction or something from one of the forums moderators.</p>
<p>Here is the link to the page with all of the rules:<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1f0dc167bcf798bdbd70b03bf0fd1bc836e54e1a.png" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/default-apple-touch-icon.png" class="thumbnail onebox-avatar" width="144" height="144">

<h3><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/" target="_blank">moparisthebest.com</a></h3>

<p>programming, irc, cars</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>Or here are the list of rules in this spoiler:<br>
[spoiler]</p>
<p>This board is the place where you may post advertisements for your RuneScape private servers. Please make sure that you follow the below rules and guidelines so we can keep this board as clean as possible. If you see someone breaking the rules, please report it as soon as possible. Simply posting in the advertisement thread will not notify a moderator as quick as a report will.</p>
<p>Guidelines/Ideals:<br>
•Although providing some sort of media is not required, it will make your advertisement more appealing, and ultimately draw more players to your server.<br>
•If someone decides to host a server that has previously been released in the downloads section, it is not your job to point it out and make a fool of the poster. Everyone has their own tastes, and if they like what they’ve found then let them have their fun.<br>
•Criticism/server reviews are one of the first things potential players look out for when trying to find a server to play. If you see someone negatively criticizing your game, they are allowed to do so. The only time someone will be penalized is if they attempt to start an argument.<br>
•Simply because a poster has a low post count does not mean that they don’t have a quality server to offer. Don’t judge a book by its cover.<br>
Rules:<br>
•Server advertisements must be posted by the server’s owner only. Do not create an advertisement thread if you do not own the server!<br>
•You may have only ONE advertisement per server. This means that even if you posted the last one a year ago, you must still use the original. If you have changed the contents of your advertisement thread, you must still use that original advertisement. If you post multiple advertisements, and continue to do so after a moderator’s warning, you will be banned from posting in this section.<br>
•You are not allowed to bump your topic by removing and reposting a comment.<br>
•All advertisements in this section are for RS2 private servers. If you wish to advertise your RuneScape Classic server, please do so here.<br>
•You may advertise links without approval within in this board only. If you wish to reference your website anywhere else on this website (including your signature), please message a staff member to receive approval beforehand.<br>
•Failure to provide links within 1 hour of moderator warning will result in a thread lock until the original poster notifies the moderator and wishes to reopen the thread with links. This rule is in place to ensure that posters are here to accept criticism from other members, and that they are willing to be actual members of the site.<br>
•Selling of any sort of product/service is by no means permitted on this website. All sorts of sales are to be handles outside of this website. We are not responsible for anything exchanged outside of this site.<br>
•If a staff member notices that you are selling staff positions, your advertisement will be locked and you will not be permitted to create a new one until you stop selling ranks.<br>
•If any malicious activity (be it viruses, keyloggers, RATs, etc) is found to be related to your server in any way, your server will be banned from this website permanently.<br>
•Respect other people’s feelings when posting. If you find the need to post nonconstructive or otherwise disrespectful comments in someone’s thread, then it will be removed. If you are found to constantly post disrespectful, rude, or nonconstructive on people’s advertisements, you will be given an infraction. Continued infringement of this rule will ultimately result in a ban from posting in this section.<br>
•If you are found to be constantly starting arguments, continuously getting others to bump your topic, or getting friends to post more advertisements, all related topics/advertisements will be locked and you will not be permitted to create a new one.<br>
•By no means is any person permitted to remove their reply in a thread and repost it in order to bring the advertisement back to the first spot in the board. The reply will be removed each time by a moderator, and continued thread-bumping in such a manner will result in an infraction.<br>
•You may not provide links to your donation page through this website. We do not want to be responsible for any transactions that occur through your game. Feel free to provide donation links on your website, though.<br>
◦Exceptions to this rule:<br>
<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/black_medium_small_square.png?v=6" title=":black_medium_small_square:" class="emoji" alt=":black_medium_small_square:">You may say that your server accepts donations.<br>
<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/black_medium_small_square.png?v=6" title=":black_medium_small_square:" class="emoji" alt=":black_medium_small_square:">You may say that your server has an automated donating system.<br>
<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/black_medium_small_square.png?v=6" title=":black_medium_small_square:" class="emoji" alt=":black_medium_small_square:">You may explain what your server puts all donations towards.</p>
<p>The above rules and guidelines may be interpreted by a moderator as they see fit in order to properly enforce the rules of the website. Understand that this site’s Global Rules are also in effect here, along with every other board on this site. Failure to comply with these rules will result in action taken against your account. If you have any questions/concerns, please either post them in this topic or message a staff member.[/ul]<br>
[/spoiler]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 02:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553234-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234.rss">/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@atno1 atno1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/atno1">@atno1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>actually i agree the xp rate should be higher, however i am not the owner, nor the developers, nor the admin, im just advertising. you will have to talk to the developers on this issue</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 01:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553234-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234.rss">/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Bivins Bivins]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bivins">@Bivins</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="5" data-topic="553234">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/ykcud/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Ykcud:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I can not give you enough praise for your server not being pay to win but I have to agree that I feel xp rate is rather low. If your community agreed, would you raise the xp amount? Also so far, top notch remake! I can even change my the brightness.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I agree with this guy, server looks like it would be awesome, just the xp rate is like “Why not just play osrs”?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 01:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553234-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234.rss">/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ykcud Ykcud]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ykcud">@Ykcud</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can not give you enough praise for your server not being pay to win but I have to agree that I feel xp rate is rather low. If your community agreed, would you raise the xp amount? Also so far, top notch remake! I can even change my the brightness.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 00:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553234-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234.rss">/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@i_dd_s_k0_i i dd s k0 i]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_dd_s_k0_i">@i_dd_s_k0_i</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“atno1, post:3, topic:553234”]osrs was orignally a 2007 remake but with all the updates its now a completely different content that an actual remake.<br>
however we are an accurate remake of what rs was like a decade ago and there is no fee[/quote]<br>
I absolutely appreaciate your work, the server is playing amazignly (only 30 minutes into playing). Although I just had a conversation with player who just joined after me, he asked me if this is a remake, I said yes it is. And he said ‘cba going to start rs again’. I completely understand the clash of the xp rates issue - half of the players want challenge, and the other half doesn’t have time or patience for that and would appreciate something like 40x.<br>
Just saying my opinion based on all the discussions I’ve witnessed on remakes for the past few years.</p>
<p>(:<br>
Goodluck anyways!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 20:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553234-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234.rss">/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@atno1 atno1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/atno1">@atno1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>osrs was orignally a 2007 remake but with all the updates its now a completely different content that an actual remake.<br>
however we are an accurate remake of what rs was like a decade ago and there is no fee</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 20:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553234-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234.rss">/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@i_dd_s_k0_i i dd s k0 i]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/i_dd_s_k0_i">@i_dd_s_k0_i</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>60 Quests seem like a lot. Although not sure about the xp rates, it’s dangerously close to questioning ‘why not play osrs then?’. Anyways goodluck! Will try out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 19:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553234-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234.rss">/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@atno1 atno1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/atno1">@atno1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><a href="http://vidyascape.no-ip.org/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://vidyascape.no-ip.org/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.upload.ee/files/4726571/vidyascape_launcher.jar.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.upload.ee/files/4726571/vidyascape_launcher.jar.html</a></p>
<p>What is /v/scape?<br>
It is basically the most advanced and ACCURATE 2006 remake with 60 working quests, daily-weekly updates, 6 developers, xp rates are 2.25x ,  about 30 online players on weekdays, and much more on weekends.<br>
But instead of just being a plain old 2006 server we have merged content with a later build, this allows us to use the better models Jagex provided at the time (Goblins, Unicorns,ect) aswell as some items that aren’t acquirable on other 2006 servers, for example Elegant clothing.</p>
<p>What can I get if I donate?<br>
We do not accept donations whatsoever, there are no donators or members benefits, no one should get an advantage for paying.</p>
<p>How frequent are updates?<br>
If not daily they will probably come out a day after, our updates for bugs are frequent and we pay close attention for what the community has to say.<br>
But every weekend we have huge updates that add a huge amount of content such as quests or mini games</p>
<p>How big is the community at the moment?<br>
Right now /v/ was only a small community peaking at 60-70 players, but we have decided that its time to advertise to get more people playing outside of 4chan.</p>
<p>Whats currently in the game?<br>
Currently all items are in the game, we have 60 quests with more coming in the future, nearly all areas are accessible, Duel Arena, Barrows, nearly all skills perfectly implemented and much more.</p>
<p>How can I play?<br>
Just simply download our .jar file from one of these mirrors and just run it and clicking “Existing user” and just type in any desired username and password and you should just jump into the game</p>
<p>List of features<br>
-All skills perfectly implemented<br>
-All npcs have their appropriate spawns<br>
-An already thriving economy<br>
-Infinite run<br>
-Barrows<br>
-Removed chat filter<br>
-commands such as ::yell (Global chat), ::hideyell, ::hidecolor, ::report, ::home (Lumbridge teleport)<br>
-Duel Arena working perfectly with staking<br>
-Daily updates<br>
-Weekly content updates<br>
-XP rate is x2.25<br>
-Castle Wars and Pest control<br>
-Whole music system<br>
-Much, much more, just give me some more time to think about it.</p>
<p>Why come here?<br>
Besides rune2006, we are the only other ONLINE 2006 remake today.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 19:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-553234-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/v-scape-late-2006-runescape-remake/553234.rss">/v/scape late 2006 runescape remake</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
