<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cheat client</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cheat-client/406015</link>
    <description>So I logged off my server for about.... An hour... Two hours max. To find out when I logged on, and was at &#39;home&#39; on my server. I got there, and got attacked by all the shop NPC&#39;s and everything else. Everything had been moved and all that. And ontop of that, I know it was a cheat client. How can I block cheat clients. I know there is something, I tried looking for the tut for it, but it&#39;s not simple since mine is not PI, or Delta. :/ So I am trying to find out what I can do so that when someone tries to connect via cheat client, they can not connect to the server. :) Any help is greatly appreciated. :D</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:13:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cheat-client/406015.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cheat client</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Demon6994 Demon6994]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/demon6994">@Demon6994</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So I logged off my server for about… An hour… Two hours max. To find out when I logged on, and was at ‘home’ on my server. I got there, and got attacked by all the shop NPC’s and everything else. Everything had been moved and all that. And ontop of that, I know it was a cheat client. How can I block cheat clients. I know there is something, I tried looking for the tut for it, but it’s not simple since mine is not PI, or Delta. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> So I am trying to find out what I can do so that when someone tries to connect via cheat client, they can not connect to the server. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Any help is greatly appreciated. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cheat-client/406015/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cheat-client/406015/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-406015-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cheat-client/406015.rss">Cheat client</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
