<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Help With Blurr&#39;s client and more</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-blurrs-client-and-more/303774</link>
    <description>I would like to start with I have used the search button I repeat [b]I HAVE USED THE SEARCH BUTTON![/b] People seem to get B*****D at a bought not using that also i have used Google and have got no results. Also pardon my language! Anyways I am getting way off topic. Now I would like to know how to Get blurr&#39;s client? Every link i go to is broken or i get there and the link to download is broken *i have bad luck :P* Then i would like to know how to Edit it to have my servers name at the top of the client,How to make it so it goes to my servers ip address,How to add my forums under the tab,How to add cheat scripts *such as autos*,And how to add some more cursors and music,And last how to change the background on the log in screen oops i lied also how to change the whole fire thing the log in box and the Runescape swords saying Runescape. [b]THANKS!   [/b] Dang i lied again i also want to know how to use a server file with it? [b]YES I AM A NOOB![/b] And how to edit some stuff in there. So thanks for your help and please if i have done anything wrong or you used the search bar and found this info [b]SORRY![/b] I tried ! So hold in the anger and be positive ! :)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 22:29:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-blurrs-client-and-more/303774.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Help With Blurr&#39;s client and more</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@wicksy wicksy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/wicksy">@wicksy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I would like to start with I have used the search button I repeat <span class="bbcode-b">I HAVE USED THE SEARCH BUTTON!</span> People seem to get B*****D at a bought not using that also i have used Google and have got no results. Also pardon my language! Anyways I am getting way off topic. Now I would like to know how to Get blurr’s client? Every link i go to is broken or i get there and the link to download is broken <em>i have bad luck <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></em> Then i would like to know how to Edit it to have my servers name at the top of the client,How to make it so it goes to my servers ip address,How to add my forums under the tab,How to add cheat scripts <em>such as autos</em>,And how to add some more cursors and music,And last how to change the background on the log in screen oops i lied also how to change the whole fire thing the log in box and the Runescape swords saying Runescape. <span class="bbcode-b">THANKS!   </span> Dang i lied again i also want to know how to use a server file with it? <span class="bbcode-b">YES I AM A NOOB!</span> And how to edit some stuff in there. So thanks for your help and please if i have done anything wrong or you used the search bar and found this info <span class="bbcode-b">SORRY!</span> I tried ! So hold in the anger and be positive ! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-blurrs-client-and-more/303774/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-blurrs-client-and-more/303774/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 22:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-303774-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/help-with-blurrs-client-and-more/303774.rss">Help With Blurr&#39;s client and more</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
