<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[639] Dementhium Coordinate/NPC Grabber</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966</link>
    <description>Hello, before we go any further, I would like to say, [b]This is [u]NOT[/u] my work, i&#39;m only releasing it.[/b] Full credits go to Dementhium, creator of the Dementhium 639 Server (637 Loading 639). I had no participation in the development or creation of this tool.

Okay, recently I downloaded the 639 Eclipse Server, which had a variety of tools for the server. There was, a Shop Editor, a Drop Editor, there was even a Godwars NPC Grabber, and an Item Definition Editor. As I was looking through the files in more detail, I found a Coordinate Grabber. What I did, was created a small and simple Batch file (.bat) to load the directory of the coordinate grabber and to start the tool. 

Once it started, it worked successfully. So I practiced it even further. What this tool does, is it basically displays the surface of the [b]World Map[/b] of RuneScape 639. Wherever you hoover your mouse at, it displays the coordinates over that specific area wherever the mouse is at, making it MUCH easier to find coordinates. You can even spawn an NPC over a specific coordinate, making NPC Spawning made easy. The code for the Batchfile below:

[code]
@echo off
title World Map Editor
color A
&quot;C:/Program Files/Java/jre6/bin/java.exe&quot; -Xmx512m -cp bin;lib/* org.dementhium.tools.coordinategrabber.Main
pause
[/code]

Save that in a file, named [b]WorldMapEditor.bat[/b] in the same folder where [b]~ Run.bat[/b] is located. If you misplace this file, it may not work.

Okay, so let&#39;s get into further detail. This tool loads the 639 cache for the coordinates of the map. What it does, is instead of displaying the actual world map, it displays a picture of it instead, which makes no difference. Wherever you hoover your mouse at, a coordinate is displayed for that specific area. If you click anywhere on the map, a message below will also give you the coordinates of that specific area, and will ask you if you would like to spawn an NPC over that area. You can simply click yes, or no.

Thank you for reading my tutorial, even though this is NOT my work, i&#39;m still releasing it to the community. The reason I posted this into the tutorial section and not snippet section, is because I added more detail to the tool than was needed, so it basically is a complete tutorial of how to get going with the system of the tool and how it works.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 20:44:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[639] Dementhium Coordinate/NPC Grabber</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MelStone MelStone]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/melstone">@MelStone</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey well when i do create a spawn and successfully spawn npc, once i get on my client and log in and go to where i spawned in on this thing, it isn’t there. Do i need to compile? Does it even spawn then on the client so all can kill it and stuff?</p>
<p>Anyway thanks for the Tut</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 20:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-423966-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966.rss">[639] Dementhium Coordinate/NPC Grabber</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[639] Dementhium Coordinate/NPC Grabber</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fridder Fridder]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fridder">@Fridder</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You should also add the class in [ code ] tags.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 22:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-423966-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966.rss">[639] Dementhium Coordinate/NPC Grabber</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[639] Dementhium Coordinate/NPC Grabber</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@QuestMaster_2K10 QuestMaster 2K10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/questmaster_2k10">@QuestMaster_2K10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, before we go any further, I would like to say, <span class="bbcode-b">This is <span class="bbcode-u">NOT</span> my work, i’m only releasing it.</span> Full credits go to Dementhium, creator of the Dementhium 639 Server (637 Loading 639). I had no participation in the development or creation of this tool.</p>
<p>Okay, recently I downloaded the 639 Eclipse Server, which had a variety of tools for the server. There was, a Shop Editor, a Drop Editor, there was even a Godwars NPC Grabber, and an Item Definition Editor. As I was looking through the files in more detail, I found a Coordinate Grabber. What I did, was created a small and simple Batch file (.bat) to load the directory of the coordinate grabber and to start the tool.</p>
<p>Once it started, it worked successfully. So I practiced it even further. What this tool does, is it basically displays the surface of the <span class="bbcode-b">World Map</span> of RuneScape 639. Wherever you hoover your mouse at, it displays the coordinates over that specific area wherever the mouse is at, making it MUCH easier to find coordinates. You can even spawn an NPC over a specific coordinate, making NPC Spawning made easy. The code for the Batchfile below:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">@echo off
title World Map Editor
color A
"C:/Program Files/Java/jre6/bin/java.exe" -Xmx512m -cp bin;lib/* org.dementhium.tools.coordinategrabber.Main
pause</code></pre>
<p>Save that in a file, named <span class="bbcode-b">WorldMapEditor.bat</span> in the same folder where <span class="bbcode-b">~ Run.bat</span> is located. If you misplace this file, it may not work.</p>
<p>Okay, so let’s get into further detail. This tool loads the 639 cache for the coordinates of the map. What it does, is instead of displaying the actual world map, it displays a picture of it instead, which makes no difference. Wherever you hoover your mouse at, a coordinate is displayed for that specific area. If you click anywhere on the map, a message below will also give you the coordinates of that specific area, and will ask you if you would like to spawn an NPC over that area. You can simply click yes, or no.</p>
<p>Thank you for reading my tutorial, even though this is NOT my work, i’m still releasing it to the community. The reason I posted this into the tutorial section and not snippet section, is because I added more detail to the tool than was needed, so it basically is a complete tutorial of how to get going with the system of the tool and how it works.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 17:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-423966-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/639-dementhium-coordinate-npc-grabber/423966.rss">[639] Dementhium Coordinate/NPC Grabber</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
