<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[The New Classic] A Server Like You&#39;ve Never Seen It (Web Integration) [317]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479</link>
    <description>This is a new project that has been on-going for about two weeks now, and we&#39;ve maid some pretty good progress so far. Especially with a development team of only two people. Our plan is to introduce things that no one has ever seen on other private servers, or probably not even Runescape. We are planning (and will succeed) to make this server partly website integrated. If some of you know me from other sections around these forums, I&#39;ve done website development for quite some time by now. I picked up on Java pretty quickly, due to the fact I knew PHP, and some C#/C+. We are using a custom forums, and custom website, with a custom Wiki. All of which I&#39;ll be programming, if I haven&#39;t already. I&#39;m sure you don&#39;t want to read my blabber, so I&#39;ll present you with a table of contents and let you go on yourself.

[size=12pt][u][i]Table of Contents[/i][/u][/size]
[b]I. The Development Team
II. Base Source
III. Website Implementation
IV. Multiple Worlds
V. Current Progress[/b]

[size=12pt][b]I. The Development Team[/b][/size]
Though we have a small development team, of two, we have made great progress, due to the skills of the two of us. 

[u][i][b]Anthony/The Web Guy[/b][/i][/u] - I&#39;m the one writing this development thread to you, so hello. My current knowledge of a few subjects are: 
Website Development - HTML/CSS, Javascript, PHP, SQL, Ajax.
Other - Networking with servers (physical servers; not Runescape Private Servers), General Networking, Graphics (Using GIMP or Photoshop), Other Software/Hardware knowledge, which is good for user support, also 3D modeling/terrain texturing. 
Other Programming Languages - Some C#/C+, Ruby, Python, and DOS. 
I&#39;ve also done hacking for some time, but purely for the reason so that I would know how to prevent being hacked, and develop software and programs/scripts that aren&#39;t weak to common hacking methods. 

My main role in the development of this server is to work on the website, client, and managing the network infrastructure. However, I&#39;ll be working on the server periodically, from time to time.

[u][i][b]Dylan [/b][/i][/u]- This is the other person in the development team, let me also add that he is my brother, and we live in the same household, this allows for easy communication between the two owners. His primary role with the development is the Java programmer, he has re-written and created new systems and scripts for a few skills so far, and he has more to come!

[size=12pt][b]II. Base Source[/b][/size]
We downloaded a basic Delta cleaned source, with a blank client, so far we have added the new items, and optimized a few things, to help the server run smoother. This includes cleaning up code that will never be used, and rewriting some of the scripts that would put out a slow performance rate. For more information on our progress, check out some of the other sections of this development thread. 

[size=12pt][b]III. Website Implementation[/b][/size]
This is what will rule us, &#39;different&#39; than other servers, coming with new ideas that have never been used. We figured that, hey, we have a website, why use it just for forums and a webclient when you can do so much more. We&#39;ve projected this server to be large, very large (though every development team strives this) we, will hopefully, achieve this. With the large player base, getting moderator status or administrative rights, isn&#39;t just a walk in the park. We expect staff members to be dedicated, so we offer them a server control panel. It&#39;s nothing special, they log in with their forums account, and depending on their rights in-game, it will justify what resources they have access to. This control panel will also be made the fit just about any screen, and any device. Mobile, iPad/Tablets, Computers (of course), just about anything you can think of, giving the staff access from wherever they may be in the world. 

[b][i]Staff Panel Features:[/i][/b]
- 25 &#39;security&#39; cameras that are actually a virtualized user that displays a birds eye view, or the view from a corner. Three are placed in Edgeville, one on the bank, one in the wilderness, and one about mid-way. This is the only location with three, as it&#39;s the home area, and projected to be the most populated. Others are placed around the private server world, where we project users will be skilling, pking, trading, monster fighting, etc. These cameras will take a picture every 10-30 seconds, and they will be stored on the server, where they can be viewed from the staff panel by any staff member. The security cameras also display players username, and the chat of the users within 100 blocks away. We believe this feature will help ours and the moderators performance, and create a cleaner server, and prevent tons of problems (merely because users know they will be watched.)

[b]- [/b]The staff panel will also have sections to ban, kick, mute, and ip-ban, depending on your rights. As well as private message a user, with hidden identity, it will appear as [Staff] to the user and they will respond to [Staff], if abused, this right will be revoked from the staff member.

[b]-[/b] The staff panel also includes basic moderator or administrator features to make it so that a staff member doesn&#39;t have to be online to perform their job or tasks. It also displays players online, tick rate, average fps, chat logs, yell logs, command logs, teleportation logs, killing logs, drop logs, etc. 

[b][i]Forums In-game Stats and Whatnot:[/i][/b]
- When a user goes to another users forums profile, they will be presented with that users in-game stats, combat level, total level, and a few other pieces of information that can be viewed by the person. This option can be disabled by the user as well, as it may not be wanted. 

[b][i]Shopping/Player eBay:[/i][/b]
- We are planning to have a huge shopping system involved with my website, somewhat branching off my development that can be found [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,567986.msg4124692.html#msg4124692]HERE[/url]. Users will be able to sell their items for other items, GP, and possibly Vote Points (haven&#39;t decided). There will also be a donator shop and vote points shop on the site. 

[size=12pt][b]IV. Multiple Worlds[/b][/size]
- This is another new feature, some servers may have a few worlds, but what about five? This is just a base start for our worlds, we will add more as player base increases, or as players want them to be added. We will be allocating ports 4300-4400, dedicated to up to 100 worlds, if we would want. There will be of course worlds dedicated to various different things, skilling, pking, economy, etc. Though they all can be done on each, you&#39;re bound to find more skilling supplies for sale by players on the skilling world. And more people to kill on the pking worlds. However, your user account is automatically saved to the same SQL database, allowing you to have the same user account on every world you choose to go to. 

[size=12pt][b]V. Current Progress[/b][/size]

[size=10pt][b](Re-Coding Skills)[/b][/size]
Skills already done and working..
Attack, Strength, Defense, Range, Prayer, Magic, HP, Mining, Thieving, Farming, Woodcutting.

Skills in progress/almost completed..
Crafting, Fletching, Fishing, Cooking.

What wasn&#39;t listed, is obviously what needs to be done.

[size=10pt][b](Website Integration; Accurate, calculated percentages)[/b][/size]
Website Template - 98% (Website template wont be finished until website is finished.)
Custom Forums - 62% (I&#39;m creating my own forums from scratch, you can log in, post, reply, manage profile, etc.)
Custom Hiscores - 88% (The scripts are done and reading the user stats cleanly, just need to work on the design.)
Player eBay/shopping/auctioning - 20% (People can sell items through the set (checks inventory), haven&#39;t created in-game part.)
Donate Shop - 77% (Mostly done, just need to work on the in-game claiming system.)
Vote Shop - 70% (Items and prices planned out, scripts need to be changed some.)
Staff Panel - 10% (Security camera system and panel layout is mostly done.)
Security Camera System - 40% (Website sided is mostly done.)
User Profile Stats - 98% (Information is there, just need to make PHP scripts.)
Donation and Voting Systems - 20% (This is different than the shops for each.)

[size=10pt][b](Multiple Worlds)[/b][/size]
Saving to SQL - 80% (Saves most player info.)
Loading from SQL - 2% (Base methods added.)
Worlds are mostly planned out, undergoing coordination between worlds is being structured.

I will be adding pictures soon, of mostly the site, and some in-game features, hope you stick around to checkout our future updates, we may be needing help with this project, if we will, I&#39;ll post a thread in the Server Development Teams section, private message me if you think you would be helpful. Any feedback is welcome, that&#39;s what will structure a server, user feedback, whether it be good or bad.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 03:46:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[The New Classic] A Server Like You&#39;ve Never Seen It (Web Integration) [317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hotkid8200 hotkid8200]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hotkid8200">@hotkid8200</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Good luck Man.<br>
(from Yusuf)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 03:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-475479-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479.rss">[The New Classic] A Server Like You&#39;ve Never Seen It (Web Integration) [317]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[The New Classic] A Server Like You&#39;ve Never Seen It (Web Integration) [317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ciaran6889 ciaran6889]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ciaran6889">@ciaran6889</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Gl</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 18:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-475479-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479.rss">[The New Classic] A Server Like You&#39;ve Never Seen It (Web Integration) [317]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[The New Classic] A Server Like You&#39;ve Never Seen It (Web Integration) [317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@arham_4 arham 4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/arham_4">@arham_4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Gl man</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 18:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-475479-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479.rss">[The New Classic] A Server Like You&#39;ve Never Seen It (Web Integration) [317]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[The New Classic] A Server Like You&#39;ve Never Seen It (Web Integration) [317]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This is a new project that has been on-going for about two weeks now, and we’ve maid some pretty good progress so far. Especially with a development team of only two people. Our plan is to introduce things that no one has ever seen on other private servers, or probably not even Runescape. We are planning (and will succeed) to make this server partly website integrated. If some of you know me from other sections around these forums, I’ve done website development for quite some time by now. I picked up on Java pretty quickly, due to the fact I knew PHP, and some C#/C+. We are using a custom forums, and custom website, with a custom Wiki. All of which I’ll be programming, if I haven’t already. I’m sure you don’t want to read my blabber, so I’ll present you with a table of contents and let you go on yourself.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i">Table of Contents</span></span>[/size]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">I. The Development Team<br>
II. Base Source<br>
III. Website Implementation<br>
IV. Multiple Worlds<br>
V. Current Progress</span></p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">I. The Development Team</span>[/size]<br>
Though we have a small development team, of two, we have made great progress, due to the skills of the two of us.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Anthony/The Web Guy</span></span></span> - I’m the one writing this development thread to you, so hello. My current knowledge of a few subjects are:<br>
Website Development - HTML/CSS, Javascript, PHP, SQL, Ajax.<br>
Other - Networking with servers (physical servers; not Runescape Private Servers), General Networking, Graphics (Using GIMP or Photoshop), Other Software/Hardware knowledge, which is good for user support, also 3D modeling/terrain texturing.<br>
Other Programming Languages - Some C#/C+, Ruby, Python, and DOS.<br>
I’ve also done hacking for some time, but purely for the reason so that I would know how to prevent being hacked, and develop software and programs/scripts that aren’t weak to common hacking methods.</p>
<p>My main role in the development of this server is to work on the website, client, and managing the network infrastructure. However, I’ll be working on the server periodically, from time to time.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-i"><span class="bbcode-b">Dylan </span></span></span>- This is the other person in the development team, let me also add that he is my brother, and we live in the same household, this allows for easy communication between the two owners. His primary role with the development is the Java programmer, he has re-written and created new systems and scripts for a few skills so far, and he has more to come!</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">II. Base Source</span>[/size]<br>
We downloaded a basic Delta cleaned source, with a blank client, so far we have added the new items, and optimized a few things, to help the server run smoother. This includes cleaning up code that will never be used, and rewriting some of the scripts that would put out a slow performance rate. For more information on our progress, check out some of the other sections of this development thread.</p>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">III. Website Implementation</span>[/size]<br>
This is what will rule us, ‘different’ than other servers, coming with new ideas that have never been used. We figured that, hey, we have a website, why use it just for forums and a webclient when you can do so much more. We’ve projected this server to be large, very large (though every development team strives this) we, will hopefully, achieve this. With the large player base, getting moderator status or administrative rights, isn’t just a walk in the park. We expect staff members to be dedicated, so we offer them a server control panel. It’s nothing special, they log in with their forums account, and depending on their rights in-game, it will justify what resources they have access to. This control panel will also be made the fit just about any screen, and any device. Mobile, iPad/Tablets, Computers (of course), just about anything you can think of, giving the staff access from wherever they may be in the world.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Staff Panel Features:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li>25 ‘security’ cameras that are actually a virtualized user that displays a birds eye view, or the view from a corner. Three are placed in Edgeville, one on the bank, one in the wilderness, and one about mid-way. This is the only location with three, as it’s the home area, and projected to be the most populated. Others are placed around the private server world, where we project users will be skilling, pking, trading, monster fighting, etc. These cameras will take a picture every 10-30 seconds, and they will be stored on the server, where they can be viewed from the staff panel by any staff member. The security cameras also display players username, and the chat of the users within 100 blocks away. We believe this feature will help ours and the moderators performance, and create a cleaner server, and prevent tons of problems (merely because users know they will be watched.)</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">- </span>The staff panel will also have sections to ban, kick, mute, and ip-ban, depending on your rights. As well as private message a user, with hidden identity, it will appear as [Staff] to the user and they will respond to [Staff], if abused, this right will be revoked from the staff member.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">-</span> The staff panel also includes basic moderator or administrator features to make it so that a staff member doesn’t have to be online to perform their job or tasks. It also displays players online, tick rate, average fps, chat logs, yell logs, command logs, teleportation logs, killing logs, drop logs, etc.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Forums In-game Stats and Whatnot:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li>When a user goes to another users forums profile, they will be presented with that users in-game stats, combat level, total level, and a few other pieces of information that can be viewed by the person. This option can be disabled by the user as well, as it may not be wanted.</li>
</ul>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-i">Shopping/Player eBay:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li>We are planning to have a huge shopping system involved with my website, somewhat branching off my development that can be found <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,567986.msg4124692.html#msg4124692" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">HERE</a>. Users will be able to sell their items for other items, GP, and possibly Vote Points (haven’t decided). There will also be a donator shop and vote points shop on the site.</li>
</ul>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">IV. Multiple Worlds</span>[/size]</p>
<ul>
<li>This is another new feature, some servers may have a few worlds, but what about five? This is just a base start for our worlds, we will add more as player base increases, or as players want them to be added. We will be allocating ports 4300-4400, dedicated to up to 100 worlds, if we would want. There will be of course worlds dedicated to various different things, skilling, pking, economy, etc. Though they all can be done on each, you’re bound to find more skilling supplies for sale by players on the skilling world. And more people to kill on the pking worlds. However, your user account is automatically saved to the same SQL database, allowing you to have the same user account on every world you choose to go to.</li>
</ul>
<p>[size=12pt]<span class="bbcode-b">V. Current Progress</span>[/size]</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">(Re-Coding Skills)</span>[/size]<br>
Skills already done and working…<br>
Attack, Strength, Defense, Range, Prayer, Magic, HP, Mining, Thieving, Farming, Woodcutting.</p>
<p>Skills in progress/almost completed…<br>
Crafting, Fletching, Fishing, Cooking.</p>
<p>What wasn’t listed, is obviously what needs to be done.</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">(Website Integration; Accurate, calculated percentages)</span>[/size]<br>
Website Template - 98% (Website template wont be finished until website is finished.)<br>
Custom Forums - 62% (I’m creating my own forums from scratch, you can log in, post, reply, manage profile, etc.)<br>
Custom Hiscores - 88% (The scripts are done and reading the user stats cleanly, just need to work on the design.)<br>
Player eBay/shopping/auctioning - 20% (People can sell items through the set (checks inventory), haven’t created in-game part.)<br>
Donate Shop - 77% (Mostly done, just need to work on the in-game claiming system.)<br>
Vote Shop - 70% (Items and prices planned out, scripts need to be changed some.)<br>
Staff Panel - 10% (Security camera system and panel layout is mostly done.)<br>
Security Camera System - 40% (Website sided is mostly done.)<br>
User Profile Stats - 98% (Information is there, just need to make PHP scripts.)<br>
Donation and Voting Systems - 20% (This is different than the shops for each.)</p>
<p>[size=10pt]<span class="bbcode-b">(Multiple Worlds)</span>[/size]<br>
Saving to SQL - 80% (Saves most player info.)<br>
Loading from SQL - 2% (Base methods added.)<br>
Worlds are mostly planned out, undergoing coordination between worlds is being structured.</p>
<p>I will be adding pictures soon, of mostly the site, and some in-game features, hope you stick around to checkout our future updates, we may be needing help with this project, if we will, I’ll post a thread in the Server Development Teams section, private message me if you think you would be helpful. Any feedback is welcome, that’s what will structure a server, user feedback, whether it be good or bad.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 17:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-475479-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/the-new-classic-a-server-like-youve-never-seen-it-web-integration-317/475479.rss">[The New Classic] A Server Like You&#39;ve Never Seen It (Web Integration) [317]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
