<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586</link>
    <description>I figured I&#39;d recreate this popular topic because my and Aftermath_96&#39;s lil word fight got it locked...
Credit to Booduh for making the first one, and sorry we got it locked.

Yeh, I&#39;m an actual P Mod. Don&#39;t really care if some people think I&#39;m full of it.

I&#39;ll answer as many questions as I can, if anyone ever posts  :|</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 23:29:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bigtimekillr bigtimekillr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bigtimekillr">@bigtimekillr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“uncfan1119, post:88, topic:7586”]You need atleast 7 successful reports, + atleast 1 years of experience, and no black marks.[/quote]woot i only need 7 reports</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/100">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/100</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 23:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-100</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@NickMoran06 NickMoran06]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nickmoran06">@NickMoran06</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="5" data-topic="7586">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mod J:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Maybe you should have not broken the rules. Even if you did, you could have asked for another chance. But making up a story and calling him an “emo fag” won’t get it unbanned. Andrew wasn’t a dickhead, you were.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Very strong words from a “Mod” I might add.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/99</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 01:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-99</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@N00b1 N00b1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/n00b1">@N00b1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>dude can u upload a pick of the moderator center plx ;D</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/98</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2006 18:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-98</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rare_z Rare z]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rare_z">@Rare_z</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Mod J, i really doubt you’re a pmod. If you were you would careless to post a picture of the Report Abuse thing -.-… Show us some proof other than your good grammar &gt;.&gt;</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/97</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2006 07:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-97</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@footballplayar34 footballplayar34]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/footballplayar34">@footballplayar34</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>they can mute i got mute.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/96</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 00:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-96</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Actually, they can mute.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/95</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2006 23:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-95</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Blapmanjr Blapmanjr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blapmanjr">@Blapmanjr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Mod j is lieng guys player mods are like normal players they cannot do anything and they cant mute so hes lieng and p mods suck cock</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/94</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2006 21:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-94</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Erj Erj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/erj">@Erj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="13" data-topic="7586">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Mod J:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Either way I doubt we will ever be able to play RSC again.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Private severs pl0x?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/93</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2006 01:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-93</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@D27L7T D27L7T]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/d27l7t">@D27L7T</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I figured I’d post here to get this locked again.</p>
<p>~~Aftermath.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/92</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2006 00:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-92</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chrishead168 Chrishead168]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chrishead168">@chrishead168</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>boberick you so in deep trouble for spamming like that</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/91</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 23:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-91</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mr.Chris Mr.Chris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mr.chris">@Mr.Chris</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Don’t be a bender now boberick. If people over the internet can get you mad, GTFO, to be honest.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/90</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 19:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-90</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boberick boberick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boberick">@boberick</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <h2>retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards [br][size=1]Posted at: October 25, 2006, 09:24:08 AM[/size][hr]retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards [br][size=1]Posted at: October 25, 2006, 09:24:41 AM[/size][hr]<br>
retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retardsretards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards<br>
Posted at: October 25, 2006, 09:24:08 AM</h2>
<h2>retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retardsretards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards<br>
Posted at: October 25, 2006, 09:24:08 AM</h2>
<h2>retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retardsretards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards<br>
Posted at: October 25, 2006, 09:24:08 AM</h2>
<h2>retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retardsretards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards<br>
Posted at: October 25, 2006, 09:24:08 AM</h2>
<h2>retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards[br][size=1]Posted at: October 25, 2006, 09:28:00 AM[/size][hr]retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards<br>
retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retardsretards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards<br>
Posted at: October 25, 2006, 09:24:08 AM</h2>
<p>retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards retards</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/89</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 19:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-89</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@uncfan1119 uncfan1119]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uncfan1119">@uncfan1119</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You need atleast 7 successful reports, + atleast 1 years of experience, and no black marks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/88</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 18:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-88</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@whothe0 the fu superior]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/whothe0">@whothe0</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="11" data-topic="7586">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/fishygame/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Fishygame:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>[quote=Mod J]prevent scum like autoers</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>WTH! Why are you here?[/quote]</p>
<p>amen!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/87</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 08:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-87</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@admir107 admir107]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/admir107">@admir107</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>plzzz i was watching a vidio on youtube and he wrote something i and he got some cool stuff can u plz tell me were this website is that it will tell u all of the cheats i need for moparscape its boring having to kill some1 with my hands it is stupid i want to have fun can u plz find out. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/86</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 05:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-86</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boberick boberick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boberick">@boberick</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>all right…<br>
i will stop here before i ruin somebodys life…<br>
beleive me when i get mad, i go psyco, and you dont want to see that…<br>
unles you was in a diferent country…<br>
anyway ive got bigger fish to fry that stoping player mod wanabes.<br>
much bigger…[br][size=1]Posted at: September 14, 2006, 03:44:05 PM[/size][hr]i just read your post…<br>
FUCK YOU GOD DAMNED WANKER I HATE YOU! GO TO HELL YOU SON OF A BITCH I TOLD YOU I HAVE DISLEXIA AND DISPRAXIA AND HAVE BAD MOTERING SKILLS! I THINK YOU AND ALL THE OTHER CHAVS SHOULD GO TO HELL! YOU FUCKING MOTHER FUCKING DIPSHIT!<br>
GROW A DICK AND STOP SUCKING YOUR MUMS TITS CHAV!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/85</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2006 01:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-85</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original_Daniel Original Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original_daniel">@Original_Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>EATALOT2002… you should actually read the thread before posting you tard…</p>
<p>boberick was the one saying thehate isnt a mod not me, I couldn’t care less about who is a mod and who isn’t, and i wouldn’t waste my time looking up the names.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/84</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 09:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-84</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@EATALOT2002 EATALOT2002]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/eatalot2002">@EATALOT2002</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote author=PI55ED link=topic=10635.msg230088#msg230088 date=1157834519]<br>
Thehate is a player mod <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> </p><blockquote>thedude87<br>
thegame2002<br>
thegumbyone<br>
–&gt; thehate &lt;–<br>
thehumongus</blockquote><br>
or you can look here <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,16407.msg221511.html#msg221511" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">List from Phonnygoblin</a><br>
[[quote=“ThAt0n36Uy, post:82, topic:7586”]rofl! that is hilarious!!
<p>[quote author=Original Daniel link=topic=10635.msg226105#msg226105 date=1157719053]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>and if anybody had botherd 2 read my writing it has proof this nerd isnt a mod (“mod j”), because thehate is not a player mod, it took me ages to write this properly, stop making fun of me, thank you.<br>
i told u stfu moron!<br>
nobody can read…<br>
if u think he is a mod somehow and i am completely wrong please tell me your addres so i can hire sum1 2 kill u, dumbass.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You don’t have proof he isn’t a mod, every single player mod, does not know every single other player mod.<br>
Even if this guy isn’t a mod, doesnt give you the excuse to flame and ramble on about crap nobody cares about whilst not being able to put together a proper sentence.<br>
If you actually have a good argument then post it properly, and don’t use fuck in every sentence.</p>
<p>You spent ages doing that? Half of your words are spelt wrong and you have very poor gramma, if you took “ages” to write that up, why not take an extra 2 minutes to make it legible?</p>
<p>My address is 9-15 Buena Vista Drive Logan Village QLD Australia. Im waiting for the assassin so we can make jokes and laugh about how stupid you are over a drink.</p>
<p>Bitch.<br>
[/quote][/quote]/quote] Original Daniel…you should actually look at the list before posting you tard…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/83">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/83</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 06:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-83</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>rofl! that is hilarious!!</p>
<p>[quote=“Original Daniel, post:80, topic:7586”][quote author=boberick link=topic=10635.msg224137#msg224137 date=1157670153]<br>
and if anybody had botherd 2 read my writing it has proof this nerd isnt a mod (“mod j”), because thehate is not a player mod, it took me ages to write this properly, stop making fun of me, thank you.<br>
i told u stfu moron!<br>
nobody can read…<br>
if u think he is a mod somehow and i am completely wrong please tell me your addres so i can hire sum1 2 kill u, dumbass.<br>
[/quote]<br>
You don’t have proof he isn’t a mod, every single player mod, does not know every single other player mod.<br>
Even if this guy isn’t a mod, doesnt give you the excuse to flame and ramble on about crap nobody cares about whilst not being able to put together a proper sentence.<br>
If you actually have a good argument then post it properly, and don’t use fuck in every sentence.</p>
<p>You spent ages doing that? Half of your words are spelt wrong and you have very poor gramma, if you took “ages” to write that up, why not take an extra 2 minutes to make it legible?</p>
<p>My address is 9-15 Buena Vista Drive Logan Village QLD Australia. Im waiting for the assassin so we can make jokes and laugh about how stupid you are over a drink.</p>
<p>Bitch.[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/82</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 05:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-82</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PI55ED PI55ED]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pi55ed">@PI55ED</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Thehate is a player mod <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> </p><blockquote>thedude87<br>
thegame2002<br>
thegumbyone<br>
–&gt; thehate &lt;–<br>
thehumongus</blockquote><br>
or you can look here <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,16407.msg221511.html#msg221511" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">List from Phonnygoblin</a>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/81</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2006 20:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-81</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original_Daniel Original Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original_daniel">@Original_Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“boberick, post:78, topic:7586”]and if anybody had botherd 2 read my writing it has proof this nerd isnt a mod (“mod j”), because thehate is not a player mod, it took me ages to write this properly, stop making fun of me, thank you.<br>
i told u stfu moron!<br>
nobody can read…<br>
if u think he is a mod somehow and i am completely wrong please tell me your addres so i can hire sum1 2 kill u, dumbass.[/quote]<br>
You don’t have proof he isn’t a mod, every single player mod, does not know every single other player mod.<br>
Even if this guy isn’t a mod, doesnt give you the excuse to flame and ramble on about crap nobody cares about whilst not being able to put together a proper sentence.<br>
If you actually have a good argument then post it properly, and don’t use fuck in every sentence.</p>
<p>You spent ages doing that? Half of your words are spelt wrong and you have very poor gramma, if you took “ages” to write that up, why not take an extra 2 minutes to make it legible?</p>
<p>My address is 9-15 Buena Vista Drive Logan Village QLD Australia. Im waiting for the assassin so we can make jokes and laugh about how stupid you are over a drink.</p>
<p>Bitch.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/80</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2006 12:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-80</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ThAt0n36Uy Elijah]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/that0n36uy">@ThAt0n36Uy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>wow your the biggest idiot i have ever seen. Honestly, go hoer off some extra tonight who knows michael jackson might pay a visit</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/79</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2006 04:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-79</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boberick boberick]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boberick">@boberick</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>and if anybody had botherd 2 read my writing it has proof this nerd isnt a mod (“mod j”), because thehate is not a player mod, it took me ages to write this properly, stop making fun of me, thank you.<br>
i told u stfu moron!<br>
nobody can read…<br>
if u think he is a mod somehow and i am completely wrong please tell me your addres so i can hire sum1 2 kill u, dumbass.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/78</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 23:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-78</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Surajd Surajd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/surajd">@Surajd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lmao, nice one Daniel <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/77</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 14:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-77</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Original_Daniel Original Daniel]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/original_daniel">@Original_Daniel</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>boberick grow the fuck up, what are you, like 10?<br>
Someones cranky, go take your nap. And no more red cordial for you.</p>
<p>Come back when you’ve grown some pubes</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586/76</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 14:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-7586-76</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/got-more-p-mod-questions-ask-me/7586.rss">Got more P Mod questions? Ask me</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
