<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>A Good Safe For Your Computer</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-good-safe-for-your-computer/220668</link>
    <description>Some downloads are now containing viruses and trojans and more.  If the malware is in .exe form, then it will be detected if you scan it with one of these.  If it is not and the virus is written in the server, then the scanner will not detect it, so DO NOT rely on scanners.

http://oms.hitmanpro.nl/
http://www.virustotal.com/
http://virusscan.jotti.org/
http://housecall.trendmicro.com/
http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus
http://www.bitdefender.com/scan8/ie.html


If there is no .exe, it doesnt mean you are safe.  On your runserver.bat, right click it and press edit.  If it says anything .exe or &quot;del&quot; do not use the server.  Many people try to delete your hard drive or activate a virus by doing that.

Ways to prevent/fix viruses

If you are unfortunate and get a virus or trojan, Then download one of these.

free.grisoft.com
http://www.pctools.com/spyware-doctor-antivirus/?ref=google_av&amp;gclid=CPiVuJvxrYwCFSDrYAodfmtwOQ
http://macrovirus.com/?hop=jimmy777&amp;&amp;gid=1068739735&amp;oid=1296250392&amp;aid=
http://www.avast.com/eng/avast-virus-cleaner.html
http://www.geeksquad.com/tools/default.aspx


Thanks and stay safe.


Here is some information on what a virus is and what it does.


What is a virus?

A computer virus is a computer program that can copy itself and infect a computer without permission or knowledge of the user. The original may modify the copies or the copies may modify themselves, as occurs in a metamorphic virus. A virus can only spread from one computer to another when its host is taken to the uninfected computer, for instance by a user sending it over a network or carrying it on a removable medium such as a floppy disk, CD, USB drive or by the Internet. Additionally, viruses can spread to other computers by infecting files on a network file system or a file system that is accessed by another computer. Viruses are sometimes confused with computer worms and Trojan horses. A worm, however, can spread itself to other computers without needing to be transferred as part of a host. A Trojan horse is a file that appears harmless until executed. In contrast to viruses, Trojan horses do not insert their code into other computer files. Many personal computers are now connected to the Internet and to local-area networks, facilitating their spread. Today&#39;s viruses may also take advantage of network services such as the World Wide Web, e-mail, and file sharing systems to spread, blurring the line between viruses and worms. Furthermore, some sources use an alternative terminology in which a virus is any form of self-replicating malware.

The term comes from the term virus in biology. A computer virus reproduces by making (possibly modified) copies of itself in the computer&#39;s memory, storage, or over a network. This is similar to the way a biological virus works.

Some viruses are programmed to damage the computer by damaging programs, deleting files, or reformatting the hard disk. Others are not designed to do any damage, but simply replicate themselves and perhaps make their presence known by presenting text, video, or audio messages. Even these benign viruses can create problems for the computer user. They typically take up computer memory used by legitimate programs. As a result, they often cause erratic behavior and can result in system crashes. In addition, many viruses are bug-ridden, and these bugs may lead to system crashes and data loss.

There are many viruses operating in the general Internet today, and new ones are created and discovered every day.
What is spyware?

Spyware is computer software that is installed surreptitiously on a personal computer to intercept or take partial control over the user&#39;s interaction with the computer, without the user&#39;s informed consent.

While the term spyware suggests software that secretly monitors the user&#39;s behavior, the functions of spyware extend well beyond simple monitoring. Spyware programs can collect various types of personal information, but can also interfere with user control of the computer in other ways, such as installing additional software, redirecting Web browser activity, or diverting advertising revenue to a third party.

In response to the emergence of spyware, a small industry has sprung up dealing in anti-spyware software. Running anti-spyware software has become a widely recognized element of computer security best practices for Microsoft Windows desktop computers. A number of jurisdictions have passed anti-spyware laws, which usually target any software that is surreptitiously installed to control a user&#39;s computer.

Tool-bars can contain spyware:


What is a trojan?

In the context of computer software, a Trojan horse is a program that installs malicious software while under the guise of doing something else. A Trojan horse differs from a virus in that a Trojan horse does not insert its code into other computer files and appears harmless until executed. The term is derived from the classical myth of the Trojan Horse. Trojan horses may appear to be useful or interesting programs (or at the very least harmless) to an unsuspecting user, but are actually harmful when executed. (See Social engineering.)

Often the term is shortened to simply Trojan.

There are two common types of Trojan horses. One is ordinary software that has been corrupted by a hacker. A cracker inserts malicious code into the program that executes while the program is used. Examples include various implementations of weather alerting programs, computer clock setting software, and peer-to-peer file sharing utilities. The other type of Trojan is a standalone program that masquerades as something else, like a game or image file, in order to trick the user into running the program.

Trojan horse programs cannot operate autonomously, in contrast to some other types of malware, like viruses or worms. Just as the Greeks needed the Trojans to bring the horse inside for their plan to work, Trojan horse programs depend on actions by the intended victims. As such, if Trojans replicate and distribute themselves, each new victim must run the Trojan. Therefore their virulence is of a different nature, depending on successful implementation of social engineering concepts rather than flaws in a computer system&#39;s security design or configuration.

In the field of computer architecture, &#39;Trojan Horse&#39; can also refer to security loopholes that allow Kernel Code to access anything for which it is not authorized.


Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 12:31:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-good-safe-for-your-computer/220668.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>A Good Safe For Your Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@agent_nukks agent nukks]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/agent_nukks">@agent_nukks</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice post, thanks.<br>
People really need to watch out now-a-days.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-good-safe-for-your-computer/220668/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-good-safe-for-your-computer/220668/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 12:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-220668-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-good-safe-for-your-computer/220668.rss">A Good Safe For Your Computer</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A Good Safe For Your Computer</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@godswordman godswordman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/godswordman">@godswordman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Some downloads are now containing viruses and trojans and more.  If the malware is in .exe form, then it will be detected if you scan it with one of these.  If it is not and the virus is written in the server, then the scanner will not detect it, so DO NOT rely on scanners.</p>
<p><a href="http://oms.hitmanpro.nl/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://oms.hitmanpro.nl/</a><br>
<a href="http://www.virustotal.com/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.virustotal.com/</a><br>
<a href="http://virusscan.jotti.org/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://virusscan.jotti.org/</a><br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://www.trendmicro.com/content/dam/trendmicro/favicon.ico" class="site-icon" width="16" height="16">
      <a href="https://www.trendmicro.com/de_de/forHome/products/housecall.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">www.trendmicro.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    

<h3><a href="https://www.trendmicro.com/de_de/forHome/products/housecall.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">HouseCall</a></h3>

<p>Lassen Sie nicht zu, dass Ihr System infiziert wird. Entdecken und entfernen Sie Malware, Würmer, Spyware und andere bösartige Bedrohungen kostenlos. Starten Sie Ihren kostenlosen Scan – es ist ganz einfach.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<a href="http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.kaspersky.com/scanforvirus</a><br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://download.bitdefender.com/resources/images/favicon/favicon-196x196.png" class="site-icon" width="196" height="196">
      <a href="https://www.bitdefender.com/toolbox/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">bitdefender.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    

<h3><a href="https://www.bitdefender.com/toolbox/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bitdefender Toolbox - Essential Free Online Antivirus Tools</a></h3>

<p>Stay safe from all e-threats: check out the Bitdefender Toolbox loaded with free online antivirus tools and apps for desktop &amp; mobile devices.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
</p>
<p>If there is no .exe, it doesnt mean you are safe.  On your runserver.bat, right click it and press edit.  If it says anything .exe or “del” do not use the server.  Many people try to delete your hard drive or activate a virus by doing that.</p>
<p>Ways to prevent/fix viruses</p>
<p>If you are unfortunate and get a virus or trojan, Then download one of these.</p>
<p><aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://static2.avg.com/1000912/web/i/favicons/favicon.ico" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://www.avg.com/en-ww/homepage" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">AVG.com</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    

<h3><a href="https://www.avg.com/en-ww/homepage" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">AVG 2019 | FREE Antivirus &amp; TuneUp for PC, Mac, Android</a></h3>

<p>Download FREE antivirus and malware protection. Tune up your PC, Mac and Android devices for peak performance. Surf safely and privately, wherever you are.</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<a href="http://www.pctools.com/spyware-doctor-antivirus/?ref=google_av&amp;gclid=CPiVuJvxrYwCFSDrYAodfmtwOQ" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.pctools.com/spyware-doctor-antivirus/?ref=google_av&amp;gclid=CPiVuJvxrYwCFSDrYAodfmtwOQ</a><br>
<a href="http://macrovirus.com/?hop=jimmy777&amp;&amp;gid=1068739735&amp;oid=1296250392&amp;aid=" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://macrovirus.com/?hop=jimmy777&amp;&amp;gid=1068739735&amp;oid=1296250392&amp;aid=</a><br>
<a href="http://www.avast.com/eng/avast-virus-cleaner.html" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.avast.com/eng/avast-virus-cleaner.html</a><br>
<a href="http://www.geeksquad.com/tools/default.aspx" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.geeksquad.com/tools/default.aspx</a></p>
<p>Thanks and stay safe.</p>
<p>Here is some information on what a virus is and what it does.</p>
<p>What is a virus?</p>
<p>A computer virus is a computer program that can copy itself and infect a computer without permission or knowledge of the user. The original may modify the copies or the copies may modify themselves, as occurs in a metamorphic virus. A virus can only spread from one computer to another when its host is taken to the uninfected computer, for instance by a user sending it over a network or carrying it on a removable medium such as a floppy disk, CD, USB drive or by the Internet. Additionally, viruses can spread to other computers by infecting files on a network file system or a file system that is accessed by another computer. Viruses are sometimes confused with computer worms and Trojan horses. A worm, however, can spread itself to other computers without needing to be transferred as part of a host. A Trojan horse is a file that appears harmless until executed. In contrast to viruses, Trojan horses do not insert their code into other computer files. Many personal computers are now connected to the Internet and to local-area networks, facilitating their spread. Today’s viruses may also take advantage of network services such as the World Wide Web, e-mail, and file sharing systems to spread, blurring the line between viruses and worms. Furthermore, some sources use an alternative terminology in which a virus is any form of self-replicating malware.</p>
<p>The term comes from the term virus in biology. A computer virus reproduces by making (possibly modified) copies of itself in the computer’s memory, storage, or over a network. This is similar to the way a biological virus works.</p>
<p>Some viruses are programmed to damage the computer by damaging programs, deleting files, or reformatting the hard disk. Others are not designed to do any damage, but simply replicate themselves and perhaps make their presence known by presenting text, video, or audio messages. Even these benign viruses can create problems for the computer user. They typically take up computer memory used by legitimate programs. As a result, they often cause erratic behavior and can result in system crashes. In addition, many viruses are bug-ridden, and these bugs may lead to system crashes and data loss.</p>
<p>There are many viruses operating in the general Internet today, and new ones are created and discovered every day.<br>
What is spyware?</p>
<p>Spyware is computer software that is installed surreptitiously on a personal computer to intercept or take partial control over the user’s interaction with the computer, without the user’s informed consent.</p>
<p>While the term spyware suggests software that secretly monitors the user’s behavior, the functions of spyware extend well beyond simple monitoring. Spyware programs can collect various types of personal information, but can also interfere with user control of the computer in other ways, such as installing additional software, redirecting Web browser activity, or diverting advertising revenue to a third party.</p>
<p>In response to the emergence of spyware, a small industry has sprung up dealing in anti-spyware software. Running anti-spyware software has become a widely recognized element of computer security best practices for Microsoft Windows desktop computers. A number of jurisdictions have passed anti-spyware laws, which usually target any software that is surreptitiously installed to control a user’s computer.</p>
<p>Tool-bars can contain spyware:</p>
<p>What is a trojan?</p>
<p>In the context of computer software, a Trojan horse is a program that installs malicious software while under the guise of doing something else. A Trojan horse differs from a virus in that a Trojan horse does not insert its code into other computer files and appears harmless until executed. The term is derived from the classical myth of the Trojan Horse. Trojan horses may appear to be useful or interesting programs (or at the very least harmless) to an unsuspecting user, but are actually harmful when executed. (See Social engineering.)</p>
<p>Often the term is shortened to simply Trojan.</p>
<p>There are two common types of Trojan horses. One is ordinary software that has been corrupted by a hacker. A cracker inserts malicious code into the program that executes while the program is used. Examples include various implementations of weather alerting programs, computer clock setting software, and peer-to-peer file sharing utilities. The other type of Trojan is a standalone program that masquerades as something else, like a game or image file, in order to trick the user into running the program.</p>
<p>Trojan horse programs cannot operate autonomously, in contrast to some other types of malware, like viruses or worms. Just as the Greeks needed the Trojans to bring the horse inside for their plan to work, Trojan horse programs depend on actions by the intended victims. As such, if Trojans replicate and distribute themselves, each new victim must run the Trojan. Therefore their virulence is of a different nature, depending on successful implementation of social engineering concepts rather than flaws in a computer system’s security design or configuration.</p>
<p>In the field of computer architecture, ‘Trojan Horse’ can also refer to security loopholes that allow Kernel Code to access anything for which it is not authorized.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-good-safe-for-your-computer/220668/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-good-safe-for-your-computer/220668/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 12:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-220668-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/a-good-safe-for-your-computer/220668.rss">A Good Safe For Your Computer</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
