<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Some ideas</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546</link>
    <description>Here&#39;s some ideas I was planning to use in a game I was planning to make (mainly features wise)

Project wise, have goals to aim for, otherwise nothing will get done. (Note that nothing is likely to get done anyways, but if we have same actual goals, we won&#39;t waste time doing absolutely nothing)

When fighting NPCs, if you die the NPC will retain some of your items (rest are dropped onto the floor.) The next time this NPC is killed, it will drop the items it picked up, and whoever killed it gets your items.

Have a &quot;test/debug&quot; mode, where stat, inventory, position changing commands are available, and characters aren&#39;t saved. Also, only allowed IPs can access the server at these times.

Have an actual economy - I can&#39;t handle playing a game with a shit economy :|

Make training faster then real RS, but not ridiculously fast, ie, you can&#39;t get flat 99&#39;s in &lt; 1 day...

No commands etc, available to regular players, and only limited commands available to mods/admins, and only in &quot;test/debug mode&quot;.

Have a reusable inventory object that can be used for shops, banks and the players inventory.

Shops only have a limited amount of money, so cannot buy endless amounts of items (keeping the economy from going over the top), and make more money by merchanting the items they buy/sell. (If they can&#39;t sell the items after a certain amount of time, they can store them or something and get them on special request maybe?)

NPCs have an actual attack, strength, defense etc, level which varies from NPC to NPC.

Scriptable, so that once the core is done, it needn&#39;t be touched.

Also, ground and inventory items use a reference Item object which gets modified.

The HP level is not necessarily the HP value, ie, 99 HP could mean you have 15000 or so HP. Also, hits become much higher to accommodate for this, making the game much more exciting/fast paced etc.

When I remember everything else, I&#39;ll add it to this post.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 04:55:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Some ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 04:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257546-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546.rss">Some ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xEnt xEnt]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xent">@xEnt</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I like the HP thing, lets say HP * 10 = Health.  55HP = 550Health. Obviously every other damage factor would need to be * 10, but this gives room for a more unique number hits.</p>
<p>Lets say i attack Jorsa and my max hit could be 16, giving 16 different unique numbers a chance to hit, whilst if we increase everything 10* that gives the max hit 160, having 160 unique numbers to use.</p>
<p>Might be a stupid suggestion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 02:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257546-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546.rss">Some ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The goal of this project is to emulate actual Runescape to at least a reasonable extent. That said, I see that a few of your ideas are geared at minimising staff corruption - something that seems to be a large problem for many servers.</p>
<p>As far as stopping staff corruption, I’ve always planned on doing what Jagex did - simply disallow any trading/fighting with administrators.<br>
If they want to PVP then they can have a secondary account and maybe give it player moderator status (which would have the ability to mute someone where necessary, but nothing else).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 00:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257546-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546.rss">Some ideas</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Some ideas</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_Vengeance _Vengeance]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_vengeance">@_Vengeance</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Here’s some ideas I was planning to use in a game I was planning to make (mainly features wise)</p>
<p>Project wise, have goals to aim for, otherwise nothing will get done. (Note that nothing is likely to get done anyways, but if we have same actual goals, we won’t waste time doing absolutely nothing)</p>
<p>When fighting NPCs, if you die the NPC will retain some of your items (rest are dropped onto the floor.) The next time this NPC is killed, it will drop the items it picked up, and whoever killed it gets your items.</p>
<p>Have a “test/debug” mode, where stat, inventory, position changing commands are available, and characters aren’t saved. Also, only allowed IPs can access the server at these times.</p>
<p>Have an actual economy - I can’t handle playing a game with a shit economy <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=6" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"></p>
<p>Make training faster then real RS, but not ridiculously fast, ie, you can’t get flat 99’s in &lt; 1 day…</p>
<p>No commands etc, available to regular players, and only limited commands available to mods/admins, and only in “test/debug mode”.</p>
<p>Have a reusable inventory object that can be used for shops, banks and the players inventory.</p>
<p>Shops only have a limited amount of money, so cannot buy endless amounts of items (keeping the economy from going over the top), and make more money by merchanting the items they buy/sell. (If they can’t sell the items after a certain amount of time, they can store them or something and get them on special request maybe?)</p>
<p>NPCs have an actual attack, strength, defense etc, level which varies from NPC to NPC.</p>
<p>Scriptable, so that once the core is done, it needn’t be touched.</p>
<p>Also, ground and inventory items use a reference Item object which gets modified.</p>
<p>The HP level is not necessarily the HP value, ie, 99 HP could mean you have 15000 or so HP. Also, hits become much higher to accommodate for this, making the game much more exciting/fast paced etc.</p>
<p>When I remember everything else, I’ll add it to this post.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 13:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-257546-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/some-ideas/257546.rss">Some ideas</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
