<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New minecraft pvp server</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-minecraft-pvp-server/456111</link>
    <description>Ip: [b]mc.factionpvp.com[/b]


FactionPvP is a brand new server based fully around a fun and enjoyable PvP experience for all players. Currently run by padda363, the server is constantly changing and updating to make the server better for its players, with numerous helpful mods and admins that are happy to help and have a bit of fun. Have fun and stay a while! 

To make the server more enjoyable for its players, the server has various plugins, some of these are:

- Factions: Whats a PvP server without the ability to raid?. Useless right? Well Factions allows for fun and competitive game-play in which groups of friends can team up, build a base and fight against the other factions that roam the land.

- MobArena: Feeling bored of just building your base? No factions nearby to raid? Well don&#39;t worry, MobArena is a fun plugin that allows the players to fight against various waves of mobs for xp &amp; prizes.

- Spleef: If MobArena isn&#39;t enough for you or not something you like, then how about Spleef? Spleef is the classic game of destroying blocks from underneath your opponents causing them to fall to their death! Oh what fun. 

- Mcmmo: Like RPG type gameplay? Mcmmo allows just that. You can level up various skills like swords, mining and even fishing! Each skill comes with its own special effects like bleeding on hits or finding diamonds in soil!

- NoCheat: Keep hackers at bay with NoCheat. Our admins and OP&#39;s will be informed whenever a player is doing something suspicious!

- Essentials: Exactly what it says on the box folks, all the essential plugins for a MC server like /sethome or /tpa

- Votify: Currently being implemented, but you will receive items!


If this seems like the right server for you then come on over, we are accepting all new players! 
If you would like to donate, please visit us on our website for more information.

NOTE: Rules are clearly displayed on the server!
Additional Details
Currently a small, factions PvP server with plenty of great plugins with a hope of becoming one of the most favored and enjoyable servers. Join us now!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 09:32:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Minecraft</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-minecraft-pvp-server/456111.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New minecraft pvp server</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@factionpvp factionpvp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/factionpvp">@factionpvp</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Ip: <span class="bbcode-b"><a href="http://mc.factionpvp.com" rel="nofollow noopener">mc.factionpvp.com</a></span></p>
<p>FactionPvP is a brand new server based fully around a fun and enjoyable PvP experience for all players. Currently run by padda363, the server is constantly changing and updating to make the server better for its players, with numerous helpful mods and admins that are happy to help and have a bit of fun. Have fun and stay a while!</p>
<p>To make the server more enjoyable for its players, the server has various plugins, some of these are:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Factions: Whats a PvP server without the ability to raid?. Useless right? Well Factions allows for fun and competitive game-play in which groups of friends can team up, build a base and fight against the other factions that roam the land.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>MobArena: Feeling bored of just building your base? No factions nearby to raid? Well don’t worry, MobArena is a fun plugin that allows the players to fight against various waves of mobs for xp &amp; prizes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Spleef: If MobArena isn’t enough for you or not something you like, then how about Spleef? Spleef is the classic game of destroying blocks from underneath your opponents causing them to fall to their death! Oh what fun.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Mcmmo: Like RPG type gameplay? Mcmmo allows just that. You can level up various skills like swords, mining and even fishing! Each skill comes with its own special effects like bleeding on hits or finding diamonds in soil!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>NoCheat: Keep hackers at bay with NoCheat. Our admins and OP’s will be informed whenever a player is doing something suspicious!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Essentials: Exactly what it says on the box folks, all the essential plugins for a MC server like /sethome or /tpa</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Votify: Currently being implemented, but you will receive items!</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>If this seems like the right server for you then come on over, we are accepting all new players!<br>
If you would like to donate, please visit us on our website for more information.</p>
<p>NOTE: Rules are clearly displayed on the server!<br>
Additional Details<br>
Currently a small, factions PvP server with plenty of great plugins with a hope of becoming one of the most favored and enjoyable servers. Join us now!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-minecraft-pvp-server/456111/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-minecraft-pvp-server/456111/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 09:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-456111-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-minecraft-pvp-server/456111.rss">New minecraft pvp server</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
