<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My runescape life</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474</link>
    <description>[b]I quit runescape so stop telling me to quit[/b]


Im bored as hell so i thought i would share what i have accomplish and failed at in my rs life :P

Also if you want you can post your story on here i dont really care lol im just really bored. Ill go over this tomorrow and make it easier to read.

Alright well i started runescape about 5 years ago and i got addicted on it. My friend first showed me it and his name is Alex. Well he was a rich person but not very rich.. back then 1k was very rich to me. Anyways i was a noob it took me 2 weeks to get 8 cmb. Anyways after i trained for a while i got 20 attk. and i spent about 3 weeks buying my first weapon. and of course it was a mith scimmy :P i ended up buying it from the shop. Anyways basically after that i started fishing and cooking and i got 40 fishing/cooking in one. Once this happened i realized i was addicted to runescape and my life changed :P. After about 6months to a year i became a member and so did my friend. Me and my friend got our first 100k from picking flax Woot!. it took us about 3 days to pick 1k flax and we sold it for 200k then split the money. I being a careless noob bought a rune warhammer for 100k thinking it was worth more (wow was i wrong) After that i took about a 2 week break and then came back. When i came back i started to work on ranging and me and my friend had a race to see who could get 40 range first. Well i won :P anyways after that i decided to keep ranging and got 58 range. 

After 58 range i quit for about 1 month and came back. I got 83 range when i came back and my current stats. Im not sure if my the times i gave are correct (this should be about my 3rd year of rs now). I had my current stats which i loved and i found better ways of making money :P the first mass amount of money i made i made through pass scaming by typing &quot;runescape really blocks your pass ****** see try it!&quot; i made roughly 6m off this and bought my first whip. Then i merchanted a little and ended up with my first 10m (and a little more scamming) then i lost it all messing around in cw. I gave away a whip (back then were 3m) and a obby shield (back then it was 600k) Anyways after that i quit for about 3 months. I came back and the game changed alot and i almost quit because i couldnt grasp it but i didnt and continued. Then i continued to play and i got my fletching up and woodcutting up and just started to skill. Then they came out with POH and i spent every cent i had to try and get 50 construction in 1 day =\ i got 48 lol. After that i took a break for about 1 week and came back. I played randomly on and off nothing exciting happening. Now to present time. A few motnhs ago i tried to scam my friend for 25m and i failed miserably. I got on his account put it on my account and thought i was set. But i forgot that the account we shared had the same pass as mine so he took it all back. I had put 2m on my main and bought a whip for 1.5 and kept 500k. Well i had nothing to do and i had been watching youtube and looking at staking videos so i said well what the hell i have nothing to lose and started to stake. I ended up with more then i could every dream of in my life. In total i won over 120m i won 2 santas a blue mask and 60m cash :). It took me 3 days of staking. I cleaned around 4 people. the last guy i cleaned i won a santa a blue mask and 25m. Then i decided to go train for a day and i got 1 def level which got me a cmb lvl and seriously fucked me over. I went back to staking the next day and lost 40m. I was determined to get it back and lost everything but 25m. This is where my first serious pure came in. He was the best pure i had ever made. He was 52 cmb 73 range 73 mage 59 hp 32 att 30 str 11 pray and dt done. I loved him and i started to stake and pk on him. Well i won 10m the first day then lost 15m the next day so i gave up staking. After that i went pking for fun and forgot to take off my fury :( well i died skulled and lost my fury. So i went and staked 5m and won another then quit staking again. Now i had about 15m and i started to train a little then my friend got on and lost my 15m staking. (im not sure if he stole it or not) Basically now i was broke and had a good pure and a good main but nothing to do so i quit again and took about a month off. Then i came back and my friend told me about this glitch which was a force telly and we tried it. It took us 4 hours to get it to work the first time but the rest of the time it took us 5 min max to set it up. Anyways we started to steal items from places. Such as bloods from BA baricades out of castlewars Dragonstones out of the arena and other things. We also figured out how to get unlimited tokkul from it :) and we were going to buy some onyx gems. I left for the weekend for vacation and when i came back my friends account was banned but my accounts were not. I got on and my account was banned in 15 min. Then i got on my pure and it was banned within 15 min as well. I was pissed as fuck at rs and decided to get revenge but i didnt know how. (i still dont know how to do anything about it) Anyways after i was banned me and my friend started a new account because he was banned as well. It&#39;s name was Next Update and he seriously was one of the greatest pures i have ever seen. He was 54 cmb 52 hp 80 mage 60 range with dt done and he owned everyone even with his low hp. D bow and blitz was fun as hell on noobs because i could hit 25 25 with d bow and 26 with blitz :P 3 hit k0 at 54 cmb. Anyways me and my friend made about 10m and started to stake and got around 15m and we thought yes we are getting something finally. Well he was banned for a offensive name. There is no possible way to get him back. Now we literally had absolutely nothing on the game and still do. We have 2 pures zaros zezima and like these. Also 2 unlimited membership accounts which im not going to name just because i dont want to and 2 account withs 1 year members on them both are lvl 3 though. So we have abbout 2m al together and we are deciding what to do. We also made a def staker but he sucks so it didnt work out =\ Well thats about it. My rs Life was great until a few months ago. Jagex is banning all our account left and right. We had about 17 accounts banned for offensive names or no reason at all. I was literally amazed at what they do because you abuse 1 bug. And if you actually read this make a good comment or any comment about it :P i think my rs life has been ok and it is starting to decline. Also to let all you know i am the most unlucky person on this earth probably.

[b]Holy fuck i typed alot[/b]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 20:21:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@billygotshot billygotshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billygotshot">@billygotshot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Swordskid61, post:33, topic:142474”][quote author=billygotshot link=topic=194919.msg1804396#msg1804396 date=1191659494]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Then there would be no need for yours either, 3 freakin days, don’t need broken necks from a fender bender.</p>
<p>You’re runescape life sounds pretty boring.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lol trust me some points were boring as hell others were not. Bug abusing was probably the best thing i ever did on rs. It was insanely awesome i also found a few other bugs i never posted about. Anyways it was really funny to freak people out.<br>
[/quote]<br>
what did it do? (the bug)</p>
<p>~XDZ[/quote]</p>
<p>umm the one bug that was posted on tainted… The force telly. I found a few other ones and abused them but they were the same as the duel arena bug just with a few tweaks in them they are all fixed now though.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 20:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@swordskid61 Swordskid61]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/swordskid61">@swordskid61</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“billygotshot, post:32, topic:142474”][quote author=MastrChief link=topic=194919.msg1802878#msg1802878 date=1191631995]<br>
Then there would be no need for yours either, 3 freakin days, don’t need broken necks from a fender bender.</p>
<p>You’re runescape life sounds pretty boring.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>lol trust me some points were boring as hell others were not. Bug abusing was probably the best thing i ever did on rs. It was insanely awesome i also found a few other bugs i never posted about. Anyways it was really funny to freak people out.[/quote]<br>
what did it do? (the bug)</p>
<p>~XDZ</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 17:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@billygotshot billygotshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billygotshot">@billygotshot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“MastrChief, post:31, topic:142474”]Then there would be no need for yours either, 3 freakin days, don’t need broken necks from a fender bender.</p>
<p>You’re runescape life sounds pretty boring.[/quote]</p>
<p>lol trust me some points were boring as hell others were not. Bug abusing was probably the best thing i ever did on rs. It was insanely awesome i also found a few other bugs i never posted about. Anyways it was really funny to freak people out.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 08:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Then there would be no need for yours either, 3 freakin days, don’t need broken necks from a fender bender.</p>
<p>You’re runescape life sounds pretty boring.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 00:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@swordskid61 Swordskid61]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/swordskid61">@swordskid61</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Sync, post:28, topic:142474”]You managed to take away 20 minutes of my boredom, I’ll put that in short form.(btw Billy it’s Dark Child from Codex)<br>
Started out as a noob, got 1k, picked flax(got 100k), gave away his whip and obby shield, staked, gained money lost money, abused bug, got banned, started new acc, got banned(offensive name).[/quote][quote=“x ancients x, post:29, topic:142474”]whats the point in playing at first if you just gunna give ur stuff away :S…you should have kept it incase you wanted to go back on…[/quote]<br>
No need for these bumps k? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>~XDZ</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2007 16:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@x_ancients_x x ancients x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/x_ancients_x">@x_ancients_x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>whats the point in playing at first if you just gunna give ur stuff away :S…you should have kept it incase you wanted to go back on…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2007 20:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sync Sync]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sync">@Sync</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You managed to take away 20 minutes of my boredom, I’ll put that in short form.(btw Billy it’s Dark Child from Codex)<br>
Started out as a noob, got 1k, picked flax(got 100k), gave away his whip and obby shield, staked, gained money lost money, abused bug, got banned, started new acc, got banned(offensive name).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2007 19:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sir_coakley sir coakley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sir_coakley">@sir_coakley</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ive never heard so much dribble in all my life u reli  sat there an wrote that crap nnnnnnnnnnnnnneeeeeeeeeeeeeeerrrrrrrrrrrrrrrddddddddddd!!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2007 23:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Carazon Carazon ™]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/carazon">@Carazon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The title made me laugh… No-one has a life in RuneScape. Runescape is probably 0.01 % of my life… LOL</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2007 22:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bobby Bobby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobby">@bobby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“billygotshot, post:24, topic:142474”][quote author=dragonus18 link=topic=194919.msg1777329#msg1777329 date=1190612265]<br>
i read liek a sentence then i was like im not reading this becuz it looked intimidating with it being 1 big block of text<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I’m glad you didn’t write it. I can barely read that sentence.[/quote] thats true, but the big block is annyoing to read.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2007 03:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@billygotshot billygotshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billygotshot">@billygotshot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="23" data-topic="142474">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/dragonus18/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> dragonus18:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i read liek a sentence then i was like im not reading this becuz it looked intimidating with it being 1 big block of text</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m glad you didn’t write it. I can barely read that sentence.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 05:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragonus18 dragonus18]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragonus18">@dragonus18</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i read liek a sentence then i was like im not reading this becuz it looked intimidating with it being 1 big block of text</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 05:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@billygotshot billygotshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billygotshot">@billygotshot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taharok, post:21, topic:142474”][quote author=Exception link=topic=194919.msg1768295#msg1768295 date=1190262609]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>l2outside</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lmfao xD<br>
Billygotshot, do you know what the ENTER key is for? It’s really great for making an otherwise excessively large undecipherable block of misspelled text slightly more legible.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Agreed, a lot of people do not even read big blocks of text unless they are categorized into one-topic paragraphs.[/quote]</p>
<p>i know <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> i was going to fix it up but i knew this thread would die so i would rather not waste my time. Apparently though people like to post on it for no reason other then to critize my writing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 02:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Exception, post:18, topic:142474”][quote author=fellixombc link=topic=194919.msg1768053#msg1768053 date=1190257343]<br>
l2outside<br>
[/quote]<br>
Lmfao xD<br>
Billygotshot, do you know what the ENTER key is for? It’s really great for making an otherwise excessively large undecipherable block of misspelled text slightly more legible.[/quote]</p>
<p>Agreed, a lot of people do not even read big blocks of text unless they are categorized into one-topic paragraphs.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 05:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bobby Bobby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bobby">@bobby</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="19" data-topic="142474">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 ß Boring ß:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>RuneScape Life = No Life.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>thats spam. if your oging to post, at least explain your thoughts</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/20</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 04:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ss_Boring_ss Boring_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ss_boring_ss">@ss_Boring_ss</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>RuneScape Life = No Life.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/19</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 04:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Exception Exception]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exception">@Exception</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="17" data-topic="142474">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/fellixombc/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> fellixombc:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>l2outside</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Lmfao xD<br>
Billygotshot, do you know what the ENTER key is for? It’s really great for making an otherwise excessively large undecipherable block of misspelled text slightly more legible.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 04:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fellixombc fellixombc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fellixombc">@fellixombc</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>l2outside</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 03:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@billygotshot billygotshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billygotshot">@billygotshot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="15" data-topic="142474">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/mujahed/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> MujaheD:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Glad to see that your leaving rs… Are there any other bugs you can share with us? (or just me ;))</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>working on one with my friend <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> if it works it will be freaking sick otherwise nope =\ (none that i want to share atleast)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 02:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MujaheD Radeon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mujahed">@MujaheD</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Glad to see that your leaving rs… Are there any other bugs you can share with us? (or just me ;))</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2007 17:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SHANT_THE_MAN SHANT_THE_MAN!]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/shant_the_man">@SHANT_THE_MAN</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thats the longest written passage i’ve ever seen on this forum</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2007 11:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@billygotshot billygotshot]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/billygotshot">@billygotshot</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“sicarius99, post:12, topic:142474”][quote author=billygotshot link=topic=194919.msg1752239#msg1752239 date=1189648669]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>waste of time</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>umm you mean playing rs being a waste of time? not really because i know how to make a assload of cash really fast then i can sell the for rl money. The only problem is i dont have a account that has the ability to do what i need to do =.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>i ment typing all that shit out[/quote]</p>
<p>im going with you didnt read it because i said i was bored as hell somewhere in there</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2007 00:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sicarius99 sicarius99]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sicarius99">@sicarius99</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“billygotshot, post:8, topic:142474”][quote author=sicarius99 link=topic=194919.msg1751311#msg1751311 date=1189617565]<br>
waste of time<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>umm you mean playing rs being a waste of time? not really because i know how to make a assload of cash really fast then i can sell the for rl money. The only problem is i dont have a account that has the ability to do what i need to do =.[/quote]</p>
<p>i ment typing all that shit out</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/12</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2007 17:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@dragonus18 dragonus18]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dragonus18">@dragonus18</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“MastrChief, post:10, topic:142474”][quote author=dragonus18 link=topic=194919.msg1752861#msg1752861 date=1189659674]<br>
l1k3 z0mg d15 1 71m3 i w45 411 y0 h0mi3’s 4nd 5um1 g4v3 m3 a ph4t th3n i w45 411 i r0ck 4nd i 473 17<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Leetspeak is so annoying, either translate or stop posting the morons’ language.[/quote]</p>
<p>it was a joke dude… and translated it says</p>
<p>like omg this one time i was all yo homies and someone gave me a phat and i was all i rock and i ate it</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/11</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2007 05:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My runescape life</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MastrChief MastrChief]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mastrchief">@MastrChief</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="9" data-topic="142474">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/dragonus18/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> dragonus18:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>l1k3 z0mg d15 1 71m3 i w45 411 y0 h0mi3’s 4nd 5um1 g4v3 m3 a ph4t th3n i w45 411 i r0ck 4nd i 473 17</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Leetspeak is so annoying, either translate or stop posting the morons’ language.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2007 05:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-142474-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-life/142474.rss">My runescape life</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
