<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>BattleScape based client issues! Please Help (:</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452</link>
    <description>Okay so heres the deal...

I&#39;m starting a server thats based off of battlescape/nocturnal pk source....
First time coding a battlescape base and im confused.. 


1. Need to know how to change ip it connects to(No EGUI, GUI doesn&#39;t have it, Nor does Client.JAVA)
2. How to change background(Has no sprites folder and cannot find it)
3. How to get commands to work, nothing works as a command! (ban, mute, pickup etc etc.--Post an example of what works and I can do the rest)


THANKS!~ ;)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 23:21:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Game Development</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>BattleScape based client issues! Please Help (:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Ace1 Ace.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ace1">@Ace1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, he’s right.<br>
Most clients can’t run without a client.java, unless it’s named something else. Client.java is probably one of the main files needed.<br>
To find if there’s any hidden files, this is what I do.</p>
<ol>
<li>Right click on your folder, and select the “Properties” button, it might be “Options” depending on your computer.</li>
<li>Click on the “Hidden” folder, to trigger it, then press “OK”.<br>
THIS WILL HIDE ALL THE FILES IN THAT FOLDER. THAT IS NORMAL, KEEP READING.</li>
<li>After you pressed the “Ok” button, right click the folder again, go to “Properties” again,  Un-trigger the “Hidden” option, by clicking on the box next to it, and this should now make all folders viewable. Click “Ok” once you have done that, and you’re finished. Go check if you have these files to change:<br>
Clickingmost.java - Changing the co-ords of where the teleport takes you.<br>
Texthandler.java - Changing the name of a teleport<br>
Client.java - To change where the teleport takes you, IF YOU DON’T HAVE CLICKINGMOST.JAVA.</li>
</ol>
<p>Changing the Co-ords of a teleport:<br>
First, make sure you are an Administrator, or Mod on your server so you can use the “::mypos” command. This command tells you your co-ords. For an example, 1432, 6534.</p>
<p>Step 1. What we do is go to the area that the teleport takes you to, the EXACT spot would be great. Type the “::mypos” command, so it tells you the co-ords. We need these to be able to change the teleport. It would be best if you wrote these down.</p>
<p>Step 2. Go to the area where you want, for the teleport to take you, type the “::mypos” command, and read the co-ords. It should come up with something quite simular to this:<br>
PosyX: 3000 PosyY: 4000.<br>
The two numbers are the co-ords. We need them.</p>
<p>Now when you have the co-ords, right click and choose the “Edit” button on clickingmost.java. This is how we edit the file.<br>
Press Control + F (To find things) and enter the first FOUR DIGITS in the original co-ords of the teleport. Type in the box that popped up the co-ords of the original teleport (we found them in Step. 1). In this case, it would be “1432”. You most likely won’t get any results, so if you do, we will remove the LAST number of the co-ord in the search box, to get some better results. This usually happens because a teleport takes you to a different tile each time, usually 3-4 tiles apart. ANYWAY, in this case it would be “143”. You most likely will get a result this time. Keep finding the numbers, until you find TWO sets of numbers that look quite close to the original Co-ords. Say it’s “1436” and “6538”.<br>
Change these to where you want the teleport to take you to (found in Step. 2).</p>
<p>NOTE: IF YOU ARE STILL NOT FINDING ANYTHING, TRY FINDING THE FIRST 3 NUMBERS IF THE CO-ORD, IN THE SECOND NUMBER! IN THIS CASE IT WOULD BE: 653.<br>
If you find results, do the step ABOVE this step.</p>
<p>That’s pretty much it, I think… Save, Compile, and you’re finished.</p>
<p>LESSON 2:<br>
Changing the Teleports name:</p>
<p>Step 1. Find the name of the teleport you would like to be changing. You can simply do this by logging in, going to the magic book, and finding it there.</p>
<p>Step 2. Open the Texthander.java file (Right click, and chose EDIT to open it). Press Control + F (this opens the search/find box) and type in the name of the original teleport you would like to change. You will most likely find a result straight away.</p>
<p>Step 3. Replace that name with what you would like to rename the teleport with.<br>
NOTE: The line under that name will be what the text says under the name. Such as “The town of Varrock”.</p>
<p>Step 4. Changing the colour of the teleport name.<br>
Here are just SOME of the many colours you can do. What you need to do, is place them infront of the text.<br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/red">@red</a>@<br>
<a class="mention" href="/u/xxx">@xxx</a>@<br>
<span class="mention">@whi</span>@<br>
<span class="mention">@gre</span>@<br>
<span class="mention">@yel</span>@<br>
<span class="mention">@ora</span>@ - I think<br>
Example - <a class="mention" href="/u/red">@red</a>@ Varrock<br>
Example 2, for UNDER the name teleport. - <span class="mention">@whi</span>@ The home town of ________</p>
<p>That’s pretty much it. Save, Compile, and that’s all you need to do.<br>
If you get compiling errors, see what you did wrong.<br>
Hopefully I helped. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 23:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-323452-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452.rss">BattleScape based client issues! Please Help (:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BattleScape based client issues! Please Help (:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fatal_Desire Fatal Desire]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fatal_desire">@Fatal_Desire</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>For commands go into you client.Java on your SOURCE not client, and add them.</p>
<p>No client.Java or gui in your client? Try seeing if any files are hidden.</p>
<p>Same thing for the sprites folder.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 06:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-323452-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452.rss">BattleScape based client issues! Please Help (:</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>BattleScape based client issues! Please Help (:</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@forest419 forest419]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/forest419">@forest419</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Okay so heres the deal…</p>
<p>I’m starting a server thats based off of battlescape/nocturnal pk source…<br>
First time coding a battlescape base and im confused…</p>
<ol>
<li>Need to know how to change ip it connects to(No EGUI, GUI doesn’t have it, Nor does Client.JAVA)</li>
<li>How to change background(Has no sprites folder and cannot find it)</li>
<li>How to get commands to work, nothing works as a command! (ban, mute, pickup etc etc.–Post an example of what works and I can do the rest)</li>
</ol>
<p>THANKS!~ <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 22:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-323452-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/battlescape-based-client-issues-please-help/323452.rss">BattleScape based client issues! Please Help (:</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
