<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sending fake emails from any address</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113</link>
    <description>In this tutorial I will show step by step how to send an email with the sender address as anything you specify. I will not be held liable if you use this information illegally. The idea is to get some pretty good pranks going on and also this will follow on nicely from a previous tute &quot; How to get any @Domain.com/net/org/gov/etc.......... &quot; [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,46809.0.html]http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,46809.0.html[/url]. I have had a good search and I can&#39;t seem to find this anywhere on moparisthebest so I thought it might be a good idea to enlighten people but I apologize if it is already on.

Its alot easier just to use [url=http://deadfake.com]http://deadfake.com[/url] but this site also states that the email is a fake from deadfake at the bottom of the email so it&#39;s not as fun.

First off Credits go to: [url=http://www.xult.org/fake.html]http://www.xult.org/fake.html[/url] which gave me the original idea and method ( I put credits at the start so that people actually read them, hence credit is actually received).

Hope this is simple enough

*Warning emails are traceable and it is unadvisable to do anything other then pranking people using this information or using it for some other legitimate purpose. I do not approve of scamming in anyway shape or form*
1. You will need an open relay smtp server. Usually your isp will provide you with one or you can find one online or use gmail, hotmail etc (*but there are limitations with using gmail and hotmail which will be explained later). NOTE:If you try using an isp that isnt yours you will most likely be blocked from connecting.

2. Now that you have chosen your server open command prompt by pressing the start button, finding the run function and entering cmd.exe in the run function.
[URL=http://img126.imageshack.us/my.php?image=cmdzp5.png][IMG]http://img126.imageshack.us/img126/7325/cmdzp5.th.png[/img][/URL]

3. A black box will appear in front of you. Now based on what your server is you will have to put in their address. Type in the following &quot;nslookup -q=mx (the address of your server)&quot;. I will use my isp (my university) as an example.
[URL=http://img511.imageshack.us/my.php?image=nslookup1wc9.png][IMG]http://img511.imageshack.us/img511/6029/nslookup1wc9.th.png[/img][/URL]

4. Now we want to choose one of the mail exchangers if there is more then one. In my case there is only one (mail.otago.ac.nz). If there is more then one, choose a random one. Now in command prompt type &quot;telnet (address of the mail exchanger) 25&quot; this allows you to connect to the mail exchanger through port 25.
[URL=http://img56.imageshack.us/my.php?image=telnet1hz1.png][IMG]http://img56.imageshack.us/img56/87/telnet1hz1.th.png[/img][/URL]

Note: from now on if you make a mistake you will have to do the whole line again you cannot go back and delete the mistake or add new stuff. So if i type &quot;mail rom: .....&quot; then go back and add a f to make it &quot;mail from: .....&quot; then it will not be accepted. Just press enter if you make a mistake and do the whole line again.
5. Ok now you should be connected with some writing at the top, dont worry about that. First you will have to introduce yourself. Any random email address will do (doesnt even have to exist). In my case I am just giving a random domain, this may apply to you as well if it wont accept an email address. After this type &quot;mail from: (sender address)&quot; press enter then &quot;rcpt to: (recipients address)&quot;. *Now here comes the limitation of using gmail and hotmail. If you use them your recipient may only be using said server. For example if i was using hotmail as my smtp server then I can only send emails via this technique to people who use hotmail, I wouldnt be able to send emails to say someone&#39;s gmail account or (insert email provider here) account. You can try if you want but the server will just say it cannot find the account.
[URL=http://img119.imageshack.us/my.php?image=mailco7.png][IMG]http://img119.imageshack.us/img119/2307/mailco7.th.png[/img][/URL]

6.Now type in &quot;Data&quot; and enter. Then &quot;subject: (your subject)&quot; then press enter twice, there should be one line with absolutely nothing on it below the subject. You will now be two lines below the subject and this is where you type your email. When your done press enter. Do a full stop (.) on a new line then enter again and the message should be sent. Once your done type &quot;quit&quot; to disconnect then &quot;exit&quot; to close command prompt.
[URL=http://img253.imageshack.us/my.php?image=messageqw1.png][IMG]http://img253.imageshack.us/img253/2708/messageqw1.th.png[/img][/URL]

Now you can not only use fake email addresses on messengers but you can also email people using fake email addresses. Hope this is simple enough and i wish you fun. If you need help please feel free to ask in the thread.

*Once again fraudulent use of this is not advised*

Thank you for your time
-Mantis out-
P.S Sorry about my bad english I tried not to make any mistakes</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2009 13:32:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Sending fake emails from any address</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@benman2305 benman2305]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/benman2305">@benman2305</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>LOL THIS SOUNDS FUN</p>
<p>but you realy need to use photo bucket not imageshack</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2009 13:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236113-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113.rss">Sending fake emails from any address</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sending fake emails from any address</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mantis1 Mantis1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mantis1">@Mantis1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I searched up fake email address.</p>
<p>edit<br>
Oh my bad there was one but it was entitled “hacking with xp”.</p>
<p>My apologies</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 14:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236113-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113.rss">Sending fake emails from any address</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sending fake emails from any address</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I searched ‘sending emails’ in this section and it was the third thing that popped up (it’s in the tutorial list).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 12:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236113-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113.rss">Sending fake emails from any address</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sending fake emails from any address</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mantis1 Mantis1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mantis1">@Mantis1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>oops my bad somone delete then, sorry obviously need to use better keyword search refining</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 09:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236113-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113.rss">Sending fake emails from any address</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sending fake emails from any address</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’ve already read this somewhere, I believe it was on this site. So you didn’t search that well.</p>
<p>Edit: <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,30823.0.html" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,30823.0.html</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 09:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236113-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113.rss">Sending fake emails from any address</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Sending fake emails from any address</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Mantis1 Mantis1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mantis1">@Mantis1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In this tutorial I will show step by step how to send an email with the sender address as anything you specify. I will not be held liable if you use this information illegally. The idea is to get some pretty good pranks going on and also this will follow on nicely from a previous tute " How to get any <span class="mention">@Domain.com</span>/net/org/gov/etc… " <a href="http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,46809.0.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,46809.0.html</a>. I have had a good search and I can’t seem to find this anywhere on moparisthebest so I thought it might be a good idea to enlighten people but I apologize if it is already on.</p>
<p>Its alot easier just to use <a href="http://deadfake.com" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://deadfake.com</a> but this site also states that the email is a fake from deadfake at the bottom of the email so it’s not as fun.</p>
<p>First off Credits go to: <a href="http://www.xult.org/fake.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.xult.org/fake.html</a> which gave me the original idea and method ( I put credits at the start so that people actually read them, hence credit is actually received).</p>
<p>Hope this is simple enough</p>
<p><em>Warning emails are traceable and it is unadvisable to do anything other then pranking people using this information or using it for some other legitimate purpose. I do not approve of scamming in anyway shape or form</em></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>You will need an open relay smtp server. Usually your isp will provide you with one or you can find one online or use gmail, hotmail etc (*but there are limitations with using gmail and hotmail which will be explained later). NOTE:If you try using an isp that isnt yours you will most likely be blocked from connecting.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Now that you have chosen your server open command prompt by pressing the start button, finding the run function and entering cmd.exe in the run function.<br>
<a href="http://img126.imageshack.us/my.php?image=cmdzp5.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img126.imageshack.us/img126/7325/cmdzp5.th.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A black box will appear in front of you. Now based on what your server is you will have to put in their address. Type in the following “nslookup -q=mx (the address of your server)”. I will use my isp (my university) as an example.<br>
<a href="http://img511.imageshack.us/my.php?image=nslookup1wc9.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img511.imageshack.us/img511/6029/nslookup1wc9.th.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Now we want to choose one of the mail exchangers if there is more then one. In my case there is only one (mail.otago.ac.nz). If there is more then one, choose a random one. Now in command prompt type “telnet (address of the mail exchanger) 25” this allows you to connect to the mail exchanger through port 25.<br>
<a href="http://img56.imageshack.us/my.php?image=telnet1hz1.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img56.imageshack.us/img56/87/telnet1hz1.th.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Note: from now on if you make a mistake you will have to do the whole line again you cannot go back and delete the mistake or add new stuff. So if i type “mail rom: …” then go back and add a f to make it “mail from: …” then it will not be accepted. Just press enter if you make a mistake and do the whole line again.<br>
5. Ok now you should be connected with some writing at the top, dont worry about that. First you will have to introduce yourself. Any random email address will do (doesnt even have to exist). In my case I am just giving a random domain, this may apply to you as well if it wont accept an email address. After this type “mail from: (sender address)” press enter then “rcpt to: (recipients address)”. *Now here comes the limitation of using gmail and hotmail. If you use them your recipient may only be using said server. For example if i was using hotmail as my smtp server then I can only send emails via this technique to people who use hotmail, I wouldnt be able to send emails to say someone’s gmail account or (insert email provider here) account. You can try if you want but the server will just say it cannot find the account.<br>
<a href="http://img119.imageshack.us/my.php?image=mailco7.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img119.imageshack.us/img119/2307/mailco7.th.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>6.Now type in “Data” and enter. Then “subject: (your subject)” then press enter twice, there should be one line with absolutely nothing on it below the subject. You will now be two lines below the subject and this is where you type your email. When your done press enter. Do a full stop (.) on a new line then enter again and the message should be sent. Once your done type “quit” to disconnect then “exit” to close command prompt.<br>
<a href="http://img253.imageshack.us/my.php?image=messageqw1.png" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://img253.imageshack.us/img253/2708/messageqw1.th.png" alt width="" height=""></a></p>
<p>Now you can not only use fake email addresses on messengers but you can also email people using fake email addresses. Hope this is simple enough and i wish you fun. If you need help please feel free to ask in the thread.</p>
<p><em>Once again fraudulent use of this is not advised</em></p>
<p>Thank you for your time<br>
-Mantis out-<br>
P.S Sorry about my bad english I tried not to make any mistakes</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 06:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-236113-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/sending-fake-emails-from-any-address/236113.rss">Sending fake emails from any address</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
