<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Packet Building Abstraction</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-building-abstraction/293086</link>
    <description>I&#39;m currently building in multiple RS version support into my Blitz framework in the form of plugins. You may or may not know this, but overall all the content of the server is added through plugins, even the basics like the logout button.

[center]Here is a screenshot of the three main plugin projects, the core version support:
[img]http://www.allgofree.org/rs/pics/blitz/core_support.jpg[/img]

And parts of the Core 508 plugin:
[img]http://www.allgofree.org/rs/pics/blitz/core_508.jpg[/img][/center]

Right now the plugins support login packet reading and general packet reading for each version. However the &quot;Old Engine&quot; clients must connect on an alternate port for technical reasons. So right now 474 and 508 connect on the default port, while 317 connects on 43593.
However &quot;Old Engine&quot; clients can connect on the default port by specifying a specific opcode instead of the usual 14.

[center]Here is a picture of one invalid login attempt for each version, all at the same time on the same server:
[img]http://www.allgofree.org/rs/pics/blitz/multi_login_scaled.jpg[/img][/center]

Now the only thing left for full multiple version support is packet building; but I am looking for a good way to make it abstract to the server. There are some specific packets that must be provided specially, like the player and npc update packets, but I&#39;ve already worked those out.

Please post any ideas/comments/suggestions/random crap. ;)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 15:44:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-building-abstraction/293086.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Packet Building Abstraction</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@ry60003333 ry60003333]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/ry60003333">@ry60003333</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m currently building in multiple RS version support into my Blitz framework in the form of plugins. You may or may not know this, but overall all the content of the server is added through plugins, even the basics like the logout button.</p>
<p>[center]Here is a screenshot of the three main plugin projects, the core version support:<br>
<img src="http://www.allgofree.org/rs/pics/blitz/core_support.jpg" alt width="" height=""></p>
<p>And parts of the Core 508 plugin:<br>
<img src="http://www.allgofree.org/rs/pics/blitz/core_508.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p>Right now the plugins support login packet reading and general packet reading for each version. However the “Old Engine” clients must connect on an alternate port for technical reasons. So right now 474 and 508 connect on the default port, while 317 connects on 43593.<br>
However “Old Engine” clients can connect on the default port by specifying a specific opcode instead of the usual 14.</p>
<p>[center]Here is a picture of one invalid login attempt for each version, all at the same time on the same server:<br>
<img src="http://www.allgofree.org/rs/pics/blitz/multi_login_scaled.jpg" alt width="" height="">[/center]</p>
<p>Now the only thing left for full multiple version support is packet building; but I am looking for a good way to make it abstract to the server. There are some specific packets that must be provided specially, like the player and npc update packets, but I’ve already worked those out.</p>
<p>Please post any ideas/comments/suggestions/random crap. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-building-abstraction/293086/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-building-abstraction/293086/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 15:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-293086-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/packet-building-abstraction/293086.rss">Packet Building Abstraction</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
