<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Environment variables?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/environment-variables/347059</link>
    <description>ok so i had to format my computer because of a virus screwing my windows installation, and i thought i&#39;d get back to programming. so i install java and everything, and it&#39;s time to set my Path variables.

now when i try to set something, it looks like it&#39;s edited. then when i close the window, nothing&#39;s changed. it&#39;s still the same value and my CLASSPATH variable is not even there. any help with this guys? i&#39;m debating having a fll scan of my computer for viruses but i&#39;m kind of working on a project now and scans always lag my computer, so i&#39;m waiting for confirmation.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 22:17:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/environment-variables/347059.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Environment variables?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Svitkona Svitkona]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/svitkona">@Svitkona</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ok so i had to format my computer because of a virus screwing my windows installation, and i thought i’d get back to programming. so i install java and everything, and it’s time to set my Path variables.</p>
<p>now when i try to set something, it looks like it’s edited. then when i close the window, nothing’s changed. it’s still the same value and my CLASSPATH variable is not even there. any help with this guys? i’m debating having a fll scan of my computer for viruses but i’m kind of working on a project now and scans always lag my computer, so i’m waiting for confirmation.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/environment-variables/347059/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/environment-variables/347059/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 22:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-347059-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/environment-variables/347059.rss">Environment variables?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
