<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Online Money</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/online-money/411646</link>
    <description>Probably not the best community I could find to ask this question, but: Does anybody know of any small corner of the internet where actually DECENT money can be made? (I&#39;m 21, so age is not really a problem if need be over 18 with verified ID or something.)

I work at a movie theater and it&#39;s getting to be the &#39;slow&#39; season, so they&#39;re cutting down on our shifts. This doesn&#39;t help with my saving up for a motorcycle right now, and so I need some other on-the-side way to make some money. I don&#39;t need like $15/hour or anything, but decent chump change is always nice.

I&#39;ve worked for ChaCha before, made about $100 after MANY hours. (Their money per-question is crap.) I&#39;ve also done the &quot;Help people do the Get A Free iPad ads and they pay you&quot; scheme, and made a few hundred. But that&#39;s going down the drain as fewer companies offer that sort of thing.

So, yeah, any suggestions? (Preferably with some sort of experience or knowledge of somebody who&#39;s done it successfully.)

Thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 21:48:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/online-money/411646.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Online Money</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jamie1200 Jamie1200]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jamie1200">@Jamie1200</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>As you stated not the best idea in the world to ask this community.<br>
<a href="http://www.101waystomakemoney.com/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.101waystomakemoney.com/</a> is a good way to start.<br>
Alternatively get another job or get a second Job. maybe?</p>
<p>Edit: Ever heard of Money flipping websites?<br>
<a href="http://www.101waystomakemoney.com/make-money-flipping-websites/" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.101waystomakemoney.com/make-money-flipping-websites/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/online-money/411646/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/online-money/411646/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 21:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-411646-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/online-money/411646.rss">Online Money</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Online Money</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Slave_Scyth Slave Scyth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/slave_scyth">@Slave_Scyth</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Probably not the best community I could find to ask this question, but: Does anybody know of any small corner of the internet where actually DECENT money can be made? (I’m 21, so age is not really a problem if need be over 18 with verified ID or something.)</p>
<p>I work at a movie theater and it’s getting to be the ‘slow’ season, so they’re cutting down on our shifts. This doesn’t help with my saving up for a motorcycle right now, and so I need some other on-the-side way to make some money. I don’t need like $15/hour or anything, but decent chump change is always nice.</p>
<p>I’ve worked for ChaCha before, made about $100 after MANY hours. (Their money per-question is crap.) I’ve also done the “Help people do the Get A Free iPad ads and they pay you” scheme, and made a few hundred. But that’s going down the drain as fewer companies offer that sort of thing.</p>
<p>So, yeah, any suggestions? (Preferably with some sort of experience or knowledge of somebody who’s done it successfully.)</p>
<p>Thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/online-money/411646/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/online-money/411646/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 21:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-411646-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/online-money/411646.rss">Online Money</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
