<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>508- really need help</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-really-need-help/354722</link>
    <description>okay, so i have a netgear router, and everytime i try to portforward i get my friends to try and connect but they never can. i have a Sky Router Netgear DG834GT, and i just cannot get my server online, i have tried alot of things but it&#39;s just not happening. i have tried utorrent, but same thing- doesn&#39;t connect, yes i put the port as 43594, and my no-ip DUC is active but it&#39;s still not working. i can get it online on hamachi, but who wants a hamachi server? if you think you can help me please post below. i have been coding this alot lately and dont feel like making it a waste of time. if it helps, im using a client my friend uses to run his server off (508-ipchanger).

i have teamviewer if u could help or just reply here PLEASE!!, if you like i can give u staff position on my server if you help me fix this problem!!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2010 13:46:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-really-need-help/354722.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>508- really need help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TOKSICK TOKSICK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/toksick">@TOKSICK</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i can help you</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-really-need-help/354722/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-really-need-help/354722/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2010 13:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-354722-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-really-need-help/354722.rss">508- really need help</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>508- really need help</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@fourzerotwo fourzerotwo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fourzerotwo">@fourzerotwo</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>okay, so i have a netgear router, and everytime i try to portforward i get my friends to try and connect but they never can. i have a Sky Router Netgear DG834GT, and i just cannot get my server online, i have tried alot of things but it’s just not happening. i have tried utorrent, but same thing- doesn’t connect, yes i put the port as 43594, and my no-ip DUC is active but it’s still not working. i can get it online on hamachi, but who wants a hamachi server? if you think you can help me please post below. i have been coding this alot lately and dont feel like making it a waste of time. if it helps, im using a client my friend uses to run his server off (508-ipchanger).</p>
<p>i have teamviewer if u could help or just reply here PLEASE!!, if you like i can give u staff position on my server if you help me fix this problem!!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-really-need-help/354722/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-really-need-help/354722/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2010 11:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-354722-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/508-really-need-help/354722.rss">508- really need help</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
