<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pull more user data other than skills, and store in MySQL? (Get an Inventory)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pull-more-user-data-other-than-skills-and-store-in-mysql-get-an-inventory/457174</link>
    <description>First i&#39;ll elaborate some on what i&#39;m trying to do. As a web developer i&#39;m always trying to do new things involving RSPS. I can easily pull and enforce data from MySQL databases, I can pull Hiscores currently because I used a basic hiscores system to add information to the database. 

In my current Hiscores.java I have this:
[code]Skills skills = player.getSkills();[/code]

Obviously this is what gets the players skills, this is before the query and obviously the query is what actually puts the skills into the database.
What would I do if I want to pull other things such as the players inventory items? I know i&#39;ll have to add something below the player.getSkills, and something along the lines of player.getInventory, but i&#39;m not exactly sure what to do and what the correct format is to get the inventory.

Seeing as I do Web Development, I&#39;m not very good with Java. So if someone who knows java better than I could help me it would be greatly appreciated! I just need to know the code for pulling the users inventory.

More information on what I&#39;m trying to do: I want to pull the users items from the database and use my RS_Items_Pack (Pack of over 20k Runescape Items 32x32 as they appear in the inventory), and make a little graphical inventory that someone can enable on their SMF profile to display what items they currently have. I can do everything website sided, i&#39;m just not sure how to pull the users inventory java-sided. 

Also, I&#39;m using a 711 (loading 722), in-case this information is useful.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 19:35:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pull-more-user-data-other-than-skills-and-store-in-mysql-get-an-inventory/457174.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Pull more user data other than skills, and store in MySQL? (Get an Inventory)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Web_Guy The Web Guy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_web_guy">@The_Web_Guy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>First i’ll elaborate some on what i’m trying to do. As a web developer i’m always trying to do new things involving RSPS. I can easily pull and enforce data from MySQL databases, I can pull Hiscores currently because I used a basic hiscores system to add information to the database.</p>
<p>In my current Hiscores.java I have this:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto"></code></pre>
<p>Obviously this is what gets the players skills, this is before the query and obviously the query is what actually puts the skills into the database.<br>
What would I do if I want to pull other things such as the players inventory items? I know i’ll have to add something below the player.getSkills, and something along the lines of player.getInventory, but i’m not exactly sure what to do and what the correct format is to get the inventory.</p>
<p>Seeing as I do Web Development, I’m not very good with Java. So if someone who knows java better than I could help me it would be greatly appreciated! I just need to know the code for pulling the users inventory.</p>
<p>More information on what I’m trying to do: I want to pull the users items from the database and use my RS_Items_Pack (Pack of over 20k Runescape Items 32x32 as they appear in the inventory), and make a little graphical inventory that someone can enable on their SMF profile to display what items they currently have. I can do everything website sided, i’m just not sure how to pull the users inventory java-sided.</p>
<p>Also, I’m using a 711 (loading 722), in-case this information is useful.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pull-more-user-data-other-than-skills-and-store-in-mysql-get-an-inventory/457174/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pull-more-user-data-other-than-skills-and-store-in-mysql-get-an-inventory/457174/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 19:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-457174-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pull-more-user-data-other-than-skills-and-store-in-mysql-get-an-inventory/457174.rss">Pull more user data other than skills, and store in MySQL? (Get an Inventory)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
