<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My RuneScape history</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810</link>
    <description>I started playing RuneScape at 2006

When I was 12, was a complete fool... Didn&#39;t even could pass the tutorial, my friends did it for me...

I trained an account to level almost 54 (Not with bot didn&#39;t knew there were!), and then I got bored... Quited it for 2 months, then one of my friends offered me a level 68 account with full rune and full quests (Exept shield of arav), I say sure...

Then I play on the account, train it to level 92 - 95, Got bored.. quited again...

I&#39;ve never been a member except for this year (2010), One of my friends made me a member...

Now I got cool states...and I play on that 68 that my friend gave me...

 
I got 120 quest points... 1462 Total level, 1 skillcape (Firemaking)

Here is more about me, check this picture :

[img]http://www.draynor.net/stat/wilderness/male/hd_firemaking_cape_emote/XZ_Bashar_XZ.png[/img]


Why don&#39;t you tell us something about you&#39;rself on RuneScape?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 10:09:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mrjad mrjad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrjad">@mrjad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>joined at 5 years old - 2001 rsclassic ftw, my brother 10 introduced me to the game, he made me make new accounts(surpisingly i could do)and give him the free runes to make him money, then after that day i knew he played everyday, but then my parents said he couldn’t play anymore(he got a gf on the site, and i couldn’t play either)then in 2003, we got a new computer, i played on a new account, i killed cows, and killed imps, and had tons of beads that i tired to use on wool to make a necklace, then my dad caught me i wasn’t allowed to play anymore - then im 12 i got my own computer and have been playing till 13 then i got a new laptop, surprisinly better than my desktop, so i started playing more runescape till one day in june, i was in a clan called w22 farming, and someone was talking about private servers, and i was like wtf is that, and they set its like runescape just with better xp rates and easier to get items,</p>
<p>and me being low level was like FUCK YEAH, so i searched it up, and found runelocus played servers on there - then the site was down, then i found mopar, and got into coding and now will forever camp here</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 10:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@0bbyme 0bbyme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/0bbyme">@0bbyme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>haha i cant believe you made all that up for this thread…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/21</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 05:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Frell Frell]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/frell">@Frell</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It was a cold stormy night. The power was out. I was huddled in a corner in my dark wet room when suddenly the power flickered. I stumbled over to my computer to check the weather. There was a very severe storm headed our way with intense hail and wind. I ran back into my corner. I could have sworn i heard the sound of a train during the storm. I looked out the window to see nothing but pitch black darkness. A quick bolt of blue light cracks through the sky and i coudlnt believe my eyes. A swirling funnel of ice and wind headed straight towards my house, throwing rain and hail at my window until it broke. The glass flew in and struck me in the eye. I screamed the loudest i had ever screamed, in dire pain i stood up to get into a more inner part of my house. The wind ripped the boards from around my window flinging planks at my back. As i was being thumped, one single plank with 12 rusty nails was flying at me faster than ever. It struck me in the back. I fell straight down and landed face first, pushing the glass further into my eye socket causing it to crumble into shards. Blood rained down my face into my mouth, along with glass shards. The glass ripped apart my tongue and cheek as the storm drew closer. I was grabbed by the tornado and whipped around several times, hitting everything in my way. I was thrown 3000 miles and landed in a house where a young boy was playing a game on the computer. I stood up, drenching blood all over the boys home and soaking wet i walked over and asked “what is that you’re playing?” Spitting blood all over his screen as i spoke. He turned around and screamed and ran out of the house. I sat down at the computer and started playing and i got hooked.</p>
<p>Thats my runescape story</p>
<p>i cant believe i fucking wrote all that just for this thread…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/20</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 05:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@drubrkletern drubrkletern]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/drubrkletern">@drubrkletern</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lol i first started in 2005, on april 9, 2005, (my brothers birthday) 11:23 am in the morning, when i saw tutorial island, i said omg… best…game…ever!!! I finished tut island really fast, then im like “omg i r 1337s” so much fun…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/19</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 05:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@hawkgames hawkgames]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hawkgames">@hawkgames</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was stuck at tutorial island for 3 months ,Because I couldnt find out how to get pass smithing.When my favorite server shuted down.I went back to rs and prayed at zamoraks temple,then my fellow zamorak monks atked me,I died after that my favorite server went back on.</p>
<p>RS GOD R AWESOME</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/18</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 02:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@the_elve_age the elve age]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_elve_age">@the_elve_age</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="16" data-topic="349810">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/0bbyme/40/5_513041d5f7104045db30895d3b90af16.png" class="avatar"> 0bbyme:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>has any one logged into runescape and then thought, “hmm… its not cool again, im gonna wait a few more months.” or am i the only one?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I thought the same things. Maybe it might be fun when I join. But it gets lame after a week of loosing, and getting banned from botting</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/17</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 02:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@0bbyme 0bbyme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/0bbyme">@0bbyme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>has any one logged into runescape and then thought, “hmm… its not cool again, im gonna wait a few more months.” or am i the only one?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/16</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 02:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pk_planet pk planet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pk_planet">@pk_planet</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="14" data-topic="349810">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 noobs are ftw:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>i joined rs in october 2006 i nearly didnt finish halloween event lol then i trained it to lvl 48 quit joined 2 years later trained to 82 atm(im lazy as fuck :D) i currently am not a mem and quit again only go on to dump mapdata</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You going to join again? =o</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/15</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 01:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@noobs_are_ftw noobs are ftw]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/noobs_are_ftw">@noobs_are_ftw</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i joined rs in october 2006 i nearly didnt finish halloween event lol then i trained it to lvl 48 quit joined 2 years later trained to 82 atm(im lazy as fuck :D) i currently am not a mem and quit again only go on to dump mapdata</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 19:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@spy_man47 spy man47]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spy_man47">@spy_man47</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The Reaper? GRATZ for mod!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 13:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Reaper_X The Reaper X]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_reaper_x">@The_Reaper_X</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I played RS before the botting days. I did the free quests alone, without tutorials. my goal was to get every quest completed, but I got tired of everything after I was introduced to moparscape. I got into RS emulating instead.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 21:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Natey Natey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/natey">@Natey</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was in 6th grade 2006, April 9th to be exact, all my good friends where talking about this game called “RoomSkate” (I didn’t know it was RuneScape) I said it sounded stupid, I was talking to one of my closest friends Tyler about it and he gave me the website, next day at the bookfair whe had every semester I was on the library computer and made my first account “Doggy36” played on the tutorial, quit that for a few days, then on April 15th I got my first own computer and decided to play RuneScape again, so I made a new account “Natecole4” played that for a few days, quit that, then around April 20th my friend asked if I wanted a level 12 account with some black stuff on it, I took it and that was my main from 2006-2008 (I still have it too) I quit him once my good friend Nate (LOL) and I started sharing our old account, Nest81, we also shared his staker account Som 1s b4ck and his main Aclaw (ranked <span class="hashtag">#1</span> attack) after his 2 accounts got keylogged we got nest81 from level 76-96 in a whole summer, then that account got locked for chargeback fees and is locked.<br>
My current main Pker0000888 was my dads girlfriends sons and I account, we made it to share and work on together, which is one of my current 2 mains.<br>
We’ve made that account pretty bad-ass, so that’s ny story o.-</p>
<p>Here are my mains:<br>
<img src="http://www.draynor.net/stat/black/male/hd_attackcape_1/ISteezy.png" alt width="320" height="125"><br>
<img src="http://www.draynor.net/stat/mithril/male/hd_magic_cape/We_ddos_u.png" alt width="320" height="125"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 18:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Phaze_One Fuscate]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phaze_one">@Phaze_One</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Started back when I was around 11 back in 2005 my friend told me he was playing this game which I thought was called ‘Run Escape’. He asked me to join so after school I googled this run escape game and the top result was Runescape. He told me to use a random name generator which I did and created an account called ‘XRaider2’. I spent about two months on this account until one day I saw some guy buying accounts so I sold him my back-up account for an Adamant axe and three gold bars. Being the 11 year old I was I used the same password for both accounts which he quickly discovered and unfortunately stole my account.</p>
<p>After that I quit Runescape not really caring too much until a family friend offered me an account. It had 40 something Smithing so I used this account for a while. My parents offered to purchase me membership and I played on that account until I was around 13. When I was 13 I was introduced to private servers which I thought was the coolest thing in the world. Because I had no use for Runescape I gave my account to my cousin and said he can use it but not change the password. Unfortunately he quit Runescape about a year later and we both forgot the password and he changed the recovery questions and lost them so no more account. Here is a picture:</p>
<p>[center]<a href="http://www.draynor.net/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="http://www.draynor.net/stat/default/male/hd_elegant/Dylan982.png" alt width="320" height="125"></a>[/center]</p>
<p>So I pretty much gave up on Runescape after that, concentrated on private servers and such but recently started working on account called ‘Asert One’. So I’m hoping to get all my favourite things back I earned on Dylan982 such as legends cape, 200 something quest points, full grey pirate outfit etc.</p>
<p>For all the idiots who say tl;dr add my rs account: Asert One</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 14:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@marcbob marcbob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/marcbob">@marcbob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Atm im working on my first account i every made on runescape. During the years I would get bored and quit and come back and make new pures or mains. All of them got banned pretty quick but were all good pures and mains. So I took about a year and a half break from runescape and been playing rsps. I always used to do both runescape and rsps but i quit that. I started playing again to go to my friends 99 fishing party and i got into rs again. Now im about to get my first 99 on the first account i made on runescape (thieving)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 14:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@primadude Primadude]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/primadude">@primadude</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><img src="http://www.draynor.net/stat/bluestorm/male/hd_fletching_emote/Primadude12.png" alt width="320" height="125"></p>
<p>I created this account back in 2005; it’s the second account that I ever made (My first one got hacked). I played until around the end of 2007, that’s when I found this site. I started playing again about a year ago.</p>
<p>I’m working on 99 fletching at the moment, I’m almost half way there in experience ;).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 13:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@spy_man47 spy man47]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spy_man47">@spy_man47</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“pure2ownage, post:6, topic:349810”][quote author=spy man47 link=topic=446183.msg3274614#msg3274614 date=1279456626]</p>
<p>[quote author=pure2ownage link=topic=446183.msg3274609#msg3274609 date=1279456453]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I was stuck on tutorial island for ~1 week; didn’t know how to turn “run” on.<br>
Now am lv128</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Didn’t you every quit? or left for couple of months?<br>
[/quote]Yer i did, late 2009 ~August i quit to join the RSPS scene again; now i have returned to rs and decided that RSPS suck balls as they all close at some point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I sometimes quit rs, say it sucks balls, then go to rsps and I like… till my favarote server shutted…</p>
<p>And then I go pray in Rs temple… :L<br>
[/quote]Lmao[/quote]</p>
<p>XD I go there and pray for god… To let me back in game <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 12:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“spy man47, post:5, topic:349810”][quote author=pure2ownage link=topic=446183.msg3274609#msg3274609 date=1279456453]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I was stuck on tutorial island for ~1 week; didn’t know how to turn “run” on.<br>
Now am lv128</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Didn’t you every quit? or left for couple of months?<br>
[/quote]Yer i did, late 2009 ~August i quit to join the RSPS scene again; now i have returned to rs and decided that RSPS suck balls as they all close at some point.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I sometimes quit rs, say it sucks balls, then go to rsps and I like… till my favarote server shutted…</p>
<p>And then I go pray in Rs temple… :L[/quote]Lmao</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 12:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@spy_man47 spy man47]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spy_man47">@spy_man47</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“pure2ownage, post:4, topic:349810”][quote author=spy man47 link=topic=446183.msg3274606#msg3274606 date=1279456378]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I was stuck on tutorial island for ~1 week; didn’t know how to turn “run” on.<br>
Now am lv128</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Didn’t you every quit? or left for couple of months?<br>
[/quote]Yer i did, late 2009 ~August i quit to join the RSPS scene again; now i have returned to rs and decided that RSPS suck balls as they all close at some point.[/quote]</p>
<p>I sometimes quit rs, say it sucks balls, then go to rsps and I like… till my favarote server shutted…</p>
<p>And then I go pray in Rs temple… :L</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 12:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“spy man47, post:3, topic:349810”][quote author=pure2ownage link=topic=446183.msg3274602#msg3274602 date=1279456200]<br>
I was stuck on tutorial island for ~1 week; didn’t know how to turn “run” on.<br>
Now am lv128<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Didn’t you every quit? or left for couple of months?[/quote]Yer i did, late 2009 ~August i quit to join the RSPS scene again; now i have returned to rs and decided that RSPS suck balls as they all close at some point.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 12:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@spy_man47 spy man47]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spy_man47">@spy_man47</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“pure2ownage, post:2, topic:349810”]I was stuck on tutorial island for ~1 week; didn’t know how to turn “run” on.<br>
Now am lv128[/quote]</p>
<p>Didn’t you every quit? or left for couple of months?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 12:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@pure2ownage Pure_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pure2ownage">@pure2ownage</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I was stuck on tutorial island for ~1 week; didn’t know how to turn “run” on.<br>
Now am lv128</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My RuneScape history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@spy_man47 spy man47]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/spy_man47">@spy_man47</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I started playing RuneScape at 2006</p>
<p>When I was 12, was a complete fool… Didn’t even could pass the tutorial, my friends did it for me…</p>
<p>I trained an account to level almost 54 (Not with bot didn’t knew there were!), and then I got bored… Quited it for 2 months, then one of my friends offered me a level 68 account with full rune and full quests (Exept shield of arav), I say sure…</p>
<p>Then I play on the account, train it to level 92 - 95, Got bored… quited again…</p>
<p>I’ve never been a member except for this year (2010), One of my friends made me a member…</p>
<p>Now I got cool states…and I play on that 68 that my friend gave me…</p>
<p>I got 120 quest points… 1462 Total level, 1 skillcape (Firemaking)</p>
<p>Here is more about me, check this picture :</p>
<p><img src="http://www.draynor.net/stat/wilderness/male/hd_firemaking_cape_emote/XZ_Bashar_XZ.png" alt width="320" height="125"></p>
<p>Why don’t you tell us something about you’rself on RuneScape?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-349810-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/my-runescape-history/349810.rss">My RuneScape history</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
