<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026</link>
    <description>Hey everyone. I&#39;m trying to use a new client for my source, the FormationX v3 client. I&#39;ve got a few things that I need fixing, and a few things that I&#39;m not really sure as to how to do, and I&#39;m willing to pay if you can get them working right.

[B]I&#39;m posting this in the server section as most of these issues are things that need to be added server-sided![/B]



HitSplats/HP Bar - Hit splats aren&#39;t showing and the HP bars aren&#39;t changing when you attack something, or someone.

Wilderness Ditch - The wild starts to far up, and the ditch does have an option to let you cross it.

New Items - I can&#39;t spawn or wield any new items over 16000. Any store items that are over 16000 are labeled as &quot;Unarmed&quot; when I click Value.

Full Screen - The full screen icon goes where the option button was, so I can&#39;t open it to change my details. I would like there to be a new tab (where the music tab should go), that lets you edit your options.

Icon Issues - When I ::yell, or use a clan chat, I have a messed up donator icon next to my name instead of the gold mod crown that I had it displaying before.

Banking - You can&#39;t use the bank booths. I would also like the Deposit Carried Items tab, and search tabs to work if possible.

Equipment Tab - Two issues. First, the Experience lock button is where the donation button was. When I click it, it just freezes, so I need to make it work as the experience lock again. Second, there&#39;s a Items on Death button, where the old experience lock was. I need it to show the items on death. Last, I need a button to show donator options. It would be cool if a new tab could be made.

NPC Animations - Some animations on the new NPC&#39;s are messed up. I just want to know how to change them, and how to find the right animations for the certain NPCs.

NpcConstants.cfg - It doesn&#39;t work correctly. I&#39;m assuming that the NpcConstants is the things that a certain NPC always drops. If I&#39;m right, then it doesn&#39;t work correctly. My dragons don&#39;t drop bones. Nothing drops bones, or any other item that they should drop 100% of the time.


I know this is a good amount of work, so I&#39;m willing to pay a good amount for it. Send me a message, or post on here if you want to try. 

I&#39;m NOT going first! I&#39;ll send you the source and client. After everything is done, you can show me, and a middle man, on teamviewer. If everything is okay, then I&#39;ll send the money to the middle man, and you&#39;ll send the source and client to him. He&#39;ll send you the money, and me the source and client. Then we live out our lives as happy people. :)


Sincerely, 
TimeBroken</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 01:19:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TimeBroken TimeBroken]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/timebroken">@TimeBroken</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“mrdrzj, post:4, topic:409026”]what i can help u with:<br>
the hitmarks and hp bar dont appear because the source is not configured to the formationx v3 client to show that stuff.<br>
example:<br>
Im using torvapkz or any other source that hasnt fading hitmarks or whatever<br>
I start using formationx client, hitmarks wont appear.<br>
so you should just use formationx source, or configure that stuff which idk how to.[/quote]</p>
<p>I know the issue. I’m trying to get it fixed. I’m not going to switch sources because of the hit marks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 01:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-409026-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026.rss">[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mrdrzj mrdrzj]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mrdrzj">@mrdrzj</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what i can help u with:<br>
the hitmarks and hp bar dont appear because the source is not configured to the formationx v3 client to show that stuff.<br>
example:<br>
Im using torvapkz or any other source that hasnt fading hitmarks or whatever<br>
I start using formationx client, hitmarks wont appear.<br>
so you should just use formationx source, or configure that stuff which idk how to.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 01:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-409026-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026.rss">[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TimeBroken TimeBroken]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/timebroken">@TimeBroken</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="2" data-topic="409026">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/k1ng0frs/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> k1ng0frs:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you know people not gonna answer all these’s questions you can around on R-S</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m paying for these things to be done, so I figure greed is enough of a motivation to help me out.<br>
I’ve posted this on R-S, RL, and here on Mopar.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 01:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-409026-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026.rss">[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@k1ng0frs k1ng0frs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/k1ng0frs">@k1ng0frs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you know people not gonna answer all these’s questions you can around on R-S</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 01:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-409026-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026.rss">[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TimeBroken TimeBroken]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/timebroken">@TimeBroken</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey everyone. I’m trying to use a new client for my source, the FormationX v3 client. I’ve got a few things that I need fixing, and a few things that I’m not really sure as to how to do, and I’m willing to pay if you can get them working right.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">I’m posting this in the server section as most of these issues are things that need to be added server-sided!</span></p>
<p>HitSplats/HP Bar - Hit splats aren’t showing and the HP bars aren’t changing when you attack something, or someone.</p>
<p>Wilderness Ditch - The wild starts to far up, and the ditch does have an option to let you cross it.</p>
<p>New Items - I can’t spawn or wield any new items over 16000. Any store items that are over 16000 are labeled as “Unarmed” when I click Value.</p>
<p>Full Screen - The full screen icon goes where the option button was, so I can’t open it to change my details. I would like there to be a new tab (where the music tab should go), that lets you edit your options.</p>
<p>Icon Issues - When I ::yell, or use a clan chat, I have a messed up donator icon next to my name instead of the gold mod crown that I had it displaying before.</p>
<p>Banking - You can’t use the bank booths. I would also like the Deposit Carried Items tab, and search tabs to work if possible.</p>
<p>Equipment Tab - Two issues. First, the Experience lock button is where the donation button was. When I click it, it just freezes, so I need to make it work as the experience lock again. Second, there’s a Items on Death button, where the old experience lock was. I need it to show the items on death. Last, I need a button to show donator options. It would be cool if a new tab could be made.</p>
<p>NPC Animations - Some animations on the new NPC’s are messed up. I just want to know how to change them, and how to find the right animations for the certain NPCs.</p>
<p>NpcConstants.cfg - It doesn’t work correctly. I’m assuming that the NpcConstants is the things that a certain NPC always drops. If I’m right, then it doesn’t work correctly. My dragons don’t drop bones. Nothing drops bones, or any other item that they should drop 100% of the time.</p>
<p>I know this is a good amount of work, so I’m willing to pay a good amount for it. Send me a message, or post on here if you want to try.</p>
<p>I’m NOT going first! I’ll send you the source and client. After everything is done, you can show me, and a middle man, on teamviewer. If everything is okay, then I’ll send the money to the middle man, and you’ll send the source and client to him. He’ll send you the money, and me the source and client. Then we live out our lives as happy people. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Sincerely,<br>
TimeBroken</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 00:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-409026-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/pi-multiple-bugs-and-things-i-need-help-with-paying/409026.rss">[PI] Multiple Bugs and Things I need help with! [Paying]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
