<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343</link>
    <description>Hi, I just wanted your opinion on an api that I&#39;m designing for work. 

What we&#39;re working on is a networking lib that we can use internally that we know inside out. I know there are exisiting librarys out there however company wants to have their own library. 

The goal is to have an api that is scalable and multithreaded. Multithreading seems to be a heavy topic for us atm and we don&#39;t want to keep things single threaded (although there will be support for this)

Some snippets from a report that somebody did: 
&lt;blockquote&gt;Networky is a Java networking library based of NIO.2. It is a solution to creating multithreaded networks. Everything is handled asynchronously, we try to reduce waiting time for operations to complete as much as possible. Networky does its best to remove the need for queuing (or at least lessen it) by running tasks in parallel.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;A traditional system would only have one thread to listen connections. This is fine however introduces a long queuing system. Imagine waiting in line to buy tickets for the cinema to watch a new movie that has come out. The line is long and there is only 1 person serving at the checkouts. What Networky is trying to achieve is to reduce the wait time for clients so that they can quickly be processed and handled. 

Now the Handlers, if you think of all the people in the cinema watching a movie, they all (logically, not scientifically) receive data at the same time. As Networky is still in very early development, feel free to contribute your thoughts to this. Creating a new Handler for every Channel seems very resourceful. The HandlerWorker in the above image purpose is to show a ConnectionHandler. This ConnectionHandler would deal with channelOpen, channelClose, channelRead, channelWrite and so forth. Small applications may find it hard to deal with a massive number of Handlers. Just like the Listeners, the Handlers will try to process as many people as it can at once and reduce the queue time by as much as possible.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Yes it&#39;s garbage. 

They want to have multiple worker threads that handle listening and handling. 

The Moparscape community (while still under mitb :p) are pro vets and I&#39;m sure you guys can give me all your opinions on this.
What do you think about the concept? Any possible design ideas? Help me!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 14:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Programming</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_nova1 _nova]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_nova1">@_nova1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Tree, post:27, topic:555343”][quote author=Yz85Racer link=topic=674535.msg4508507#msg4508507 date=1463194564]<br>
In my short lived thus far career as a professional software engineer, here’s my honest advice - shut up and just do what your superiors tell you. Use whatever the fudge libraries they decide to use, but let them decide.<br>
[/quote][/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 14:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Tree Tree]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tree">@Tree</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="26" data-topic="555343">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/yz85racer/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Yz85Racer:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In my short lived thus far career as a professional software engineer, here’s my honest advice - shut up and just do what your superiors tell you. Use whatever the fudge libraries they decide to use, but let them decide.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Yz85Racer Yz85Racer]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yz85racer">@Yz85Racer</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In my short lived thus far career as a professional software engineer, here’s my honest advice - shut up and just do what your superiors tell you. Use whatever the fuck libraries they decide to use, but let them decide.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 02:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So what did you want from us? Validation? If things aren’t up for discussion then that’s fine, but why create a discussion?</p>
<p>Developers do have pet peeves, sure. A sane business won’t bin something because of pet peeves though. Instead, where is someone to tell these developers to cop onto themselves and deal with it?</p>
<p>Anyway, whatever works. If your business can tolerate the cost of developing, testing and supporting a component instead of buying one off the shelf or using an open-source one then that’s fine.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 12:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i don’t get what this topic is about. you’re proposing a solution to a problem, you wont tell us clearly what the problem is you’re trying to solve, and you don’t want to hear our feedback. what exactly do you want to discuss?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 11:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@my-swagger my-swagger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/my-swagger">@my-swagger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s not about the lowest layer, that is already optimum. The system could be the only bottle neck right now hence we want to be able to handle clients, as many as possible at the same time.</p>
<p>The reason we don’t fork netty directly is because <span class="bbcode-i">some </span>of us don’t like a lot of how things are done. This is natural to some developers to have pet peeves. The most we’ll do is reference netty or even use some of it’s features.</p>
<p>Try not to think of the deeper issue here. Physical layer, programming language of choice etc etc is not up for discussion.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 10:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Death_Style Death Style]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/death_style">@Death_Style</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="19" data-topic="555343">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/_nova/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> _nova:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>indian, engineers.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>nice meme</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 04:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’m not sure I understand what you want. At the lowest level (the physical cable running between the server and your switch) the network card is going to be acting in a manner that could be seen as ‘single-threaded’.<br>
Specifically, it’s going to be dispatching a series of IP packets in a spray-and-pray fashion, and the higher level (TCP) will take care of detecting loss and re-dispatch.</p>
<p>The key indicators of performance you guys should be looking at are throughput (i.e., MB/s sent over the network card) and latency (average and max - the max latency is where Java enters into a GC cycle and underperforms). These need to be measured by a third-party widget (not the JVM you’re running your code on).</p>
<p>Going back to real-time systems, you’ll also want to measure jitter. That’s essentially deviation from the average (i.e., the difference between your min/max and your average latency above).</p>
<hr>
<p>In the worst case, perhaps you guys should fork Netty and make the changes there, not that I understand the change particularly well. At least then you’ll have a reasonable starting point instead of building it from scratch (know that thousands of hours have gone into Netty - that’s hundreds of thousands of dollars in salaries for a business).</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 21:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@my-swagger my-swagger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/my-swagger">@my-swagger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lothy,</p>
<p>Netty has bad scaling when it comes to multi-threading. Here’s an example; when multi-threading to multiple channels. It’s also not multi-threaded in the aspect that I want. Multi-threading to one channel? I except to be able to perform io to multiple connections in parallel. Netty does this in a linear fashion afaik on the default implementation. The throughput does not scale (from a client’s perspective). Look at their effective performance.</p>
<p>Regards to speed, in some situtations a reponse is needed as quick as possible. Netty will not supply this. In fact we desperately need this.</p>
<p>There are about 100ish sites in the UK that we need a fast strong connection with (disregarding connection speed, this is a different topic). Heres an actual thing we can all agree on; a payment terminal.</p>
<p>Also there is a lot of inspiration from Erlangs OTP (not in multi-threading or parallel).</p>
<p>Next time I go to work, I’ll get all the information you’ll need.</p>
<p>Just a note; Netty is brilliant, in no way am I saying it’s a piple of crap. We actually used <a href="http://vertx.io/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://vertx.io/</a> - based off netty before.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="19" data-topic="555343">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/_nova/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> _nova:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Yeah buying a library that can handle real time networking is probably a lot cheaper from a business perspective unless you have VERY efficient engineers. I mean 10-30 years experience of software engineering, indian, engineers.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m just a junior developer. These guys are very old; not indian though <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 16:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_nova1 _nova]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_nova1">@_nova1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah buying a library that can handle real time networking is probably a lot cheaper from a business perspective unless you have VERY efficient engineers. I mean 10-30 years experience of software engineering, indian, engineers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 15:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lothy Lothy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lothy">@lothy</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In what way is Netty not multi-threaded / concurrent / parallelised? You specify one thread group (i.e., a pool with one or more threads) specifically for accepting connections, and one thread group for all work that occurs after initial connection acceptance.<br>
There’s no logical limit on the thread count in these thread groups (although you’ll want to discover the ideal through profiling).</p>
<p>Honestly, the only bad thing about Netty that I’ve heard of is the undue memory pressure it places on the garbage collector. This makes it potentially unsuitable for real-time networking applications (such as FIX servers) and anything else that demands low-latency/real-time responsiveness due to producing a non-zero amount of garbage (therefore resulting in intermittent execution of the garbage collector).</p>
<p>If you or your colleagues can’t make heads or tails of what I’ve just said, or you’re not working on something that demands real-time/low-latency response within hard SLAs, then you’re making a bad decision from a business perspective by choosing to build rather than ‘buy’ (Netty is free, I know) on this occasion.</p>
<p>Just remember that IT as a value stream has no value until whatever you’re making is in production. And not a moment sooner.</p>
<p>EDIT: As an addendum, if you truly need that low-latency networking capability within Java software then consider the CoralBlocks CoralReactor software. Here’s a link comparing it to Netty: <a href="http://www.coralblocks.com/index.php/2014/04/coralreactor-vs-netty-performance-comparison/" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.coralblocks.com/index.php/2014/04/coralreactor-vs-netty-performance-comparison/</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 12:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_nova1 _nova]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_nova1">@_nova1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>then go to another forum and watch them tell you the same thing<br>
and the next<br>
and the next</p>
<p>the reasons you have aren’t convincing at all and aren’t backed by evidence or fact.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 11:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@my-swagger my-swagger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/my-swagger">@my-swagger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="15" data-topic="555343">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/_nova/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> _nova:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>theyd all say the same thing</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Id appreciate an open mind set.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 10:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_nova1 _nova]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_nova1">@_nova1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>theyd all say the same thing</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 21:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“my-swagger, post:13, topic:555343”][quote author=Justin Bieber link=topic=674535.msg4508179#msg4508179 date=1462729398]<br>
sorry mate, I thought you were replying to my question about what problem they’re trying to solve</p>
<p>dunno what the salty comment about moparscape is all about, a lot of people here have solid cs degrees and good jobs<br>
[/quote]<br>
Hopefully they will then comment![/quote]nice</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 20:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@my-swagger my-swagger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/my-swagger">@my-swagger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Justin Bieber, post:12, topic:555343”]sorry mate, I thought you were replying to my question about what problem they’re trying to solve</p>
<p>dunno what the salty comment about moparscape is all about, a lot of people here have solid cs degrees and good jobs[/quote]<br>
Hopefully they will then comment!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>sorry mate, I thought you were replying to my question about what problem they’re trying to solve</p>
<p>dunno what the salty comment about moparscape is all about, a lot of people here have solid cs degrees and good jobs</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 17:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@my-swagger my-swagger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/my-swagger">@my-swagger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="555343">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/_nova/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> _nova:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Competent doesn’t mean intelligent</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well they’re not programmers that have a degree from moparscape</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="10" data-topic="555343">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Justin Bieber:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>parallelism isn’t a problem it’s a solution to a problem</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That’s what I said lol</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/11</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>parallelism isn’t a problem it’s a solution to a problem</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/10</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 17:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_nova1 _nova]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_nova1">@_nova1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Competent doesn’t mean intelligent</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/9</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 17:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@my-swagger my-swagger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/my-swagger">@my-swagger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Justin Bieber, post:6, topic:555343”]what problem are they actually trying to solve with this? is it just a learning exercise?</p>
<p>i hate it when people write their own shit libraries at work because they think they can do better than everyone else, then they leave and we’re all stuck using some unmaintainable piece of wank for the next eternity. just because they’ve been in the game longer doesn’t mean they know what they’re doing - they’re just better at bullshitting[/quote]<br>
The idea is that parallelism and multithreading the the way forward.<br>
I’m not sure what environment you’re based around but mostly everybody here are very competent programmers.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 16:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_nova1 _nova]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_nova1">@_nova1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Justin Bieber, post:6, topic:555343”]what problem are they actually trying to solve with this? is it just a learning exercise?</p>
<p>i hate it when people write their own shit libraries at work because they think they can do better than everyone else, then they leave and we’re all stuck using some unmaintainable piece of wank for the next eternity. just because they’ve been in the game longer doesn’t mean they know what they’re doing - they’re just better at bullshitting[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xx_matty_xx Justin Bieber]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xx_matty_xx">@xx_matty_xx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>what problem are they actually trying to solve with this? is it just a learning exercise?</p>
<p>i hate it when people write their own shit libraries at work because they think they can do better than everyone else, then they leave and we’re all stuck using some unmaintainable piece of wank for the next eternity. just because they’ve been in the game longer doesn’t mean they know what they’re doing - they’re just better at bullshitting</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 20:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@my-swagger my-swagger]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/my-swagger">@my-swagger</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“penguinimp, post:4, topic:555343”]I’d be interested in what you find</p>
<p>Are you guys going to make this library public?[/quote]<br>
Who knows, I don’t see why not though. A guy made a POC and it’s flipping user friendly as fudge!<br>
The worry is how scalable it will actually be. My attempt (for fun) did not go so well lol</p>
<p>Seems very complicated.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 17:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@penguinimp penguinimp]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/penguinimp">@penguinimp</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I’d be interested in what you find</p>
<p>Are you guys going to make this library public?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 17:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-555343-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/java-multithreaded-network-api-discussion/555343.rss">Java Multithreaded Network API (discussion)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
