<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>FFS.. It just won&#39;t work!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ffs-it-just-wont-work/217318</link>
    <description>OKay, well I&#39;ve got my source, got my no-ip, got my portforwarding done, and it STILL WILL NOT WORK.

I&#39;ve read the guide under the tut section, a nice and well thought out one, and it helped A LOT. But I still am having problems. I can only loggin to my server using LocalHost, not the IP.

I have no clue what&#39;s wrong. I&#39;m thinking it&#39;s the no-ip though.. The No-Ip is not connected at all. All i did was make my no-ip, download it, and finished. I think i might be missing somthing connecting the no-ip to the source or somthing..

IDK if that&#39;s the reason though, that&#39;s just what I thought.

Can anyone help ? 

Thanks[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 03, 2008, 07:16:25 PM[/size][hr]Anyone?

If I could, I would rep++</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 05:46:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ffs-it-just-wont-work/217318.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>FFS.. It just won&#39;t work!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Fun_4_me_not_u Fun 4 me not u]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/fun_4_me_not_u">@Fun_4_me_not_u</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>OKay, well I’ve got my source, got my no-ip, got my portforwarding done, and it STILL WILL NOT WORK.</p>
<p>I’ve read the guide under the tut section, a nice and well thought out one, and it helped A LOT. But I still am having problems. I can only loggin to my server using LocalHost, not the IP.</p>
<p>I have no clue what’s wrong. I’m thinking it’s the no-ip though… The No-Ip is not connected at all. All i did was make my no-ip, download it, and finished. I think i might be missing somthing connecting the no-ip to the source or somthing…</p>
<p>IDK if that’s the reason though, that’s just what I thought.</p>
<p>Can anyone help ?</p>
<p>Thanks[br][br][size=1]Posted on: July 03, 2008, 07:16:25 PM[/size][hr]Anyone?</p>
<p>If I could, I would rep++</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ffs-it-just-wont-work/217318/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ffs-it-just-wont-work/217318/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 05:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-217318-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/ffs-it-just-wont-work/217318.rss">FFS.. It just won&#39;t work!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
