<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New Fagex Owner</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873</link>
    <description>[code]Hey guys, i&#39;ll try to make this as short as possible but i&#39;m not making any promises.I&#39;ll try to cover as many grey spots as possible so hang in there. I&#39;ll start by introducing myself. 

Introduction: 
My name is Steph, I&#39;m 18 years old and I&#39;m a volunteer FireFighter. I&#39;m currently still in high school but going to Seneca College to become a career FireFighter in september. I have 2 parents (go figure) and a younger sister. I would also like to add that i&#39;m not from NY. I&#39;m from Canada Ontario for all the people wondering . 

Why I purchased fagex.net: 
The reasons why I purchased fagex was because I know this site has great potential and I was hoping to make this place a nice place to come and chill. I hope I can do a good job leading and working with others to realise this goal. 

Current Staff: 
I&#39;m planning on keeping ALL current staff.You have nothing to worry about there. I&#39;m hoping you guys will help me maintain the forum like you helped Juan. 

DDos Attacks: 
I was made aware that there was many issues with ddos attacks previously. I don&#39;t who or why you guys where doing this, but I&#39;m hoping this is all over. I personally have nothing against any other website and i&#39;m hoping it&#39;s the same with you all. If you have any issues, feel free to contact me and I will do my best to resolve them. 

Future Plans: 

Right now, I am going to spend alot of time fixing up the forum to my liking. Rest assured nothing much will change just minor things. I have spoken briefly with Humble and she seems to have many updates to the site that, for the most part, I have no objection to. 

Ads: 
It seems to be bugging alot of people so I want to clear this up. I will NEVER put in POP UP adds. I do ask you tho, that for the ads we do have to maby, if you like click it once a day. This money is ALL going to pre-pay the hosting and NOTHING else. I will also sell my RS2GP to be able to pre-pay the site and guarentee many months of up time. 

Well that&#39;s it for now. If you have any questions, feel free to post the here or PM me. I&#39;m also planning to start a contest soon to start bringing back people to fagex. 

Enjoy, 
FireFly 

EDIT:: I thought it was really important to mention, that I do not expect your respect any time soon. I know that people are not happy with this decision and I totally respect that. A famous quote my dad always tells me is &quot;Respect is not given, it is earned.&quot; So do what you feel is right...[/code]

i hope he does a good job</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 13:49:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New Fagex Owner</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>meh, another rs cheating forum gone downhill.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 13:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2873-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873.rss">New Fagex Owner</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Fagex Owner</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yuhaiyang1 yuhaiyang1]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yuhaiyang1">@yuhaiyang1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>its a guy, fool lol <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> and i think he will do a good job</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 12:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2873-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873.rss">New Fagex Owner</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Fagex Owner</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@thiefmn6092 thiefmn6092]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/thiefmn6092">@thiefmn6092</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-post="3" data-topic="2873">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/xerozcheez/40/5_8504b32b4165840149d2c3dd52eb0686.png" class="avatar"> xerozcheez:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Lol it’s a girl so why do you say “he does a good job”? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It’s a guy</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 12:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2873-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873.rss">New Fagex Owner</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Fagex Owner</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@xerozcheez xerozcheez]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xerozcheez">@xerozcheez</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol it’s a girl so why do you say “he does a good job”? <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 12:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2873-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873.rss">New Fagex Owner</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Fagex Owner</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yna_ajhear5 yna_ajhear5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yna_ajhear5">@yna_ajhear5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Yeah, the 20m competition is a good idea.</p>
<blockquote>Ok well since fagex has been down for awhile, I thought I would host a competition to get members back into fagex. The competition is VERY simple. 
<p>Ok people don’t seem to understand. I’ll try to explain it better. You have to make 20 post from here to thursday. Once you make your 20 post you are eligable to win 5M rs2 GP for that week. On friday, I will take everybody who made their 20 posts and draw 1 person for that week to win the 5M. It will be like that for the next 4 weeks.</p>
<p>Not hard eh guys? So go out there and post. Competition starts tommorow(Monday, May 15th).</p>
<p>UPDATE: Whoever can put 2.0 at the end of <a href="http://fagex.net" rel="nofollow noopener">fagex.net</a> on the banner, will receive some GP aswell (500k). It has to be the same text tho.<br>
Good luck to all! Please remember, NO SPAM WILL COUNT!</p>
<p>FireFly</p>
<p>Thank you BlueFlames for donating 10M for this competition.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I just hope Fagex stays up for more than a week at a time. :-/</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 12:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2873-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873.rss">New Fagex Owner</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>New Fagex Owner</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kuiren2 Kuiren]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kuiren2">@kuiren2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[code]Hey guys, i’ll try to make this as short as possible but i’m not making any promises.I’ll try to cover as many grey spots as possible so hang in there. I’ll start by introducing myself.</p>
<p>Introduction:<br>
My name is Steph, I’m 18 years old and I’m a volunteer FireFighter. I’m currently still in high school but going to Seneca College to become a career FireFighter in september. I have 2 parents (go figure) and a younger sister. I would also like to add that i’m not from NY. I’m from Canada Ontario for all the people wondering .</p>
<p>Why I purchased <a href="http://fagex.net" rel="nofollow noopener">fagex.net</a>:<br>
The reasons why I purchased fagex was because I know this site has great potential and I was hoping to make this place a nice place to come and chill. I hope I can do a good job leading and working with others to realise this goal.</p>
<p>Current Staff:<br>
I’m planning on keeping ALL current staff.You have nothing to worry about there. I’m hoping you guys will help me maintain the forum like you helped Juan.</p>
<p>DDos Attacks:<br>
I was made aware that there was many issues with ddos attacks previously. I don’t who or why you guys where doing this, but I’m hoping this is all over. I personally have nothing against any other website and i’m hoping it’s the same with you all. If you have any issues, feel free to contact me and I will do my best to resolve them.</p>
<p>Future Plans:</p>
<p>Right now, I am going to spend alot of time fixing up the forum to my liking. Rest assured nothing much will change just minor things. I have spoken briefly with Humble and she seems to have many updates to the site that, for the most part, I have no objection to.</p>
<p>Ads:<br>
It seems to be bugging alot of people so I want to clear this up. I will NEVER put in POP UP adds. I do ask you tho, that for the ads we do have to maby, if you like click it once a day. This money is ALL going to pre-pay the hosting and NOTHING else. I will also sell my RS2GP to be able to pre-pay the site and guarentee many months of up time.</p>
<p>Well that’s it for now. If you have any questions, feel free to post the here or PM me. I’m also planning to start a contest soon to start bringing back people to fagex.</p>
<p>Enjoy,<br>
FireFly</p>
<p>EDIT:: I thought it was really important to mention, that I do not expect your respect any time soon. I know that people are not happy with this decision and I totally respect that. A famous quote my dad always tells me is “Respect is not given, it is earned.” So do what you feel is right…[/code]</p>
<p>i hope he does a good job</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 08:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-2873-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/new-fagex-owner/2873.rss">New Fagex Owner</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
