<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134</link>
    <description>Would it be acceptable to create a thread that has all the general Runescape information (like login protocol stuff, packet documentation, [url=http://www.moparisthebest.com/smf/index.php/topic,498172.msg3643002.html#msg3643002]this[/url] new tutorial on map regions and similar things [things that general server hosters may not use, but are cool documentations to have]) into one place and sticky it? It&#39;s great information to further RSPS dev, but it gets lost in the tidal wave of command tutorials and custom minigames.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 04:06:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Community Inside Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="17" data-topic="401134">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/moparisthebest/40/30_1.png" class="avatar"> Moparisthebest:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It is a new base to be used by the community, but blake/boomer has the option to actually host it and become the ‘official server of <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a>’.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Is this public knowledge or is it meant to be kept within this board? Why don’t you host the server instead?</p>
<p>The core can be continually developed by the vets etc and plugins by anyone.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/52</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 04:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mod_taharok Taharok]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mod_taharok">@mod_taharok</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The contract is a bit vague. It states two factors:</p>
<ol>
<li>The continuity of hosting at the domain <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a>
</li>
<li>The server the developer<span class="bbcode-b">s</span> host will become the sponsored server of <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a>
</li>
</ol>
<p>The initial interpretation almost makes you think that both people must be involved in the process of hosting it, and thereby creating the official server. Nevertheless, the single factor of “will become” implies that it is a single instance. It basically says the official server will be made at an instance where both developers are hosting the server (which is true, as one developer represents the domain and the other, the host). The contract refers both to hosting and to the domain, therefore to both developers. Nevertheless, the reference is valid so long as the server is not the official server of moparscape. After it has become thus, then only the second installment, being the conditions of the server being maintained by <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a> and the sponsored server page by <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a>, is valid.</p>
<p>IANAL, but the contract (at least that portion), basically says you two only need to work together until the server is recognized by mopar as being the official server. Thereafter, the special spot for the server status page only exists, by contract, through the <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a> domain. My interpretation is rather simple. If mopar considers Osiris to be the official server, which from what I’ve seen he does, then by all means boomer is correct, but so is blake. Both of you are right on the button regarding <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a>. The server must be <span class="bbcode-b">hosted</span> through that <span class="bbcode-b">domain</span>. So, indeed, at this point in the contract, blake holds all the power if he owns the domain.</p>
<p>You know, I’m friends with both of you, and I don’t want to take sides. To be honest, I don’t like how this ended up at all. But honestly, contracts are designed to protect the constituents. As david said, they are there to prevent one of you from screwing over the other. Nevertheless, blake has that power here (a limitation in the contract, imo), but he is refusing to use it. As for anything you both agreed to outside of this contract, it is complete moot. All that matters is this contract, everything else is not legally binding and therefore irrelevant. Any lawyer would tell you the same. Intentions really don’t matter when there is a legally binding contract to dictate the way things ought to be.</p>
<p>So seriously, shit happens. Just get over it and work together, please. This community needs something good, and I really don’t want to see mopar jacked out of $7,000. He went out of his way to pay you a large portion of his profits from the sponsored server page so you could be apart of the rebirth of one of the most prestigious communities in the scene. Ages ago, people would have found the participation alone enough of a payment. Stop considering this a job and consider it a contribution. I don’t care how difficult it is to work together, just do it. You’re both stuck together until this is over, so you might as well do what you need to do.</p>
<p>On a side note: the contract has nothing to do with profits earned by enkrona. As blake well knows, boomer can completely choose to keep profits earned by the enkrona server for himself, even though blake is contracted to the enkrona server. Nevertheless, boomer knows blake’s power in owning the domain. It’s icky, but it’s reality. What happens on <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a> is again moot to the contract itself, so keep it there. Just get together to finish the server so moparscape doesn’t completely suck for once, then deal with the petty profit details on your own time (not intending to be rude at all).</p>
<p>Side side note: sorry for another obnoxiously long post. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/51</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 23:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="49" data-topic="401134">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/blakeman8192/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> blakeman8192:</div>
<blockquote>
<p><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3taEuL4EHAg" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3taEuL4EHAg</a></p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The domain has nothing to do with it.<br>
All it mentions is the current domain at which the time the server was hosted.<br>
The important part is the server.</p>
<p>We can discuss with MITB when he gets back good sir.</p>
<p>But anyways, thanks for your critique on the contract, I forgot you were a lawyer.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/50</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 01:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s upsetting that I <span class="bbcode-i">still</span> must post to show everyone how wrong you are.<br>
I’m about to publish the contract itself so everyone can see how you are manipulating it and lying.</p>
<p>Boomer, you can whine all you want.  At the end of the day, you signed a legal fucking contract.<br>
You’re bound to it.  And it states (which MITB agrees with) that we both must be on the server project.</p>
<p>[quote=“boomer216, post:42, topic:401134”][quote author=Davidi2 link=topic=498194.msg3699628#msg3699628 date=1312666070]<br>
Again, it says ‘currently’, which means it’s subject to change.</p>
<p>Did you pay him for the source, or just to stop developing/leave Enkrona? Because that wouldn’t stop him from hosting his own server, and then again, because the contract specifies BOTH of you, he’d have just as much rights to the spot as you.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>I am paying our friend who developed some parts for Enkrona, and by doing that Blake agreed to give me full ownership to the server.</p>
<p>And I’m fine if we simply have 2 different “official” slots on the sponsored server page.<br>
Assuming both the servers are developed from osiris, as dictated in the contract.<br>
As the whole point is to inspire developers to use osiris.[/quote]</p>
<p>I <span class="bbcode-i">never</span> fucking agreed to give you ownership of our server.  What the hell are you talking about?  Stop trying to steal our whole project from me.  You know that I worked my ass off writing the core from scratch while you were eating BBQ chips.  Yes you did content, but I did the core.  And that was the original agreement from the get-go.  I still own equal copyright as well.</p>
<blockquote>The Osiris emulator is copyright (C) 2010-2011 Blake Beaupain, Garrett Woodard, and Travis Burtrum.</blockquote>
<p>[quote=“boomer216, post:40, topic:401134”][quote author=Davidi2 link=topic=498194.msg3699609#msg3699609 date=1312665645]<br>
No, you don’t owner the server you made together. Even if we’re saying he doesn’t need to sign anything to officially leave, that doesn’t give you <span class="bbcode-b">any</span> single ownership rights unless he specifically said he was giving his ownership to you. If I make a boat with someone, and then leave it in the marina without using it, does it make it solely the other persons property? He let you keep the hosted server, but I see no reason why, if he takes the source you guys made together (even if it doesn’t have all the content you have added since he left), and started hosting, why you would have any more rights to the sponsorship than he does.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Because the sponsorship doesn’t refer to either one of us, it refers to the server I hosted.<br>
And he gave up his rights to the server by me paying for him to leave.[/quote]</p>
<p>Um, no, the contract states (and I quote):</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">“The server the developers host using the software (currently at: <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a>) will become the official server of <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a>, and receive a prominent link to their website from the server status page (currently at: <a href="https://www.moparisthebest.com/serverstatus.php">https://www.moparisthebest.com/serverstatus.php</a>), most likely in the form of a ‘Sponsored Server’.  This will continue for as long as <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a> maintains a server status page, or as long as <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a> maintains a server.”</span></p>
<p>Oh look, I can redirect <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a> to a different host and maintain a server of my own based on Osiris.<br>
But instead, I’m willing to work with you for 50/50 of the profits.</p>
<p>That clearly is, however,  specific to the developers (not of Enkrona, but the developers as defined in the Terms section of the contract to be Blake Beaupain and Garrett Woodard) and not the project.  And if it is specific to the project (which it is not), then the only tangible defining factor of the project itself is the domain <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a> which I own.  You are reading the word “host” as a noun (and referring it to the VPS that you pay to host) when in fact it is used as a verb referring to the action of us, the developers, hosting the server.</p>
<p>Like I stated before:</p>
<p>[ul][<em>]If I am right, neither of us can make use of this opportunity unless we work together<br>
[</em>]If you are right, then I can solely make use of this opportunity as according to the contract I own the said project through ownership of <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a>[/ul]</p>
<p>You are purposefully misinterpreting the contract that you signed, and you are attempting obviously to twist the words into a situation that works better for you.  The contract is as it is, and should be interpreted as it is and was when it was signed by the 3 of us.  It is specific to the developers, not the project itself.  And if - as you so claim through misinterpretation - it is specific to the project, then the project is clearly owned by me as the <span class="bbcode-b">only tangible defining factor</span> of the project within the contract is the domain <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a>.</p>
<p>tl;dr you signed a legal contract, deal with the set forth conditions.<br>
I have everything legally in my power to completely exclude you from this, because I myself maintain ownership of the domain.</p>
<p>And I choose not to screw you over with the very contract that you signed because that would make me no better than you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/49</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 23:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-49</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree, this is not the suitable place for the discussion.<br>
When mitb is back from vacation, us three can continue the talk.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/48</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 22:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-48</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Then why is it being discussed here instead of in a private chat between the three of them? They just need to come to an agreement. I’m just saying what I personally would like to see out of it (as it affects everyone here), no matter how trivial or unimportant my opinion is <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/47</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-47</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m.dog311 m.dog311]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m.dog311">@m.dog311</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Considering you know very little to nothing about the contract and what happened between Blake and Boomer, I don’t see how you can really interpret it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/46</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-46</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nobody here is, so it’s all up to interpretation, right? I’m saying how I interpret it. It’s just my [quote=“Davidi2, post:37, topic:401134”]two cents.[/quote]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-45</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m.dog311 m.dog311]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m.dog311">@m.dog311</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>YANAL</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-44</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Wait what? What does that mean (and how would it mean he gave up ownership)?</p>
<p>But two official servers basically ruins the entire point, I think it’s best that you two just come to some sort of agreement (and if so, Blakeman would probably have to give you back any ‘leaving’ money, but I don’t understand how that worked anyway) so that everyone gets something out if it, even if it isn’t exactly what you want. Because as it stands right now, if that was a legally binding contract (which I don’t know), then he still has part ownership rights to the server you’re hosting right now (even if he ‘left’ the development team; kinda how like investors don’t actually do anything as part of the company, they just put something into it then own part of it), AND part ownership rights to the base.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-43</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:41, topic:401134”]Again, it says ‘currently’, which means it’s subject to change.</p>
<p>Did you pay him for the source, or just to stop developing/leave Enkrona? Because that wouldn’t stop him from hosting his own server, and then again, because the contract specifies BOTH of you, he’d have just as much rights to the spot as you.[/quote]</p>
<p>I am paying our friend who developed some parts for Enkrona, and by doing that Blake agreed to give me full ownership to the server.</p>
<p>And I’m fine if we simply have 2 different “official” slots on the sponsored server page.<br>
Assuming both the servers are developed from osiris, as dictated in the contract.<br>
As the whole point is to inspire developers to use osiris.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-42</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Again, it says ‘currently’, which means it’s subject to change.</p>
<p>Did you pay him for the source, or just to stop developing/leave Enkrona? Because that wouldn’t stop him from hosting his own server, and then again, because the contract specifies BOTH of you, he’d have just as much rights to the spot as you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-41</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="39" data-topic="401134">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>No, you don’t owner the server you made together. Even if we’re saying he doesn’t need to sign anything to officially leave, that doesn’t give you <span class="bbcode-b">any</span> single ownership rights unless he specifically said he was giving his ownership to you. If I make a boat with someone, and then leave it in the marina without using it, does it make it solely the other persons property? He let you keep the hosted server, but I see no reason why, if he takes the source you guys made together (even if it doesn’t have all the content you have added since he left), and started hosting, why you would have any more rights to the sponsorship than he does.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because the sponsorship doesn’t refer to either one of us, it refers to the server I hosted.<br>
And he gave up his rights to the server by me paying for him to leave.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-40</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No, you don’t owner the server you made together. Even if we’re saying he doesn’t need to sign anything to officially leave, that doesn’t give you <span class="bbcode-b">any</span> single ownership rights unless he specifically said he was giving his ownership to you. If I make a boat with someone, and then leave it in the marina without using it, does it make it solely the other persons property? He let you keep the hosted server, but I see no reason why, if he takes the source you guys made together (even if it doesn’t have all the content you have added since he left), and started hosting, why you would have any more rights to the sponsorship than he does.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-39</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:37, topic:401134”]You need to make up your mind. If you guys are following a contract system, you need to follow it all the way though, from the creation contract to a termination contract. If you’re not going to say you need contracts, then I don’t see why the first contract would be valid anymore, and thus the ‘official moparscape’ server wouldn’t be linked to you unless Moparisthebest wants it to.</p>
<p>Just my two cents.[/quote]</p>
<p>The contract only specifies the server we developed, hosted at <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a>.<br>
It doesn’t specify any company, or that we have to be together.<br>
I own the server we developed, I own the hosting it. I should own the official server sponsorship. \</p>
<p>Plus we did have a verbal contract for him to leave, I haven’t fulfilled the terms of that agreement yet, but say I do this week, then he has official left, and I should have all rights if we want to argue that he did officially leave.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You need to make up your mind. If you guys are following a contract system, you need to follow it all the way though, from the creation contract to a termination contract. If you’re not going to say you need contracts, then I don’t see why the first contract would be valid anymore, and thus the ‘official moparscape’ server wouldn’t be linked to you unless Moparisthebest wants it to.</p>
<p>Just my two cents.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:35, topic:401134”]Totally agree with you there, but the two circumstances that would happen are:</p>
<ol>
<li>No contract at all is signed, it’s unofficial and any person can do whatever they want</li>
<li>Contracts/job paperwork are signed upon joining, and then there are termination agreements yada yada yada that also need signing for it to be official that someone ‘left’. In that company, a person could give a press conference and say they are leaving, but if they don’t do the paperwork or anything it’s all just words.[/quote]</li>
</ol>
<p>We aren’t a company. We don’t have termination clauses, or employment contracts.<br>
Therefore we don’t need a signing saying he left.</p>
<p>The fact is that I own the hosting that still is pointed to from <a href="http://www.enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">www.enkrona.net</a><br>
The contract still should be in affect to sponsor my server.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Totally agree with you there, but the two circumstances that would happen are:</p>
<ol>
<li>No contract at all is signed, it’s unofficial and any person can do whatever they want</li>
<li>Contracts/job paperwork are signed upon joining, and then there are termination agreements yada yada yada that also need signing for it to be official that someone ‘left’. In that company, a person could give a press conference and say they are leaving, but if they don’t do the paperwork or anything it’s all just words.</li>
</ol>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Davidi2, post:33, topic:401134”]I agree with Blakeman, it isn’t up to ONE person to dictate where your software is hosted. If Blakeman started to host the software as well, what would happen then? That quote says ‘currently at’, which means that it is subject to change if the circumstances change.</p>
<p>As long as the server uses the software that you guys made together, he should be able to rejoin at any time (otherwise one could just kick the other out, right?) and get the same benefits as the other. Unless he countersigned a void for the contract (or it expires), he’s still part of it even if he decides to ‘leave’ or become inactive.</p>
<p>EDIT - Though it seems a bit off that boomer put 4 months more work into the server since blakeman went inactive there, but that wasn’t in the contract.[/quote]</p>
<p>We couldn’t kick each other out, we made an agreement for him to leave.</p>
<p>Oh and it wasn’t just four months. It was about 8 months that I programmed and he didn’t.<br>
The thing is he left the entire project, I had to pay to make him leave.<br>
And now he wants back in? Its complete shit.</p>
<p>The contract says the server we developed and hosted would become the official server.<br>
That server we developed and hosted is still the same, its just he is not part of the company anymore.</p>
<p>If a studio makes a game, and a publisher agrees to publish it, and one of the developers of the studio leaves half way through, there is no reason the publisher should stop publishing it. Nor does that publishing agreement give any right for the strayed developer to join the studio again.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 20:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I agree with Blakeman, it isn’t up to ONE person to dictate where your software is hosted. If Blakeman started to host the software as well, what would happen then? That quote says ‘currently at’, which means that it is subject to change if the circumstances change.</p>
<p>As long as the server uses the software that you guys made together, he should be able to rejoin at any time (otherwise one could just kick the other out, right?) and get the same benefits as the other. Unless he countersigned a void for the contract (or it expires), he’s still part of it even if he decides to ‘leave’ or become inactive.</p>
<p>EDIT - Though it seems a bit off that boomer put 4 months more work into the server since blakeman went inactive there, but that wasn’t in the contract.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 20:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“blakeman8192, post:31, topic:401134”]You <span class="bbcode-b">told me</span> to leave Enkrona bro.<br>
You said you’d pay samurai and you never did.</p>
<p>Remember that you signed the contract dude.<br>
We can all benefit off this, or if you’re going to be stubborn, then none of us can.</p>
<p>MITB isn’t going to disregard the legal contact just so you can benefit from it.<br>
We all signed it, we can all benefit from it.  Or you can be stubborn and greedy and we can do nothing with this opportunity.[/quote]</p>
<p>stubborn and greedy? coming from the kid who left a server with high potential cuz he was lazy.<br>
then when its almost done he runs back and demands 50/50.</p>
<p>yup i’m the stubborn and greedy one.</p>
<p>This is the post where he announced he was leaving Enkrona (<a href="http://enkrona.net/forums/showthread.php?1314-Leaving" rel="nofollow noopener">http://enkrona.net/forums/showthread.php?1314-Leaving</a>)</p>
<blockquote>Hey guys, I'm leaving Enkrona.
<p>Let’s face it, Enkrona doesn’t interest me anymore. I’ve tried to recommit myself to it over the past few months and it’s just not working out. I’m not going to bullshit anyone anymore. I’m tired of arguing with Boomer about working on it and the profit splits. I’m bored with Enkrona. I had a great time with all of you, and I’m sure Boomer will take this project far.</p>
<p>Maybe I’ll be one of your fellow players once Enkrona is out.<br>
Peace.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Notice how he mentions the future of the server? How he’ll be one of the ‘fellow players’.<br>
And now out of the blue he wants back in and a split of the profits.</p>
<p>Moparisthebest, if you want a well developed server that brings much innovation to this dry landscape, AND is built off Osiris, and IS THE SPECIFIC server mentioned in the deal, then we can talk.<br>
But Blake will not be a part of it, as he had already forfeited his spot in the ownership.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 20:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You <span class="bbcode-b">told me</span> to leave Enkrona bro.<br>
You said you’d pay samurai and you never did.</p>
<p>Remember that you signed the contract dude.<br>
We can all benefit off this, or if you’re going to be stubborn, then none of us can.</p>
<p>MITB isn’t going to disregard the legal contact just so you can benefit from it.<br>
We all signed it, we can all benefit from it.  Or you can be stubborn and greedy and we can do nothing with this opportunity.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 20:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@boomer216 boomer216]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/boomer216">@boomer216</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“blakeman8192, post:29, topic:401134”][quote author=boomer216 link=topic=498194.msg3699520#msg3699520 date=1312660725]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>The contract was with Boomer AND Blake, so just because blake left, it could still happen with Boomer.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe you said AND, not OR.<br>
I’m not okay with just Boomer capitalizing off a contract that we both were a part of.</p>
<p>“The server the developers host using the software (currently at: <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a>) will become the official server of <a href="http://moparisthebest.com" rel="nofollow noopener">moparisthebest.com</a>”<br>
It says developers, not one developer.  The developers are defined in the contract as myself and Boomer, not the people working on the Enkrona project.</p>
<p>As far as I’m concerned, if it isn’t a project that Boomer and I are both on, then it cannot proceed as part of the contract.<br>
Yes I left the Enkrona project, but I did not “leave the contract.”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You don’t have to leave the contract.<br>
You left the development team of the server that uses the software (currently hosted at <a href="http://www.enkrona.net" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">www.enkrona.net</a>).</p>
<p>The contract dictates that server is the one that will be the official server of moparscape.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The contract dictates that a server hosted by the <span class="bbcode-b">developers</span> will be the official server of MoparScape.<br>
The contract defines the <span class="bbcode-b">developers</span> as you and me, not the people working on the Enkrona project.</p>
<p>As far as the contract is concerned, we could start a new project using Osiris and it would work.<br>
It is specific to the <span class="bbcode-b">developers</span>, not to Enkrona.</p>
<p>But if you want to specific about the part “currently at: <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a>” then I own <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a> and your point doesn’t hold up there either.  If you really want to try to state that is is specific to the project and not the developers, then the <span class="bbcode-i">only single defining factor</span> of the project is that it is at <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a>.  Which I own.  I’m still willing to work together on this, but you wont let me join the Enkrona project again unless you get 70% of the profits which I’m not okay with.</p>
<p>You look fucking greedy dude.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The domain has nothing to do with the fact. Plus your friend owns it, not you.[/quote]</p>
<p>The domain is the <span class="bbcode-b">only</span> defining factor of the project in the contract.<br>
It has everything to do with the fact.  And I own it, Kramer is just holding on to it for me in his account.<br>
I pay for it.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
The server hosted, which was at the time at <a href="http://enkrona.net" rel="nofollow noopener">enkrona.net</a>, is and was hosted on my VPS.[/quote]<br>
In the contract, host is used as a verb and not a noun.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
You left the project, you forfeited your spot on the development team of the official moparscape server.[/quote]<br>
Nowhere in the contract does it state that “if a developer leaves the Enkrona project, he forfeits his holdings in this contract.”<br>
You are making ridiculous shit up, stick to what the contract states.  By the way, we had a verbal agreement that if I left Enkrona, you would pay $500 to samuraiblood2.  Which you haven’t done in several months.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
Don’t even talk about greedy. You barely programmed after the first 3 days of the project.[/quote]<br>
Let’s see how well your code works without the server core that hosts it (which I made).  A server is not a server if clients cannot connect to it.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
And you wanted 50% of the profits. Even though I programmed about 40k out of the 50k lines.[/quote]<br>
We never said that whoever codes more gets more profit.  We started the project as 50/50, and it never changed.</p>
<p>[quote]<br>
You left the project out of your own choosing, and now you want back in because you want to use the ‘official server spot’ to advertise your friends server that isn’t even using osiris. [/quote]<br>
I left Enkrona, I didn’t leave the contract.</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>And then when you realized that wasn’t going to happen, you’re trying to get back into enkrona now that most of the work is done. And you had the nerve to demand 50/50 from the profits. So don’t even start with “greedy”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m only offering to re-join Enkrona so we can work together and benefit off this contract.</p>
<p>The fact of the matter is as follows:</p>
<p>If I am right - that the contract defines this by the developers and not the project: then we cannot make use of this until we work together on a project based on Osiris.</p>
<p>If you are right - that the contract defines this by the project and not the developers: then the single tangible defining factor (which must be examined) in the contract is by the domain, which is owned by me.  If you are right, then we can either work together on this or I can use this, as I own the domain.[/quote]</p>
<p>i say fuck off you leech. you’ve been nothing but a thorn in my side.<br>
i’ve poured a years worth of work into this project, and I let you have 3500$.<br>
then after we sold it you continued not to develop a single line.<br>
i continued to ask you to help, but you refused saying you were bored with the project and wanted to move on.<br>
then i told you to leave enkrona, and you asked me to buy your “shares” of enkrona.<br>
then we finally came to an agreement for you to leave, and now you want back in cuz you see money.</p>
<p>you have no character and i am done working with you.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 20:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@system system]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/system">@system</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“boomer216, post:27, topic:401134”][quote author=blakeman8192 link=topic=498194.msg3699509#msg3699509 date=1312660060]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>The contract was with Boomer AND Blake, so just because blake left, it could still happen with Boomer.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I believe you said AND, not OR.<br>
I’m not okay with just Boomer capitalizing off a contract that we both were a part of.</p>
<p>“The server the developers host using the software (currently at: <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a>) will become the official server of <a href="http://moparisthebest.com">moparisthebest.com</a>”<br>
It says developers, not one developer.  The developers are defined in the contract as myself and Boomer, not the people working on the Enkrona project.</p>
<p>As far as I’m concerned, if it isn’t a project that Boomer and I are both on, then it cannot proceed as part of the contract.<br>
Yes I left the Enkrona project, but I did not “leave the contract.”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>You don’t have to leave the contract.<br>
You left the development team of the server that uses the software (currently hosted at <a href="http://www.enkrona.net" data-bbcode="true">www.enkrona.net</a>).</p>
<p>The contract dictates that server is the one that will be the official server of moparscape.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The contract dictates that a server hosted by the <span class="bbcode-b">developers</span> will be the official server of MoparScape.<br>
The contract defines the <span class="bbcode-b">developers</span> as you and me, not the people working on the Enkrona project.</p>
<p>As far as the contract is concerned, we could start a new project using Osiris and it would work.<br>
It is specific to the <span class="bbcode-b">developers</span>, not to Enkrona.</p>
<p>But if you want to specific about the part “currently at: <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a>” then I own <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a> and your point doesn’t hold up there either.  If you really want to try to state that is is specific to the project and not the developers, then the <span class="bbcode-i">only single defining factor</span> of the project is that it is at <a href="http://enkrona.net">enkrona.net</a>.  Which I own.  I’m still willing to work together on this, but you wont let me join the Enkrona project again unless you get 70% of the profits which I’m not okay with.</p>
<p>You look fucking greedy dude.<br>
[/quote]<br>
The domain has nothing to do with the fact. Plus your friend owns it, not you.[/quote]</p>
<p>The domain is the <span class="bbcode-b">only</span> defining factor of the project in the contract.<br>
It has everything to do with the fact.  And I own it, Kramer is just holding on to it for me in his account.<br>
I pay for it.</p>
<blockquote>The server hosted, which was at the time at enkrona.net, is and was hosted on my VPS.</blockquote>
In the contract, host is used as a verb and not a noun.
<blockquote>You left the project, you forfeited your spot on the development team of the official moparscape server.</blockquote>
Nowhere in the contract does it state that "if a developer leaves the Enkrona project, he forfeits his holdings in this contract."
You are making ridiculous shit up, stick to what the contract states.  By the way, we had a verbal agreement that if I left Enkrona, you would pay $500 to samuraiblood2.  Which you haven't done in several months.
<blockquote>Don't even talk about greedy. You barely programmed after the first 3 days of the project.</blockquote>
Let's see how well your code works without the server core that hosts it (which I made).  A server is not a server if clients cannot connect to it.
<blockquote>And you wanted 50% of the profits. Even though I programmed about 40k out of the 50k lines.</blockquote>
We never said that whoever codes more gets more profit.  We started the project as 50/50, and it never changed.
<blockquote>You left the project out of your own choosing, and now you want back in because you want to use the 'official server spot' to advertise your friends server that isn't even using osiris.</blockquote>
I left Enkrona, I didn't leave the contract.
<blockquote>And then when you realized that wasn't going to happen, you're trying to get back into enkrona now that most of the work is done. And you had the nerve to demand 50/50 from the profits. So don't even start with "greedy"</blockquote>
I'm only offering to re-join Enkrona so we can work together and benefit off this contract.
<p>The fact of the matter is as follows:</p>
<p>If I am right - that the contract defines this by the developers and not the project: then we cannot make use of this until we work together on a project based on Osiris.</p>
<p>If you are right - that the contract defines this by the project and not the developers: then the single tangible defining factor (which must be examined) in the contract is by the domain, which is owned by me.  If you are right, then we can either work together on this or I can use this, as I own the domain.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 20:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum tutorial idea</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You guys just need to work out something satisfactory to both of you, for my part I’ll follow the contract.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 20:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-401134-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/forum-tutorial-idea/401134.rss">Forum tutorial idea</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
