<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>474- 2007 based adventure</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227</link>
    <description>Hello and welcome to Ardour, we are aiming to be a flawless creation and a leading server for our revision. We encourage professionalism in everything we do and only have the best and most suited staff members. We aim to bring an experience you&#39;ve never had before. Here is some information about us.

[B][I][U][SIZE=6]Forums:[/SIZE][/U][/I][/B]- 
[u][b]Ardour economy:[/b][/u]

This basically means there&#39;s no spawning and any items people obtain will have been earned through PVM or from PKing. This means our items will have value, making everything more fun, giving players something to aim for and of course making it so much better when you finally get that kill for rare items. There are tons of different ways to exchange your items including specific market areas, trading with other players, and even a dedicated section on forums. Being a new server we want to get our economy right the first time. To ensure we achieve this we have made drop rates at a perfect level to maintain item drops for PvMers, but also to give just enough that we&#39;re not flooded with items and massive inflation like you see on most other private servers.


[u][b]The Ardour Experience:[/b][/u]

We want to make Ardours community like no other! We would like to see an active wilderness, active forums, and active PvMing and Clanning communities. We have a perfect clan chat with ranks and all the tools. Here at Ardour, we don’t like to mess around, we want to bring you the players the best possible experience that we can give you. 

Our community gives a warm welcome to all new players, and presents them with many endless activities. We have many events and tournaments in and out of the wilderness that makes this possible. These can be anything from Clan based PKing, to a simple games of Hide and Seek hosted by a staff member. Also try out our many minigames like castle wars, pest control and lots more.


[u][b]The Ardour staff team:[/b][/u]

All of Ardour staff are hand-picked based off applications anyone is free to submit. These applications then get voted on by our staff team and those few that provide the best application will get a chance to prove them selves by starting as a Server Support member. Not only do we make sure we have staff from different time zones to up the chance of one being online at all times. We make sure we have the nicest, most helpful staff available for you. Many of our staff all have previous experience giving you professional support and help when ever you need it. We have a command &quot;::staff&quot;, if you type that ingame it will alert all staff members that you require assistance.

[u][b]Ardour Development &amp; Progress:[/b][/u]

The development team here at Ardour knows quality updates have to come from what the community wants. Once you’ve become a part of the spectacular Ardour community, you’ll notice weekly updates, with content polls that you can vote on to bring what you want and enjoy into the game. Alternatively you can put your ideas forward as suggestions on our forums and have your voice heard and see your ideas implemented if fellow players support you.

[u][b]Ardour Forums:[/b][/u]

We would like the forums to be active with people posting their activities whether it be banter ranging from the PVM section to our clan discussion to even the market place, we want you to notice an uncontrollable amount of topics and giveaways which no other RSPS can provide you. Here at Ardour we would like to be successful in the amount of members we have and will plan to still be growing at a rapid and uncontrollable pace. We also have a dedicated black market section, you will eventually be able to buy Ardour Prem which will simply give you the status and ingame benefits such as slightly increased drop rate.. a list will be created with details, and the money earned will all go into the server. 

Features:
- Flawless skills
- Perfect Duel Arena
- Castle wars
- Quests
- Many Minigames perfected
- Mant bosses
- Friendly Staff and Active staff from all over the world
- Hundreds of PVM and PVP opportunities with countless rewards
- Huge world
- Perfect PKing with flawless switching and perfect hybriding
- Extremely stable
- No items past 2007

Please help us be up there with the best.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 18:49:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>474- 2007 based adventure</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This isn’t a showoff thread. There are no pictures, no code, no anything. This is for posting about cool developments, not advertising your server. Keep that in the advertisements section.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 18:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542227-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227.rss">474- 2007 based adventure</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>474- 2007 based adventure</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@naseem142 naseem142]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/naseem142">@naseem142</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>You cannot post links to your forums , remove it please…</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 17:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542227-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227.rss">474- 2007 based adventure</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>474- 2007 based adventure</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@nathanz nathanz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nathanz">@nathanz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello and welcome to Ardour, we are aiming to be a flawless creation and a leading server for our revision. We encourage professionalism in everything we do and only have the best and most suited staff members. We aim to bring an experience you’ve never had before. Here is some information about us.</p>
<p>[B][I][U][SIZE=6]Forums:[/SIZE][/U][/I][/B]-<br>
<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Ardour economy:</span></span></p>
<p>This basically means there’s no spawning and any items people obtain will have been earned through PVM or from PKing. This means our items will have value, making everything more fun, giving players something to aim for and of course making it so much better when you finally get that kill for rare items. There are tons of different ways to exchange your items including specific market areas, trading with other players, and even a dedicated section on forums. Being a new server we want to get our economy right the first time. To ensure we achieve this we have made drop rates at a perfect level to maintain item drops for PvMers, but also to give just enough that we’re not flooded with items and massive inflation like you see on most other private servers.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">The Ardour Experience:</span></span></p>
<p>We want to make Ardours community like no other! We would like to see an active wilderness, active forums, and active PvMing and Clanning communities. We have a perfect clan chat with ranks and all the tools. Here at Ardour, we don’t like to mess around, we want to bring you the players the best possible experience that we can give you.</p>
<p>Our community gives a warm welcome to all new players, and presents them with many endless activities. We have many events and tournaments in and out of the wilderness that makes this possible. These can be anything from Clan based PKing, to a simple games of Hide and Seek hosted by a staff member. Also try out our many minigames like castle wars, pest control and lots more.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">The Ardour staff team:</span></span></p>
<p>All of Ardour staff are hand-picked based off applications anyone is free to submit. These applications then get voted on by our staff team and those few that provide the best application will get a chance to prove them selves by starting as a Server Support member. Not only do we make sure we have staff from different time zones to up the chance of one being online at all times. We make sure we have the nicest, most helpful staff available for you. Many of our staff all have previous experience giving you professional support and help when ever you need it. We have a command “::staff”, if you type that ingame it will alert all staff members that you require assistance.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Ardour Development &amp; Progress:</span></span></p>
<p>The development team here at Ardour knows quality updates have to come from what the community wants. Once you’ve become a part of the spectacular Ardour community, you’ll notice weekly updates, with content polls that you can vote on to bring what you want and enjoy into the game. Alternatively you can put your ideas forward as suggestions on our forums and have your voice heard and see your ideas implemented if fellow players support you.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">Ardour Forums:</span></span></p>
<p>We would like the forums to be active with people posting their activities whether it be banter ranging from the PVM section to our clan discussion to even the market place, we want you to notice an uncontrollable amount of topics and giveaways which no other RSPS can provide you. Here at Ardour we would like to be successful in the amount of members we have and will plan to still be growing at a rapid and uncontrollable pace. We also have a dedicated black market section, you will eventually be able to buy Ardour Prem which will simply give you the status and ingame benefits such as slightly increased drop rate… a list will be created with details, and the money earned will all go into the server.</p>
<p>Features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Flawless skills</li>
<li>Perfect Duel Arena</li>
<li>Castle wars</li>
<li>Quests</li>
<li>Many Minigames perfected</li>
<li>Mant bosses</li>
<li>Friendly Staff and Active staff from all over the world</li>
<li>Hundreds of PVM and PVP opportunities with countless rewards</li>
<li>Huge world</li>
<li>Perfect PKing with flawless switching and perfect hybriding</li>
<li>Extremely stable</li>
<li>No items past 2007</li>
</ul>
<p>Please help us be up there with the best.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 17:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-542227-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/474-2007-based-adventure/542227.rss">474- 2007 based adventure</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
