<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can&#39;t log into 704 servers</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-log-into-704-servers/437143</link>
    <description>Well I&#39;m not sure where this question actually goes but it is an issue. It&#39;s not my server it is someone else&#39;s server. Anyway I can&#39;t log in I&#39;ll make a new account half the screen loads everything is frozen and it returns me to the login screen. This is happening on Webclients and the downloadable clients too. I&#39;ll refresh the page and it doesn&#39;t work. Nothing I try doesn&#39;t work. So why does it do this? I have the latest JDK and JRE. Would really like an answer. If this is in the wrong section I apologize.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 04:50:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-log-into-704-servers/437143.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can&#39;t log into 704 servers</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@lolwutnoob lolwutnoob]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/lolwutnoob">@lolwutnoob</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Well I’m not sure where this question actually goes but it is an issue. It’s not my server it is someone else’s server. Anyway I can’t log in I’ll make a new account half the screen loads everything is frozen and it returns me to the login screen. This is happening on Webclients and the downloadable clients too. I’ll refresh the page and it doesn’t work. Nothing I try doesn’t work. So why does it do this? I have the latest JDK and JRE. Would really like an answer. If this is in the wrong section I apologize.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-log-into-704-servers/437143/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-log-into-704-servers/437143/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 04:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-437143-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cant-log-into-704-servers/437143.rss">Can&#39;t log into 704 servers</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
