<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;STAMFORD, Conn. (Feb. 18) -- The frantic owner of a 200-pound chimpanzee that went berserk in Connecticut pleaded with police over the phone to help her stop the animal from mauling her friend, begging them to &quot;Hurry, please! He ripped her face off.&quot;
Police in Stamford released 911 tapes of Sandra Herold&#39;s desperate call to police Monday as her 15-year-old chimp, Travis, was attacking 55-year-old Charla Nash.

The chimp can be heard grunting at times on the tape, as Herold cries, &quot;He&#39;s killing my friend!&quot;
The dispatcher says, &quot;Who&#39;s killing your friend?&quot;
Herold replies, &quot;My chimpanzee! He ripped her apart! Shoot him, shoot him!&quot;
After police arrive, one officer radios back: &quot;There&#39;s a man down. He doesn&#39;t look good,&quot; he says, referring to the disfigured Nash. &quot;We&#39;ve got to get this guy out of here. He&#39;s got no face.&quot;
The chimp attacked Nash as Herold, 70, frantically stabbed her beloved pet with a butcher knife and pounded him with a shovel.
&quot;He looked at me like, &#39;Mom, what did you do?&#39;&quot; Herold told NBC&#39;s &quot;Today Show&quot; in an interview aired Wednesday. &quot;It was horrific what happened and I had to do what I had to do, but still, I&#39;ll miss him for the rest of my life.&quot;

Nash remained was in critical condition early Wednesday with major injuries to her face and hands.
Police said they are looking into the possibility of criminal charges. A pet owner can be held criminally responsible if he or she knew or should have known that an animal was a danger to others.
Police said that the chimp was agitated earlier Monday and that Herold had given him the anti-anxiety drug Xanax in some tea. Police said the drug had not been prescribed for the 14-year-old chimp.
In humans, Xanax can cause memory loss, lack of coordination, reduced sex drive and other side effects. It can also lead to aggression in people who were unstable to begin with, said Dr. Emil Coccaro, chief of psychiatry at the University of Chicago Medical Center.
&quot;Xanax could have made him worse,&quot; if human studies are any indication, Coccaro said.
Investigators said they were also told that Travis had Lyme disease, a tick-borne illness with flu-like symptoms that can lead to arthritis and meningitis in humans.
&quot;Maybe from the medications he was out of sorts,&quot; Stamford police Capt. Richard Conklin said.
Nash had gone to Herold&#39;s home in Stamford on Monday to help her coax the chimp back into the house after he got out, police said. After the animal lunged at Nash when she got out of her car, Herold ran inside to call 911 and returned with a knife.

After the initial attack, Travis ran away and started roaming Herold&#39;s property until police arrived, setting up security so medics could reach the critically injured woman, Conklin said.
But the chimpanzee returned and went after several of the officers, who retreated into their cars, Conklin said. An officer shot Travis several times after the animal opened the door to his cruiser and started to get in.
The wounded chimpanzee fled into the house and retreated to his living quarters, where he died.
Herold, a widow whose daughter was killed in a car accident several years ago, told the Today Show that the incident was &quot;a freak thing.&quot;
She said Travis &quot;couldn&#39;t have been more my son than if I gave birth to him,&quot; and rejected criticism that chimpanzees are inappropriate pets.
&quot;It&#39;s a horrible thing, but I&#39;m not a horrible person and he&#39;s not a horrible chimp.&quot; she said.
The unexplained attack was uncharacteristic of Travis, a veteran of TV commercials who could eat at the table, drink wine from a stemmed glass, use the toilet, and dress and bathe himself.
Don Mecca, a family friend from Colchester, N.Y., said Herold fed the chimp steak, lobster, ice cream and Italian food.
Travis brushed his teeth with a Water Pik, logged on to a computer to look at photos and channel-surfed television with the remote control.
Colleen McCann, a primatologist at the Bronx Zoo, said chimpanzees are unpredictable and dangerous even after living among humans for years.
&quot;I don&#39;t know the effects of Lyme disease on chimpanzees, but I will say that it&#39;s deceiving to think that if any animal is, quote-unquote, well-behaved around humans that means there is no risk involved to humans for potential outbursts of behavior,&quot; she said. &quot;They are unpredictable, and in instances like this you cannot control that behavior or prevent it from happening if it is in a private home.&quot;
Connecticut law requires anyone who owns a primate heavier than 50 pounds to obtain a state permit. But Herold was exempted from the law.
When he was younger, Travis starred in TV commercials for Old Navy and Coca-Cola, made an appearance on the &quot;Maury Povich Show&quot; and took part in a television pilot, according to a 2003 story in The Advocate newspaper of Stamford.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Source: [url=http://news.aol.com/article/chimp-attack/345471]http://news.aol.com/article/chimp-attack/345471[/url]

This is probably about the 3rd chimp attack I have heard about in the past few years.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 08:05:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@phonnygoblin phonnygoblin]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/phonnygoblin">@phonnygoblin</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“bootnecklad, post:8, topic:262994”][quote author=R.I.P RSC link=topic=347411.msg2676850#msg2676850 date=1235129981]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. <span class="bbcode-b">Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat.</span> And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.<br>
[/quote]I think you’re a fuckin’ moron.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think you are a fucking moron until you explain what’s wrong about the bold statement.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A dog will only attack if it’s threatened or provoked. So your saying if you put a baby and a dog in a room the dog would attack the baby? Your the moron, I bet you got attacked by a dog when you were younger.[/quote]</p>
<p>Hey dipshit, dogs have sadistic sides too.  OMG THEY’RE NOT GOD’S CREATIONS TO SERVE MAN.  WHATDOIDOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 08:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@maniown maniown]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/maniown">@maniown</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Did you listen to the video!? Lmfao.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 20:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>regardless of the size and age which was the original point</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 19:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Taios Taios]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/taios">@Taios</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“sanga282, post:16, topic:262994”][quote author=Taios link=topic=347411.msg2680290#msg2680290 date=1235322374]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>my point was that regardless of age it would attack if it saw you as a threat</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Depends on the animal too though =/ i mean wolfs have been known to bring up babies into their pack…wolfs see humans as threats, you’d think it’d see the baby as a threat to its cubs.<br>
[/quote]<br>
ok think of it like this: a man comes to steal a wolf’s baby it will attack. If a child steal a wolf’s baby same result[/quote] Fair enough…although that’s maternal instincts which is slightly different…Most human mothers would do the exact same thing.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 19:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Taios, post:15, topic:262994”][quote author=sanga282 link=topic=347411.msg2679826#msg2679826 date=1235296776]<br>
my point was that regardless of age it would attack if it saw you as a threat<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>Depends on the animal too though =/ i mean wolfs have been known to bring up babies into their pack…wolfs see humans as threats, you’d think it’d see the baby as a threat to its cubs.[/quote]<br>
ok think of it like this: a man comes to steal a wolf’s baby it will attack. If a child steal a wolf’s baby same result</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 18:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Taios Taios]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/taios">@Taios</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Depends on the animal too though =/ i mean wolfs have been known to bring up babies into their pack…wolfs see humans as threats, you’d think it’d see the baby as a threat to its cubs.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 17:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>my point was that regardless of age it would attack if it saw you as a threat</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 09:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Taios Taios]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/taios">@Taios</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“R.I.P RSC, post:3, topic:262994”]Look how people will feel sorry for the owner of that animal. I hope that bitch gets raped to death in prison.</p>
<p>Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat. And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.[/quote]</p>
<p>A chimp isn’t bigger then an adult is it?..<br>
The chimp went crazy, i guess you would too if you were held against your natural world.<br>
And thats horrible, i don’t particularly feel sorry for the owner but how the hell would she know something like this would happen?<br>
Someone had a bad experience with animals.</p>
<p>And as for ‘will attack a child if viewed as a threat’…When we take my dog to the fields, (shepherd) she will try and protect other children from things she views as threats. If ever im walking and talking to a person with a child she won’t go out of eye sight…if im on my own, she tends to go through the woods, chasing rabbits and squirrels etc. And if im with my little brother, she won’t go further then about 50 meters.</p>
<p>[quote=“sanga282, post:12, topic:262994”][quote author=Pwnd link=topic=347411.msg2675898#msg2675898 date=1235071884]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. <span class="bbcode-b">Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat.</span> And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.<br>
[/quote]I think you’re a fuckin’ moron.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>a dog will attack an adult as much as it would a child if it thought it was a threat. Otherwise guard dogs would be fucking next to useless[/quote]</p>
<p>Guard dogs are TRAINED to attack people.<br>
I’ve had Germanb Shephers, German shepherds cross Dobermans and other dogs all throughout.<br>
German shepherd cross doberman, thats two of the most used guard dogs in one breed…He’d never attack anyone, ever. Infact he was abused <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> and never fought back. When my younger brother was born, he was 9 or 10, never a jealousy problem. Never a problem when we had other dogs, no jealousy, never attacked anyone or anything.</p>
<p>And my current Shepherd, she’d defend you to the death if you were attacked however is petrified of the watering can and Little dogs lmao…but she’d greet anyone happily and friendly. Any little terrier that barks and nips, she legs it. But she is GREAT with other dogs and people. People are always commenting on how friendly she is.</p>
<p>As with this animal, im sure the person thought she knew him and he knew her. But she just lived with him, im guessing he may not have been used to competition for his owners affection…but keeping an animal like that i have to agree is stupid…Chimps/Monkey family can be very emotional creatures, like humans, however they cannot express their emotions by speaking. For example if you had a girlfriend who went out with a guy, its natural to feel some kinda of jealously depending on cirumcstances. But you speak to others or find some other outlet…he didn’t have much else…he had to be house trained, trained not to express himself as an animal normally would, can’t be angry, frustrated etc…eventually snapped.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 11:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-13</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sanga282 sanga282]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/sanga282">@sanga282</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Pwnd, post:5, topic:262994”][quote author=R.I.P RSC link=topic=347411.msg2675766#msg2675766 date=1235065791]<br>
Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. <span class="bbcode-b">Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat.</span> And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.<br>
[/quote]I think you’re a fuckin’ moron.[/quote]<br>
a dog will attack an adult as much as it would a child if it thought it was a threat. Otherwise guard dogs would be fucking next to useless</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/12</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 11:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-12</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxKanexX Kane.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxkanexx">@XxKanexX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“bootnecklad, post:8, topic:262994”][quote author=R.I.P RSC link=topic=347411.msg2676850#msg2676850 date=1235129981]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. <span class="bbcode-b">Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat.</span> And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.<br>
[/quote]I think you’re a fuckin’ moron.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think you are a fucking moron until you explain what’s wrong about the bold statement.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A dog will only attack if it’s threatened or provoked. So your saying if you put a baby and a dog in a room the dog would attack the baby? Your the moron, I bet you got attacked by a dog when you were younger.[/quote]<br>
Shut up.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-11</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“bootnecklad, post:8, topic:262994”][quote author=R.I.P RSC link=topic=347411.msg2676850#msg2676850 date=1235129981]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. <span class="bbcode-b">Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat.</span> And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.<br>
[/quote]I think you’re a fuckin’ moron.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think you are a fucking moron until you explain what’s wrong about the bold statement.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>A dog will only attack if it’s threatened or provoked. So your saying if you put a baby and a dog in a room the dog would attack the baby? Your the moron, I bet you got attacked by a dog when you were younger.[/quote]</p>
<p>You must be the fucking moron, as that is exactly what I said: <span class="bbcode-b">Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children [size=25pt]if[/size] they see them as a threat.</span></p>
<p>And a little more explanation about the fourth sentence in that quote: If you have a dog for a few years, and you give him all the attention because you don’t have children, the dog feels great. But when you get a child, the attention is given to the child. So if your dog can’t handle the loss of attention, it will see the child as a threat. Then it depends on other factors whether or not the dog will actually attack, but the odds favor an attack.</p>
<p>Oh, and I love dogs, and no: I’ve never been attacked by one.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 13:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@XxKanexX Kane.]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/xxkanexx">@XxKanexX</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I listened to the full 911 call. It’s so sad to listen to her poor friend watch her friend get ripped apart.<br>
<img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=6" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 12:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“R.I.P RSC, post:7, topic:262994”][quote author=Pwnd link=topic=347411.msg2675898#msg2675898 date=1235071884]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. <span class="bbcode-b">Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat.</span> And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.<br>
[/quote]I think you’re a fuckin’ moron.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think you are a fucking moron until you explain what’s wrong about the bold statement.[/quote]</p>
<p>A dog will only attack if it’s threatened or provoked. So your saying if you put a baby and a dog in a room the dog would attack the baby? Your the moron, I bet you got attacked by a dog when you were younger.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 12:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Pwnd, post:5, topic:262994”][quote author=R.I.P RSC link=topic=347411.msg2675766#msg2675766 date=1235065791]<br>
Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. <span class="bbcode-b">Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat.</span> And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.<br>
[/quote]I think you’re a fuckin’ moron.[/quote]</p>
<p>I think you are a fucking moron until you explain what’s wrong about the bold statement.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 11:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Uriko, post:2, topic:262994”][quote author=Chassy13 link=topic=347411.msg2674576#msg2674576 date=1234997536]</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>The unexplained attack was uncharacteristic of Travis, a veteran of TV commercials who could eat at the table, drink wine from a stemmed glass, use the toilet, and dress and bathe himself.[/quote][/quote]Wow, he can perform more tasks than bootnecklad.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>awww someone remembered my name <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Hey wait a minute! what makes you say that <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 19:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Pwnd Pwnd]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/pwnd">@Pwnd</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“R.I.P RSC, post:3, topic:262994”]Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. <span class="bbcode-b">Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat.</span> And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.[/quote]I think you’re a fuckin’ moron.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 19:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A chimp with my name makes me laugh.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 17:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@R.I.P_RSC R.I.P RSC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/r.i.p_rsc">@R.I.P_RSC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Look how people will feel sorry for the owner of that animal. I hope that bitch gets raped to death in prison.</p>
<p>Animals shouldn’t be trusted. Not even dogs. Dogs don’t attack adults because they are too big for them, but they will attack children if they see them as a threat. And children are always a threat for a dog, because dogs want the attention that the children get. So owning an animal that is bigger then an adult is plain stupid.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 17:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uriko Uriko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uriko">@Uriko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Chassy13, post:1, topic:262994”][quote]The unexplained attack was uncharacteristic of Travis, a veteran of TV commercials who could eat at the table, drink wine from a stemmed glass, use the toilet, and dress and bathe himself.[/quote][/quote]Wow, he can perform more tasks than bootnecklad.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 23:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@chassy13 Chassy13]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/chassy13">@chassy13</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>STAMFORD, Conn. (Feb. 18) -- The frantic owner of a 200-pound chimpanzee that went berserk in Connecticut pleaded with police over the phone to help her stop the animal from mauling her friend, begging them to "Hurry, please! He ripped her face off."
Police in Stamford released 911 tapes of Sandra Herold's desperate call to police Monday as her 15-year-old chimp, Travis, was attacking 55-year-old Charla Nash.
<p>The chimp can be heard grunting at times on the tape, as Herold cries, “He’s killing my friend!”<br>
The dispatcher says, “Who’s killing your friend?”<br>
Herold replies, “My chimpanzee! He ripped her apart! Shoot him, shoot him!”<br>
After police arrive, one officer radios back: “There’s a man down. He doesn’t look good,” he says, referring to the disfigured Nash. “We’ve got to get this guy out of here. He’s got no face.”<br>
The chimp attacked Nash as Herold, 70, frantically stabbed her beloved pet with a butcher knife and pounded him with a shovel.<br>
“He looked at me like, ‘Mom, what did you do?’” Herold told NBC’s “Today Show” in an interview aired Wednesday. “It was horrific what happened and I had to do what I had to do, but still, I’ll miss him for the rest of my life.”</p>
<p>Nash remained was in critical condition early Wednesday with major injuries to her face and hands.<br>
Police said they are looking into the possibility of criminal charges. A pet owner can be held criminally responsible if he or she knew or should have known that an animal was a danger to others.<br>
Police said that the chimp was agitated earlier Monday and that Herold had given him the anti-anxiety drug Xanax in some tea. Police said the drug had not been prescribed for the 14-year-old chimp.<br>
In humans, Xanax can cause memory loss, lack of coordination, reduced sex drive and other side effects. It can also lead to aggression in people who were unstable to begin with, said Dr. Emil Coccaro, chief of psychiatry at the University of Chicago Medical Center.<br>
“Xanax could have made him worse,” if human studies are any indication, Coccaro said.<br>
Investigators said they were also told that Travis had Lyme disease, a tick-borne illness with flu-like symptoms that can lead to arthritis and meningitis in humans.<br>
“Maybe from the medications he was out of sorts,” Stamford police Capt. Richard Conklin said.<br>
Nash had gone to Herold’s home in Stamford on Monday to help her coax the chimp back into the house after he got out, police said. After the animal lunged at Nash when she got out of her car, Herold ran inside to call 911 and returned with a knife.</p>
<p>After the initial attack, Travis ran away and started roaming Herold’s property until police arrived, setting up security so medics could reach the critically injured woman, Conklin said.<br>
But the chimpanzee returned and went after several of the officers, who retreated into their cars, Conklin said. An officer shot Travis several times after the animal opened the door to his cruiser and started to get in.<br>
The wounded chimpanzee fled into the house and retreated to his living quarters, where he died.<br>
Herold, a widow whose daughter was killed in a car accident several years ago, told the Today Show that the incident was “a freak thing.”<br>
She said Travis “couldn’t have been more my son than if I gave birth to him,” and rejected criticism that chimpanzees are inappropriate pets.<br>
“It’s a horrible thing, but I’m not a horrible person and he’s not a horrible chimp.” she said.<br>
The unexplained attack was uncharacteristic of Travis, a veteran of TV commercials who could eat at the table, drink wine from a stemmed glass, use the toilet, and dress and bathe himself.<br>
Don Mecca, a family friend from Colchester, N.Y., said Herold fed the chimp steak, lobster, ice cream and Italian food.<br>
Travis brushed his teeth with a Water Pik, logged on to a computer to look at photos and channel-surfed television with the remote control.<br>
Colleen McCann, a primatologist at the Bronx Zoo, said chimpanzees are unpredictable and dangerous even after living among humans for years.<br>
“I don’t know the effects of Lyme disease on chimpanzees, but I will say that it’s deceiving to think that if any animal is, quote-unquote, well-behaved around humans that means there is no risk involved to humans for potential outbursts of behavior,” she said. “They are unpredictable, and in instances like this you cannot control that behavior or prevent it from happening if it is in a private home.”<br>
Connecticut law requires anyone who owns a primate heavier than 50 pounds to obtain a state permit. But Herold was exempted from the law.<br>
When he was younger, Travis starred in TV commercials for Old Navy and Coca-Cola, made an appearance on the “Maury Povich Show” and took part in a television pilot, according to a 2003 story in The Advocate newspaper of Stamford.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Source: <a href="http://news.aol.com/article/chimp-attack/345471" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">http://news.aol.com/article/chimp-attack/345471</a></p>
<p>This is probably about the 3rd chimp attack I have heard about in the past few years.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 22:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-262994-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/horrific-details-emerge-in-chimp-attack/262994.rss">Horrific Details Emerge in Chimp Attack</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
