<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobb Deep - Blood Money (Music)</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobb-deep-blood-money-music/16002</link>
    <description>Rating: 1.5/5

 Well, what good could possibly come of Mobb signing to G-Unit? That&#39;s right... none. Mobb Deep is officially dead. Progidy and Havoc have sold their souls to the devil.

 This album is just what you expected: a horrible, nearly unlistenable pile of steaming donkey shit. It seems as if Progidy has completely forgotten how to rap. He sounds as if he&#39;s high on crack through the whole album, and nothing he says even fucking rhymes. Havoc is barely any better, but he tosses a few decent lines back and forth. There are virtually no decent songs on here. &quot;Put Em In There Place&quot; is somewhat ok. &quot;Pearly Gates&quot; is actually good, but 50 Cent&#39;s horrible singing hook ruins it. All of the appearances of G-Unit members are weak.

 In summation, this album is trash, and you&#39;ll stay far away from it if you value your eardrums. Even if you loved the old Mobb Deep, seriously stay the fuck away from this mess. There&#39;s almost nothing of redeeming value here.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2006 16:18:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobb-deep-blood-money-music/16002.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Mobb Deep - Blood Money (Music)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Zezima_is_cool Zezima is cool]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/zezima_is_cool">@Zezima_is_cool</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>yea it sukd</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobb-deep-blood-money-music/16002/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobb-deep-blood-money-music/16002/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2006 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16002-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobb-deep-blood-money-music/16002.rss">Mobb Deep - Blood Money (Music)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Mobb Deep - Blood Money (Music)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@leet_haxer_dood leet haxer dood]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/leet_haxer_dood">@leet_haxer_dood</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Rating: 1.5/5</p>
<p>Well, what good could possibly come of Mobb signing to G-Unit? That’s right… none. Mobb Deep is officially dead. Progidy and Havoc have sold their souls to the devil.</p>
<p>This album is just what you expected: a horrible, nearly unlistenable pile of steaming donkey shit. It seems as if Progidy has completely forgotten how to rap. He sounds as if he’s high on crack through the whole album, and nothing he says even fucking rhymes. Havoc is barely any better, but he tosses a few decent lines back and forth. There are virtually no decent songs on here. “Put Em In There Place” is somewhat ok. “Pearly Gates” is actually good, but 50 Cent’s horrible singing hook ruins it. All of the appearances of G-Unit members are weak.</p>
<p>In summation, this album is trash, and you’ll stay far away from it if you value your eardrums. Even if you loved the old Mobb Deep, seriously stay the fuck away from this mess. There’s almost nothing of redeeming value here.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobb-deep-blood-money-music/16002/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobb-deep-blood-money-music/16002/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 08:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-16002-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/mobb-deep-blood-money-music/16002.rss">Mobb Deep - Blood Money (Music)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
