<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Break-up</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159</link>
    <description>ITT: break-up stories, gogogogoo

















so like today i broke up with my girlfriend. sigh i love her so much (she initiated the break up) yet she fell for another guy. a really sad day for me. i told my mom about it because she was close to her and she said its ok and send a letter to her so i did, i wrote: never gonna give you up, never gonna let you down, never gonna run around and desert you, never gonna make you cry, never gonna say goodbye, never gonna tell a lie and hurt you. then she sympathized with me and wanted to get back into a relationship. she asked me to meet her out a mall so i did when i was there, there were three men with her. she was laying on the ground and the men kept beating her head up before shooting her in the head. the men eventually got off in a car and sped off. i was so shocked to see her in such poor state, i don&#39;t know what to do so i decided to run away pretending i didn&#39;t see it (the blood everywhere was gross). when i came home i was visibly shaken. i told my mom what i had seen. Then she got scared and said you&#39;re moving with your auntie and uncle in bel-air I whistled for a cab and when it came near the license plate said fresh and had a dice in the mirror. if anything i could say that this cab was rare. but I thought now forget it, yo home to bel-air. i pulled up to a house about seven or eight and i yelled to the cabby yo, homes smell you later. looked at my kingdom, i was finally there to settle my throne as the prince of bel-air.

inb4 cool story bro</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 14:33:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Break-up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Go back to 4chan</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 14:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340159-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159.rss">Break-up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Break-up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@justinxg27 justinxg27]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/justinxg27">@justinxg27</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“B2300 T4nk, post:4, topic:340159”]Believed it for a moment.[/quote]Same…</p>
<p>but then When I heard here get beat up, I lol’d and started writing this.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 14:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340159-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159.rss">Break-up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Break-up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@B2300_T4nk B2300 T4nk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/b2300_t4nk">@B2300_T4nk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Believed it for a moment.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 14:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340159-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159.rss">Break-up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Break-up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@demonlover14 demonlover14]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/demonlover14">@demonlover14</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I t hough this was true…<br>
And that’s not how the theme song goes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 12:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340159-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159.rss">Break-up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Break-up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Stupit Stu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/stupit">@Stupit</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>lolwat.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 12:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340159-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159.rss">Break-up</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Break-up</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Rixxx Rix_]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/rixxx">@Rixxx</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>ITT: break-up stories, gogogogoo</p>
<p>so like today i broke up with my girlfriend. sigh i love her so much (she initiated the break up) yet she fell for another guy. a really sad day for me. i told my mom about it because she was close to her and she said its ok and send a letter to her so i did, i wrote: never gonna give you up, never gonna let you down, never gonna run around and desert you, never gonna make you cry, never gonna say goodbye, never gonna tell a lie and hurt you. then she sympathized with me and wanted to get back into a relationship. she asked me to meet her out a mall so i did when i was there, there were three men with her. she was laying on the ground and the men kept beating her head up before shooting her in the head. the men eventually got off in a car and sped off. i was so shocked to see her in such poor state, i don’t know what to do so i decided to run away pretending i didn’t see it (the blood everywhere was gross). when i came home i was visibly shaken. i told my mom what i had seen. Then she got scared and said you’re moving with your auntie and uncle in bel-air I whistled for a cab and when it came near the license plate said fresh and had a dice in the mirror. if anything i could say that this cab was rare. but I thought now forget it, yo home to bel-air. i pulled up to a house about seven or eight and i yelled to the cabby yo, homes smell you later. looked at my kingdom, i was finally there to settle my throne as the prince of bel-air.</p>
<p>inb4 cool story bro</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 12:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-340159-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/break-up/340159.rss">Break-up</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
