<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Google plans to make PCs history</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652</link>
    <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;Google is to launch a service that would enable users to access their personal computer from any internet connection, according to industry reports. But campaigners warn that it would give the online behemoth unprecedented control over individuals&#39; personal data.

The Google Drive, or &quot;GDrive&quot;, could kill off the desktop computer, which relies on a powerful hard drive. Instead a user&#39;s personal files and operating system could be stored on Google&#39;s own servers and accessed via the internet.

The long-rumoured GDrive is expected to be launched this year, according to the technology news website TG Daily, which described it as &quot;the most anticipated Google product so far&quot;. It is seen as a paradigm shift away from Microsoft&#39;s Windows operating system, which runs inside most of the world&#39;s computers, in favour of &quot;cloud computing&quot;, where the processing and storage is done thousands of miles away in remote data centres.

Home and business users are increasingly turning to web-based services, usually free, ranging from email (such as Hotmail and Gmail) and digital photo storage (such as Flickr and Picasa) to more applications for documents and spreadsheets (such as Google Apps). The loss of a laptop or crash of a hard drive does not jeopardise the data because it is regularly saved in &quot;the cloud&quot; and can be accessed via the web from any machine.

The GDrive would follow this logic to its conclusion by shifting the contents of a user&#39;s hard drive to the Google servers. The PC would be a simpler, cheaper device acting as a portal to the web, perhaps via an adaptation of Google&#39;s operating system for mobile phones, Android. Users would think of their computer as software rather than hardware.

It is this prospect that alarms critics of Google&#39;s ambitions. Peter Brown, executive director of the Free Software Foundation, a charity defending computer users&#39; liberties, did not dispute the convenience offered, but said: &quot;It&#39;s a little bit like saying, &#39;we&#39;re in a dictatorship, the trains are running on time.&#39; But does it matter to you that someone can see everything on your computer? Does it matter that Google can be subpoenaed at any time to hand over all your data to the American government?&quot;

Google refused to confirm the GDrive, but acknowledged the growing demand for cloud computing. Dave Armstrong, head of product and marketing for Google Enterprise, said: &quot;There&#39;s a clear direction ... away from people thinking, &#39;This is my PC, this is my hard drive,&#39; to &#39;This is how I interact with information, this is how I interact with the web.&#39;&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
sauce: http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/2009/jan/25/google-drive-gdrive-internet

Hmm.. I love Google and all, but I&#39;m not sure I&#39;m ready to let the privacy-of-users--hungry company to store my whole hard drive.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 21:18:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Google plans to make PCs history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scrubs Scrubs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scrubs">@Scrubs</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>A while back I had an idea kinda like this. To give those who can’t afford an actual computer and the wealth of knowledge it brings along, why not make a computer that depended on the internet that way making the price of a computer drop way below an average computer’s price. Although I really have no idea how much it would cost to make a screen with a mouse and have access to the internet, seems a lot cheaper than an actual computer with an os and all the memory etc.</p>
<p>What I mean is, a ‘computer’ which had it’s os on the internet. All storage etc on the internet. Google was the first to cross my mind. Google offers all the memory (not much really considering the fact they give you email with 7gb for free) that you would need to store your files. Access to the internet (obviously), Google Docs (create documents), etc etc.<br>
/end</p>
<p>Now that I read the first post, the above paragraphs are useless.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 21:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-258652-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652.rss">Google plans to make PCs history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Google plans to make PCs history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@moparisthebest Moparisthebest]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/moparisthebest">@moparisthebest</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I can already access my computer from the internet anytime I want to by way of WOL (Wake-On-Lan, meaning I can turn the computer on from the internet) and RDP (Remote Desktop Protocol, like VNC) and SSH sometimes.  And only I have access to my stuff.</p>
<p>Still it is a cool idea, depending on the advantages and disadvantages I might still use it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652/3</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-258652-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652.rss">Google plans to make PCs history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Google plans to make PCs history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bootnecklad bootnecklad]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bootnecklad">@bootnecklad</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Google is the creator of sky net, they will one day take over the world and Uriko will be the leader of the resistance.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-258652-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652.rss">Google plans to make PCs history</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Google plans to make PCs history</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Uriko Uriko]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/uriko">@Uriko</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Google is to launch a service that would enable users to access their personal computer from any internet connection, according to industry reports. But campaigners warn that it would give the online behemoth unprecedented control over individuals' personal data.
<p>The Google Drive, or “GDrive”, could kill off the desktop computer, which relies on a powerful hard drive. Instead a user’s personal files and operating system could be stored on Google’s own servers and accessed via the internet.</p>
<p>The long-rumoured GDrive is expected to be launched this year, according to the technology news website TG Daily, which described it as “the most anticipated Google product so far”. It is seen as a paradigm shift away from Microsoft’s Windows operating system, which runs inside most of the world’s computers, in favour of “cloud computing”, where the processing and storage is done thousands of miles away in remote data centres.</p>
<p>Home and business users are increasingly turning to web-based services, usually free, ranging from email (such as Hotmail and Gmail) and digital photo storage (such as Flickr and Picasa) to more applications for documents and spreadsheets (such as Google Apps). The loss of a laptop or crash of a hard drive does not jeopardise the data because it is regularly saved in “the cloud” and can be accessed via the web from any machine.</p>
<p>The GDrive would follow this logic to its conclusion by shifting the contents of a user’s hard drive to the Google servers. The PC would be a simpler, cheaper device acting as a portal to the web, perhaps via an adaptation of Google’s operating system for mobile phones, Android. Users would think of their computer as software rather than hardware.</p>
<p>It is this prospect that alarms critics of Google’s ambitions. Peter Brown, executive director of the Free Software Foundation, a charity defending computer users’ liberties, did not dispute the convenience offered, but said: “It’s a little bit like saying, ‘we’re in a dictatorship, the trains are running on time.’ But does it matter to you that someone can see everything on your computer? Does it matter that Google can be subpoenaed at any time to hand over all your data to the American government?”</p>
<p>Google refused to confirm the GDrive, but acknowledged the growing demand for cloud computing. Dave Armstrong, head of product and marketing for Google Enterprise, said: “There’s a clear direction … away from people thinking, ‘This is my PC, this is my hard drive,’ to ‘This is how I interact with information, this is how I interact with the web.’”</p>
</blockquote><br>
sauce: <a href="http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/2009/jan/25/google-drive-gdrive-internet" rel="nofollow noopener">http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/2009/jan/25/google-drive-gdrive-internet</a>
<p>Hmm… I love Google and all, but I’m not sure I’m ready to let the privacy-of-users–hungry company to store my whole hard drive.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 20:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-258652-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/google-plans-to-make-pcs-history/258652.rss">Google plans to make PCs history</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
