<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>You are born gay</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949</link>
    <description>I will not argue with you if you&#39;re going to post &quot;because I think so!&quot; - I&#39;m arguing here purely based on logic.

I believe people are born homosexual, because simply put, who would choose to be homosexual against all current hate. That&#39;s just my first point.

Additionally, one popular argument is that at the age of 1-3 and early childhood, one cannot say that they like males (for males) and females (for females). Well, this argument applies to both scenarios, females (for males) and males (for females), meaning the aforementioned persona has no sexual orientation whatsoever. Yet, the way one finds their sexual &#39;direction&#39; is through curiousity, and clearly that curiousity is directed in your interests as a child. Eg, males for example, already know instinctually what turns them on, not their choice, but it occurred early on through childhood. As it continues, they realise what they are. [b]Just because they finally identified that they like females, doesn&#39;t mean it was their choice. It (from logic) had already existed, BUT they finally identified it[/b]. This is the same for females. This is no way a choice, it happens itself subconsciously.

Let this be a good debate.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 14:10:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jamie1200 Jamie1200]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jamie1200">@Jamie1200</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This topic is a debate that’s been baffling scientists and psychologists for years.<br>
When it comes to sexual orientation, I think you can go down the lines of the <span class="bbcode-i">nature versus nurture</span> debate. For example the <span class="bbcode-b">Nature side</span> of the argument could be you are born gay. In relation to homosexuality, the nature concept explores the possibility of a specific gene or combination of genes present at the time of birth that genetically predispose people to homosexuality. In other words, some people are born gay.<br>
Or the <span class="bbcode-b">nurture argument </span>, We’re all influenced by our environment, but to what extent? The nurture concept of homosexuality argues that social, parental and environmental variables influence a person’s homosexuality. A nurtured gay person is one that is “made” gay.</p>
<p>As a gay individual myself and I have no shame in the fact to admit that, I can say and would like to think that both of the factors mentioned above, played a part, in my sexual orientation.<br>
I can not see nor fathom, hate crimes and discriminate actions against homosexuals.<br>
religion, politics and peers all play part in ones sexual choice and each to their own.   However, The debate could be said about the majority of the norm when it comes to heterosexuality and are you influenced to believe that is correct?</p>
<p>Also to mention. “Topic: You are born gay.” Should really be a question as appose to a statement. Thought I’d add that in.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/74</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 14:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-74</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Kidpaparoach Kidpaparoach]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kidpaparoach">@Kidpaparoach</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Their is more to being homo/gay however that is not part of the defination. The reason their is more because of the way they are treated, its nothing to do with being gay itself. Its to do with society. This is my opinion, not a fact.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/73">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/73</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-73</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>take the humble pidgeon for example, some small percentage of them will exhibit same-sex behaviour, they will even go as far as to build nests and lay infertile eggs and incubate them</p>
<p>you picked an extreme example and are running with it, running away from my point that you still fail to grasp</p>
<p>you cannot change who you are sexually attracted to, you can change who you decide to fuck, being a homosexual or heterosexual is more than who you decide to fuck it is who you are sexually attracted to</p>
<p>I bought up pansexuals before, it’s time to bring them up again, without getting into an argument about what pansexuals actually are I’ll use the wikipedia example:</p>
<p>Pansexuality, or omnisexuality,[1] is sexual attraction, sexual desire, romantic love, or emotional attraction toward persons of all gender identities and biological sexes.</p>
<p>how is this different from bisexuality?</p>
<p>Bisexuality is romantic or sexual attraction or behavior toward males and females. The term is especially used in the context of human sexual attraction to denote romantic or sexual feelings toward men and women.</p>
<p>the difference is subtle but it’s there, pansexuality wouldn’t exist if sexuality was as simple as “you fuck the opposite gender you are heterosexual, you fuck the same gender you are homosexual, you fuck both (implying there are only two genders) then you are bisexual”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/72">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/72</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 19:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-72</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Take the Bonobo Monkey for instance. The Bonobo monkey is born into a group in which every member is bi-sexual.The Bonobo monkey learns how to interact with other Bonobo Monkeys and so that new baby Bonobo Monkey is now a bi-sexual because that is normal for it. It wasn’t born gay, it was born into a group where everyone was gay and so it thought it was normal to be gay.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/71">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/71</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 19:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-71</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="69" data-topic="460949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/m1lkman/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> m1lkman:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Humans are humans and animals are animals. Just because it is natural for hippos to shit all over themselves to attract a mate doesn’t mean it’s natural for humans.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>and you completely missed my point</p>
<p>the argument I was making that if it’s a concious choice or if it’s due to environmental issues (“daddy raped him as a boy, that’s why he’s gay”) then WHY is homosexual behaviour also exhibited in nature without said concious choice, or said environmental issues</p>
<p>it’s not a case of “if animals can do it, so can humans”, it’s a case of “humans only do it because x, y, z, but why do animals do it <span class="bbcode-b">without </span>x, y, z”</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/70">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/70</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 18:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-70</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <blockquote>Other species are homosexual</blockquote>
<p>Praying mantises murder their mate after sex, why don’t we do that?<br>
Bed bugs stab their mates in the stomach to release sperm into the blood stream and reproduce, why don’t we do that?<br>
Squids cut and claw holes into their mate and then ejaculate into those cuts, why don’t we do that?</p>
<p>Humans are humans and animals are animals. Just because it is natural for hippos to shit all over themselves to attract a mate doesn’t mean it’s natural for humans.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/69">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/69</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 18:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-69</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="67" data-topic="460949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (N)eon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Right</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>a bit ambiguous but otherwise straight to the point, good day sir, I bid you adieu</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/68">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/68</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 18:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-68</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_N_eon (N)eon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_n_eon">@_N_eon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Right</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/67">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/67</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 18:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-67</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>without getting too much into the semantics of the argument, everyone should realise that ‘sexual preference’ and ‘who you are sexually attracted to’ are completely different things, if you are a man and find men sexually attractive and do not find women sexually attractive you are by definition a homosexual, if you are a man and find women sexually attractive but do not find men sexually attractive you are by definition a heterosexual</p>
<p>however, heterosexuals can engage in homosexual sex and still be heterosexuals, that is the only choice in the matter; their sexual preference, the vise versa of this can be true that homosexuals can engage in heterosexual sex but by definition they are still homosexuals and they can not choose to be heterosexuals</p>
<p>[quote=“Fails, post:39, topic:460949”]i saw a few comments assuming people are born gay. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"></p>
<p>imo, i believe it’s a choice (when you’re older), if you’re a guy and you like guys, so be it. saying someone is born gay is rather idiotic, that’s like saying people are born knowing what their career is going to be.[/quote]</p>
<p>question for you specifically and directly, do you decide what gender you are sexually attracted to? can you, personally, make the concious choice, if just for a minute, to be sexually attracted to another gender?</p>
<p>furthermore, if it is indeed a choice as you suggest, then why do many other species of animal exhibit homosexual behaviour?</p>
<p>[quote=“Fails, post:53, topic:460949”]gay = dick on dick<br>
bi-sexual = dick in vagina and dick on dick</p>
<p>excuse me for being so blunt.[/quote]</p>
<p>and to throw a metaphorical dick in your gears, what do you feel about pansexuals? I’m just kidding, don’t answer</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="60" data-topic="460949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 (N)eon:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I think gay is just a choice people make… They want the D.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>just like you being sexually attracted to females is a choice, right? you made the concious choice to be sexually attracted to females, and aren’t just attracted to them because that’s instinct, right?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/66">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/66</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 17:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-66</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“JavaTC, post:64, topic:460949”][quote author=Fails link=topic=563884.msg4113590#msg4113590 date=1348789573]<br>
gay = dick on dick<br>
bi-sexual = dick in vagina and dick on dick</p>
<p>excuse me for being so blunt.<br>
[/quote]<br>
There’s more to being Homosexual and Bisexual than sexual preference.[/quote]</p>
<p>Please elaborate</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/65">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/65</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 15:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-65</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JavaTC JavaTC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/javatc">@JavaTC</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Fails, post:53, topic:460949”]gay = dick on dick<br>
bi-sexual = dick in vagina and dick on dick</p>
<p>excuse me for being so blunt.[/quote]<br>
There’s more to being Homosexual and Bisexual than sexual preference.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/64">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/64</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 14:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-64</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@m1lkman m1lkman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/m1lkman">@m1lkman</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“amy_webb, post:61, topic:460949”]Asking if drug addicts are born drug addicts are completely different to asking if someone is born gay, the only thing close to that is asking someone if they were born straight.</p>
<p>Has anyone ever been attracted to the same sex despite being heterosexual? I know males usually aren’t forward when answering questions about being homosexual so just think about it. If you have, have you ever just though ‘not ganna happen’ and forgotten about it? Well that is a choice, something you didn’t act on. I believe it can be the same for homosexuals, male or female. Some are just more open to it and go for it rather then other people who think instinctively ‘that’s wrong’.</p>
<p>But then you have the homosexuals who are completely repelled by the opposite sex parts that they’d never think about it, which is the same for heterosexuals who are repelled by the same sex parts. So really it could be both a choice or being born like it.[/quote]</p>
<p>I understand where you are coming from.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/63">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/63</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 10:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-63</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="57" data-topic="460949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 Fails:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>In all honesty, it doesn’t matter if you’re gay, straight, or homosexual. You are who you are.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Well, duh. That’s wasn’t my question. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/62">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/62</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-62</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@amy_webb1 amy_webb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/amy_webb1">@amy_webb1</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Asking if drug addicts are born drug addicts are completely different to asking if someone is born gay, the only thing close to that is asking someone if they were born straight.</p>
<p>Has anyone ever been attracted to the same sex despite being heterosexual? I know males usually aren’t forward when answering questions about being homosexual so just think about it. If you have, have you ever just though ‘not ganna happen’ and forgotten about it? Well that is a choice, something you didn’t act on. I believe it can be the same for homosexuals, male or female. Some are just more open to it and go for it rather then other people who think instinctively ‘that’s wrong’.</p>
<p>But then you have the homosexuals who are completely repelled by the opposite sex parts that they’d never think about it, which is the same for heterosexuals who are repelled by the same sex parts. So really it could be both a choice or being born like it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/61">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/61</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 01:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-61</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@_N_eon (N)eon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/_n_eon">@_N_eon</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think gay is just a choice people make… They want the D.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/60">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/60</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 01:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-60</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@F_A_I_L_S Fails]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/f_a_i_l_s">@F_A_I_L_S</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="58" data-topic="460949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/davidi2/40/2579_1.png" class="avatar"> Davidi2:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I found the topic title very offensive.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>lul, maybe you should add a “?” to the end. <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/59">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/59</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-59</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@davidi2 Davidi2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/davidi2">@davidi2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I found the topic title very offensive.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/58">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/58</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-58</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@F_A_I_L_S Fails]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/f_a_i_l_s">@F_A_I_L_S</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>In all honesty, it doesn’t matter if you’re gay, straight, or homosexual. You are who you are.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/57</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-57</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@kronixz kronikz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kronixz">@kronixz</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Jc22493, post:54, topic:460949”][quote author=Fails link=topic=563884.msg4113590#msg4113590 date=1348789573]<br>
gay = dick on dick<br>
bi-sexual = dick in vagina and dick on dick</p>
<p>excuse me for being so blunt.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>So in your opinion, being homosexual is based solely off sexual preference.</p>
<p>I was just curious of what everyone thinks since I know two homosexuals who have had serious relationships with the opposite sex without doing anything sexual. Does that still mean they’re homosexual?[/quote]<br>
No because they had a serious relationship which means they male had some sort of attraction to ‘her’</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/56</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-56</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@F_A_I_L_S Fails]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/f_a_i_l_s">@F_A_I_L_S</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>homosexual thoughts.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/55</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 23:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-55</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“Fails, post:53, topic:460949”]gay = dick on dick<br>
bi-sexual = dick in vagina and dick on dick</p>
<p>excuse me for being so blunt.[/quote]</p>
<p>So in your opinion, being homosexual is based solely off sexual preference.</p>
<p>I was just curious of what everyone thinks since I know two homosexuals who have had serious relationships with the opposite sex without doing anything sexual. Does that still mean they’re homosexual?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/54</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 23:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-54</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@F_A_I_L_S Fails]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/f_a_i_l_s">@F_A_I_L_S</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>gay = dick on dick<br>
bi-sexual = dick in vagina and dick on dick</p>
<p>excuse me for being so blunt.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/53</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 23:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-53</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jc22493 Jc22493]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jc22493">@jc22493</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>No one knows.</p>
<aside class="quote quote-modified" data-post="49" data-topic="460949">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/frell/40/5_e05bb34c421432ee4d40de30c10af3e5.png" class="avatar"> Frell:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Bisexual is another word for gays who don’t want to admit theyre gay.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>It really just depends on what you consider homosexual.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/52</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 23:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-52</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@F_A_I_L_S Fails]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/f_a_i_l_s">@F_A_I_L_S</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Bowser: agreed, when I think of johnny depp, oh man. I don’t even want to get into that.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/51</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 22:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-51</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You are born gay</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@bowserjr2 Bowser jr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/bowserjr2">@bowserjr2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[quote=“m1lkman, post:47, topic:460949”][quote author=Bowser jr link=topic=563884.msg4113478#msg4113478 date=1348783422]</p>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<aside class="quote">
<blockquote>
<p>Are people born to be bisexual?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Do you feel bisexual urges?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>No.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then you are most likely not born bisexual. There you have the answer to your question.<br>
[/quote]</p>
<p>What the hell are you talking about?[/quote]<br>
I just misunderstood you. It seemed like you asked if everybody is born bisexual, and we just take a choice from there.</p>
<p>Fails: Only sometimes, depending on the person.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949/50</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 22:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-460949-50</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/you-are-born-gay/460949.rss">You are born gay</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
