<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cartier Love Bangles</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cartier-love-bangles/510111</link>
    <description>The company has a long and distinguished history, as well as stars and celebities. One Prince of Wales hailed Cartier as &quot;Joaillier des Rois, Roi des Joailliers&quot; (Jeweller to Kings, King of Jewellers&quot;). Cartier received an order for 27 tiaras for the coronation of the future King. King Edward VII was crowned in 1902 and in 1904 he honoured the Company with the Royal warrant of supplier to the Royal Court of England. Similar warrants soon followed from the courts of Spain, Portugal, Russia, Siam, Greece, Serbia, Belgium, Romania, Egypt and finally Albania, and also from the House of Orleans and the Principality of Monaco. 
[url=http://www.hellojewelry.co.uk/products/Cartier-Double-Love-Rings-Necklace-Pink-Gold.html]Cartier Pink Gold[/url] 
Cartier Marcello De Cartier Worldwide Tote Bag in Black Crocodile Printed Leather. The exceptional Marcello de Cartier leather goods collection pays striking tribute to Cartier&#39;s unique skill. Precious leathers are fashioned from python, crocodile, water-snakeskin and calfskin suede, honouring traditional methods of craftsmanship. Signature features of Cartier&#39;s premier leather goods collection include openwork, topstitched corners and charms bearing the “double C” logo. 
[url=http://www.hellojewelry.co.uk/categories/Cartier-Rings/]Cartier Rings[/url]  
Cartier Love Earring Gold Come from Love collection, the LOVE collection is both a provocative talisman and a bold symbol of passionate love. 100% similar to the original, so you save your money. Great opportunity to own a genuine Cartier love earring at a great price. 
[url=http://www.hellojewelry.co.uk/]Cartier Love Bracelet[/url]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 02:39:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Uncategorized</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cartier-love-bangles/510111.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Cartier Love Bangles</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jokeflk jokeflk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jokeflk">@jokeflk</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The company has a long and distinguished history, as well as stars and celebities. One Prince of Wales hailed Cartier as “Joaillier des Rois, Roi des Joailliers” (Jeweller to Kings, King of Jewellers"). Cartier received an order for 27 tiaras for the coronation of the future King. King Edward VII was crowned in 1902 and in 1904 he honoured the Company with the Royal warrant of supplier to the Royal Court of England. Similar warrants soon followed from the courts of Spain, Portugal, Russia, Siam, Greece, Serbia, Belgium, Romania, Egypt and finally Albania, and also from the House of Orleans and the Principality of Monaco.<br>
<a href="http://www.hellojewelry.co.uk/products/Cartier-Double-Love-Rings-Necklace-Pink-Gold.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Cartier Pink Gold</a><br>
Cartier Marcello De Cartier Worldwide Tote Bag in Black Crocodile Printed Leather. The exceptional Marcello de Cartier leather goods collection pays striking tribute to Cartier’s unique skill. Precious leathers are fashioned from python, crocodile, water-snakeskin and calfskin suede, honouring traditional methods of craftsmanship. Signature features of Cartier’s premier leather goods collection include openwork, topstitched corners and charms bearing the “double C” logo.<br>
<a href="http://www.hellojewelry.co.uk/categories/Cartier-Rings/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Cartier Rings</a><br>
Cartier Love Earring Gold Come from Love collection, the LOVE collection is both a provocative talisman and a bold symbol of passionate love. 100% similar to the original, so you save your money. Great opportunity to own a genuine Cartier love earring at a great price.<br>
<a href="http://www.hellojewelry.co.uk/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Cartier Love Bracelet</a></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cartier-love-bangles/510111/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cartier-love-bangles/510111/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 02:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-510111-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/cartier-love-bangles/510111.rss">Cartier Love Bangles</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
