<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Ops II: Glitching</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/black-ops-ii-glitching/511834</link>
    <description>So me and a few friends have been doing locked XP lobbies lately, which is good and all, but it has its downsides. Back before 1.08 (the latest update), you could run this lobby with bots set to recruit in the lobby with your friends. I just need some help figuring out a way to exploit this once again, after the most recent patches. For those of you that don&#39;t know about the glitch, I&#39;ll explain it, so that you can see if there is a time to set up bots or not.

First you have to sit there and hover over public match, while your friend selects a game mode and map. After this is done, your friend must press B and hover over the &quot;yes&quot; to leave lobby. Then, while still hovering over public match, press Y to go to your friends list, the press X to join his session in progress, RIGHT after you press X, begin to spam A. The 2nd player must leave the lobby the second your name pops up, and you must keep spamming A until your PUBLIC MATCH create a classes pop up, once the pop up, quickly press B and go to your name on the right, and press A to go to your player card. If you don&#39;t, you will freeze.

You can&#39;t leave the player card ever until the game starts, and the bots don&#39;t carry over from the custom game lobby to the public match. With there being some knowledge of how game codes work in this community, I&#39;m hoping I can get some intelligent ideas from you all, for me and my friend to try.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 20:14:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Games</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/black-ops-ii-glitching/511834.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Black Ops II: Glitching</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@tyb97 tyb97]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/tyb97">@tyb97</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>So me and a few friends have been doing locked XP lobbies lately, which is good and all, but it has its downsides. Back before 1.08 (the latest update), you could run this lobby with bots set to recruit in the lobby with your friends. I just need some help figuring out a way to exploit this once again, after the most recent patches. For those of you that don’t know about the glitch, I’ll explain it, so that you can see if there is a time to set up bots or not.</p>
<p>First you have to sit there and hover over public match, while your friend selects a game mode and map. After this is done, your friend must press B and hover over the “yes” to leave lobby. Then, while still hovering over public match, press Y to go to your friends list, the press X to join his session in progress, RIGHT after you press X, begin to spam A. The 2nd player must leave the lobby the second your name pops up, and you must keep spamming A until your PUBLIC MATCH create a classes pop up, once the pop up, quickly press B and go to your name on the right, and press A to go to your player card. If you don’t, you will freeze.</p>
<p>You can’t leave the player card ever until the game starts, and the bots don’t carry over from the custom game lobby to the public match. With there being some knowledge of how game codes work in this community, I’m hoping I can get some intelligent ideas from you all, for me and my friend to try.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/black-ops-ii-glitching/511834/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/black-ops-ii-glitching/511834/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 20:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-511834-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/black-ops-ii-glitching/511834.rss">Black Ops II: Glitching</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
