<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629</link>
    <description>Today we see jagex have made an update to rune ess mining. 
&lt;blockquote&gt;  20 April 2006 - Rune Essence adjustment   
Today we have made an adjustment to rune essence mining due to players breaking rule 7 and rule 12, using macros to mine the rune essence and then selling it. 
As you are probably aware we have various systems in place to detect people breaking rule 7 and ban them. These systems work very effectively at detecting people breaking this rule, and make macroing a really bad way to try and train a high level character. 

The problem we are now solving is not a problem with our macro detection systems which are still working well, but rather a problem with banning being an ineffective punishment against abusers who only use very low level accounts, and who have no intention of ever playing the game properly. 

Over the last few weeks we have banned literally hundreds of accounts a day for macroing at the rune essence mine. However the bans were ineffective as the abusers could just create more low level accounts that they didn&#39;t care about to mine more. We also track trades so we can ban the recipiant of the illegally obtained items, but the abusers in this case were swapping the runes for gp, and then selling the gp for real world money on auction sites. Of course the person buying the gp for real world money gets banned, because we track the money they received in an unbalanced trade to a macro account, but the seller doesn&#39;t care that their customers get banned shortly after, as they have their real world money by then. 

The fundamental problem is that rune essence was one of the few areas of the game which could be used to generate a reasonable amount of RuneScape money on a &#39;throwaway&#39; low level free account. Normally to earn large amounts of money quickly you need to level up an account first, and then of course you care if it gets banned so our normal deterrant is effective. 

We have therefore split rune essence to have 2 grades. Normal essence can only be used to make the six basic runes, whereas pure essence can be used to make any rune. You can mine both types of essence at the same place as before. The kind of essence you receive is automatically decided when you mine the rock. You will always get pure essence only if your mining is over 30 and you are on a members&#39; world, otherwise you will get normal essence. 

As a one-off event whilst we introduce this, existing essence in your bank and inventory will have been automatically converted to pure essence if you are a member or have other members-only items in your bank. 

Since free players can only craft the six basic runes anyway, the normal essence is just as good for its intended purpose of letting free players do low level rune crafting. However it is not so useful for selling to members who want to make law and nature runes (who we believe buy the vast majority of rune essence in Runescape) which should reduce its price significantly and make it a much less appealing proposition for real world traders. 

The only people who should be significantly affected by this are players mining very large amounts of essence on free accounts purely to sell to members. There are better way of making money on high level free accounts anyway, so this change should only really affect players trying to making large amounts of money on a low level free account - which is of course the exact idea. 

We would also like to yet again remind our players NOT to break rule 12 and be tempted to buy RuneScape gold for real world money. Nearly all the gold being offered for sale in this way was generated by cheating on &#39;throwaway&#39; accounts. If you buy it not only are you encouraging further cheating, but you run the very real risk of being banned yourself as the money you receive is dirty money and will be tracked. Again we have banned countless players for breaking rule 12 and fuelling this problem, and will continue to do so. 

We hope most players will agree we shouldn&#39;t let rule breakers spoil this game, and we are determined to not let them do so. As well as banning, where necessary we will also make minimal changes to the game to make rule breaking unviable&lt;/blockquote&gt;
What are your opinions on this, do u think this update seriously fucks up autoers? 
I reckon it does  :(</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 00:24:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BlackThursday BlackThursday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blackthursday">@BlackThursday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I tell ya jme, sum radicals are gonna sue sayin jagex is trying to extort them for $5 a month, you know what happens if they win, more for the free people, or jagex jus goes down all together.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 00:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-38</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jme jme]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jme">@jme</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I am laughing about all the topics of this on like every runescape forum imaginable. </p>

<p>Well, either way if it gets bad then they'll try to fix it. Although, I hope the economy gets even more killed(if it's possible?). It'll be funny to see what happens in a few months from now.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 00:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-37</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BlackThursday BlackThursday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blackthursday">@BlackThursday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Its gonna be ok guys, sell you ess. If jagex goes after miners people are gonna shit on em. OR if they go after miners people are gonna join members in which case people are gonna start coming forward sayin jagex is extorting them and trying to force people to join members cause free suks.. OH there will be lawsuits.</p>

<p>Jagex couldn't track accts if they wanted to. Jagex cant even track a lawnmower through an overgrown field. Bastards.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 00:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-36</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Daniel1234 Daniel1234]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/daniel1234">@Daniel1234</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="4" data-topic="1629"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/letter_avatar_proxy/v2/letter/s/bbce88/40.png" class="avatar">skt4ever:</div>
<blockquote><p>rofl...this update did nothing to autoers and fucked up guys like me who had 1000k + ess in bank to do my nats on main and now have to buy the stupid "pure ess"</p></blockquote></aside>

<p>All of youre ess would have been converted if you were making nats because you have to be a member to make nats</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2006 22:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-35</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="27" data-topic="1629"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/letter_avatar_proxy/v2/letter/d/9d8465/40.png" class="avatar">Dingo212:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Listen up people,</p>
<p>Normal ess prices wont drop or something...so far we are  good to go. The only thing is, if you are   a member AND WANT TO CRAFT NAT/LAW/DEATH then you need pure ess...which means pure ess will go up...nothing big to us..or gonna stop us...infact they are receiving lots of complaints from their 'legit' players.</p>
<p>Logically looking...the normal ess will be around 35ea...which we can keep doing. But pure ess will be around 70ea. Nothing lost here...</p>
<p>JagEx just pushed a 5 x 20 dildo up its own arse</p>
<p>[br][size=1]Posted at: April 21, 2006, 09:56:13 am[/size][hr][quote author=yna_ajhear5 link=topic=1662.msg16051#msg16051 date=1145620130]<br>you should be complaining about the economy.</p>
<p>Just wait till nats are 500ea.</p>
<p>And regular ess sells for 2ea.</p>
<p>...Just wait. That, my friend, it the Runescape economy.</p>
</blockquote></aside>

<p>why would regular ess 2ea? nats = 500ea...reasonable..</p>

<p>But think ppl...</p>

<p>Because of this...lots of rcing ppl will switch to airs...(so cheap ess)</p>

<p>Because of that...the demand will be there...so the normal ess will be up and around 30ea...</p>

<p>the only thing gonna go up is pure ess prices and high lvl rune prices[/quote]</p>

<p>Normal ess will go down quite a bit. Unless you have a stupidly high runecrafting level you won't make much off selling normal runes. In 1 year of F2P, my friend got 27 runecrafting. In <em>1 night</em> of using Mad Cow's air crafter, I got 37.</p>

<p>Basically, pure ess can only make runes up to body. Now, using data from tip.it, you need either 35 runecrafting to make double fires, 40gp for both of them, or 70 for 3 times fires for 60gp, or 1680 per load. Since no one really buys earths and waters in bulk we'll exclude them. 77 Runecrafting needed for 8 times airs, or 4480 per load, about the same or a little bit more with minds, after awhile no one will need air/mind/water/earth/fire runes because all the autoers move on to crafting them and we have bulk, members ess won't run out for awhile since alot of it was drop traded so in a month or 2, all the members ess will be dropping so low there won't be enough pure ess, this is where supply and demand comes in. Not enough supplyers means the demand goes up, the price goes up and if it gets too bad people will become members to mine ess to sell for even more profit. Either that or too many people will complain and it will go back to normal.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2006 11:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-34</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Exernet Exernet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exernet">@Exernet</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="32" data-topic="1629"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/letter_avatar_proxy/v2/letter/p/ecae2f/40.png" class="avatar">poopy4231:</div>
<blockquote><p>tell me about it.. i just autoed 100k ess in a day and a half now this update...</p></blockquote></aside>

<p>Oh wow, an entire day of running your computer, cry me a river</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/33</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 22:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-33</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@poopy4231 poopy4231]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/poopy4231">@poopy4231</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>tell me about it.. i just autoed 100k ess in a day and a half now this update...</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/32</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 21:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-32</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SuperNewb SuperNewb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/supernewb">@SuperNewb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>it's the end of the autoing world as I see it...</p>

<p>Andrew: Paul, why are the lights goin' out?<br>Paul: 'cause of the runecrafting system!<br>Andrew: What does that have to do with lights?<br>-Blackout-<br>Andrew:  :eek:<br>Noobs:  <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/confused.png?v=3" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"><br>Noob: Oh sheet runescape crashed.<br>Other Noob: Who cares? <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=3" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"><br>Noobs:Party!  <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/cool.png?v=3" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/cool.png?v=3" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/cool.png?v=3" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"> <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/cool.png?v=3" title=":cool:" class="emoji" alt=":cool:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/31</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 20:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-31</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Exernet Exernet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exernet">@Exernet</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Regular essence is pointless, don't you understand that the essence economy relies ONLY on P2P. F2P runecrafters are maybe 5% of total essence sales. Nobody will pay a reasonable price for the regular essence, as they can just buy the runes themselves cheaper. Essence autoing is over, just face it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 20:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-30</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Nashiu Nashiu]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/nashiu">@Nashiu</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I've always wanted to get a group of like 100+ people all in one place, preferrably Varrock Square and start auto-talking using SCAR all saying the same thing. Preferrably a world packed with people in Varrock. <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/slight_smile.png?v=3" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 18:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-29</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@BlackThursday BlackThursday]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/blackthursday">@BlackThursday</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Calm down everyone. Your all complaining how you cant sell your ess anymore. Of course you can sell you ess because mages need RUNECRAFT skill to even thin kabout makin higher runes. The market will take a hit yes, but we do as MissSilabsoft said still have the Moparironbanker and such (btw it could use some tweaking).</p>

<p>So the way i see it one of two things will happen:<br>1) Jagex keeps bein bitchy to the non-mems and people start switching to members and jagex makes alooot of $, at which point people will start to accuse them of extortion or sumthin like that.</p>

<p>2) keep bein bitches to non-mems and everyone goes to iron and copper mining and they lock that up too in which case everyone starts to bitch and Jagex takes a gigantic finacial hit.</p>

<p>Add or correct to this. I jus want to see them suffer for this pure ess shit.</p>

<p>And Akriam, keep workin on that code.. That'll be the day jagex shits their pants.. over 120 non-members walkin around wit pure ess that they didn't buy or sell from anyone.And on the subject of them stalkin ur acct and the people you trade to:Jagex couldn't track a  lawnmover through an overgrown field. Dumbasses.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 17:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-28</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Dingo212 Dingo212]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/dingo212">@Dingo212</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Listen up people,</p>

<p>Normal ess prices wont drop or something...so far we are  good to go. The only thing is, if you are   a member AND WANT TO CRAFT NAT/LAW/DEATH then you need pure ess...which means pure ess will go up...nothing big to us..or gonna stop us...infact they are receiving lots of complaints from their 'legit' players.</p>

<p>Logically looking...the normal ess will be around 35ea...which we can keep doing. But pure ess will be around 70ea. Nothing lost here...</p>

<p>JagEx just pushed a 5 x 20 dildo up its own arse</p>

<p>[br][size=1]Posted at: April 21, 2006, 09:56:13 am[/size][hr]</p>

<aside class="quote" data-post="24" data-topic="1629"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/letter_avatar_proxy/v2/letter/y/858c86/40.png" class="avatar">yna_ajhear5:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>you should be complaining about the economy.</p>
<p>Just wait till nats are 500ea.</p>
<p>And regular ess sells for 2ea.</p>
<p>...Just wait. That, my friend, it the Runescape economy.</p>
</blockquote></aside>

<p>why would regular ess 2ea? nats = 500ea...reasonable..</p>

<p>But think ppl...</p>

<p>Because of this...lots of rcing ppl will switch to airs...(so cheap ess)</p>

<p>Because of that...the demand will be there...so the normal ess will be up and around 30ea...</p>

<p>the only thing gonna go up is pure ess prices and high lvl rune prices</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-27</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Andrew Andrew]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/andrew">@Andrew</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="9" data-topic="1629"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/user_avatar/forum.moparisthebest.com/moparisthebest/40/30_1.png" class="avatar">moparisthebest:</div>
<blockquote><p>I merged the 2 topics, since they were the same thing <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/emoji_one/wink.png?v=3" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p></blockquote></aside>

<p>Cool you can do that lol?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 14:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-26</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Un-Named The Un-Named]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_un-named">@The_Un-Named</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>When nats get over 400 each mages will complain. There won't be enough member ess miners to keep up with the alchers and runecrafters.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 13:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-25</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yna_ajhear5 yna_ajhear5]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/yna_ajhear5">@yna_ajhear5</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>you should be complaining about the economy.</p>

<p>Just wait till nats are 500ea.</p>

<p>And regular ess sells for 2ea.</p>

<p>...Just wait. That, my friend, it the Runescape economy.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 11:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-24</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@okeR okeR]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/oker">@okeR</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Lol, who's complaining about the economy. Its not like the fucking stock market or anything. But a bad move on jagex behaf nevertheless.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 10:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-23</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KyleGut3 KyleGut3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kylegut3">@KyleGut3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>LMAO thats awesome, but we would need to organize a LOT of autoers to do it at the same time.. on the same world with like 1-10 characters each <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/smiley.png?v=3" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 04:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-22</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@anony2 anony2]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/anony2">@anony2</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i say we send hundreds of autoers to the same spot and constantly saying "jagex suhks autoers ftw!" </p>

<p>see how mad they get then</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 02:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-21</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@KyleGut3 KyleGut3]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/kylegut3">@KyleGut3</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>well this bites.. i have 52k ess in my bank that I wanted to sell off D:</p>

<p>and eventually i was going to become a member on my main just SO I could make the higher runes.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/20</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 02:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-20</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@1337h4x 1337h4x]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/1337h4x">@1337h4x</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>whats next? the only rock non members can mine is tin?<br>and then the only fish nonmems can fish is shrimp?</p>

<p>SCRUW JAGEX PL0X</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 01:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-19</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Im working on a way to send code through the server to change items! I will change all of the essence back! Every last one! (check out the thread under Questions and Talk about Rs2 client hacking) Im not sure it will work though (the thread is called ..::Idea::..)</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/18</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 21:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-18</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SuperNewb SuperNewb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/supernewb">@SuperNewb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>and I was just about to sell my largest load (15k) of ess yesterday  :mad:<br>if we strike against runescape, i'm bringing the torches</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/17</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 21:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-17</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Akriam Akriam]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/akriam">@Akriam</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Autoers = Owned??</p>

<p>Jagex = Owned</p>

<p>By who?</p>

<p>Jagex = Owned by Jagex and the mages with there Natures. This will ruin the economy![br][size=1]Posted at: April 20, 2006, 02:07:29 pm[/size][hr]Erm...Somewhat ruin it!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/16</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 21:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-16</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Exernet Exernet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/exernet">@Exernet</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote" data-post="14" data-topic="1629"><div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/letter_avatar_proxy/v2/letter/s/fbc32d/40.png" class="avatar">SuperNewb:</div>
<blockquote><p>hello chaos<br>goodbye economy<br>haha jagex pwned themselves!<br>runescape will soon (years?) die, unless noobs still want to play<br>projected earnings for jagex: $0,000,000.01<br>mages will strike, runescape will pay  <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/smiley.png?v=3" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p></blockquote></aside>

<p>Runescape has 200k+ players playing simultaneosly and rising, it's not dieng any time soon.</p>

<p>People will just mine iron and guild mine now...</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/15</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 21:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-15</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Autoers = owned?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SuperNewb SuperNewb]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/supernewb">@SuperNewb</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>hello chaos<br>goodbye economy<br>haha jagex pwned themselves!<br>runescape will soon (years?) die, unless noobs still want to play<br>projected earnings for jagex: $0,000,000.01<br>mages will strike, runescape will pay  <img src="//forum.moparisthebest.mopar/images/emoji/emoji_one/smiley.png?v=3" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629/14</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 19:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-1629-14</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/autoers-owned/1629.rss">Autoers = owned?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
