<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Server Tool&#39;s Discussion Thread</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672</link>
    <description>This thread is for those who have recently, or have had tools that can be used in making the development of a server Fast, or Easier. Try to include a clear discription to the subject, and what excactly it does. I&#39;ve created a tool, so why don&#39;t you read my Tool Discription to give you an idea on what to post:

I recently developed a Tool, which is actually simple enough to be a command, server or client-side!

The command, is &quot; ::clip &quot;, and &quot; ::checkclip &quot;


The ::Clip command allows you to add Noclipping to the specified area your standing on. Adding Noclipping manually for certain regions can take tiring minutes, to sometimes hours. This command helped me develop the entire Lumbridge, and Draynor area with every bit of objects &quot;Noclipped&quot;, so NPCs can&#39;t walk through them on their current x and y positioning in only two hours! That would be days doing it manually!

The command feaures Three Core Files. One Main one, and two sub files. The Main file creates the File writing system to add new lines of code to the Noclipping procedure. The two subfiles have miscellaneous purposes in the method that have different particular properties.

The &quot; ::CheckClip &quot; command works quite simple. Just stand over any coordinate that you wish to check weather or not it&#39;s &quot;Noclipped&quot;, which is, coordinates that can&#39;t be walked through by NPCs. Then it will send a Message to the Player, of weather or not the coordinates is are Noclipped.

If they&#39;re not, it will prompt the user to verify confirmation to weather or not create the coordinate &quot;Noclipped&quot;.



This is very easy, and FAST. I&#39;ve done some many new developments with just a simple yet basic command that doesn&#39;t even seem worth doing as big. Discuss what you think about this, and some useful tools that you&#39;ve developed in the past that became a big role in development:


DISCUSS</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 22:48:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Server Tool&#39;s Discussion Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@deathschaos9 DeathsChaos9]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/deathschaos9">@deathschaos9</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I don’t see any significance in this thread, and its not really server development.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 22:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-368672-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672.rss">Server Tool&#39;s Discussion Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server Tool&#39;s Discussion Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asyo4 asyo4]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/asyo4">@asyo4</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>this isnt a development…?</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 21:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-368672-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672.rss">Server Tool&#39;s Discussion Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server Tool&#39;s Discussion Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@PLayRooney PLayRooney]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/playrooney">@PLayRooney</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Nice man.<br>
First post <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 21:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-368672-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672.rss">Server Tool&#39;s Discussion Thread</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Server Tool&#39;s Discussion Thread</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@QuestMaster_2K10 QuestMaster 2K10]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/questmaster_2k10">@QuestMaster_2K10</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>This thread is for those who have recently, or have had tools that can be used in making the development of a server Fast, or Easier. Try to include a clear discription to the subject, and what excactly it does. I’ve created a tool, so why don’t you read my Tool Discription to give you an idea on what to post:</p>
<p>I recently developed a Tool, which is actually simple enough to be a command, server or client-side!</p>
<p>The command, is " ::clip ", and " ::checkclip "</p>
<p>The ::Clip command allows you to add Noclipping to the specified area your standing on. Adding Noclipping manually for certain regions can take tiring minutes, to sometimes hours. This command helped me develop the entire Lumbridge, and Draynor area with every bit of objects “Noclipped”, so NPCs can’t walk through them on their current x and y positioning in only two hours! That would be days doing it manually!</p>
<p>The command feaures Three Core Files. One Main one, and two sub files. The Main file creates the File writing system to add new lines of code to the Noclipping procedure. The two subfiles have miscellaneous purposes in the method that have different particular properties.</p>
<p>The " ::CheckClip " command works quite simple. Just stand over any coordinate that you wish to check weather or not it’s “Noclipped”, which is, coordinates that can’t be walked through by NPCs. Then it will send a Message to the Player, of weather or not the coordinates is are Noclipped.</p>
<p>If they’re not, it will prompt the user to verify confirmation to weather or not create the coordinate “Noclipped”.</p>
<p>This is very easy, and FAST. I’ve done some many new developments with just a simple yet basic command that doesn’t even seem worth doing as big. Discuss what you think about this, and some useful tools that you’ve developed in the past that became a big role in development:</p>
<p>DISCUSS</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 07:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-368672-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/server-tools-discussion-thread/368672.rss">Server Tool&#39;s Discussion Thread</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
