<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Error: T2, mismatch in getplayer pos</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-t2-mismatch-in-getplayer-pos/134179</link>
    <description>Alright everyone, my server is buggin&#39; me out. PKing works, ALMOST. I&#39;m trying to actually learn the stuff here, and perhaps I should look at a tut, but I haven&#39;t for now. 

The error occurs ALMOST every time I attack another player in the server. The reason for this I&#39;m not really sure though. It seems like the client doesn&#39;t know where the other player is when it attacks it, and ultimately goes berserk and crashes. The server is fine however, just the client freaks out.

Now, there have been a few times that the client hasn&#39;t crashed, mind you, both crashed normally.

1. (Once) I attacked a player who had been sitting there for a long time while searching these forums. Player attacking did not crashed, but the one being attacked was. The player who was attacking had to move to attack.

2. (Once) The player who was attacked died in the first hit, which then led to some crazy bugs. He died, and was teled back to where you start. But then, I logged back in on the attacking client who crashed, and he was no where to be found. Seems like an error with updating positon, but I thought I had fixed that problem with NPC&#39;s on death, why would it be different for people?

If anyone is willing to get me started in the right direction, just leave some posts. I have to get a haircut, so I won&#39;t be able to reply for an hour. =\ Thanks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2007 21:41:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Runescape</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-t2-mismatch-in-getplayer-pos/134179.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Error: T2, mismatch in getplayer pos</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Archbishop Archbishop]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/archbishop">@Archbishop</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Alright everyone, my server is buggin’ me out. PKing works, ALMOST. I’m trying to actually learn the stuff here, and perhaps I should look at a tut, but I haven’t for now.</p>
<p>The error occurs ALMOST every time I attack another player in the server. The reason for this I’m not really sure though. It seems like the client doesn’t know where the other player is when it attacks it, and ultimately goes berserk and crashes. The server is fine however, just the client freaks out.</p>
<p>Now, there have been a few times that the client hasn’t crashed, mind you, both crashed normally.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>(Once) I attacked a player who had been sitting there for a long time while searching these forums. Player attacking did not crashed, but the one being attacked was. The player who was attacking had to move to attack.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>(Once) The player who was attacked died in the first hit, which then led to some crazy bugs. He died, and was teled back to where you start. But then, I logged back in on the attacking client who crashed, and he was no where to be found. Seems like an error with updating positon, but I thought I had fixed that problem with NPC’s on death, why would it be different for people?</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>If anyone is willing to get me started in the right direction, just leave some posts. I have to get a haircut, so I won’t be able to reply for an hour. =\ Thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-t2-mismatch-in-getplayer-pos/134179/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-t2-mismatch-in-getplayer-pos/134179/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2007 21:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-134179-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/error-t2-mismatch-in-getplayer-pos/134179.rss">Error: T2, mismatch in getplayer pos</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
