<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
    <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675</link>
    <description>[size=20pt][b]THESE ARE NOT MINE THEY ARE TAKEN FROM VARIOUS WEBSITES![/b][/size]
Easter Eggs (Definition) - A hidden message or feature in an application. This guide covers the undocumented and hidden features in Windows XP. All of the following were tested in Windows XP only.


[u][size=19pt][b]Norton[/b][/size][/u]
[b]Norton Anti-Virus[/b]
[tt]Norton Antivirus - Developers&#39; Credits 

In Norton Antivirus, click on the menu Help, About 
Hold down N, A, &amp; V all at the same time 
A dialog box with the picture of the Norton Antivirus team appears 
To close it, press Esc[/tt]

[b]Norton DeskTop[/b]
[tt]Norton Desktop - Developers&#39; Credits 

From the menu, select Help, About menu. 
Click three times while holding down the keys N, D, and W[/tt]

[b]Norton Utilities[/b]
[tt]Norton Utilities - Special Movies

Pop into your drive the Norton Utilities CD-ROM 
Go to the folder named Media on the CD-ROM. 
The easter eggs themselves are in  two AVI files named Egg1.avi &amp; Egg2.avi 
Double-click a file &amp; watch the Norton Staff morphing and getting soaked 
Norton Utilities - Developers&#39; Credits

Open any Norton Utilities application under windows that has a menu. 
On the menubar, click on Help, About 
Depending on your version of Norton Utilities, you will have to press N, U &amp; 8 keys or N, U &amp; W 
Press them simultaneously. 
THe credits screen should appear 
The rest are all self-explainary[/tt]

[b]Norton Commander[/b]
[tt]Norton Commander - Developers&#39; Credits 

Select  Help, About 
Press CTRL while double-clicking on Icon 
A large photo of the programming team will appear[/tt]

[b]Norton NT Tools[/b]
[tt]Norton NT Tools - Developers&#39; Credits 

Open any Norton Utilities application under windows that has a menu. 
On the menubar, click on Help, About 
Press simultaneously N &amp; T 
THe credits screen should appear 
The rest are all self-explainary[/tt]



[u][size=19pt][b]MicroSoft[/b][/size][/u]
[b]MS Front Page[/b]
[tt]Frontpage 97/98 - Developers&#39; Credits

Start FrontPage Explorer. 
With FrontPage Explorer application open, hold down the Shift key 
Select Help | About 
Click OK 
With the Shfit key still held down, click on Help | About for the second time 
Click OK 
With the Shfit key still held down, click on Help | About for the last time 
The credits screen should appear with a song[/tt]

[b]MS OutLook[/b]
[tt]Outlook 97/98 - Developers Credits

Click on the menubar, Contact | New Contact
Name of contact is Ren Hoek. Save the contact
On the left side, click on contact and then click on the new contact name you have just created
Click on the menubar, Help | About Microsoft Outlook
Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and click on the OK button
THe credits screen should appear. If you want more, click on the link and it will bring you to the online credits screen
[/tt]

[b]MS PowerPoint[/b]
[tt]Access 97 - Developers Credits

Create a new normal database
Make new table and save it as Go Speed Racer Go 
Choose Help, About and right double-click on the Bitmap.

Access 97 - Make My Computer Smile

On the toolbar, click on the Help menu and go to Find
Search for the word happiness or smile.&quot; 
The sentence Make my computer smile comes up although it isn&#39;t in 

PowerPoint 97

Open PowerPoint 97 
Click on Help/About 
Click on PowerPoint Icon 
[/tt]

[b]MS Visual C++[/b]
[tt]Visual C++ - Developers&#39; Credit 

Put your Visual C++ CD-ROM in your CD-ROM drive 
Start Visual C++ 
Click on the Help, About menu 
Hold down Ctrl and double-click, releasing Ctrl at same time as 2nd click is released 
Visual C++ 2.2 displays a spinning plus, with programmer credits 
Visual C++ 4.0 lets you fly around a landscape made up of programmer mug shots. 
Use the keypad to navigate and the A &amp; Z to accelerate/decelerate[/tt]

[b]MS Access[/b]
[tt]Access 97 - Developers Credits

Create a new normal database
Make new table and save it as Go Speed Racer Go 
Choose Help, About and right double-click on the Bitmap.

Access 97 - Make My Computer Smile 

On the toolbar, click on the Help menu and go to Find 
Search for the word happiness or smile 
The sentence Make my computer smile comes up although it isn&#39;t in 
Access 97 - Magic Eight Ball 

Load Acess 
Create a blank database 
Click on the Macros tab 
Click on New 
Press space 
Close the dialog box 
Click Yes 
Save this macro as Magic Eight Ball 
Go to View | Toolbars | Customize... and check on Macro Design 
Drag the macro to the second toolbar, start clicking on it[/tt]

[b]MS Excel[/b]
[tt]Excel 95 - Hall Of The Tortured Souls 

Open a blank work sheet 
Go down to the 95th row 
Select the whole row 
Tab over to coloum B 
Goto Help/About 
Hold down ctrl-alt-shift 
and click on the tech support button 
A window appears call &quot;Hall of Tortured souls&quot; 
At the end of the hall and all the programmers names. This is something a Doom simulation. 
Now, here&#39;s the fun part: do a 180 turn and type excelkfa. Walk through the wall and see the pictures. 
Excel 97 - Another Copy Of A Menu Item 

Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift 
Click on any menu item 
You will see the cursor with a plus sign 
Drag it to another part of the menu 
You will now have another copy of the menu item! 
Excel 97 - Flight Simulation 

On a new Worksheet, Press F5 
Type X97:L97 and hit enter 
Press the Tab key 
Hold Ctrl-Shift 
Click on the Chart Wizard toolbar button 
Depending on how well your DirectX is intergrated, you will either find yourself in an eerrie lanscape or if you are using Windows 98, you will probably find yourself in a beautiful purple lanscape. 
Use mouse to fly around - Right button forward/ Left button reverse 
There shoud be a hidden shrine in the middle with the programmers message. 
Here&#39;s more: 

Face the hidden shrine (credits screen) 
Move foreward towards the Hill using the left click for foreward thrust 
At the edge of the Hill stop the thrust using right click 
Point the view down by moving the mouse upwards 
You should then see at the bottom of the cliff a water motion 
There&#39;s the Blue Laggoon![/tt]

[b]MS Office[/b]
[tt]Microsoft Office 95/97 - Developers&#39; Credits

Click on small four-color square on the MS Office toolbar 
Click on About Microsoft Office 
Hold down Ctrl-Shift and double-click on the MS Office Logo 
Floating Splash screen appears 
Click anywhere on the plate[/tt]

[b]MS Plus![/b]
[tt]Usually after creating a software, the computer programmers will include a credit screen. However, they are usually hidden, like an Easter Egg. These are the list of easter eggs you can find in common software.

Plus! 95/98 Unnoticed Mouse Cursor

Many of us didn&#39;t notice this before but here it is. The busy mouse cursor for the Inside My Computer theme is a monitor with the number 101011 scrolling. This binary string, translated into ASCII is actually &quot;+&quot;  which stands for Plus!

Plus! 98 - Developers&#39; Credits 

Go to the edit playlist dialog for any song. 
Type Microsoft Plus!98 Product Team in for the artist 
Type Credits in for the title 
Hold down the control key and click cancel [/tt]

[b]MS Visual Basic[/b]
[tt]Visual Basic 5.0 - Developers Credits

Launch Visual Basic 5.0 
When the New Project dialog box appears, just click Open 
Click the View menu, point to Toolbars, and click Customize 
Go to the Commands tab 
Click the Help category, and drag the About Microsoft Visual Basic item into the help menu 
Click the Modify Selection button and set the name for the newly inserted menu item to Show VB Credits 
Click the Close button 
From the Help menu, choose Show VB Credits 
Visual Basic 4.0 - Developers Credits 

Add a test box to a form set its text property to Thunder 
Lock the control on the form 
Move mouse over the tools in the toolbox 
The names of developers and testers should appear instead of the usual tooltips![/tt]

[b]MS Word[/b]
[tt]Word Viewer

Go to Help/About... 
Hold down Ctrl and Shift and click on the logo 

Word 97 - Floating Word 97 Splash Screen

Select Help, About Microsoft Word 
The About Box appears 
Hold down Ctrl+Shift+Alt keys 
Click on the horizontal divider in the About Box 
A floating splash screen appears

Word 97 - Deletable Menu Items

Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and the cursor should change into a minus sign. Click on a menu and then click on any menu item.
That menu item will disappear! Don&#39;t worry, this is only temporary and will be restored the next time you restart your computer
If you really need it back, right-click on the toolbar and select Customize... Highlight Menu Bar and click on Reset... 
The menu item wuill be restored

Word 97 - No Competition 

Word knows when to win a competition. Type Maxis, highlight the word and run the Thesaurus 
Then type Smartsuite and look at that 
Word 97 - Define zzzz

Open a blank document and type zzzz and run the spell checker. See what&#39;s the definition for it.

Word 97 - Problems? 

Open a new document in Word 
Type Unable to follow directions 
Highlight the entire sentence you just typed 
Click Tools, Thesaurus (or hit shift-F7 to open the thesaurus) 
Now, does Bill Gates have a problem the world doesn&#39;t know about? 

Word 97 - Naked? 

Open Word and type I&#39;d love to see you naked. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus. 
Try I want to see you naked and be just as suprised! 
Word 97 - Pagan?

Open Word and type Who is God?. Highlight the word and run a spell check. See who does the Word 97 programmers think God is.

Word 97 - Corny Developers? 

Open Word and type I love porn. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus. 
How about typing I am gay and run the thesaurus again. 
Word 97 - Hairy?

Open Word and type Shag Me. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus. How&#39;s the definition?

Word 97 - Define Eat Me Shorts 

Open Word and type Eat Me Shorts. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus. 
What does it says? 
Word 97 - Can I ... 

Open Word and type May I screw your daughter?. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus. 
Check out the answer. 
Word 97 - Biological Associates 

Open Word and type Ice boobs go with what?. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus. 
Check out the associate - now who says Word is dumb? 
Word 97 - Bill Gates Dead? 

Open Word and type I’d like to see Bill Gates dead 
On the Tools, Language, Set Launguage menu, set the language to English (United States) 
Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus 
Enjoy what you see 
Word 97 - Naughty, naughty! 

On any document, type in Love her and leave her 
Highlight the text, press Shift+F7 to activate the thesaurus and enjoy! 

-Twin Towers
1. Open MS Word

2. Change font to Wingdings

3. Change font size to 36

4. Type in Q33 NY[/tt]

[b]MS Developer Studio[/b]
[tt]Developer Studio 97 - Developers&#39; Credits 

On the Developer Studio CD-ROM, look around for a file named DEVCRD.DLL in the \DEVSTUDIO\SHAREDIDE\Bin directory. 
Right-click and copy that file to the C:\DevStudio\SharedIDE\Bin folder on your hard disk. 
Launch a Developer Studio component such as Visual C++. 
Click on the Help, About menu, hold down Ctrl and click anywhere in the dialog box.[/tt]


[u][size=19pt][b]Adobe[/b][/size][/u]
[b]Adobe Illustrator[/b]
[tt]Adobe Illustrator - Credits Screen

Launch Illustrator 
Press CTRL+ALT and click on the Venus picture on the top of the toolbar. 
The credit screen comes up, with all the developers name anagrammed[/tt]

[b]Adobe Photo Deluxe[/b]
[tt]Adobe Photo Deluxe - Developers Credits

Launch Adobe Photodeluxe 
Click on Help, About Photodeluxe 
Hold down ALT for 5 seconds 
The credits screen will appear [/tt]

[b]Adobe PageMaker[/b]
[tt]Adobe Pagemaker - Dedication Flower

Launch Pagemaker 
Press Ctrl-Alt-Shift 
Click on Help, About 
Double Click the logo (a flower will appear)[/tt]

[b]Adobe Photoshop[/b]
[tt]Adobe Photoshop 4/5 - Credits Screen

Hold down Alt and click on Help, About Photoshop... 
You will see a different about box with the Big Electric Cat 
Wait for a few seconds 
The credits screen will start to scroll 
Hold down Alt to speed up the scrolling process 
At the end of the credits screen, you will see your name as a &quot;faithful customer&quot; 
Egg In An Egg - Hidden Messages 
When you activate the Big Electric Cat, wait until the credits screen appears 
Press the Alt key to speed them scrolling. 
While you&#39;re still holding the Alt key, click on the cat&#39;s big eye press the Ctrl key 
Now, release the Alt key. 
Secret messages will pop up just right above the credits screen 
Adobe Photoshop 4.0 - Splash Screen Changes

The splash screen will change to the Big Electric Cat on April the 1st (All Fools&#39; Day)! 
Note: You can activate this by changing the date on your PC, but it isn&#39;t recommended 
To change the splash screen into the Big Electric Cat, hold down the Alt key while Photoshop is loading 
Adobe Photoshop 4.0 - Merlin Lives

Whenever we click on the small black vertical arrow on the Layers toolbar and select Palette Properties, a picture of small Merlins appears. Now this egg is a rather cute twist to that 
Hold down Ctrl+Alt and click on the black arrow and select Palette Properties again 
Merlin is back! 
Adobe Photoshop 5.0 - Strange Cargo Credits

While holding down Ctrl+Alt+Shift, click on Help, About Photoshop... 
Check out the strange cargo credits [/tt]



[u][size=19pt][b]Windows Games[/b][/size][/u]
[b]Solitaire[/b]
[tt]You can actually turn only one card at a time in 3 cards over mode. Just hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and click and the card! This will turn only one card instead of 3.

Secret - Instant Win
Instructions - Press Alt + Shift + 2 during game play to instantly win.
[/tt]

[b]Free Cell[/b]
[tt]Can&#39;t win? Hold down Ctrl+Shift+F10. A pop-up menu can let you choose whether you want to win, lose or restart.

Secret - Hidden Game Modes 
Instructions - In the &quot;Game&quot; menu choose &quot;Select Game&quot;. Enter -1 or -2 to activate the hidden game modes.[/tt]

[b]Minesweeper[/b]
[tt]Hold down the Shift key and type XYZZY. Release Shift and then press it again. Now whenever your cursor is over the top of a mine, the top left pixel on your screen shows as a black dot. 
This is more towards an undocumented feature than an egg. Open up winmine.ini. At the end of the file, add the line Sound=3. Run the game. If you have your PC speaker on, you will hear something the next time you hit a mine. 
[/tt]

[b]Hearts[/b]
[tt]
NOTE:THIS EGG MAY WORK WITH OTHER COMPUTERS BUT BE CAREFUL!  This Egg works only with the Windows 95 release of Hearts. Run Regedit.exe (the Win95 Registry editor, located in your Win95 folder) and go to: HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Applets\Hearts. Now, you might be wondering why this teeny game needs its own registry entry (??). In the right hand pane add a new key (string) and name it zb (no quotes). Give it a value of 42. Now run Mshearts.exe and during gameplay press Ctrl + Alt + Shift + F12 the same time[/tt]




[u][size=19pt][b]Other[/b][/size][/u]
[b]WinAmp[/b]
[tt]Winamp 2.xx - See Developer Justin&#39;s Face

Start Winamp and go to the About box 
Make sure you are in the Winamp tab 
Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and click on the copyright notice line 
See the developer&#39;s face! 
You can also find out how old is he 
Still in the About box, click on the Shareware tab 
Double-click on Usage statistics to know his age 
Winamp 2.xx - Hidden Message

Start Winamp go to Preferences and click on the Visualization tab 
Scroll down and select Vis_Mux and click Configure 
You&#39;ll notice a small pi sign in the bottom-right corner 
Double-click the pi sign to reveal the hidden message 
Winamp 2.xx - Funny Message &amp; Cat Image

Start Winamp 
Type in nullsoft, pressing the Esc key after every &quot;l&quot; 
If you do that correctly, you should see a message It really whipps the llama&#39;s ass 
But wait, there&#39;s more! 
Go to Winamp&#39;s About box 
Click on the Credits tab 
Wait and you should see a picture of a cat 
If you try another skin like Fusion for example, and try the &quot;nullsoft&quot; trick, you&#39;ll get another message![/tt]

[b]mIRC[/b]
[tt]IRC Version 3.63 and above

See how funny your favorite chat client can get! 

Move your mouse over the yellow About button on the toolbar. Once the tool tip appears, click your right mouse button over and over. Keep clicking to see a &quot;personalized&quot; message! On later versions, you can right-click every buttons and get the same results. 


Hold down your right mouse button over the toolbar for a few seconds, then while keeping the right mouse button depressed, move your mouse over the yellow About button on the toolbar and hold down the left mouse button. Hold both buttons for a few seconds, then let go. The About icon will turn into a smiley face!


Open the About dialog box (the one with the author&#39;s picture). Right-click anywhere in the dialog box (except over a button) and a dot over the I in mIRC will start bouncing!


Open the About dialog box and left-click that author&#39;s nose for a &quot;squeeky&quot; surprise!


Open the About dialog box and type arnie to see the author&#39;s favorite playtime pal![/tt]

[b]Netscape Navigator[/b]
[tt]Netscape Navigator 4 - Developers&#39; Biography

Type in location bar about: 
And one of these authors&#39; names
ari, atotic, blythe, chouck, dmose, dp, ebina, hagan, jeff, jg, jsw, jwz, karlton, kipp, marca, mlm, montulli, mtoy, paquin, robm, sharoni, terry, timm 
You have to be online to view all of the biography 
Netscape Navigator 4 - Hidden Message

In the location bar, type in about:mozilla 
See the developers hidden message 
Netscape Navigator 4 - The Amazing Fish CAm

In any Navigator window, hold down the Ctrl+Alt+F combination 
THe Fish Cam will appear (make sure you are online) 
Netscape Navigator 4 - Embedded Logos

In the location bar, type in about:logo to see the original Netscape logo 
Type about:qtlogo to see the Quick Time logo 
Type about:mmlogo to see the Macromedia logo 
Type about:rsalogo to see the RSA logo 
Type about:coslogo to see theCosmo player logo 
Netscape Navigator 4 - More Useful Eggs

These are a few more useful about: eggs 
about:cache to view contents of cache 
about:global for global history 
about:memory-cache to view contents of memory cache 
about:image-cache to view contents of pictures on disk 
And for general purposes, type Ctrl+Alt+T to show the status of Active URLs and Ctrl+Alt+S to toggle the status bar on and off[/tt]




 
[u][size=19pt][b]Coming Soon[/b][/size][/u]
More Eggs For More Types Of Windows
Some Eggs For Games Such A WoW






[size=18pt][u][b][glow=red,2,300]MADE BY MVP566//DYLAN[/glow][/b][/u][/size]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2006 05:11:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General Discussion</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="9" data-topic="13675">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt width="20" height="20" src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/letter_avatar/hellfish/40/5_6259e4fa9dfe0dec282fb0955bb1974c.png" class="avatar"> Hellfish:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Sweet! I Love these ones.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Thanks!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2006 05:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-10</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hellfish Hellfish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/hellfish">@Hellfish</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Sweet! I Love these ones.<br>
Make a new .txt file and put “this app can break” in it and save and open!</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2006 05:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-9</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Scyther Scyther]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/scyther">@Scyther</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>thanks, this is kul to show some noobs</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2006 03:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-8</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">More Games</span>[/size]</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Pinball</span><br>
[tt]Secret - Extra Balls<br>
Instructions - Type 1max at the start of a new ball to get extra balls.</p>
<p>Secret - Gravity Well<br>
Instructions - Type gmax at the start of a new game to activate the Gravity Well.</p>
<p>Secret - Instant Promotion<br>
Instructions - Type rmax at the start of a new game to go up in ranks.</p>
<p>Secret - Skill Shot<br>
Instructions - Launch the ball partially up the chute past the third yellow light bar so it falls back down to get 75,000 points. There are six yellow light bars that are worth a varying amount of points:</p>
<p>First: 15,000 points<br>
Second: 30,000 points<br>
Third: 75,000 points<br>
Fourth: 30,000 points<br>
Fifth: 15,000 points<br>
Sixth: 7,500 points</p>
<p>Secret - Test Mode<br>
Instructions - Type hidden test at the start of a new ball to activate Test Mode. No notification will be given that this is activated but you can now left-click the mouse button and drag the ball around.</p>
<p>Secret - Unlimited Balls<br>
Instructions - Type bmax at the start of a new ball. No notification will be given that this is activated but when a ball is lost a new ball will appear from the yellow wormhole indefinitely. Once this is activated you will be unable to activate other secrets without restarting the game.</p>
<p>[size=20pt]<span class="bbcode-b"><span class="bbcode-u">OS Secrets</span></span>[/size]<br>
<span class="bbcode-b">NOTE USING THE FOLLOWING SECRETS COULD DAMAGE YOUR COMPUTER USE AT YOU OWN RISK</span></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b"> Add/Remove</span><br>
[tt]Secret - Hidden Uninstall Options<br>
Instructions - Warning: Proceed at your own risk! Browse to C:\Windows\inf\ and make a backup copy of sysoc.inf. Then open the original file C:\Windows\inf\sysoc.inf in notepad. Go to “Edit” and select “Replace”. In “Find what:” type ,hide and in “Replace with:” type , then select “Replace All”, save and close the file. Go to the control panel, “Add/Remove”, select “Add/Remove Windows Components”. You will now see many more Windows components to uninstall. Do not remove anything with no label or that you do not recognize or fully understand what it does. Doing so can break certain functionality in Windows[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Control Panel</span><br>
[tt]Secret - Hidden Control Panel Extensions<br>
Instructions - Download and install <a href="http://download.microsoft.com/download/f/c/a/fca6767b-9ed9-45a6-b352-839afb2a2679/TweakUiPowertoySetup.exe" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">TweakUI</a>, launch, go to “Control Panel” and check any item not selected, then “Apply” and “OK”. You will now see the hidden control panel extensions[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Device Manager</span><br>
[tt]- Hidden Devices<br>
Instructions - Go to the control panel, “System” icon, “Hardware” tab and select “Device Manager”. Select View and Show hidden devices.[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Music</span><br>
[tt]Secret - Music from the Installer<br>
Instructions - Browse to C:\Windows\system32\oobe\images\title.wma and play.[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Shutdown</span><br>
[tt]Secret - Display Hibernate Option on the Shut Down dialog<br>
Instructions - Go to “Start”, “Turn Off Computer…” and press either Shift key to change the “Stand By” button to “Hibernate”.[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Support Tools</span><br>
[tt]Instructions for Pre-SP2 users - If you do not have SP2 installed, put the original Windows XP CD in the CD-ROM Drive, run the D:\Support\Tools\setup.exe file[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Games</span>[/size]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Warcraft 2</span><br>
[tt]Warcraft 2 - Disco</p>
<p>This isn’t recorded in any of the cheat codes<br>
During the game, press Enter, type disco, and press Enter again<br>
Enjoy the music!<br>
Warcraft 2 - Critter Explodes</p>
<p>Keep clicking on a critter 7-8 times<br>
Most of the time, you will hear them squeal<br>
If you do it right, after some time, it will explode! [/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Need For Speed 2</span><br>
[tt]Need For Speed 2 - Drive By Night</p>
<p>As usual, choose your track, car and opponents<br>
Start your race. While your track is loading up hold down the n key<br>
Now youwill be racing at night (cool!)<br>
Need For Speed 2 - Rush-hour Towncar</p>
<p>In the main menu, type rushhour<br>
You should hear a WHOOSH sound before you press race<br>
Make sure you disabled all opponents and activate traffic<br>
Click on race and you will find yourself in a towncar there will be traffic waiting for you!<br>
Need For Speed 2 - Ford Indigo</p>
<p>In main menu, type in redracer<br>
The car icon should change to a ford indigo logo<br>
Start a race and you will find yourself driving the ford indigo<br>
Need For Speed 2 - Bonus Track</p>
<p>At the main menu type hollywood<br>
Monolithic Studios will be added to the list of tracks tracks<br>
Need For Speed 2 - Cool Alternate Vehicles</p>
<p>On the main menu of Need For Speed 2, type in one the following to use as the vehicle:<br>
ARMYTRUCK<br>
BUS<br>
JEEPYJ<br>
LANDCRUISER<br>
MERCEDES<br>
VWBUG<br>
The code are all self-explainary of what the vehicles you will get [/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Need For Speed 3</span><br>
[tt]Need For Speed 3 - Drive As Different Vehicles</p>
<p>In the car select menu, type go01 to go20 (you can only try one at a time)<br>
If you do that correctly, you should hear a “whoosh” sound<br>
Start the race and you will find yourself in a new vehicle[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Age Of Empires</span><br>
[tt]Age Of Empires - Futuristic Units</p>
<p>To get some cool hidden units, press enter for chat box and type the following:</p>
<p>e=mc2 trooper - Get a nuke trooper with cool nuclear missiles. Be careful not to shoot too closely or you can damage yourself.<br>
photon man - Get an army man with lasers. He can shoot at far range as well as close range.<br>
big daddy - Get a car equipped with lasers.<br>
You will get only one unit every time you type. They will appear in the town center. So use the copy+paste trick to get units real fast. Also another tip: be careful with enemy priests. They can convert these units as well!</p>
<p>Age Of Empires - Fun Features</p>
<p>For more fun, press enter for chat box and type the following:</p>
<p>flying dutchman - Juggernaughts become flying dutchmen and can go on land.<br>
gaia - Gain control over the animals (but you’ll lose control over your humans).<br>
jack be nimble - Catapult fires villagers and cows.<br>
Of course there are other codes but they are considered cheats and not posted here[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Flight Simulator 6.0</span><br>
[tt]Flight Simulator 6.0 - Developers Credits</p>
<p>Start the game as normal, click World on the menu bar, and then choose Set Exact Location<br>
Set your latitude/longitude to N047* 39’ 23" W122* 08’ 40.5" Altitude 0 feet, Heading 340 degrees<br>
You’ll end up in front of one of the buildings at the Microsoft campus in Redmond, Washington<br>
Head into the lobby (press Y to enter Slew mode and then move forward)<br>
When you’re inside, you’ll see a photo mural on the wall<br>
Press 5 on your numerical keypad and watch the picture toggle between two photos of some of the members of the Flight Simulator design team[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">SpyCraft</span><br>
[tt]Spycraft - Weird Phones</p>
<p>When you’re at The Farm and in Jeffries’s office, if you keep pressing the message button on his phone, you’ll hear an interesting James Bond-ish message<br>
When you’re in the Washington, D.C. office, try dialing 976-SUCK.<br>
Spycraft - Developers Credits</p>
<p>When you’re using the Mole Tool, deactivate the Peg button and move your cursor around the Interactive Entertainment button until you find a hidden hot spot<br>
Click it and go into the Interactive Entertainment page<br>
Deactivate the Peg button and move your cursor around the Organizational button at the upper left corner until you find another hidden hot spot<br>
Click it, and you’ll reveal a photo of the Spycraft design team[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Random</span>[/size]</span><br>
Try To Make A Folder Called “con” On Your Desktop No Parentheses</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Thanks To</span>[/size]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Websites:</span><br>
<a href="http://mywebpages.comcast.net/SupportCD/XPSecrets.html" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">Mywebpages.comcast</a><br>
<a href="http://www.activewin.com/tips/eeggs/" data-bbcode="true" rel="nofollow noopener">ActiveWin</a></p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Mopar Members:</span><br>
The Prince of Randomness<br>
Taylor</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 20:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-7</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@The_Prince_of_Random The Prince of Randomness]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/the_prince_of_random">@The_Prince_of_Random</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>The hearts one works with WINXP home edition SP1… i just tryed it.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 14:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-6</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>i know that one with all those links took forever, theres a whole of 2 post on this page that r not yours  :eek: <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> :rolleyes:</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 08:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-5</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jonckr jonckr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonckr">@jonckr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I surely will think so. I have been posting some usefully topics too! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> They Took me quite some time because i had to research more about them till i come across some websites, Then i decide to post them <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 07:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-4</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>they took a min but i think alot of people will like them</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 07:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-3</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@jonckr jonckr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/jonckr">@jonckr</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hey thanks for the Post! It works Great! <img src="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/images/emoji/twitter/smiley.png?v=9" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 06:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-2</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@mvp566 mvp566]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/u/mvp566">@mvp566</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>[size=20pt]<span class="bbcode-b">THESE ARE NOT MINE THEY ARE TAKEN FROM VARIOUS WEBSITES!</span>[/size]<br>
Easter Eggs (Definition) - A hidden message or feature in an application. This guide covers the undocumented and hidden features in Windows XP. All of the following were tested in Windows XP only.</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Norton</span>[/size]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Norton Anti-Virus</span><br>
[tt]Norton Antivirus - Developers’ Credits</p>
<p>In Norton Antivirus, click on the menu Help, About<br>
Hold down N, A, &amp; V all at the same time<br>
A dialog box with the picture of the Norton Antivirus team appears<br>
To close it, press Esc[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Norton DeskTop</span><br>
[tt]Norton Desktop - Developers’ Credits</p>
<p>From the menu, select Help, About menu.<br>
Click three times while holding down the keys N, D, and W[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Norton Utilities</span><br>
[tt]Norton Utilities - Special Movies</p>
<p>Pop into your drive the Norton Utilities CD-ROM<br>
Go to the folder named Media on the CD-ROM.<br>
The easter eggs themselves are in  two AVI files named Egg1.avi &amp; Egg2.avi<br>
Double-click a file &amp; watch the Norton Staff morphing and getting soaked<br>
Norton Utilities - Developers’ Credits</p>
<p>Open any Norton Utilities application under windows that has a menu.<br>
On the menubar, click on Help, About<br>
Depending on your version of Norton Utilities, you will have to press N, U &amp; 8 keys or N, U &amp; W<br>
Press them simultaneously.<br>
THe credits screen should appear<br>
The rest are all self-explainary[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Norton Commander</span><br>
[tt]Norton Commander - Developers’ Credits</p>
<p>Select  Help, About<br>
Press CTRL while double-clicking on Icon<br>
A large photo of the programming team will appear[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Norton NT Tools</span><br>
[tt]Norton NT Tools - Developers’ Credits</p>
<p>Open any Norton Utilities application under windows that has a menu.<br>
On the menubar, click on Help, About<br>
Press simultaneously N &amp; T<br>
THe credits screen should appear<br>
The rest are all self-explainary[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">MicroSoft</span>[/size]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">MS Front Page</span><br>
[tt]Frontpage 97/98 - Developers’ Credits</p>
<p>Start FrontPage Explorer.<br>
With FrontPage Explorer application open, hold down the Shift key<br>
Select Help | About<br>
Click OK<br>
With the Shfit key still held down, click on Help | About for the second time<br>
Click OK<br>
With the Shfit key still held down, click on Help | About for the last time<br>
The credits screen should appear with a song[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS OutLook</span><br>
[tt]Outlook 97/98 - Developers Credits</p>
<p>Click on the menubar, Contact | New Contact<br>
Name of contact is Ren Hoek. Save the contact<br>
On the left side, click on contact and then click on the new contact name you have just created<br>
Click on the menubar, Help | About Microsoft Outlook<br>
Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and click on the OK button<br>
THe credits screen should appear. If you want more, click on the link and it will bring you to the online credits screen<br>
[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS PowerPoint</span><br>
[tt]Access 97 - Developers Credits</p>
<p>Create a new normal database<br>
Make new table and save it as Go Speed Racer Go<br>
Choose Help, About and right double-click on the Bitmap.</p>
<p>Access 97 - Make My Computer Smile</p>
<p>On the toolbar, click on the Help menu and go to Find<br>
Search for the word happiness or smile."<br>
The sentence Make my computer smile comes up although it isn’t in</p>
<p>PowerPoint 97</p>
<p>Open PowerPoint 97<br>
Click on Help/About<br>
Click on PowerPoint Icon<br>
[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS Visual C++</span><br>
[tt]Visual C++ - Developers’ Credit</p>
<p>Put your Visual C++ CD-ROM in your CD-ROM drive<br>
Start Visual C++<br>
Click on the Help, About menu<br>
Hold down Ctrl and double-click, releasing Ctrl at same time as 2nd click is released<br>
Visual C++ 2.2 displays a spinning plus, with programmer credits<br>
Visual C++ 4.0 lets you fly around a landscape made up of programmer mug shots.<br>
Use the keypad to navigate and the A &amp; Z to accelerate/decelerate[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS Access</span><br>
[tt]Access 97 - Developers Credits</p>
<p>Create a new normal database<br>
Make new table and save it as Go Speed Racer Go<br>
Choose Help, About and right double-click on the Bitmap.</p>
<p>Access 97 - Make My Computer Smile</p>
<p>On the toolbar, click on the Help menu and go to Find<br>
Search for the word happiness or smile<br>
The sentence Make my computer smile comes up although it isn’t in<br>
Access 97 - Magic Eight Ball</p>
<p>Load Acess<br>
Create a blank database<br>
Click on the Macros tab<br>
Click on New<br>
Press space<br>
Close the dialog box<br>
Click Yes<br>
Save this macro as Magic Eight Ball<br>
Go to View | Toolbars | Customize… and check on Macro Design<br>
Drag the macro to the second toolbar, start clicking on it[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS Excel</span><br>
[tt]Excel 95 - Hall Of The Tortured Souls</p>
<p>Open a blank work sheet<br>
Go down to the 95th row<br>
Select the whole row<br>
Tab over to coloum B<br>
Goto Help/About<br>
Hold down ctrl-alt-shift<br>
and click on the tech support button<br>
A window appears call “Hall of Tortured souls”<br>
At the end of the hall and all the programmers names. This is something a Doom simulation.<br>
Now, here’s the fun part: do a 180 turn and type excelkfa. Walk through the wall and see the pictures.<br>
Excel 97 - Another Copy Of A Menu Item</p>
<p>Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift<br>
Click on any menu item<br>
You will see the cursor with a plus sign<br>
Drag it to another part of the menu<br>
You will now have another copy of the menu item!<br>
Excel 97 - Flight Simulation</p>
<p>On a new Worksheet, Press F5<br>
Type X97:L97 and hit enter<br>
Press the Tab key<br>
Hold Ctrl-Shift<br>
Click on the Chart Wizard toolbar button<br>
Depending on how well your DirectX is intergrated, you will either find yourself in an eerrie lanscape or if you are using Windows 98, you will probably find yourself in a beautiful purple lanscape.<br>
Use mouse to fly around - Right button forward/ Left button reverse<br>
There shoud be a hidden shrine in the middle with the programmers message.<br>
Here’s more:</p>
<p>Face the hidden shrine (credits screen)<br>
Move foreward towards the Hill using the left click for foreward thrust<br>
At the edge of the Hill stop the thrust using right click<br>
Point the view down by moving the mouse upwards<br>
You should then see at the bottom of the cliff a water motion<br>
There’s the Blue Laggoon![/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS Office</span><br>
[tt]Microsoft Office 95/97 - Developers’ Credits</p>
<p>Click on small four-color square on the MS Office toolbar<br>
Click on About Microsoft Office<br>
Hold down Ctrl-Shift and double-click on the MS Office Logo<br>
Floating Splash screen appears<br>
Click anywhere on the plate[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS Plus!</span><br>
[tt]Usually after creating a software, the computer programmers will include a credit screen. However, they are usually hidden, like an Easter Egg. These are the list of easter eggs you can find in common software.</p>
<p>Plus! 95/98 Unnoticed Mouse Cursor</p>
<p>Many of us didn’t notice this before but here it is. The busy mouse cursor for the Inside My Computer theme is a monitor with the number 101011 scrolling. This binary string, translated into ASCII is actually “+”  which stands for Plus!</p>
<p>Plus! 98 - Developers’ Credits</p>
<p>Go to the edit playlist dialog for any song.<br>
Type Microsoft Plus!98 Product Team in for the artist<br>
Type Credits in for the title<br>
Hold down the control key and click cancel [/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS Visual Basic</span><br>
[tt]Visual Basic 5.0 - Developers Credits</p>
<p>Launch Visual Basic 5.0<br>
When the New Project dialog box appears, just click Open<br>
Click the View menu, point to Toolbars, and click Customize<br>
Go to the Commands tab<br>
Click the Help category, and drag the About Microsoft Visual Basic item into the help menu<br>
Click the Modify Selection button and set the name for the newly inserted menu item to Show VB Credits<br>
Click the Close button<br>
From the Help menu, choose Show VB Credits<br>
Visual Basic 4.0 - Developers Credits</p>
<p>Add a test box to a form set its text property to Thunder<br>
Lock the control on the form<br>
Move mouse over the tools in the toolbox<br>
The names of developers and testers should appear instead of the usual tooltips![/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS Word</span><br>
[tt]Word Viewer</p>
<p>Go to Help/About…<br>
Hold down Ctrl and Shift and click on the logo</p>
<p>Word 97 - Floating Word 97 Splash Screen</p>
<p>Select Help, About Microsoft Word<br>
The About Box appears<br>
Hold down Ctrl+Shift+Alt keys<br>
Click on the horizontal divider in the About Box<br>
A floating splash screen appears</p>
<p>Word 97 - Deletable Menu Items</p>
<p>Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and the cursor should change into a minus sign. Click on a menu and then click on any menu item.<br>
That menu item will disappear! Don’t worry, this is only temporary and will be restored the next time you restart your computer<br>
If you really need it back, right-click on the toolbar and select Customize… Highlight Menu Bar and click on Reset…<br>
The menu item wuill be restored</p>
<p>Word 97 - No Competition</p>
<p>Word knows when to win a competition. Type Maxis, highlight the word and run the Thesaurus<br>
Then type Smartsuite and look at that<br>
Word 97 - Define zzzz</p>
<p>Open a blank document and type zzzz and run the spell checker. See what’s the definition for it.</p>
<p>Word 97 - Problems?</p>
<p>Open a new document in Word<br>
Type Unable to follow directions<br>
Highlight the entire sentence you just typed<br>
Click Tools, Thesaurus (or hit shift-F7 to open the thesaurus)<br>
Now, does Bill Gates have a problem the world doesn’t know about?</p>
<p>Word 97 - Naked?</p>
<p>Open Word and type I’d love to see you naked. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus.<br>
Try I want to see you naked and be just as suprised!<br>
Word 97 - Pagan?</p>
<p>Open Word and type Who is God?. Highlight the word and run a spell check. See who does the Word 97 programmers think God is.</p>
<p>Word 97 - Corny Developers?</p>
<p>Open Word and type I love porn. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus.<br>
How about typing I am gay and run the thesaurus again.<br>
Word 97 - Hairy?</p>
<p>Open Word and type Shag Me. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus. How’s the definition?</p>
<p>Word 97 - Define Eat Me Shorts</p>
<p>Open Word and type Eat Me Shorts. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus.<br>
What does it says?<br>
Word 97 - Can I …</p>
<p>Open Word and type May I screw your daughter?. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus.<br>
Check out the answer.<br>
Word 97 - Biological Associates</p>
<p>Open Word and type Ice boobs go with what?. Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus.<br>
Check out the associate - now who says Word is dumb?<br>
Word 97 - Bill Gates Dead?</p>
<p>Open Word and type I’d like to see Bill Gates dead<br>
On the Tools, Language, Set Launguage menu, set the language to English (United States)<br>
Highlight the word and press Shift+F7 to run the Thesaurus<br>
Enjoy what you see<br>
Word 97 - Naughty, naughty!</p>
<p>On any document, type in Love her and leave her<br>
Highlight the text, press Shift+F7 to activate the thesaurus and enjoy!</p>
<p>-Twin Towers</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Open MS Word</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Change font to Wingdings</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Change font size to 36</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Type in Q33 NY[/tt]</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">MS Developer Studio</span><br>
[tt]Developer Studio 97 - Developers’ Credits</p>
<p>On the Developer Studio CD-ROM, look around for a file named DEVCRD.DLL in the \DEVSTUDIO\SHAREDIDE\Bin directory.<br>
Right-click and copy that file to the C:\DevStudio\SharedIDE\Bin folder on your hard disk.<br>
Launch a Developer Studio component such as Visual C++.<br>
Click on the Help, About menu, hold down Ctrl and click anywhere in the dialog box.[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Adobe</span>[/size]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Adobe Illustrator</span><br>
[tt]Adobe Illustrator - Credits Screen</p>
<p>Launch Illustrator<br>
Press CTRL+ALT and click on the Venus picture on the top of the toolbar.<br>
The credit screen comes up, with all the developers name anagrammed[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Adobe Photo Deluxe</span><br>
[tt]Adobe Photo Deluxe - Developers Credits</p>
<p>Launch Adobe Photodeluxe<br>
Click on Help, About Photodeluxe<br>
Hold down ALT for 5 seconds<br>
The credits screen will appear [/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Adobe PageMaker</span><br>
[tt]Adobe Pagemaker - Dedication Flower</p>
<p>Launch Pagemaker<br>
Press Ctrl-Alt-Shift<br>
Click on Help, About<br>
Double Click the logo (a flower will appear)[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Adobe Photoshop</span><br>
[tt]Adobe Photoshop 4/5 - Credits Screen</p>
<p>Hold down Alt and click on Help, About Photoshop…<br>
You will see a different about box with the Big Electric Cat<br>
Wait for a few seconds<br>
The credits screen will start to scroll<br>
Hold down Alt to speed up the scrolling process<br>
At the end of the credits screen, you will see your name as a “faithful customer”<br>
Egg In An Egg - Hidden Messages<br>
When you activate the Big Electric Cat, wait until the credits screen appears<br>
Press the Alt key to speed them scrolling.<br>
While you’re still holding the Alt key, click on the cat’s big eye press the Ctrl key<br>
Now, release the Alt key.<br>
Secret messages will pop up just right above the credits screen<br>
Adobe Photoshop 4.0 - Splash Screen Changes</p>
<p>The splash screen will change to the Big Electric Cat on April the 1st (All Fools’ Day)!<br>
Note: You can activate this by changing the date on your PC, but it isn’t recommended<br>
To change the splash screen into the Big Electric Cat, hold down the Alt key while Photoshop is loading<br>
Adobe Photoshop 4.0 - Merlin Lives</p>
<p>Whenever we click on the small black vertical arrow on the Layers toolbar and select Palette Properties, a picture of small Merlins appears. Now this egg is a rather cute twist to that<br>
Hold down Ctrl+Alt and click on the black arrow and select Palette Properties again<br>
Merlin is back!<br>
Adobe Photoshop 5.0 - Strange Cargo Credits</p>
<p>While holding down Ctrl+Alt+Shift, click on Help, About Photoshop…<br>
Check out the strange cargo credits [/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Windows Games</span>[/size]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">Solitaire</span><br>
[tt]You can actually turn only one card at a time in 3 cards over mode. Just hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and click and the card! This will turn only one card instead of 3.</p>
<p>Secret - Instant Win<br>
Instructions - Press Alt + Shift + 2 during game play to instantly win.<br>
[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Free Cell</span><br>
[tt]Can’t win? Hold down Ctrl+Shift+F10. A pop-up menu can let you choose whether you want to win, lose or restart.</p>
<p>Secret - Hidden Game Modes<br>
Instructions - In the “Game” menu choose “Select Game”. Enter -1 or -2 to activate the hidden game modes.[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Minesweeper</span><br>
[tt]Hold down the Shift key and type XYZZY. Release Shift and then press it again. Now whenever your cursor is over the top of a mine, the top left pixel on your screen shows as a black dot.<br>
This is more towards an undocumented feature than an egg. Open up winmine.ini. At the end of the file, add the line Sound=3. Run the game. If you have your PC speaker on, you will hear something the next time you hit a mine.<br>
[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Hearts</span><br>
[tt]<br>
NOTE:THIS EGG MAY WORK WITH OTHER COMPUTERS BUT BE CAREFUL!  This Egg works only with the Windows 95 release of Hearts. Run Regedit.exe (the Win95 Registry editor, located in your Win95 folder) and go to: HKEY_CURRENT_USER\Software\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Applets\Hearts. Now, you might be wondering why this teeny game needs its own registry entry (??). In the right hand pane add a new key (string) and name it zb (no quotes). Give it a value of 42. Now run Mshearts.exe and during gameplay press Ctrl + Alt + Shift + F12 the same time[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Other</span>[/size]</span><br>
<span class="bbcode-b">WinAmp</span><br>
[tt]Winamp 2.xx - See Developer Justin’s Face</p>
<p>Start Winamp and go to the About box<br>
Make sure you are in the Winamp tab<br>
Hold down Ctrl+Alt+Shift and click on the copyright notice line<br>
See the developer’s face!<br>
You can also find out how old is he<br>
Still in the About box, click on the Shareware tab<br>
Double-click on Usage statistics to know his age<br>
Winamp 2.xx - Hidden Message</p>
<p>Start Winamp go to Preferences and click on the Visualization tab<br>
Scroll down and select Vis_Mux and click Configure<br>
You’ll notice a small pi sign in the bottom-right corner<br>
Double-click the pi sign to reveal the hidden message<br>
Winamp 2.xx - Funny Message &amp; Cat Image</p>
<p>Start Winamp<br>
Type in nullsoft, pressing the Esc key after every “l”<br>
If you do that correctly, you should see a message It really whipps the llama’s ass<br>
But wait, there’s more!<br>
Go to Winamp’s About box<br>
Click on the Credits tab<br>
Wait and you should see a picture of a cat<br>
If you try another skin like Fusion for example, and try the “nullsoft” trick, you’ll get another message![/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">mIRC</span><br>
[tt]IRC Version 3.63 and above</p>
<p>See how funny your favorite chat client can get!</p>
<p>Move your mouse over the yellow About button on the toolbar. Once the tool tip appears, click your right mouse button over and over. Keep clicking to see a “personalized” message! On later versions, you can right-click every buttons and get the same results.</p>
<p>Hold down your right mouse button over the toolbar for a few seconds, then while keeping the right mouse button depressed, move your mouse over the yellow About button on the toolbar and hold down the left mouse button. Hold both buttons for a few seconds, then let go. The About icon will turn into a smiley face!</p>
<p>Open the About dialog box (the one with the author’s picture). Right-click anywhere in the dialog box (except over a button) and a dot over the I in mIRC will start bouncing!</p>
<p>Open the About dialog box and left-click that author’s nose for a “squeeky” surprise!</p>
<p>Open the About dialog box and type arnie to see the author’s favorite playtime pal![/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-b">Netscape Navigator</span><br>
[tt]Netscape Navigator 4 - Developers’ Biography</p>
<p>Type in location bar about:<br>
And one of these authors’ names<br>
ari, atotic, blythe, chouck, dmose, dp, ebina, hagan, jeff, jg, jsw, jwz, karlton, kipp, marca, mlm, montulli, mtoy, paquin, robm, sharoni, terry, timm<br>
You have to be online to view all of the biography<br>
Netscape Navigator 4 - Hidden Message</p>
<p>In the location bar, type in about:mozilla<br>
See the developers hidden message<br>
Netscape Navigator 4 - The Amazing Fish CAm</p>
<p>In any Navigator window, hold down the Ctrl+Alt+F combination<br>
THe Fish Cam will appear (make sure you are online)<br>
Netscape Navigator 4 - Embedded Logos</p>
<p>In the location bar, type in about:logo to see the original Netscape logo<br>
Type about:qtlogo to see the Quick Time logo<br>
Type about:mmlogo to see the Macromedia logo<br>
Type about:rsalogo to see the RSA logo<br>
Type about:coslogo to see theCosmo player logo<br>
Netscape Navigator 4 - More Useful Eggs</p>
<p>These are a few more useful about: eggs<br>
about:cache to view contents of cache<br>
about:global for global history<br>
about:memory-cache to view contents of memory cache<br>
about:image-cache to view contents of pictures on disk<br>
And for general purposes, type Ctrl+Alt+T to show the status of Active URLs and Ctrl+Alt+S to toggle the status bar on and off[/tt]</p>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">[size=19pt]<span class="bbcode-b">Coming Soon</span>[/size]</span><br>
More Eggs For More Types Of Windows<br>
Some Eggs For Games Such A WoW</p>
<p>[size=18pt]<span class="bbcode-u"><span class="bbcode-b">[glow=red,2,300]MADE BY MVP566//DYLAN[/glow]</span></span>[/size]</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.moparisthebest.com-post-13675-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forum.moparisthebest.com/t/eggs-glitches-not-just-for-windows/13675.rss">Eggs/Glitches, Not Just For Windows!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
